Chapter 19

Snape's POV:

Severus Snape approached his office door with the confidence of a man who knew precisely what he would find behind it. Being a man who could in most situations use the phrase "been there, done that" with complete truthfulness (not that he would, as that particular phrase had too much bounce to be used by someone as serious as Severus Snape), he considered himself to be in general thoroughly unimpressed with life's little surprises.

It was in this frame of mind that Professor Snape entered his office, and looking back he could only be thankful that Poppy hadn't been with him at the time. Or worse, Minerva—nay, Albus! He didn't think he'd be able to live down being made to gape like a first-year encountering a three-headed dog if there had been any witness. As it was, the sight that greeted him upon disabling his wards and entering his office made him stop. Stare. Frown. Stare some more. Finally he reached up to rub tiredly at his eyes, sure that the fatigue must be getting to him at last.

His office had been almost entirely overtaken by crates. Part of his mind noted in a distant way that this explained where all his crates had been disappearing to, but most of his mind was still trying to wrap itself around the fact that his office was filled with crates—and not empty crates, but crates with potions in them.

There must be two dozen at least, he thought, moving forward finally and reaching into the closest crate to pull out one of the beakers inside with his free hand. It contained Sweat Inducer; that much was immediately clear. What was less clear was how roughly 30 crates of Sweat Inducer—for indeed it appeared to be the same potion in every one—had gotten into his office. The obvious answer nearly made him growl with vexation.

Of course, he scowled, Give a Black an inch…

What was that fool boy thinking? Hadn't he told the little idiot that quality was more important than quantity? Severus would be lucky if any of them were viable, and even if he ended up with one good crate after all, the rest was a waste of ingredients so flagrant he was tempted to curse aloud. Severus carefully set down the two crates of Snowhit he'd been cradling under his arm to take to Poppy and rounded his desk to dig through the drawers for the Pepper-Up potion he kept there. He wouldn't be able to deliver the potions until he knew which were usable and which were duds, and with his magical core so depleted from brewing Snowhit Draught he'd need something to tide him over while he went through them all.

Face grim, Severus turned to the nearest crate and set to work, flexing his magic toward the first potion to get a feel for it. Sighing at the thought of doing this another 800 or so times, the Potions Master settled in for a long night.

Normal POV:

Rigel's breakfast Sunday morning was interrupted rather spectacularly by an irate Potions Master who looked as if he hadn't slept all night. Snape's robes were rumpled and his hair looked lankier than usual, but those things were completely eclipsed by his scowl, which Rigel thought worthy of epic poetry. The first years around her shrank back, not eager to be caught in even the peripherals of their Head of House's rage, and Rigel hastily scooted her butter knife out of Snape's reach, just in case.

Luckily for the Slytherins around Rigel, Snape didn't stay long. He barked out the words, "Black. My office. Now," before turning and stalking out of the Great Hall as quickly as he'd come.

Unluckily for Rigel, it didn't sound as though Professor Snape was inviting her to tea. Under the sympathetic and slightly fearful looks from her Housemates, Rigel stood and sent Pansy and Draco a small rueful smile before heading off toward the dungeons.

She had no idea why Professor Snape would be so angry with her, but she could only assume that a) he was angry about something else and happened to need to speak with her at the same time or b) it was something to do with the potions she'd left in his office the night before.

Did I not brew enough? Rigel wondered as she walked down the stone steps from the Entrance Hall, I was sure he'd be happy with how much I accomplished, but maybe it wasn't enough. That would be strange indeed, for Rigel had yet to meet an adult who expected more of her than she expected from herself. Maybe Mrs. Norris got into the office somehow and spilled them all? Or Peeves? No, surely Snape would have wards against animals and poltergeists. It's got to be something else, she mused, but what?

The familiar office door stood half-open, and Rigel wasn't sure if she was glad she didn't have to pause and work up the nerve to knock or not. She knocked anyway as she entered the room, which seemed much smaller when it was filled with crates. After a moment, she realized that the crates weren't where she'd left them. They were stacked on the opposite side of the office instead, as if someone had methodically moved them from one side to the other. Snape was seated at his desk, and the look on his face was one of a man physically restraining himself from doing something rash. Rigel gently closed the door behind her and moved to stand before the desk quietly, hoping that by seeming unobtrusive she would be less likely to draw his anger onto herself. Given the fact that there was no one else present for it to fall upon, she felt she should take every precaution.

Silence reigned, grating on her nerves until Snape finally spoke, in a voice as hard as a grinding wheel, "Tell me, Mr. Black, do I seem to you to be an overly trusting sort of wizard?"

Rigel blinked, pretty sure there was no polite way to answer that, but Snape went on.

"When I give my trust to someone, let's say when I assign them a task, for instance, do you think it pleases me to have that trust abused?" he pressed, black eyes crackling with small lightning bolts of anger.

"No, sir," Rigel said carefully, mind working clumsily to try and figure out what Snape was implying.

"Then perhaps, Mr. Black, you understand why I am less than pleased this morning," Snape said darkly as Rigel stood rather taken aback at the fury in his tone, "No? You cannot think of any reason why I might have called you in here to explain yourself to me?"

Rigel swallowed heavily and cleared her throat when it seemed as though the Potions Master was in fact waiting for an answer.

"Is it… because I used all the hellebore from the student stores?" she guessed, unable to think of any other way she might have abused his faith in her, "Because I ordered more, and I was planning on replacing—"

"That is not why, you foolish child," Snape slammed one hand down on the desk and Rigel bit her lip to keep from flinching. Snape grabbed a flask from a crate beside his chair and thrust it into her line of sight, "What is this, Mr. Black?"

Rigel gazed at the potion helplessly, "A beaker of Sweat Inducer, sir."

"And who brewed this Sweat Inducer, Mr. Black, can you tell me that?"

"I did, sir," she said softly, still confused.

"How do you know this one is yours?" he asked, a snide tone to his voice she didn't understand. Had he been brewing Sweat Inducer, too?

"It is my handwriting on the label," she said slowly.

"All of these potions have your handwriting on their labels."

"Yes, sir," Rigel agreed, thinking, Of course they do.

"But you did not make all of these potions, Mr. Black," Snape said. It was not a question.

Rigel's eyes narrowed in frustration, "Excuse me, sir, but I did."

"Do not take me for a fool, boy," the Potion Master growled. "You expect me to believe that you brewed over 100 cauldrons of Sweat Inducer in two weeks on top of maintaining your studies, which the other Professors assure me have not slipped?" he scoffed dismissively. "You would have been smarter to deliver a tenth of these Potions and turn the rest in slowly over a course of a couple of months. That would be, at least, believable."

Rigel frowned, the point of Snape's tirade finally penetrating her brain. She had been met with scepticism when it came to her brewing before, when she was younger, but never outright accusation. And still he was not through.

"But no, not you Black, you just had to try and look like a hero," he taunted, "Just had to try and impress us all with your talents and selflessness. Just like a Gryffindor to try and take credit for another's hard work and—"

Rigel had had enough. Her hands were shaking in clenched fists and she was not going to stand there and let him belittle her without just cause no matter how much she admired him.

"That's not true!" she said loudly, glaring at Snape, who looked ready to commit murder at having been interrupted so rudely. She went on before he could stop her, "Aside from the fact that a few beakers of Sweat Inducer wouldn't make anyone a hero, I didn't do whatever it is you're accusing me of, Professor." Her voice was back to a reasonable volume, but the tone was harsh and defensive. "I would never take credit for another's work, not least because mine is probably better," she said, missing the look of surprised recognition in his face as she ranted. "I worked my butt off brewing those potions, and you'd better believe that each and every one of them is perfect. I didn't ask for help, mostly because I don't like taking help from anyone but also because I know how important it is for this project to remain a secret!"

Rigel whirled around and stalked the few paces to the door, then whirled back again and advanced on the Potion Master's desk, "You think I would really jeopardize both your trust and my classmates' health just so I could look cooler by contracting the potions out to other people and claiming them as mine? I am not my father, Professor Snape. Maybe I was trying to impress you, because you're everything I ever wanted to be and I respect your opinion, but I want to impress you on my own merits. Not because I want to show how hardworking and selfless I am, but because success matters to me, and it doesn't mean anything if it's someone else's work." Rigel was panting now but she had one more thing to say. She glared at her Head of House, "And I am a Slytherin. You of all people should know that."

It took her several moments after her tirade to realize that the roaring in her ears wasn't Snape yelling back at her, but rather the sound of her own erratic heartbeat and breathing. Snape was just sitting there, eyes narrowed and focused beneath a heavy frown. Finally, when she was starting to feel a bit embarrassed that she'd exploded again at the Potions Master, he said, "Swear on your magic that you brewed all of these potions."

Rigel bristled, but Snape snapped, "Spare me a child's pride, Mr. Black. You have spoken convincingly but I must be sure."

Rigel took in a long, slow breath, and let it out as she thought. Considering the nature of the illness, she supposed, it was not an unreasonable demand. After all, if she had contracted the potions out, the potion-maker could have nefarious intentions and poisoned the potions somehow. Snape could not clear them for administering to the children at Hogwarts unless he had absolutely no doubts as to their origin.

"I swear in risk of my magic that if these are the same potions I and Alesana Selwyn delivered to this room yesterday, then I did brew every one myself," she said carefully, sure to word it so that if somehow a potion she hadn't made had gotten mixed in with the ones she'd delivered she wouldn't lose her magic on a technicality. Rigel felt the bone-deep thrumming in her core as the magic induced by the vow swept over her mind and soul to assess the validity of her claim. Both she and Snape relaxed as the oppressive magic faded harmlessly away.

Snape cleared his throat, "I owe you an apology for—"

"Please don't, sir," Rigel cut across him quietly, "In truth I think I hoped to surprise you with how much I'd gotten done, so it is partly my fault that I did not consider how suspicious such a surprise would seem in the current climate." Snape nodded in placid agreement, and Rigel added, "That said, please don't doubt my word, whether given or implied, without reasonable proof from now on."

Snape's sharp eyes pierced her flat grey gaze, but she refused to back down on this. If they couldn't trust each other, they couldn't work together.

"Such a thing should not have to be asked for," he allowed, and Rigel nodded in acceptance of his unspoken concession, "Perhaps we should overlook the past ten minutes and start this meeting where it should have begun." Snape took out his wand and conjured a chair, "Please, have a seat, Mr. Black."

"Thank you, Professor Snape," Rigel said, taking the chair without hesitation, "I see you've received the Sweat Inducers. I trust everything was in order?"

"Quite," Snape said wryly, no doubt wondering why their every meeting devolved in such a way. Rigel thought it was likely a combination of Snape's approaching every situation involving her from a biased point of view because of who her father was and her reacting defensively to even the slightest hint of accusation or censure because she was constantly aware of her duplicity and the reasons behind it, thereby making her insecure and prone to overreacting. Whatever the Potions Master thought, he continued, "I am somewhat at a loss to explain how you managed to brew so many potions in two weeks, Mr. Black. Perhaps you could enlighten me?"

Rigel shrugged, "My average was four hours of brewing a day, and I usually had two or three cauldrons brewing at once. I was busy, but not overly burdened, sir."

Snape frowned, "It is not that you brewed almost 800 beakers of potion in two weeks that strains the imagination, Mr. Black. Had you turned in 33 crates of Boil Cure I would not have batted a lash, I assure you. Sweat Inducer, however, is not Boil Cure."

Rigel tilted her head to show her incomprehension, and Snape went on, "Boil Cure requires no magic to be imbued on the part of the brewer as it relies on the innate magic in the ingredients. Sweat Inducer is not viable unless magic is consciously imbued."

"Yes, sir," Rigel said, trying not to sound patronizing but really not seeing what the problem was, "You explained it to me when I got the recipe."

Snape sighed, sounding like he was like pulling teeth, "The magic required for a batch of Sweat Inducer is nothing for a first-year to sniff at. Last night I checked each and every one of these potions, and they are all viable, so the obvious question is how you managed not to pass out from magical exhaustion after brewing it 65 times a week. Were you taking Pepper-Up at every meal?"

"No, sir, Pepper-Up can have disastrous long-term effects on both neurological and magical pathways," Rigel said, reciting from a study she'd read in Potions Quarterly when she was eight.

Snape shot her a look that clearly said, I know, but he asked, "Stronger magical stimulants, then?" At her offended expression, he said, "I didn't think you would, but it simply doesn't make any sense, Mr. Black. You see now why I was so quick to jump to ignoble conclusions?"

"I don't see why it doesn't make sense to you," Rigel said plainly, "I imbued each cauldron carefully with enough magic, but it's not like it was all that hard. I never even felt tired, aside from the obvious fatigue from brewing in the early mornings. I think you're overestimating how difficult imbuing is. I mean, it was hard at first when I was still figuring out the Medi-minis, but once I got the hang of it, imbuing was the easy part of brewing compared with the delicacy of adding the feverfew thistles in the third stage."

The expression on Snape's face was a lot like the one she was growing accustomed to seeing on Draco's when she did or said something that a 'normal' pureblood wizard wouldn't have done or said. A pensive expression crossed his face, and he said softly, "The simplest explanation indeed, but the likelihood…"

"Sir?" Rigel prompted when he'd stared at the wall behind her long enough to make her feel a bit sorry for the blank stone.

Snape blinked and leaned forward in his chair, looking at her like she was a puzzle he was close to figuring out, "The simplest explanation for this…chain of events also happens to have a simple, though rather delicate, test. I require your permission before I proceed, however."

Rigel eyed her Professor a bit warily. She remembered Archie saying that a Legilimens needed permission legally to look inside a person's mind. "Proceed to do…what exactly?"

"With your permission, I would establish a temporary link between our magical cores," he said, face inscrutable, "It is not unlike the link established when one imbues a potion with their magic, the difference being that another person's magical core is not a passive receptor like a potion is. It is the only way to get an accurate…read on another person's magical core, however, and I believe it would help clear up a few things for me to have a sense of your magical core in general."

"It isn't like reading minds, is it, sir?" Rigel asked cautiously, "What kind of things can you tell about a person with that kind of link?"

"It is not very like Legilimency, Mr. Black," Snape said, speaking slowly in the way she'd come to realize he did when he wanted to be honest and was therefore choosing his words with care, "The link is created between two magical cores, not two minds, and as such it can only reveal information about magical cores. It will tell me the depth and state of your magical core. I will be able to tell things like how often you exercise your magic, if there are any blocks on your magic, and so on."

"But it can't tell you anything specific about the person whose magical core it is?" Rigel clarified.

Snape narrowed his eyes sharply at her with what was probably suspicion, and she winced inwardly, but he merely said, "That is correct. If I may?"

Rigel nodded slowly. Snape pointed his wand at her torso and Rigel tried not to gulp. She wondered how many wizards had survived being held at wand point by Professor Snape, who seemed altogether too fearsome to be a school teacher, and decided she'd do better not to think about it.

After a moment, Rigel felt something peculiar in the region of her magical core, and if she hadn't been expecting it she didn't doubt that her magic would have lashed out threateningly. As it was, she turned her magical senses inward and watched with fascination as foreign magic approached her core. Her core was a sphere of pure magic situated in her gut not unlike a ball of yarn in that it had strands and ropes of magic all coiled around the centre. Unlike a ball of yarn, the coils moved and flexed lazily when the foreign magic, which felt a bit like an iron stick, prodded them experimentally. Like Devil's Snare, she thought absently, or like a pit of snakes. Quietly, she asked her magic to extend a tendril of its own out to the inflexible stick of alien magic and complete the connection. The two appendages of magic fused instantly, the edges melting together and forging a magical conduit, which zinged happily to life.

Snape jumped and Rigel's real-world senses watched him stare at her in surprise before he concentrated on the link between their cores once more. It was somewhat hard to tell where her rope of magic stopped and Snape's metal rod began at that point. Rigel felt Snape tug a bit on the connection from his end, and the link twanged with resonance that sent what felt like pulses of pure magic back along the rope toward Snape's core. The pulses seemed to tell him something, as her physical senses told her he was frowning with concentration. Rigel thought it looked rather like magical echolocation. She wondered if the link worked both ways, so she asked her magic to carefully poke the connection the same way Snape had. She felt a brief resistance, and then the tension eased and she could sense magical pulses relaying back and forth across the connection. When they came back to her magical core, her magic seemed to digest the pulses for a moment, then Rigel was hit with a bundle of knowledge that she hadn't had a moment earlier, and realized it was information gathered from Snape's core.

If her core was made up of snakes and tendrils of magical energy wrapped in a ball, Snape's core was shielded behind a thick growth of briar. The vines made up in flexibility what the razor thorns attached to them lacked, and it was difficult to tell what lay underneath with the briars curled around his core so protectively. The stick he'd sent out to bridge the gap between their cores was in fact an elongated thorn, but Rigel was right to think it felt like iron before. All the vines of briar were made up of various kinds of metals. Iron, steel, platinum, silver, all kinds of metals, some pure and some alloys. She supposed they might represent different kinds of magic Snape used, or perhaps they just allowed for a more versatile and many-faceted magical system.

It was fascinating, assimilating information via magical pulsar. She found out that Snape's vines moved more slowly than her snakes and ropes did because he was tired, having expended a good deal of his magical energy in the last 48 hours. A strange bit of magical energy floating around the peripherals of his core, but unattached to anything, told her that he'd taken something like a Pepper-Up recently and was still running partially off that. She guessed that if he were to perform magic while the connection stood it would tell her even more about his core, but Snape withdrew his magic with a deft hand a moment later, unmelding it from her own and breaking the link as he did so. Her magical sense snapped back from his core the moment there was no longer a connection, and it took her a few moments to regain her orientation and then release her magical senses completely and focus on the tangible world once more.

"I trust you found that as enlightening as I did?" Professor Snape asked dryly when she'd regained herself. Belatedly, she realized she hadn't asked permission to view his magical core, as he had. She grimaced apologetically, but he waved her away unconcernedly, "Relax, Mr. Black, a magical pathway is usually offered two-way, for the sake of politeness, though I did not expect you to have so much control over your magical core that you would be able to take advantage of the link, considering where you were with magical control just a few weeks ago." He gazed at her rather sardonically as he added, "One day I will have to stop underestimating you, child."

Rigel didn't know what to say to that, so she asked, "Did it tell you what you needed to know?"

"Yes and no," Snape said, folding his hands on his desk thoughtfully, "Yes, because if the reading of your magical core is to be believed, you have quite extensive magical reserves beneath the first level of your core, which could account for why sacrificing magic for imbuing does not tire you noticeably. No, because your father's magical core was above average, but nothing at a level to be responsible for this." Snape paused, then went on delicately, "I did not know your mother very well. Was she magically powerful?"

Rigel blinked, taken aback at the question. Of course her mother was powerful. Everyone knew of how powerful Lily Potter was, no matter that she had muggle parents. She—

Rigel mentally smacked herself. He means Diana, she realized, feeling rather thick.

"I'm not sure," she said semi-truthfully, "Father doesn't like to talk about her much anymore, so no one mentions her around me. I suppose she might have been."

"Hmm," Snape mulled that over, "Well in any case, your magical core reads much stronger than I would expect from a first-year, in addition to having naturally deep wells of magical power. I suspect the strength of your core is a result of the suppression you exercised near constantly toward your magic as a child. It made your core dense and tough, but I believe you constrained it too much at some point, which is what caused it to lash out whenever you lost control as a result of strong emotional turbulence."

"So, my always fighting against my magic has made it…stronger? Because it had to struggle all the time?" Rigel clarified, and Snape nodded.

"I believe so. Also, your own control over your magic is unnaturally developed because you struggled against it so often," he said, "You and your magic were like old rivals, each improving in order to best the other, so the result is that you both become stronger for the competition."

"Were?"

"At the moment, your core isn't fighting much at all," Snape told her, "It flexes every now and then, but for the most part you and your magical core seem to be in tandem."

"Yes, I've come to an agreement with it," Rigel admitted, "I perform magic often enough to please it, and in return it doesn't do magic without my direction. Much."

Snape gave her an odd look, but Rigel had another question, "Sir, what did you mean by the 'first level' of my magical core?"

He went into teaching mode immediately, "Most wizards have two layers to their magical core. Some magical creatures have multiple layers, some have only one, and some don't have a magical core so much as a de-centralized network of magic, but returning to the point, what did you notice when you used the connection to perceive my magical core?"

Rigel shrugged, saying, "It looked like a briar patch."

"What shape did it have?"

"It was spherical. Are all cores spheres?" Rigel asked.

"Not necessarily," Snape said, "The sphere is the most intuitive shape for consolidating power, so usually a person's core is roughly rounded at the least. In my case, the briars you noticed are only the outside of the core. They grow around the second level and act as both a primary defence for the magical core and as a flexible surface layer that deals with everyday magic. A wizard's first layer, briars in my case, is replenished by the true core whenever magic is used, so often a person's true core is depleted before the outer layer is expended. In this way it is difficult to gauge the depth and state of a person's magical core without practice."

"Okay," Rigel said, "But what does a true core look like? Do I have one? I have never sensed anything but the surface coils from mine."

"The true core varies in appearance as much as the first layer does," Snape said, "According to how a person's magic naturally flows and how that person conceives it to be, to some extent. It takes prolonged meditation to glimpse your true core at first, though it gets easier with practice. All that is important at the moment, however, is that your true core is indeed deep enough to imbue potions on a higher level than most first years would be capable of."

"So that means I can help you more with the harder potions, right?" Rigel leaned forward in her chair with poorly suppressed excitement, "Sweat Inducer only needs three doses a week even if given constantly. Those cases should last for at least three months even if 100 kids get sick. Let me help with something else, sir. Please."

Snape made a great show of considering her request carefully, but Rigel had seen his magical core, seen how tired he was all the time and how hard he worked just keeping up with the needs of the Hospital Wing, and knew he could use the help whether he liked it or not.

"I suppose Aurora's Breath is a good potion for an aspiring Master to know in general," Snape said carefully, and Rigel grinned openly in response, "I will give you the recipe I prefer during dinner tonight, Mr. Black, along with my notes on the potion." He fixed her with a stern look, "This potion requires even more magic than Sweat Inducer, though not quite as much as Snowhit. You will make no more than 25 cauldrons a week, is that understood? That will be plenty to keep Poppy stocked, considering each child needs only a beaker a week and one cauldron makes six beakers."

"Yes, sir," Rigel agreed easily. She was willing to trade less brewing hours for a new and more difficult potion to brew.

"You are doing a rare thing, Mr. Black," Snape told her after a moment of silence.

Rigel recognized his words as an unexpected and unofficial thank you, so she said, "It says more about the world we live in that using your skills to make a difference is a rare thing than it does about me for doing something rare, Professor Snape."

Snape's face was unreadable, but Rigel wasn't expecting an answer. Instead she asked, "Professor, have you learned anything new about the illness? How it spreads or what its goal is?"

"Goal?" Snape said sharply, "What do you mean by that?"

"Well," Rigel said, remembering something Archie had once told her, "Every illness has a goal, so to speak. Viruses often infiltrate living cells in order to facilitate their own reproduction, which they can't do without a host, for instance. What is this illness caused by, and what does it want with humans? Food? Shelter? Is it a parasite, dependent on the continued existence of the host, or does the death of the host make no difference to it? Does it attack children because they are more susceptible or because they have something adults don't have?"

Snape considered her words, "That is an interesting way to look at disease."

"I've toyed with the idea of being a Healer from time to time," Rigel said, "I'm interested in inventing and experimenting with Potions, and there are many obscure diseases that currently don't have a cure or even viable treatment options."

Snape gave her a look that made her uncomfortably aware that he most likely knew how Diana had died and was probably pitying her for something that happened to her cousin.

"Well, I can answer at least one of your questions in any case," Snape said finally, "The reason children appear to be more susceptible to the sickness is, we believe, related to the way the illness is transmitted. It moves mind to mind, though proximity seems to be a factor as well."

"How is that possible?" Rigel wondered, "Unless all the victims were practising Legilimency on one another."

Snape snorted with amusement, "Magic, Mr. Black. Magical illnesses are transmitted via magical currents, including mental currents in this case. Unprotected minds leak mental energy, to a certain extent broadcasting their mental state to those who perceive such things. When unprotected minds spend a great deal of time around one another, the mental energies they leak tend to mingle and form tenuous ties to one another. Because of this, sometimes grown wizards who have been friends a very long time will know when the other is nearby. The illness is using these projected currents to move from one mind to another one, usually one 'familiar' to the original mind, and take up residence there."

"So the younger a child is, the more open and unprotected his mind is, generally speaking? And I suppose friends would infect other friends first, because their minds were peripherally familiar with one another," Rigel said, "That makes sense, I suppose, but what does the sickness do once it gets into the mind?"

"As far as we can tell, with the exception of the very first student to fall ill, Miss Jones, who slipped erratically into a coma, the illness comes on subtly, slowly taking over the mental faculties of a child until it reaches a point at which it can assume more or less complete control. At this point, it shuts down the mind it has taken over like a fortress, cutting it off from the outside world as completely as any Master Occlumens could."

"And the kid collapses into seeming unconsciousness," Rigel said, fitting the pieces together, "Is it contagious even after the mind locks down?"

"Yes," Snape said shortly, "Madam Pomfrey is careful not to spend too much time with any one patient, less she unwittingly facilitate the disease in spreading to her own mind by creating familiar mental pathways. It is not a high level of concern, however, as Pomfrey's mind is generally well protected in any case."

"What about the fever?"

"Sometimes the fever is strong, other times it is weak, sometimes it lasts, sometimes it doesn't," Snape said, "We know the fever can't be stopped with Fever Reducer, because that potion affects the mind directly, and none of our Potions that affect the mind have any effect on the sickness. The only thing that might account for the fever itself is if the fever corresponds to how violently a child mentally resists the sickness once he becomes aware of it, once the child is trapped in his own mind with it, that is, but we cannot know for sure. None of our scans can reach inside the mind when it is so well protected. All we can do at the moment is keep the body alive so that when the sickness leaves there is no lasting damage."

"To the body," Rigel said seriously, "How do we know their minds aren't being permanently damaged while the sickness maintains control over them?"

"We don't," Snape admitted, "But for reasons I will not share with you, I do not believe the illness will cause any significant damage once it has the mind locked down. It seems to be working much like a coma-curse in that respect."

Rigel frowned in thought. What Snape said didn't make much sense in terms of the way a disease worked, but he sounded quite certain. If it was something more like a curse, a contagious curse for that matter, and less like an actual illness, then Rigel supposed the goal of the sickness would depend not on what the sickness gained from infecting children, but what the intention of the caster was, like with any spell. That would assume that there was a person, a wizard, behind this sickness, but Rigel had a hard time seeing how such an illness could benefit a person. It could incapacitate your enemies, but it worked too slowly to be useful in battle, and she doubted Hogwarts children could be considered the enemy of anyone with enough power and skill to engineer an entire epidemic.

Rigel sighed, thinking that perhaps she should just trust Snape to know what he was talking about, and decided to concentrate on finding a way to keep herself safe from the illness first and foremost. Archie was right after all. More than just her health was at stake if she fell ill and was left to the mercies of immodest Healers. She knew for a fact that the doses for Snowhit were slightly different for girls than for boys, so if nothing else the Healer would have to double check her sex for that reason.

She thanked Professor Snape for telling her what he had, knowing he was under no obligation to satisfy her curiosity, and left his office with a new focus for her never-busy-enough life. If the sickness preyed on open minds, then she would just have to make sure her mind was as closed as possible.

A couple of weeks flew by between brewing Aurora's Breath, keeping up with classes, and trying to ignore the ever-mounting number of children confined to Quarantine. It wasn't until early March that she caught up with Flint after what had looked like a particularly gnarly early morning Quidditch practice. He was checking over the team's equipment in the Slytherin section of the school storage shed, making sure his team members had cleaned and stowed theirs properly, when Rigel slipped into the shed and shut the door loudly after checking to make sure there was no one else inside.

Flint whirled, wand half-raised, and Rigel held up her hands in the universal "don't shoot" posture, making sure her face was clearly visible in the morning light that filtered through the grimy window to her right.

Flint grunted and lowered his wand, but he didn't turn his back to her again. Instead, he said, "What?"

"It's about our deal," Rigel said quietly, and Flint rolled his eyes before leaning back against a crate of practice quaffles nonchalantly.

"Oh yeah?" he said mildly, "Finally decided you've had enough?"

"No," Rigel said, frowning. Surely he didn't expect her to just quit and go home. "Look, it's not that I don't trust you Flint, and so far you've kept your word, but things are getting…complicated."

"Complicated," Flint repeated.

"Dangerous," Rigel amended, "Blood identity theft is a big deal, you know that." Flint nodded, so Rigel went on, "If it was just that I was afraid of what would happen to me if I got caught, I would take your word and consider our business iron clad. Unfortunately, I don't have that luxury anymore. The political climate is too volatile. If my and Archie's deception came to light right now, there are some who would use it as an excuse to go after everyone with blood like me. I don't want to sacrifice my goals to some abstract chance that by following the rules things will work out, but neither do I want to carelessly make myself into an excuse for an all-out war against muggleborns and halfbloods."

"Okay," Flint shrugged, looking particularly unimpressed, "So?"

"You're the only one besides Archie and I that knows the truth," she said, neglecting to mention that not even he knew all of the truth, "I need a guarantee that no matter what happens, our secret is safe as long as I hold up my end of the bargain and continue to complete your assignments for you."

Flint considered her silently, then said flatly, "You want a Vow. To ensure I won't tell."

"Not exactly," Rigel said, rather nervous about asking this but unwilling to show it, "Most Vows stipulate that a person can't do or tell something without suffering consequences, but the fact remains that the person who took the Vow could still technically break it, as long as he was willing to pay a price. I want to ensure that you can't reveal our secret, even under duress, even under a Truth Spell."

"And how do you plan to do that?" Flint said sarcastically. "Last I checked, even if I took the strongest Unbreakable Vow, it wouldn't stop me from telling, it would just kill me."

"Well, there are two options, actually," Rigel told him, "The first is that you allow me to modify your memory when our contract is complete—"

"No."

Rigel took in the fiercely adamant look on Flint's face and nodded in agreement, "Right, well, that's good actually because I don't know how to modify someone's memory. The second option is a bit more intrusive, though."

"What is it?" Flint said tiredly, "Just spit out your demands already, I have breakfast to get to."

"It's a Sealing Curse," Rigel said, "I want you to let me Seal the knowledge of our duplicity in your soul. If done right, the spell prevents the knowledge from ever being shared or relayed in any way either voluntarily or involuntarily. It's not as bad as it sounds," she added quickly, anticipating Flint's objections, "It does take away free will just a tiny bit, but you wouldn't ever have to worry about accidentally slipping up ten years from now, and it gives you an easy out if the secret comes out some other way and the authorities ask you why you never told anyone if you knew. You just tell them I cursed you with a Sealing Curse, and you're off the hook."

Rigel was actually quite proud of herself for finding such a spell. It was one of the many contingent spells that purebloods had developed over the centuries to place guarantees or restrictions on matters of honour. There were Vows, Seals, and Bindings of all kinds, though most of them had fallen out of use, being rather…extreme. This one had been referenced as an example in one of the volumes on pureblood customs she'd borrowed from the Black library (which she was really planning on reading more carefully one of these days), and she'd tracked down a description in an old dueling book of all things in the Hogwarts Library the night before. Apparently the forfeits for lost duels used to be a good deal more restrictive.

Flint was staring at her with something like disbelief wrapped around the suspicion that he was witnessing something insane and didn't know what to do about it.

"You want me to let you curse me—permanently, so that I have no choice but to keep your little secret, which will probably be revealed in a year or two anyway because of the sheer ridiculousness of the nature of your duplicity, is that about the gist of it?" It was hard to tell what Flint was thinking, but Rigel nodded reluctantly. He'd pretty much summed it up, though of course she didn't think their pretense would be revealed so easily as he assumed. "What's in it for me?" Flint asked bluntly.

Rigel had to think for a moment to see what he meant, "You mean, since I'm upping the ante on our deal technically, you want an additional concession as well?"

"Yes, I do," Flint said, smirking now.

"And in return for this additional concession, you'll take the Sealing Curse, just like that?"

"Yes, I will."

Rigel shrugged, aware that she was in no position to bargain at this point, "Then, you can have whatever you want, I guess."

"I can, can't I?" Flint mused, eyes glinting with amusement as he made her wait on edge for his decision, "Hmm, the possibilities are rather endless. I could have you carry my books between classes, or personally cut up my steak at dinner, but I really think a life-long curse merits something equally…how did you put it? Intrusive. Don't you think?"

"Now who's prevaricating?" Rigel muttered, though she didn't disagree with the upperclassman. She was demanding a lot, so she'd find a way to pull off whatever he wanted in return. Frankly he could have reported her a long time ago, and she owed him for offering to make a deal with her in the first place, if for nothing else.

"Well, the trouble is I can't think of anything I really want at the moment, what with you already doing my assignments for the foreseeable future," Flint said, "So I guess I'll just have to take a leaf out of your book and demand something rather similar."

Rigel swallowed nervously at the smug look on Flint's face. She could already tell she wasn't going to like this.

"I want a Vow of Undisclosed Debt," he said, flashing his canines at her in a feral sort of grin.

"That sounds pretty self-explanatory," she remarked.

"It is," Flint said, "It's a Vow that basically acknowledges an unfulfilled debt to another person, and when the person it's keyed to calls the debt in, the Vow activates and monitors the person who owes the debt until they satisfy it. It's pretty loose on the timeframe, unless the person who calls in the debt specifies something, but if it senses you don't intend to fulfill the debt to the best of your ability it steps in."

"Steps in?" Rigel frowned.

"The Vow has been known to take control of a wizard's mind and magic and ensure that the debt gets repaid if the opportunity arises and the wizard seems reluctant," Flint shrugs, "But you wouldn't try and weasel out of it, would you? So you've nothing to worry about."

Rigel sighed, seeing the many ways in which things could go horribly wrong, depending on what Flint asked for, but not seeing any other option if she wanted to ensure that the leak Flint represented was plugged, so to speak.

"Can I qualify that slightly?" she asked.

"How so?" Flint raised an eyebrow, seeming surprised at something. Perhaps he'd been expecting a flat refusal? As if she'd give him the excuse to call the deal off entirely.

"When you call this debt in, can you run what you plan on asking for by me before you actually invoke the Vow?" Rigel widened her eyes imploringly, and Flint snorted.

"What for? Going to kill me if it turns out to be something you don't want to do?" He seemed amused at the very idea.

"Of course not," Rigel said, "But there are things you don't know about me, and if you happen to ask for something that would be literally impossible for me to do, I would like a chance to explain why it would be a bad idea to ask for such a debt."

"Like what?" Flint asked curiously.

"Well what if you asked me to kill my sister, but it turns out I don't have any sisters? What would the Vow do then?" she pointed out. She really didn't want to know what would happen if he called in the debt for something that would be physically impossible for a girl to do, simply because he assumed she was a boy.

Flint shrugged unconcernedly, "I doubt it would be something like that, but sure, I'll give you that."

"So the agreement is as follows," Rigel said, making sure she had it all straight in her head, "I will complete all the school assignments you ask me to for an unspecified amount of time, and I will also take a Vow of Undisclosed Debt to be paid at any time in the future. In return, you will allow the knowledge of my and Archie's duplicity to be Sealed permanently within you, and will warn me before you call in the Undisclosed Debt in case I have a reasonable objection. You also won't tell anyone of my secret before it is Sealed, and I will do my best to keep anyone from finding out that I am the one doing your assignments. Agreed?"

"Deal," Flint said, "We'll swap Vows and Seals on Saturday morning. Meet me here before the sun rises."

Rigel nodded. She went to leave the storage shed, but turned over her shoulder at the last moment and said, "Thanks, Flint."

"Don't thank me just yet, kid."

In the end, the exchange of promises with Flint turned out to be easier than she was expecting. They forwent a binder, for obvious reasons, and because there were only two of them in the room while they made the Vow and Seal, no names were required either, because the pronouns "you" and "me" were referentially obvious.

The Sealing Curse was child's play, as far as curses went. Because it was a precursor to the Fidelius Charm, it required the consent of the cursed to be effective, and it was for this reason, not any difficulty in the spell itself, that it fell into disuse. Once absolutes were considered honourable in pureblood circles, but nowadays most preferred to have a little wriggle room in their commitments.

Both ceremonies took barely twenty minutes, and when she left the Quidditch shed Rigel felt much lighter. No one could ever get her secret out of Flint now, and with both she and Archie working on their Occlumency as much as possible, their plans were that much closer to turning out successfully.

Speaking of Occlumency, she thought as she trekked back to the castle. Now would be a good opportunity to practise some more. She was determined not to let this sickness have a crack at her, and the best thing she could do based on Snape's description of the transmission would be to shore up her mental defences whenever she could.

Rigel made her way to her dorm room to surreptitiously pick up her "Gryffindor" disguise, and then went up to a bathroom near the Library to change. She was getting good at ensuring she was unrecognizable in her disguises, and as she deftly tucked her hair into the red wig and slid the glasses up her nose she automatically assumed a slumped sort of posture and a faraway expression. She left her Gryffindor tie a bit crooked and shuffled out of the bathroom toward the Library.

She found a nice quiet corner where she could meditate undisturbed and curled into the chair in a way that made her look more like a bookworm taking a nap than a focused wizard exercising advanced meditation techniques. She retreated into herself. It was sort of like what she did when she used her sixth senses to 'look' at her magical core, but instead of her magic, she was focusing on her mind. The same sort of visualization took place, but unlike her magical core, her mind didn't move or react independently from her will. She could act on her mental landscape, change it and shape it, but it wouldn't do anything she didn't specifically will it to do.

The mists that made up the peripherals of her mindscape parted before her awareness and revealed the great, white mountain that made up the centre of her mind. It was huge in her mental estimation, and the whiteness came from the ice and snow piled on its face. She shivered in the cold wind that blew around her mountain and quickly made her way to the small opening near the base that was hidden behind an illusion of a wall of ice. Once through the illusion, her mind opened up into a warm cavern, which glowed with the light of a huge fireplace and several torches burning on the walls. The cavern looked like an underground Potions Lab, with crates and cabinets of ingredients filling the space. There were invitingly comfortable couches where she might sit and peruse the memories bound up in the various scrolls intermixed with Potions recipes. That is, she might if she didn't know that the main cavern was one big decoy, a reflection of what people would expect her mind to look like.

Since she had built these caverns herself, Harry—for indeed, this far in her own mind she was Harry and her mental avatar looked like she thought she would have if she'd never cut off all her hair—walked straight through the cavern to the big, woven rug that lay before the hearth. She pulled the rug back to reveal the trap door beneath, grinning a bit as she hauled it open. It was so cliché but she just loved having a trap door hidden under a rug in her mindscape. When she had first gotten a solid visual on the White Mountain, as she referred to her mental fortress when she was feeling particularly cheesy, she hadn't been sure what to make of it. It took several more meditation sessions before she could figure out how to enact changes in her mental scene that would remain permanent even when her awareness left. Once she'd gotten the hang of it, though, it was a lot easier than even working with her magic. She didn't have to ask for anything here, she just imagined it, and willed it into being.

Harry dropped through the trap door to the tunnel beneath, which was carved roughly from rock, but embedded with pale green crystals that lit up automatically when the trap door swung shut above her head. The tunnel led in half a dozen directions currently, to help confuse any intruders, though the false branches didn't extend very far as of yet. She worked on them in her free time, but someday she hoped to have a labyrinth worthy of Daedalus carved out. As it was, she took the third path from the right and followed it as it sloped upwards, moving further and further into the heart of the mountain.

She emerged from the tunnel eventually into her favourite place in her mindscape so far. It was a vast, hollowed cavern that stretched as far as the eye could see, completely ignoring the laws of physics that would consider the encompassing of such infinite space within a mountain, no matter how large, to be an impossibility. And space it was. The cavern was dark as night, lit by the light of a thousand stars, which twinkled in a way that Harry knew stars really didn't as they floated by her in the enormous space. These stars were her true memories, not the decoy potion scrolls in the comparably miniscule cavern at the entrance to her mountainside. They drifted peacefully for the most part, though a select few zoomed by, leaving a trail of light behind them as they went.

In truth her Astronomy professor would be appalled to see this, Harry thought happily. In addition to the stars drifting aimlessly about the endless black space, there were planets too. The planets housed her more troublesome memories and emotions, the ones she wanted to keep a close hold on, and the number of rings around a planet corresponded to how securely she wanted the memory or emotion to be bound. The planets glowed with subtle light of their own as well, but they paled in relation to what lay at the centre of her outer-space room.

Harry pushed off the floor of the cavern and drifted upwards without constraints of gravity to worry about, floating toward the centre of the space so she could admire what lay at the heart of her Snow Mountain, the centre of her universe. It was a sun, burning bright and brilliant, and in truth she could not even take credit for it. It had been here when she'd first burrowed inside the mountain to seek shelter from the cold, windy mists, and it was what made everything possible. The sun was her magic. It was the energy that powered everything in her mindscape, from the snow on the peak of the mountain to the fire that burned merrily in the hearth of the decoy potions lab. Because it had looked like a sun when she'd found it, she'd fashioned the room that housed it to look like outer space accordingly, albeit a skewed and disproportioned version of it, considering that the 'stars' were so much smaller than the sun, when in a proportioned reality they would be roughly similar sizes.

When she reached the sun, she could feel the warmth and energy radiating off of it. She spent a moment basking in the feeling of pure life that wrapped around her mental form when she got close enough, but soon she drifted back toward the tunneled entrance to the Space Room. It wouldn't do to get too comfortable here, or she could wind up spending all her time in her head.

Harry touched earth and took a moment to steady herself as gravity kicked back in before heading off to work on carving more tunnels. Perhaps she'd see about implanting some explosives in the walls of strategic tunnels, so that she could collapse them remotely if she ever had to…

In real time, she spent about four hours meditating. She knew this because she checked her watch when she came back to herself. Mental time was a strange and not strictly speaking reliable thing. Rigel stretched out the kink in her neck and glanced around her corner of the Library. The tables around her were still empty and her book bag didn't appear to have been disturbed. Not that anyone would find much to disturb if they tried. Most of the important things she carried—Flint's assignments, the Map, and letters she was writing to her parents and Archie—were inside compartments that wouldn't open for anyone else.

She was just about to take out her Herbology book and get started on an essay for the following Tuesday when a sound caught the edges of her senses and she stilled, cocking her head to listen closer. When she zeroed in on the sound, she realized it was someone crying, and they were somewhere in the stacks to her right. Whoever it was also seemed to be attempting to stifle the noises rather unsuccessfully. Rigel sighed, but picked up her bag and moved in the direction of the muffled sobbing. It wasn't that she was a Dora Do-Gooder or anything, but she couldn't exactly concentrate on her schoolwork with someone crying nearby, could she? She ignored the voice in her head that suggested she might simply move to a different table, and peered around the edge of the bookcase that sounded closest to the source of the noise.

Sitting on the floor, knees bent and hugged tightly to her chest, was a Ravenclaw girl with long dark hair and pale pink stockings that peeped out from under her robes. Her shoes had been discarded next to her book bag, which was upturned on the floor next to her, as if it had spilled and instead of righting it she'd sunk down to the ground and just broken down.

Rigel cautiously approached the girl, not trying to sneak up on her but not wanting to startle her either. Her bag brushed against the bookcase as she passed it and the Ravenclaw looked up at her immediately through straight black bangs. Her face had an Asian look about it, and Rigel thought she might be a second year. The girl wiped her sleeve across her eyes ruefully, as if she fully expected to be teased and wasn't going to bother being embarrassed about it. Rigel dropped her own bag to the floor and slid down the stacks to sit down next to the girl.

She fished in her bag for the handkerchief she (as a pureblood boy) kept in there, and offered it to the Ravenclaw, mentally thankful that Archie didn't have his handkerchiefs monogrammed like Draco did.

The girl took it after only a moment of consideration, which frankly surprised Rigel until she remembered she was wearing Gryffindor robes, not Slytherin. No wonder the girl didn't look like she was waiting for Rigel to hex her.

"Rough morning?" Rigel asked, not sure how to get a stranger to open up, but deciding to start out general and then work her way to the specifics.

"It's this sickness," the girl burst out, "It got Marietta this morning, and I don't want to be next."

Or, Rigel thought bemusedly, they could just skip right to the point.

"You might not get sick," she started to say, but the older girl shut her up with a glare before she could get too far into the platitudes.

"All the first year Ravenclaws are ill, and it's just me and one other second year left in our dorm. Most of the Hufflepuff first through third years are sick, and Ravenclaws have the most classes with Hufflepuff, so of course I'm going to be next," she said. Her voice was sharp but her eyes were flat, "I watched Marietta collapse. She didn't even stir when Flitwick levitated her off to Quarantine. I don't want to just fall into darkness with no warning, no way to fight it or even accept that it's happened. Marietta was still smiling when she went unconscious. I won't even know before it gets me and-and-" she heaved a shuddering breath in and closed her eyes as she whispered, "I'm frightened."

Rigel sat in silence for a moment, not sure what to say. It was true that the illness had grown progressively worse over the past few weeks. Slytherin House was the least affected, probably because they seldom deigned to mix with the other Houses, and even then most of the first years were gone and almost half of the second years. Crabbe and Goyle were sick, as were Davis and Greengrass. Millicent had fallen ill just the day before. And Theo was still sick too, of course.

She'd known on some level how scary the illness was to most of her classmates, but she'd been so busy she hadn't realized what it must feel like to be able to do nothing. To have no choice but to sit around and wait for it to take you, and no one telling you anything. It was heartbreaking. Rigel hoped she never felt like that, and she made a vow to keep twice as busy if this sort of hopeless panicking was the alternative.

Still, she could at least do something for the girl.

"What's your name?" Rigel asked quietly.

"Cho," she said, still sniffling a bit but mostly together, "Cho Chang."

"Cho, did you know that the sickness that's going around isn't deadly?"

The Ravenclaw stared at her before slowly shaking her head back and forth, "How do you know?"

"I overheard some teachers talking about it," she invented, unable to tell her about her unofficial role in making potions for Snape.

"So it's not true that the Quarantine is just to hide the fact that the kids die and aren't coming back?" she asked tremulously.

"No, that's not true," Rigel said firmly. She hesitated, not wanted to reveal too much, but a look at Cho's scared and lost expression had her giving in. Please don't let her be an agent of evil, she thought wryly. Truly she didn't think there would be any harm in telling Cho a few things about the sickness to make her feel better. If nothing else, the girl was right. If the sickness traveled on mental pathways, then those who spent a lot of time together would infect each other. If Marietta was a good friend of hers, Cho likely would be one of the next to get sick. "Can you keep a secret, Cho?" she asked seriously.

Cho narrowed her eyes at her, but she nodded slowly, "Yes."

"Good," Rigel said, "Then I can tell you that all the kids who are sick are still alive and not at all in mortal danger."

Cho opened her mouth, but Rigel shook her head, "I can't tell you how I know, but I do. The illness just put them all to sleep. The Quarantine is because the sleeping is contagious, but when they cure it, all the kids will be fine."

"Sleeping?" Cho sounded sceptical, but hopeful.

"Yeah," Rigel nodded, taking the handkerchief back from Cho and stowing it in her bag while she talked, "When you go to sleep at night, can you remember the moment you stop being awake?"

"No," Cho said.

"And does that scare you? Do you think it would be scary if you fell asleep smiling because of something you were thinking about when it happened?" Rigel pressed, appealing to the Ravenclaw's logic.

"No, of course not," Cho said, smiling a bit.

"You see? The sickness is just like that. Like falling asleep," Rigel said softly, "And when you wake up, it'll be Springtime again, none of this dreary March wind. Think of all the boring History classes you'll miss."

Cho chuckled quietly, "Yeah, and maybe I'll sleep through finals too."

"And your friends won't miss you, because they'll all be asleep too," Rigel said.

"Yeah," the Ravenclaw sighed, "At least I won't be worrying about it anymore."

Rigel smiled, "Everything will be okay, Cho Chang. If nothing else, you'll get to catch up on your beauty sleep."

"Hey, what are you trying to say?" Cho laughed, shoving her shoulder indignantly.

"What? Nothing," Rigel said innocently, "I'm just saying it couldn't hurt."

"Alright, stop talking now," the Ravenclaw said. She reached for her shoes to slip them back on and started gathering up her spilled belongings as well, "Seriously though, thanks. I feel better now."

"No problem," Rigel shrugged. She stood and scooped up her bag by the strap.

Before she could leave, Cho said, "Wait. What's your name?"

Rigel hesitated. What could she say? Technically the red-haired, glasses wearing boy she was dressed as didn't exist. Oh well, it's not like Cho would go check the registry.

"I'm Reggie," she improvised, "See you around."

"Yeah, bye," Cho called as Rigel turned and headed out of the Library.

Really, what was one more lie?

She changed back into her normal Slytherin robes and stowed the wig and glasses in her bag before heading back toward the dungeons. She had an urge to see what Pansy and Draco were doing. It came to her rather suddenly that Pansy and Draco were first years too, and the thought of their vulnerability to the sickness made her acutely uncomfortable. She wanted to see for herself that they were both still conscious, even if it meant being scolded for disappearing all Saturday morning.

-*_*-[Hp]-*_*-

A few nights later, Rigel snuck out of her dorm at five minutes past midnight, invisibility cloak tucked under one arm and Marauder's Map tucked innocently in her robe pocket. She had letters to mail to Archie and Sirius and assignments to mail to Flint, and lately she'd been more on edge than usual about the attention others might pay to her correspondence. She knew it was mostly paranoia, but in general Rigel thought paranoia was a survival trait, especially for those who led potentially hazardous lives.

Perhaps it was this paranoia, on top of her admittedly rather potent curiosity, that had her slowing down, stopping, and narrowing her eyes at the Map when she caught sight of two unlikely figures standing awfully close together.

Two dots labeled Severus Snape and Quirinus Quirrell were barely a millimetre apart on the Map, and after a brief and rather disturbing moment in which she considered the possibility that they were having an "adult" moment, Rigel quickly discarded that ridiculous scenario (with no small amount of grossed-out-ness) and changed her course on a split-second whim. Letter mailing could wait in light of the information that two of her teachers were either trapped in close quarters by a band of rogue suits of armour or strangling one another.

Rigel wrapped herself in the invisibility cloak and set off toward the basement corridor the Map indicated. A few minutes later she quietly wiped and folded the Map, which was already heating up to indicate the impending presence of a teacher after curfew, so she'd have both hands to keep the invisibility cloak steady. When she was sure every part of her was covered, she rounded the corner silently and drifted down the hallway toward where she could now see Snape and Quirrell having what looked like a heated discussion.

She got just close enough to hear their conversation clearly, wishing she could get close enough to see their faces in the dim lighting but not sure she could keep her breathing quiet enough to escape Snape's notice at that range.

Snape had Quirrell backed against the wall, and looked to be keeping the reluctant Defence teacher frozen in place with his glare alone, "…need to know more, Quirrell."

Quirrell was muttering something indistinct under his breath and Snape growled menacingly in response, "Don't lie to me, Quirrell, you are the only one in this school high enough in His favour to have been charged with this mission. If you know anything about this sickness you must inform me now."

Rigel's eyes widened beneath her cloak and she frowned in concentration, straining to pick up what Quirrell was mumbling.

"If He didn't tell you, Severus," the pale-faced man said nervously, "I really can't—that is, perhaps you aren't supposed to know. Perhaps He doesn't trust—"

"He gives me no more information than necessary, that I might play my part convincingly, Quirrell," Snape snapped, "But what was necessary has changed. I must know how to end this sickness, should the need arise."

"It will be called off when the legislation has gone through," Quirrell protested.

"Fool! The sickness is spreading more rapidly than anticipated," Snape said impatiently, "I have already used up all my stores and the local suppliers are running dry as well. Without the ingredients to keep their bodies alive, it doesn't matter if the sickness is recalled when He's gotten what He wants."

"I don't know what you want me to do, Severus," Quirrell whined, flinching under the Potions Master's presumably dark expression.

"Tell me how to counter it," Snape pressed, "Just in case, Quirrell. The mission is important, but do you think He wants pureblooded children to end up dead? That will not sit well with His plans, especially if this ever gets traced back to Him somehow. Their parents will turn on more than just Dumbledore if these children come to any actual harm because you haven't given me enough information to step in if I judge it to be necessary."

"I can't, I don't know how myself, Severus," Quirrell said finally, speaking quickly, as if to convince Snape all in one breath, "But I will ask Him. I will tell Him what you say, when I am next called, and surely He will have a solution."

Snape growled wordlessly and spat, "You'd better hope you see Him soon," before turning and stalking off down the corridor at a furious pace without looking back. Rigel held her breath as Quirrell shakily adjusted his collar and walked slowly past her, his eyes glazed with some combination of fear and relief.

When Rigel was alone in the corridor, she took out the Map once more and made her way slowly but surely back to her common room. She had to think, and to do that she needed to be somewhere she could afford to space out. Rigel hurriedly stowed her cloak and map in her trunk and then returned to the main common room area and sank down into a low-backed couch to figure out what she'd just seen and heard.

The first and most obvious conclusion she was faced with was: Snape knew who sent the sickness. There was no doubt that the sickness was magically constructed now, and it had definitely been sent to Hogwarts for a purpose. Also obvious from what Snape had said was that the purpose of the sickness was not to kill. It was an intimidation tactic of some kind, meant to undermine the confidence parents had in Hogwarts and therefore the Headmaster. Someone wanted people turned against the Headmaster, and it had something to do with legislation. Her mind immediately reminded her of the friendly warnings Rosier and Rookwood had given her about legislation that was being pushed forward in June. Just a few months away, and no doubt this was when people would begin to take sides on this issue.

Rigel nodded slowly to herself as the pieces began to come together. The SOW party wanted new anti-muggle-blood legislation, but to get it ratified they needed to sway popular opinion away from Dumbledore, as well as get a good amount of Light parents away from the Headmaster. To do that, they infected the children of the most powerful purebloods, both Light and Dark, in the country with a seemingly serious sickness while Dumbledore was supposed to be responsible for said children. Faith in Dumbledore wanes, new legislation gets pushed through, children are miraculously cured when the sickness is called back, no harm done to them, but for muggleborns and halfbloods it's too late. The Marriage Law is already on the books.

But where did Snape come in?

Clearly he knew something about where this illness originated from, but if his words to Quirrell were truthful he didn't know how to cure it and seemed to be genuinely concerned about it in a practical sense. He didn't seem overly concerned in a moral sense that the sickness had been sent to a school full of children to make a political point, supposedly harmless or not, and Rigel wasn't sure how she felt about that.

Well, okay, she was pretty sure she didn't like it, but on the other hand it wasn't really her place to judge her Professor, who was older, wiser, and probably had a rational reason for most of the things he did. Also there was the fact that Snape might have been bluffing in his knowledge to Quirrell in order to trick the cure out of him, which Rigel sort of hoped for Snape's sake he hadn't been, or else things could get awkward when Quirrell told Him (whoever He was) what Snape had been fishing for.

All in all, Rigel was both more enlightened and more confused than she had been when she left for the Owlery just half an hour earlier. She guessed she could still go to the Owlery, but she was exhausted just thinking about it. Instead, she went back to her room and tried to fall asleep even though the sound of Theo's quiet breathing, which she hadn't even realized had been familiar, was conspicuously absent.

The next morning Rigel dragged herself up to the Owlery to send her post, and on her way back down was waylaid in the Entrance Hall by Alesana Selwyn, whom Rigel had trouble placing for a moment due to the fact that she'd never spoken to the upperclassman outside of Snape's office.

"Hey Black," Selwyn said after taking hold of Rigel's elbow, forcing her to pause and peer tiredly up at her, "Wow, you look like crap."

"Thanks," Rigel muttered absently. Her brain felt like mush that morning and she hadn't had breakfast yet.

"Well, just a heads up," Selwyn said, "Rookwood's looking for you. He finally figured out what was in that vial you gave him, and he wants to rail at you for misleading him or something."

Rigel blinked at the smug smirk on Selwyn's face and repeated, "He just figured it out? Does that mean you win?"

"Well, this round, sure," Selwyn said easily, "It took him more than two weeks, which means I actually get an extra point for this one."

"You guys keep score?" Rigel frowned. How long did these games run?

"Of course," the older Slytherin said, "Whoever has the most points at midnight on December 31st wins, and then next year we start all over."

"What do you win?" Rigel asked, stifling a yawn.

"I'll tell you when you're older," she winked, then strode off down the steps to the dungeons, humming contentedly.

Rigel shook her head dazedly and stumbled into the Great Hall to find food and hopefully something to wake her up a bit more.

When she sat down at the table, the first-year end of which was looking depressingly sparse, Rigel barely had time to acknowledge Pansy's polite "good morning" before Rookwood squeezed his way abruptly between the two first years with a hurried, "excuse me, Pansy," and stared expectantly at the side of Rigel's head.

Rigel turned her head slowly to look at the large upperclassman, whose stare was moving from intimidating to creepy the longer he sat there not saying anything. Finally she said, with as much emotion as she could muster after the night she'd had tossing and mentally turning over what she'd eavesdropped on, "It seems Selwyn wasn't joking about you wanting to talk to me."

"I can wait until you've eaten something," Rookwood said seriously, still turned in his seat to face her, eyes boring into her face like blank drills.

Rigel raised an eyebrow. Like I'd be more comfortable with you watching me eat. "No, that's okay," she said bracingly, "Go ahead."

Rookwood spoke immediately, "Why did you tell me you'd collected the sample you gave me yourself? Did Selwyn tell you to lie to me? I need to know if she's changing the rules of the game to include unreliable messengers, you see."

"Uh, she didn't, because I wasn't lying," Rigel said, frowning, "I collected the venom not twenty minutes before I handed it to you, Rookwood."

"Unlikely," Rookwood said thoughtfully, "Though of course its very unlikeliness is what made me dismiss the possibility of dangerous snake venom until it was too late. How did you get venom from a boomslang snake? Did Hagrid help you?"

"He did what?" Pansy leaned around Rookwood to frown disapprovingly at Rigel, "What have you been getting up to, Rigel? You look just awful this morning, and Draco said he heard you come in way past curfew last night. You really should take better care of yourself. Honestly, snake venom? That can't be safe."

Rigel smiled fondly at Pansy and shrugged noncommittally just because she knew it would annoy the blonde. Pansy just sighed and went back to her breakfast. Rigel told Rookwood, "My dad really likes snakes, believe it or not. He raises them in our courtyard, so I've gotten pretty good at handling snakes in general." Technically all of that was true, Rigel thought to herself, rather proud at how good she was getting at misdirection.

"Sirius Black, a snake-lover?" Rookwood shook his head wryly, "Well I suppose that explains it, but who could have guessed?"

"One of my father's many goals in life is to continually surprise people," Rigel said, a slight smile on her face as she thought of how true that was.

Rookwood was apparently satisfied with her explanations, for he stood and bade her good day, moving to join the other fourth years further down the table.

Rigel gratefully tucked in to her breakfast and listened to Pansy fill her in on the breakfast gossip.

That Friday evening Rigel went to Snape's office to deliver the latest batch of Aurora's Breath. She had taken to just bringing Snape the crates as soon as they were full, so that she didn't end up having to transport so many in one go again. He didn't answer her knock, but the door was slightly ajar so she pushed it open further with her foot and went in, carrying the crate carefully while at the same time trying to see if the Professor was there. She heard his voice, but she couldn't see him right away. After she set the crate down on his desk she looked around and realized that the stretch of wall that was normally blank housed a large fireplace as she had seen it do once before, and sure enough the floo network was activated, as evidenced by the emerald green flames casting eerie shadows around the room.

The head of a mostly bald middle aged wizard with a thin moustache was floating in the hearth, and Professor Snape was kneeling on the stone in front of it, looking not at all happy at what the bald man was telling him.

"You know I would if I could, Snape," the head said earnestly, "But you've cleaned us out. I don't know what the heck you need so much Ginseng for, but you know how hard it is to grow, especially in a northern climate. What did you expect after three months of snatching up every available crop?"

"Surely there is Ginseng somewhere," Snape pressed, "I need it, Horace, you have no inkling of how vitally."

Rigel silently agreed. Ginseng was one of the main ingredients in both Aurora's Breath and Snowhit Draught, due to its incredible nutritional value. If they were running low, things would go downhill very quickly.

"Well you won't find it in England," Horace sighed, "You know I'd never give away business, so if I'm telling you to look to foreign suppliers…"

"You truly don't have any recourse available," Snape finished wearily, "Damn. I don't like working with suppliers I don't know. This…project is too important to blindly trust in the quality of imported ingredients."

"Sorry, Snape," Horace said, "Have you considered using Acai berries? They aren't quite as potent, but the effect is similar."

"I have, but Acai berries cause other complications in the recipe," Snape said.

"Well, you're the Potions Master," Horace said, and Rigel got the impression that if his shoulders were visible they'd be shrugging, "Good luck with whatever you're doing."

"Indeed, Horace," Snape said shortly, "Good day."

The head disappeared and it occurred to Rigel that her presence in the room would now be a bit awkward, but when Snape stood and turned he didn't look at all surprised to see her.

"Mr. Black," Snape acknowledged.

"Hello, sir," Rigel said, not all that apologetically. She and Archie had come to the general conclusion in their youth that one could either feel bad about overhearing something one shouldn't or embrace eavesdropping and all the advantages and disadvantages that came with it.

"Another crate already?" Snape frowned at the Aurora's Breath on his desk for a moment and Rigel quickly reassured him.

"Still under my 25 cauldrons a week, sir."

"Ah," Snape said, looking tired and stressed, "Very well then."

"Sir?" Rigel ventured, "What are we going to do about the Ginseng?"

Snape looked at Rigel seriously, "Pray this sickness does not last much longer, Mr. Black."

"And if it does?" Rigel persisted.

Snape sighed, but took a moment to think seriously about the problem, "I will be honest with you, Mr. Black. We have no Ginseng unless you have any left over from this last batch of Aurora's Breath."

Rigel shook her head ruefully. In truth she had used both what Snape had given her and what she had in her personal kit to finish off the last cauldron.

Snape nodded as if he expected as much, "Then I will attempt to find alternate suppliers. I will have to go in person. I cannot accurately judge the quality of potential ingredients remotely. In the meantime, we will begin using Acai berries as a substitute in both potions. I will give you the revised recipes."

Rigel blinked at him in surprise, "Recipes?"

"Yes," Snape said, looking reluctant but resigned, "While I am gone you will be in charge of producing both potions. I do not know how long it will take for me to find a viable supplier. Ginseng is extraordinarily difficult to grow properly, so I've no doubt I will have to sift through scores of sub-quality crops to find something we can use."

Rigel's eyes widened and she swallowed. That was an awful lot of responsibility to give to a first year.

Snape eyed her knowingly, "It is a lot to ask. Normally, I would find an older student to handle things while I am gone, and indeed the prefects and other professors will likely pick up most of my duties, but I have no time to teach and test another student and you know how to make Aurora's Breath already. I've seen you watching me brew Snowhit as well. You know what both potions should look and feel like, and your magical reserves are deep enough to handle the strain for the days I am gone."

"Can the Hospital Wing afford for our production to be halved?" Rigel asked worriedly.

"It cannot," Snape said, "That is why as of Monday you are excused from all classes and assignments until I return."

Rigel took a deep breath, "What will I tell my classmates?"

"Tell them nothing except that you have a task related to your studies that will take up all of your time," Snape said, "I will speak to Dumbledore this evening, and leave tomorrow morning. If you have anything you need to take care of before you start brewing, I suggest you do so tonight. Snowhit is a demanding potion, more so than Aurora's Breath. I believe you can handle this burden, but only if you do not waste energy doing other things. You will eat three meals a day, you will sleep eight hours a night, you will brew, and you will do nothing else. Is that clear? Pomfrey will check on you periodically, and if she sees you overdoing it you will be forced to stop."

Rigel nodded, "I understand, sir. I won't let you down."

"If I thought for a moment you would, I would not have entrusted this task to you, I assure you," Snape said, "Go and rest up, Mr. Black. I will leave the recipes in Lab One along with the changes necessary to accommodate the Acai berries. The wards will be reset to allow you admittance. Any questions?"

"No, sir," Rigel said grimly, "Good luck, sir."

She left Snape to his planning and headed straight to her dorm room to grab her book bag. She had to finish Flint's assignments and mail them tonight, so that she would not be distracted from brewing while Snape was gone. Rigel wasn't going to mess this up, no matter what.

The weekend passed in a frenzy of brewing. Rigel had often been accused of eating, sleeping and breathing potions, and never had that been truer. She woke and headed straight to Lab One, brewed for two hours, went to breakfast, brewed for eight hours with a short break to eat the lunch Binny brought her, went to dinner, brewed another four hours, showered, and collapsed on her bed until she woke to her alarm and repeated the cycle.

The brewing was hard. She kept up a cauldron each of Snowhit and Aurora's Breath constantly, and by dinnertime each day she could actually feel her magical core getting tired. She wondered if this was how potion-makers were supposed to feel when imbuing high-level potions. It was a bit disconcerting to feel the loss of magical energy; she felt somehow vulnerable. She went to bed each day feeling pretty much tapped out, and knew that if she hadn't been getting a full night's sleep and three meals a day like Snape ordered her magic would be hard pressed to recover by the time she started brewing again each morning. Rigel knew that she was working just barely under her limit, and didn't know how long she would be able to keep it up before she had to cut brewing back to twelve or even ten hours a day. The Snowhit Draught in particular was noticeably more draining than the Aurora's Breath, especially since it required extra magic to force the Acai berries to substitute relatively seamlessly for the Ginseng berries.

Her mind was entirely encompassed by her task, though she vaguely noticed the concerned looks she was getting from her friends. It wasn't until Tuesday evening as she tiredly moved toward her bed once more that one of her friends decided enough was enough.

"Rigel," Draco pulled her attention away from her welcoming pillow with a hand on her shoulder, "Rigel, don't go to sleep just yet, I need to talk to you."

Rigel blinked tiredly at her blond friend, and turned to face him, sitting down on the edge of her bed to rest her feet, which ached from standing all day for the fourth day in a row, and looking up at him. "Okay," she yawned, "What's up, Draco?"

"Well that's what I want to know," Draco said, frowning down at her, "You've been like a ghost for days, and Pansy is really worried."

Rigel smiled slightly at that, raising an eyebrow.

"Well, fine, I'm worried too you prat," Draco rolled his eyes, "Because no school project is worth this. You work yourself into exhaustion every night, then get up and do it again. It isn't healthy, and the more tired you are, the more likely you are to catch this sickness when your immune system is weak. You need to take it easy."

"I can't, Draco," Rigel told him tiredly, "I'm sorry, and I know you're worried, but believe me when I say I have to do my best on this. I won't get sick, I promise. When Snape comes back I can take a break, but right now—"

She broke off, staring in confusion that rapidly turned to surprise as Draco's eyes grew unfocused before rolling back into his head. Her friend collapsed like a boneless doll, and Rigel dove off of her bed instinctively to stop his head from hitting the corner of the bedside table.

She knelt with mounting horror, Draco's head still cradled in one of her hands, the other going to his shoulder to shake him first gently, then with increasing urgency, "Draco? Draco! Wake up, get up, Draco." She shook her head wildly, "Oh, no, no, please no." But Draco didn't answer, didn't twitch, didn't wake. He slumped awkwardly on the floor, unresponsive and rapidly growing paler. Rigel jumped up, no longer tired in the slightest, and ran out to the common room as fast as she could.

She skidded to a stop in front of Salazar Slytherin's portrait and gasped out, "Salazar, Salazar, get Snape. I need Snape."

The portrait looked concernedly down at her, "I'm sorry child, but Professor Snape is still absent from the school."

Rigel groaned, she knew that, damn it. Think, she scolded herself, Draco needs to get to the Hospital Wing. But I can't carry him there, and I don't know how magic interacts with the sickness.

She looked wildly around the common room, and spotted a familiar face watching her curiously from a low-backed chair nearby.

"Flint!" she called, relief evident in her voice. She could trust Flint with Draco. She ran over to him, panting, "Flint, I need your help. Draco's collapsed, and he has to go to the Hospital Wing, and Snape's gone, so you have to carry him—"

"Slow down, Black," Flint snapped, "Get a hold of yourself."

Rigel gulped down air as quietly as she could and waited for the upperclassman to do something.

"Now, Malfoy collapsed. It's okay, he's not in immediate danger," Flint said, oddly soothing, "Did he fall unconscious in your dorm room?"

"Yes," Rigel said quickly, feeling a bit calmer now that Flint was taking charge.

"Then I can't go collect him, and neither can any of the other upperclassmen. Only first-years can get into the first-year hallway," he said plainly.

Rigel cursed at herself, she had known that too, but had forgotten in her panic. Panicking wasn't helping. She had to think.

"Crabbe and Goyle are both sick," Rigel said, frowning unhappily, "I don't know where Blaise is and Pansy won't be able to lift Draco either."

"Then you'll have to do it," Flint said obviously.

Rigel groaned, "I can't, I'm—" she broke off to take a huge steadying breath before she said something she'd regret, "I don't have the strength."

"You just have to carry him as far as the common room," Flint said flatly, towing Rigel firmly across the common room and pushing her toward the first-year dorms, "Do you want to help Malfoy?"

Rigel nodded.

"Then go help him," Flint said.

Rigel nodded again and hurried back down the hallway to her dorm room. It would have to be the last one in the hall, she thought disgustedly as she propped open the door with someone's shoe and went to where Draco's prone form was still lying awkwardly on the ground. Somehow, she hoped Draco never found out she'd left him on the floor for a good few minutes while she panicked, as his Malfoy dignity probably wouldn't survive it.

Rigel bent and lifted one of Draco's arms around her shoulders, trying to get enough leverage to haul her friend up off the ground. The angle was awkward and Draco was dead weight, no matter that he really wasn't much bigger than she was. He was denser because of the muscle he'd put on under Flint's Quidditch regimen. Rigel's arms were tired from stirring all day and her sore feet ached in protest as she dug them into the carpet and strained upwards against their combined gravity. She barely got them upright when she went staggering sideways into Draco's bed and accidentally dropped her unconscious friend down onto it when her arms gave out. She stared down at the now-disheveled blond hopelessly while she caught her breath.

I can't do this, she thought, her frustration mounting, I'm just a weak little girl with no upper-body strength. If only I was stronger. If only I really was a boy. If Archie were here, he could do it.

She didn't know if it was her imagination, but she thought Draco looked flushed. The fever was starting and there was nothing she could do to help him.

No, she shook her head, despair is what won't help Draco. If I can't carry him with my arms, I have to carry him some other way.

With renewed determination, Rigel sat on the edge of Draco's bed and hauled his torso up so that his arms went around her neck. With a little manoeuvring, she managed to get most of his weight on her back and stood carefully, gripping his upper arms and bent nearly double to keep her friend from slipping off onto the floor again. Slowly, with crab-like steps, Rigel carried Draco across the room, out the door, and down the hallway. She had to stop and lean against the walls several times, but she eventually managed to make it to the end of the hallway, where Flint immediately lifted Draco from her back and onto his shoulder in a muggle fireman's lift.

Rigel panted, hands on her knees, and Flint clapped her on the back bracingly.

"Well done, Black," he said, "I'll take him from here."

Rigel took a halting step after Flint as the upperclassman headed toward the common room entrance with his burden, but he waved her off.

"There's nothing more you can do, kid," he said firmly, "They won't let you in the Quarantine. Just go to sleep now, and deal with the rest of it tomorrow."

Rigel felt all the energy drain out of her once more, and realized the adrenaline from watching Draco collapse was probably wearing off. She thought about waking Pansy and telling her about Draco, but couldn't bring herself to do it. Let her get one more night of sleep, she thought, Flint's right, there's nothing we can do tonight. But tomorrow, when her magic and strength was recovered once more, Rigel would find a way to see Draco somehow.

She knew, logically, that Draco was going to be fine. She knew, objectively, that Pomfrey would take good care of him and that the sickness wasn't even meant to be fatal. But somehow, she had a really bad feeling in the pit of her stomach that had nothing to do with rational thinking.

Chapter 20

Rigel woke the next morning and spent an entire minute staring up at the delicate hangings above her four-poster bed, wondering why she felt so sick to her stomach, before she remembered what had happened the night before.

Draco is in Quarantine.

Rigel was sorely tempted to close her eyes once more and go back to sleep. If she wished last night had all been a dream hard enough, surely it would become true. Wasn't that how magic worked? Rolling her eyes at her own thoughts, Rigel got out of bed and slipped on her shoes, moving quietly as if she still had roommates left to disturb and determinedly not looking around the empty dorm room as she left.

She went straight to Lab One and brewed for two hours. Then she stored the flasks of Snowhit Draught and Aurora's Breath in their respective crates and locked up the lab behind her. She hadn't strictly speaking needed to brew for two hours before breakfast. Rigel was ahead in her production levels and could afford to take a couple of hours off, but to be brutally honest she was avoiding Pansy. Their other best friend would be devastated that Draco had fallen ill, and with their Head of House gone ingredient hunting Rigel didn't know who would be responsible for telling Pansy what had happened. If it were up to her, she would avoid it as long as she could, but Pansy would find out sooner or later, and Rigel knew despite her unwillingness to cause Pansy any pain that it would be better coming from her.

Because Rigel hadn't had time for their morning walks in a long while, Pansy had taken to sleeping in until just before breakfast started. Without Millicent there to wake her up either, Pansy just barely got to breakfast on time nowadays, so Rigel wasn't surprised to hear a sleepy voice answer when she knocked on Pansy's dorm room door.

"Yes? Who is it?" Pansy called drowsily. She sounded exhausted, and Rigel winced, thinking perhaps she should have let her blonde friend sleep a little longer. But no, better that Pansy know before breakfast, so she could brace herself for the flood of commiseration she would likely receive from her upperclassman acquaintances. Pansy had many friends that were not yet affected by the sickness spreading throughout the school, and everyone would want to at least appear sympathetic in the wake of the Malfoy scion falling prey to the sickness.

"It's me, Pan," Rigel said, pitching her voice softly through the door.

"Rigel?" Shuffling noises came from behind the door before the knob turned and it cracked open slightly, allowing one bright blue eye to peer through the gap at her. The eye blinked, and Pansy said, "Give me just a moment, okay?"

"Certainly," Rigel said, hiding a smile at the glimpse of mussed blonde hair she'd caught before Pansy had hastily closed the door once more. Even after seven months of friendship, she had yet to see Pansy at any state less than total perfection, unless one counted the time Pansy had cried in her arms after the Lee Jordan incident, but even then her tears had been hidden in Rigel's robes and her hair a study in flawlessness. Rigel regretted that Pansy might never feel comfortable enough proprietarily speaking to just hang out in her pyjamas like Rigel and Archie often did together, but she supposed it was only fair that she lose some degree of familiarity with her female friend in exchange for lying to said friend about her gender. She certainly made up for it with the familiarity she now had with her male roommates. Thankfully Draco wasn't the type of kid to lounge about with no shirt on, but Theo had no such qualms. Rigel was thoroughly disenchanted with the male form at this point, or at least the eleven-year-old version.

Rigel took a seat on a couch by one of the fires to wait, and soon enough Pansy came striding out of her dorm with fresh robes and a determined look on her recently washed face.

"What is it, Rigel?" Pansy asked briskly as she sat next to her, "You haven't had time to catch up for months, so if you're taking time to talk to me now, there must be something going on."

Rigel winced, and opened her mouth to apologize, but Pansy cut her off firmly.

"I don't blame you, Rigel. I know that whatever you are doing is important, or you wouldn't spend so much time and energy doing it. Draco and I simply worry about you, that's all," Pansy smiled in a way that was all too knowing, "You have a tendency to keep things all to yourself for one reason or another, and while as a Slytherin I respect you for that, as a friend it's hard to help you when you do that."

"You don't have to help me with anything," Rigel said automatically.

"It's not a matter of 'have to' or 'need to', Rigel," Pansy said, "But what did you need to talk to me about?"

Rigel swallowed, remembering her original purpose in seeking Pansy out with a clenching feeling in her gut. "Pan, it's Draco," she said, but her throat stuck on the next words and she shook her head mutely while Pansy closed her eyes with an expression that looked trapped.

"The sickness," Pansy said softly, resolutely, "We knew it was coming, though I admit I had thought it would get me first."

"Pan?" Rigel looked questioningly into her eyes as if she could see whether the sickness was lurking like a shadow behind them, but all she saw was the same determination that Pansy had already shown that morning.

"Rigel, you and Blaise and I are the only first years unaffected in the whole school," Pansy said gently, as if she were the one who had come to break the bad news, "That Gryffindor first-year Weasley was taken to Quarantine yesterday, and he was the last of the first years from other Houses. They cancelled first year classes days ago because there was just no one left to take them really, but I guess you haven't been to class in a while anyway…"

She trailed off and Rigel felt like a complete prat for missing so much of what was happening to her own year-mates. Next year would be different, she promised herself. She would pay more attention to her friends, and she would be there for them instead of the other way around, but Merlin please let her just get through this year with all of her friends in one piece.

"Draco fell ill late last night," Rigel said finally, thinking she owed Pansy at least that much of an explanation, "It was in our dorm room, and Flint helped get him to the Hospital Wing. He seemed fine before he…"

"They all do," Pansy said, patting Rigel's arm with no small amount of pity. Somehow this conversation had not gone as Rigel had expected it to, but she couldn't help but be grateful. She really really hadn't wanted to see Pansy upset. Perhaps that's why pureblooded women are so calm and collected all the time, Rigel mused thoughtfully, because they know that the rest of us couldn't handle their tears.

Rigel clasped Pansy's hand in a way that was more awkward than it was comforting, and Pansy smiled a bit ruefully at the gesture, but squeezed back nonetheless.

"Thanks, Rigel," she said seriously, "I would not have wanted to find this out over breakfast, no matter how prepared I believed myself to be."

"Of course," Rigel said, "I wish I could do more. I'm so sorry I haven't been there for you and Draco lately, Pan. I promise what I'm doing is important."

"You're brewing for Professor Snape, now that he's gone," she said knowingly, "Aren't you?"

Rigel fidgeted a bit, "I'm really not supposed to say, Pan."

"I understand," Pansy said gently, "Just like I understand that in your own way you're doing all you can for Draco, and for all those other kids too. When I get sick, I want you to promise me—"

"Pan, don't say—"

"Promise me," Pansy stressed resolutely, "That you won't stop what you're doing. Don't pause to worry about me and don't let it distract you from helping Professor Snape all you can."

"…I promise," Rigel said, meeting Pansy's resolute eyes with determination of her own, "But Pan, I might get sick before you do."

Pansy smiled in a way that seemed much too wise for her age, "Something tells me you won't, Rigel, though I don't know what. I guess I just can't imagine you sick."

"I couldn't imagine Draco sick yesterday," Rigel said, a bit morosely.

"Draco?" Pansy smiled, though it was somewhat strained, "You mean you can't see him laid up in a bed of silk, a damp Egyptian cotton towel across his aristocratic brow, dozens of servants attending to his every muffled moue of discontent? I certainly could."

Rigel felt a smile tug at her lips and nodded with slow agreement. She could sort of see Draco draped dramatically in a languid posture, like a desert queen wilting gently under the rays of the sun. Then she remembered the way he'd collapsed like a stringless puppet the night before and she stopped smiling. There was nothing delicate or romantic about the way Draco had fallen sick. It had been purely terrifying.

"Come on, Rigel," Pansy said, standing and tugging Rigel's arm up with her, "Let's get to breakfast. Everything seems better after a good pot of tea."

Rigel rose and moved her arm so that she was escorting Pansy more than she was being dragged along by her, and they headed up to breakfast alone.

When they got to the Slytherin table, they sat as close as they could to what was left of the second year students, so that the loss of their own year-mates was not felt quite so obviously. Halfway through Pansy's second cup of tea, the post arrived, and Pansy put down her teacup with a sigh upon receiving hers.

"Oh, she didn't," Pansy muttered darkly, and Rigel looked up from the letter Sirius had sent her to see what had her friend agitated, "That Skeeter woman doesn't know when to leave well enough alone." Pansy was staring at a copy of the Daily Prophet with an icy scowl, and Rigel slid closer to get a look at the headline.

MYSTERIOUS MAGICAL MALADY STRIKES HOGWARTS

Rigel felt like cursing, but settled for a deep frown instead. So the news was out. She supposed Dumbledore couldn't have kept it quiet forever, but Rigel dreaded the repercussions that would come with such publicity. If the Cow Party wanted bad press for Dumbledore's faction, they couldn't do better than Skeeter. Resigned, Rigel began reading over Pansy's right shoulder, which was stiff with distaste.

Rita Skeeter, special correspondent for the Daily Prophet, writes to inform the public of the dangerous secret currently being kept from concerned parents around the country. Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry has been recently struck with an unknown and highly contagious magical disease, which has infiltrated the population and already infected upwards of 50 school children with its strange and baffling symptoms.

This disease, a here-to-fore unknown in the magical medical community, exhibits itself through the onset of a sudden and as far as this reporter has discovered irreversible magical coma. Despite the Quarantine that was reportedly enacted immediately following the outbreak of this epidemic, the disease continues to spread unchecked through the school, particularly affecting the youngest of Hogwarts' illustrious student body. The disease does not discriminate for House or family affiliation; scions of the light and dark both have been struck down by this vicious illness.

Just last night, Mr. Draco Malfoy fell to the sickness, an event that both shocked and disturbed the young scion's well-known parents, Mr. Lucius Malfoy and Mrs. Narcissa Malfoy-nee-Black. This reporter was graciously allowed a few moments of Mr. Malfoy's time, which she employed industriously on behalf of the deserving public, that her readers may know what exactly is going on at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.

When asked whether or not Mr. Malfoy, as both a parent and a member of the Board of Governors, was aware of this illness prior to his Heir's contracting of it, Mr. Malfoy replied, "I regret to say that Headmaster Dumbledore saw no need to apprise either the parents or the members of the Board of Trustees of the situation at Hogwarts. To find out that not only has my son taken ill to a potentially lethal disease, but that he was not the first, the second, but the fiftieth student to succumb to the illness, was of course a cause of deep concern for my wife and I. I sincerely hope that Dumbledore knows just what it is he is doing, as it does not seem to involve adhering to basic protocol for dealing with epidemics of this proportion."

This reporter certainly agrees with Mr. Malfoy's keen insight into the situation. What exactly is going on at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry? How is it possible that not until roughly 1/7 of the population lay in magical comas did the general public learn of such a risk to their children and Heirs? According to what this reporter has gleaned, Hogwarts has not even called for additional medical staff, though the Hospital Wing must have reached capacity some months ago. Is this truly the best environment to be entrusting the future of the magical world?

Well, it is too late to make that call, thanks to Headmaster Dumbledore. St. Mungo's has officially declared Hogwarts a general Quarantine Zone in an effort to prevent the disease from spreading to the rest of our world. What this means, dear readers, is that at this stage in the development of the epidemic, parents cannot pull their children out of school even if they want to.

"I know it seems harsh," one anonymous Healer at St. Mungo's said, "But since the Quarantine within the school doesn't seem to be making a difference, the only option is to keep everyone who's in the school, well, in the school. Honestly, it's quite a surprise that it hasn't spread to the general population yet, and until we know how to cure the disease, we'd like to keep it that way."

This reporter asked the Healer if the reason there had been no progress made on curing the disease was due to the elaborate cover up at Hogwarts, which prevented Healers from knowing and therefore studying the disease for several months.

"Well, not really," the Healer answered. "True we just learned of the illness a few hours ago, but Madam Pomfrey is truly a credit to her profession. We've got all her notes, and the illness seems extremely straightforward, while at the same time giving no clues as to how to cure it. Days or months won't make much difference with a disease like this. You either know how to cure it or you don't, and studying it won't help. It's not like a puzzle, you know, with a right answer if you just think about it hard enough."

This reporter was not convinced, so she asked the Healer what was being done to prevent the disease from picking off helpless students one by one. The Healer shrugged, and said, "Until the disease gives us another clue, there isn't much we can do. Now don't look at me like that. It's not as though these children are in any real danger at the moment. Magical sleeps can be kept up pretty much indefinitely with the right potions, you know. All we can do at the moment is wait, and hope a solution presents itself soon."

While the parents and friends of all those bright young pureblooded children 'wait' for a solution, there are many who do not pass the time idly. Instead, they question: why is this sickness only coming to light now, months after the initial outbreak of the illness? What does this epidemic mean for the students at Hogwarts and their families? Will there be any lasting effects? Could The Hogwarts Malady have been prevented in some way or perhaps cured faster if there had been information available from the start? Where is Dumbledore leading the future of the Wizarding World, which has until now been left so trustingly in the bastion of the Light's wizened hands?

For more on the standard protocol for magical epidemics, see page 3

For more on the precedents for magical comas, including the famous cases of Snow White and Aurora aka Sleeping Beauty, see page 4

For information on where to send a letter of complaint concerning Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, see page 5

Rigel sighed as she moved away from the paper in favour of concentrating on her breakfast once more. She felt a bit sick to her stomach after reading Skeeter's article, but knew that her body needed food in order to fuel her magical core with enough energy to get through another day of brewing.

Pansy huffed indignantly as she shoved the paper away from her plate, "I can't believe she'd just splatter the news of Draco's illness all over the front page like that. As if the Malfoys really want people knowing their son and Heir is sick. Just think of the repercussions for the families of the students at Hogwarts now. They'll seem weak, unable to protect their Heirs, and the Malfoys especially will lose a lot of political clout for this; the Malfoy motto is 'blood before honour' for Merlin's sake. How will it look if people think they can't take care of their own?"

Pansy continued to mutter along in this vein for some time, and Rigel quietly let her rant. In truth, the Malfoys probably would lose a bit of political power until it became clear that Draco would be fine, but after that Rigel thought they would return to their usual state of unofficial royalty in the wizarding world. Rigel also thought Mr. Malfoy's interview with Skeeter was rather obvious in the way it sought to undermine the Headmaster, but she supposed she shouldn't be too surprised. After all, Mr. Malfoy was high in the Cow Party, so if they were indeed responsible for the illness then it stood to reason that Mr. Malfoy was in on the plan, and had been ready to slip the information to Skeeter as soon as he got the chance—which meant he knew that his son would likely catch the illness and was therefore fairly confident in the essentially harmless nature of the sickness.

If anything, Rigel actually felt better after thinking about that. If Malfoy was confident enough to allow his son to be used in the political gambit, then surely the illness was not actually harming any of the students after it locked away their minds. Though the true Malfoy motto was something like 'purity always conquers' Pansy had been right to say that the motto everyone remembered the Malfoys by was 'blood before honour' which basically amounted to blood before anything, as Malfoys took honour very seriously. So if Mr. Malfoy let his own blood, his Heir, contract this sickness, then Rigel didn't need to worry about her friends too much in the long run. As long as she kept making Potions, nothing truly terrible would befall them.

Her heart more at ease than it had been in a long while, Rigel excused herself from the breakfast table and went to take the latest batch of Potions to the Hospital Wing.

The Hospital Wing was shielded from casual approach by a line in the shape of a semi-circle gouged deep into the stone corridor in front of the big double door entrance to the Wing. It was much like an age line or any other kind of semi-permanent ward, but instead of keeping out people of a certain age, it kept out anyone not escorted in by a witch or wizard with a Healer's Badge. When Rigel approached the line, it flared blue in warning and she tapped her toe against the edge of the line, which hardened like a wall as she came into contact with it, and sent a faint bell-like tone reverberating down the corridor.

A few moments later, Pomfrey rushed out, looking harried, and said, "Mr. Black, good, good, just pass those through to me, won't you?" She held out her hand from her side of the Quarantine line, which allowed solid objects through if said objects were handed to a Badge-wearing medi-staff, but Rigel hesitated.

"I was actually hoping I could come in today, Madam Pomfrey," she said carefully.

The Healer sighed in a put upon way, "You can't, Mr. Black, no one can. You know that. Now give me the Potions, I've had a busy morning what with every Healer in the country trying to floo in and find out what's going on thanks to that Skeeter woman's article."

"Please, Madam Pomfrey," Rigel tried again, turning on the kicked puppy look for extra swaying power, "Draco's one of my best friends, so surely if the disease passes mind to mind I've already caught it and just haven't shown the symptoms yet. Our mental paths are too familiar for me to not have been infected by now. I just want to see him for a few minutes. I won't be in the way."

The nurse pursed her lips, saying, "Regardless of the likelihood that you are already at risk, I really don't think it's a good idea to let what is at present our only Potions maker into the Quarantine area, especially as your age puts you most at risk."

"I understand that, Madam Pomfrey," Rigel said earnestly, "But Professor Snape will be back soon to take over the Potion making, and we've already enough to last us more than two whole weeks even at the rate the sickness is spreading now, so it won't really cause too much trouble if I fall sick, especially since I'm bound to succumb soon anyway with my friends all sick."

Rigel chose not to mention that she really hadn't been spending enough time with her friends lately to be sure she'd been exposed to the illness. She knew it was selfish to put herself at risk to see Draco, but she had been working hard enough that if she fell sick before Snape returned the Hospital Wing would still be well-stocked.

"Still," Pomfrey said, frowning, "I'm not sure Professor Snape would agree…"

"It's just so difficult making all these potions without really seeing what they're for, ma'am," Rigel said, sighing slightly for effect, "I think if I could see my friends I would understand better, and it would seem more real to me, so that I know what I'm doing is important and I can continue with renewed determination in my heart."

Rigel knew she'd laid it on too thick when Pomfrey rolled her eyes toward the ceiling and sighed, "It's like Sirius Black all over again." Rigel opened her mouth to try another tack, but Madam Pomfrey held up a hand, "Fine, fine, I know how you Marauder boys can be, and if I don't let you in you'll likely find some extremely dangerous and irresponsible way to sneak your way in. Don't disturb any of the patients, and for Merlin's sake don't tell Severus about this." She reached through the Quarantine and pulled Rigel through by her shoulder, steering her through the big doors and into the Hospital Wing proper, which looked like it had been expanded five times over. The inside was a positively cavernous expanse of pristine white, with rows of beds filling up the elongated space industriously. There must have been about eighty beds lined up at least, though only a bit over half of them were occupied.

The eerie part was that the entire place was completely silent save for Madam Pomfrey's heels clicking against the white tiles and the potions in Rigel's arms clinking together gently as she carried the crates along after the Nurse. Though there were fifty children lying prone on beds throughout the room, none of them stirred as they passed. None of them even snored, though Rigel knew from listening to Zabini complain about it that either Crabbe or Goyle must have snored when sleeping naturally. Pomfrey stopped in front of a half-filled row of beds and took the potion crates from Rigel's arms.

"Mr. Malfoy is in the second to last occupied bed in this row," the nurse said briskly, "You have ten minutes, and then you should leave to reduce the risk of the sickness spreading to you."

"Thank you, Madam Pomfrey," Rigel said before moving quickly down the row of sleeping students. She recognized both Neville and Ron as she passed them, but she didn't pause until she reached the second to last student's bed. Rigel was somewhat ashamed to see that the last kid in the row was Blaise Zabini, who she had noticed vaguely was absent from breakfast, but whom she had not spared much thought on apart from that. She turned her eyes back to Draco, however, whose pale complexion looked washed out and sickly underneath the harsh infirmary light, and moved closer so that she could put her fingers to Draco's neck carefully.

The steady pulse beneath the pads of her fingers relaxed a knot of tension in her gut she hadn't realized was there until it was gone. Draco was fine, and he would remain so, she told herself, so the sourceless dark feeling she had obviously didn't mean anything. The proof was right beneath her fingers. She moved her hand up to brush back a bit of white-blond hair from her friend's face, wondering morosely how long it would be before she was looking at Pansy in the same way. For whatever Rigel had told her other friend, she knew Pansy was probably right. Rigel was better protected thanks to her rudimentary Occlumency than Pansy was, and Pansy had spent more time with Draco, Blaise, Millicent, and Theo, all of whom had already fallen ill, than Rigel had in the past months.

"It's going to be okay," Rigel told Draco quietly, "Professor Snape and I won't let anything happen to you, and when you wake up I'll tease you something terrible for fainting on me. And you'll say 'Malfoys don't faint' and Pansy will get that look on her face when she wants to roll her eyes but is too sophisticated to do so, and everything will be normal again. I promise."

At a stern look from Madam Pomfrey from across the room, Rigel patted Draco's head one last time and left the Hospital Wing to continue brewing.

Sometime in the afternoon, hours after Rigel had finished the lunch Binny brought her, one of the blank walls in Lab One shimmered for a distracting moment and then abruptly shifted until it held a modest fireplace. As Rigel asked her magic to put a Stasis Charm on her two cauldrons, green flames sprang up in the fireplace and a chiming noise began echoing around the room. Rigel frowned for a moment, unsure how one went about answering a floo call in Snape's labs. At Godric's Hollow, one just had to approach the fireplace, so Rigel stepped forward until she was bathed in the green light coming off the flames and sure enough the chiming stopped and a familiar head appeared in the fireplace.

"Hello, sir," Rigel said, crouching down so that she could meet his sharp gaze levelly.

"Mr. Black," Professor Snape said in his clipped voice, appearing to be just as larger than life as a floating head as he was in person, "Good. I don't have much time before I have to meet with the next potential merchant. Progress report?"

"Potions wise, the Hospital Wing is currently stocked three weeks in advance," Rigel said, "The Acai substitution is working well."

"Are you overtaxing yourself?" Snape asked, eyeing Rigel knowingly.

"No, sir," Rigel said, "The Acai requires a bit more magic be imbued than the Ginseng does, but it's nothing I can't handle. I saw Madam Pomfrey just this morning, and she had no complaints regarding my health."

"Very well," Snape said, "I have asked my London supplier to send more Acai to you, so expect the shipment tomorrow morning."

Rigel frowned. More Acai meant there was no Ginseng on the way. "No luck with foreign suppliers, Professor?" she asked.

"None," Snape said curtly, and Rigel could see the lines of frustration and a hint of some darker emotion playing about his face, "Apparently the European suppliers have all experienced an unexpected demand of Ginseng in the past month. They are to a one drained dry of the ingredient."

Rigel's eyes widened, "The sickness has spread to Europe? Why haven't we heard?"

"It hasn't," Snape said darkly, "None of the European suppliers know why their Ginseng was bought up or even who did the purchasing."

"Someone is cornering the market?" Rigel said incredulously. What were the odds that the very ingredient they needed in both of the potions vital to the continued health of the students was inexplicably removed from public trade at that exact moment?

"So it would appear," Snape said, scowling, "Since no one seems able to contact this mysterious buyer, I must look elsewhere. I am going East to continue searching, and will likely be out of touch for the next week. The wizards in those parts use other means of travel, so the floo system is spotty at best. If an emergency arises, send me an owl, but don't expect a reply for a couple of days. If there is nothing else?"

He waited expectantly and Rigel hesitated. Draco was Snape's godson, so the Professor would likely want to know that he'd fallen ill, but on the other hand, did Rigel really want to distract the Professor with news he could do nothing about while Snape was already doing something so important?

"Nothing that will not keep," Rigel said, deciding it best to tell Snape about Draco when he returned.

"In that case I will see you when I return. Rest, eat, and for Merlin's sake try not to fall ill," Snape said.

Rigel barely had time to say, "Good luck, sir," before Snape's head had disappeared and the green flames had extinguished themselves.

When Rigel returned to the Hospital Wing with another couple of crates that evening, it was to the sound of tense voices emanating though the Hospital Wing doors, which had not been closed all the way after whoever had last gone through them. Tapping her foot at the Quarantine ward, Rigel was surprised to see that her foot went through it instead of hitting against it. She tentatively stepped over the Quarantine line, realizing that it must still recognize her as someone admitted by a Healer and therefore allowed to be there. She made a mental note to look up how such a ward would work later, and used her shoulder to push the half-open door back enough to let her through.

None of the three people conversing on the other side of the Hospital Wing noticed her as she came in with her potion crates. Rigel, used to adults ignoring her by now and never one to pass up an opportunity for eavesdropping, carried the crates over to the staging tables in the middle of the infirmary and began unloading them quietly, Snowhit on one table and Aurora's Breath on the other. The voices carried over to her as she worked, and she realized after a moment that she recognized all three.

"…severe reaction to both of the necessary potions. I didn't administer them until just a few hours ago, as it takes about half a day for the unconscious processes to stop working on their own after the sickness takes hold in a child, but only ten minutes later his body rejected both potions completely. As of yet, I have not determined what is causing this reaction, as there is nothing in his file that would indicate an allergy to one of the ingredients, let alone an ingredient in each of the potions." That one was Madam Pomfrey, and she sounded both defensive and very concerned.

The next voice took her a moment to place, only because she was not expecting to hear it there. "Of course there is nothing in his file, as my son is not allergic to anything in either of those potions. Clearly this reaction is a result of something else." It was Lucius Malfoy. Rigel turned her head to stare in alarm at the three adults, peering against the bright, almost blindingly white light in the Wing. Madam Pomfrey was speaking to Lucius and Narcissa Malfoy, who were standing with stiff shoulders and even stiffer expressions in similarly undecorated dark grey robes. Rigel could hear her breathing grow louder in her ears as she realized that if Mr. and Mrs. Malfoy were there it meant that the boy they were talking about was Draco.

"What's wrong with Draco?" Rigel blurted, causing the three older witches and wizard to turn and stare at her with surprised affront at the unexpected interruption.

"Mr. Black," Lucius Malfoy spoke in a clipped tone that did nothing to hide his obvious ire. Rigel took in the hard lines around the elder Malfoy's mouth and thought he looked nothing like he'd come across in Skeeter's article that morning. This was not the face of a man who knew his son to be free from immediate danger. Malfoy looked like a father barely restraining his worry and anger, and Rigel found that she did not like the look on him at all, especially if it meant there really was something wrong with Draco.

"What brings you here, Mr. Black?" Narcissa asked with an expression that seemed cold and blank until Rigel caught the hint of fear that laced her eyes in their too-wide irises and erratically fluttering lashes.

"Just dropping off the latest batch of potions, Mrs. Malfoy," Rigel said, "Is Draco okay?"

"He reacted badly to both Snowhit and Aurora's Breath, the two potions necessary to sustain the coma harmlessly," Narcissa told her, as if she was repeating something she'd read in a textbook, "It has not yet been determined why."

"But Draco needs those potions," Rigel said blankly, unable to fully process what she was hearing, "They're all that keeps his body running healthily while his mind is locked away."

"We are aware of that, Mr. Black," Malfoy Sr. bit out through gritted teeth. Rigel winced. Of course they were aware of it. But this was bad. If Draco didn't get those potions he wouldn't last a week in the magical coma.

"Yes, sir," Rigel said, trying to be respectful of their obvious worry for their son but at the same time too worried herself for her friend not to keep talking, "Can you give me a list of his allergies? I made the potions, so I know exactly what ingredients are in each. I could tell you what he might be allergic to in each one."

The Malfoys looked at Rigel with something that might have been incredulity.

"You are the one brewing the potions for these students?" Mr. Malfoy asked, the tone of his voice suggesting without saying that perhaps her presence explained some things.

Insulted that Malfoy thought she had made a mistake with the potions and thereby caused Draco's bad reaction, Rigel bit back a hot retort. She took a breath, telling herself that Malfoy knew little to nothing of her potions skills and that he was just a man worried about his son, as anyone in his position would be.

"I am," Rigel said when her voice was even enough, "Professor Snape is currently out of the country, so I assumed responsibility for brewing Snowhit Draught and Aurora's Breath while the Professor is away."

Narcissa put a hand gently on her husband's arm and spoke before he could, "No one else has had such a reaction to the potions?" At Madam Pomfrey's nod of confirmation, Narcissa went on, "Then the problem is still in Draco's reaction to the potions specifically. If Mr. Black knows how the potions were made, then perhaps he can enlighten us as to the problem."

Madam Pomfrey thrust a piece of paper she'd pulled from a manila folder at Rigel, saying, "This is Draco Malfoy's allergy listing."

Rigel reached to take it, but Mr. Malfoy cut in. "Don't bother," he said, pulling out a different sheet of paper from inside his robes and handing that instead to Rigel, "That list is incomplete. Take this."

Madam Pomfrey looked ready to launch into a tirade about irresponsible parents who didn't list their children's allergies completely for the school's files, but Narcissa interjected gently, "Draco has a delicate constitution. He gets that from me," and here she looked so guilty and regretful that even Madam Pomfrey softened a bit, "We aren't sure ourselves what all he is allergic to, and we thought a complete list would be too much hassle for a school record."

Translation: we didn't want to so openly state all of our Heir's weaknesses in case anyone wanted to use that information to harm him, Rigel thought cynically. She could understand where they were coming from; the Malfoys had a lot of enemies. Madam Pomfrey had a point too, however. It was hard to expect the Healers to anticipate your child's allergies if you hadn't informed the Healers of them.

"In any case," Malfoy Sr. said sternly, "All of Draco's allergies to ingredients or substances used in life-saving potions were included. Severus himself went over the list, and Draco is not allergic to anything in Snowhit or Aurora's Breath."

"Clearly he is allergic to something," Madam Pomfrey said waspishly, apparently at the end of her patience, "And until we figure out what it is, I can't administer those potions in good faith."

"Can't you just keep him under the charms?" Narcissa asked anxiously.

"Assisted living spells can only work for so long before the body needs to do the work itself," Pomfrey said tiredly, "I can keep Draco's lungs breathing and his heart pumping for three days at the most on those spells. After that, a wizard's magical core begins to reject the spells, sensing that the body itself is no longer active, and automatically detaching itself from the wizard's body to rejoin the wild magic of the earth. The potions are the only long-term solution we have at present, as they mimic the signals the brain would usually send to the body to continue performing natural processes. Even though we could keep him technically nourished intravenously, Draco's magic wouldn't recognize him as alive with the Charms doing the breathing and blood-pumping for him."

Three days. Rigel shook her head to clear out the fog that was rising up behind her eyes at that thought. No, she had to concentrate. All was not lost.

"We don't need three days," Rigel said firmly, breaking through the ominous atmosphere left in the wake of Pomfrey's words. "As soon as we know what Draco's reacting to, we can work around the ingredients." Rigel looked down at the sheet of paper in her hand. The list of allergies was extensive; Draco really did have a rather temperamental immune system. As she scanned the list, rejecting each allergy as she came to it as either not related to Snowhit or Aurora's Breath or else not existent in the final product in a large enough quantity to manifest a reaction, her eyes caught on one substance and she paled with dread.

Acai.

"Draco is allergic to Acai?" Rigel whispered hoarsely, her mouth suddenly dry as parchment.

"Yes," Narcissa frowned gently, "Forgive me, but I do not believe that is an ingredient in either—"

"Substituted," Rigel murmured, still staring at the four neatly scrawled letters with something very much like horror uncurling inside of her. When she remembered herself, she tore her gaze from the page to look up at the Malfoys miserably, "We ran out of Ginseng, which is in both potions, so we had to substitute Acai."

Malfoy looked exasperated, "Then order more Ginseng and get my son his potions."

But Rigel was shaking her head back and forth even as he spoke, "We can't, there isn't any Ginseng anywhere. That's why Professor Snape isn't here; he went to look for Ginseng, but he hasn't found any yet."

"How can he have 'not found any'?" Malfoy snapped, "Severus knows suppliers all over the country. Surely someone can procure some for us. We don't need much, just enough for Draco to last the duration of this sickness." Rigel opened her mouth to explain, but he cut across her, speaking more quickly as he became more and more agitated, "Tell Severus to spare no expense. We will pay anything, just get the Ginseng to Hogwarts today."

"I can't," Rigel said, pleading with her eyes for them to understand, "There's no Ginseng anywhere in England or Europe. Snape's looked everywhere, but the market's been cornered in the last month or so, and whoever bought it all up isn't selling. The Professor went East to look for more, but he said he'd be gone another week, and he's off the floo grid. An owl will take days to reach him, and even if he gets it we'd have to hope he'd actually found Ginseng."

Rigel gripped at her hair in panicked frustration and tried in vain to calm herself down.

Meanwhile the Malfoys were both as cold as ice, clamping down on their emotions so tightly that Rigel couldn't even guess at what they might be feeling anymore.

"Well," Madam Pomfrey said shakily, "Well, we have three days to come up with a solution."

Rigel nodded, turning her mind toward a specific course of action, "Madam Pomfrey, you're stocked up with both potions for at least another three weeks, so I'm going to focus all my attention on figuring out a way to make the potions without Acai, okay?" The nurse looked rather pityingly at Rigel, but Rigel just pressed, "Okay?"

"Alright, Mr. Black," the older woman said tiredly, "You may be excused for the next three days of brewing. I w—" Whatever she was going to say was cut off by a distracting beeping noise going off in all of their ears. "Oh, that's the Snowhit alarm. Excuse me, I need to administer the next dose to these children." The nurse bustled off to take care of her duties and Rigel and the Malfoys stared at one another for a long moment.

"Until we can get a letter to Severus, it seems that our son is in your hands, Mr. Black," Narcissa said softly, "Severus speaks highly of you. I sincerely hope he was not mistaken."

Rigel set her chin under the purebloods' assessing gaze, "I will do everything I can to help Draco." I promised him it would be okay, she added silently. "Excuse me as well, Mr. and Mrs. Malfoy. I need to get to work. Is it alright if I keep this?" she gestured to the allergy list in her hand and Mr. Malfoy nodded jerkily, his eyes not on her, but across the room where his son lay still and pale as ice.

Rigel couldn't look at Draco, couldn't bear to see him under the yellow glow of the life-sustaining spells, so she bowed her head deeply to her friend's parents and left the Hospital Wing at a near run. She had work to do.

By the next evening, Rigel was more tired than she'd ever been while brewing for Snape. She had pored over the notes Snape had given her on both potions, as well as consulted the large stack of potions journals Snape kept organized by date in one of the cupboards in Lab One, and she kept coming back to the same, horrible conclusion.

She couldn't substitute a substitution. Everything she read agreed that trying to substitute an ingredient for another ingredient that was already a substitution for the ideal ingredient caused the potion to become too unstable to enact the change it was designed for. At best the potion was useless, at worst highly poisonous. She couldn't use anything in place of the Acai in either potion unless it was the original Ginseng itself. In other words, she had wasted a day and ended where she'd started, with Draco no closer to help.

The worst part of the whole thing was that even if Rigel had miraculously found a perfect substitution for Acai and gotten Draco the potions he needed, Draco would still be sick! She was wracking her brains and running herself into the ground just to keep him in stasis, when what was really wrong with him was so far outside of her skill set that she couldn't even attempt to help him.

No, she corrected herself bitterly as she locked up the Lab and walked slowly to the Great Hall for dinner, The worst part is that it's all my fault.

Rigel was acutely aware of just how much the situation was her fault. Because Rigel was helping Snape brew, they'd brewed more potions faster and therefore run out of Ginseng faster than if Snape had been working alone. While that meant production would be less if she weren't helping, it also meant Snape wouldn't have had to leave Hogwarts for Ginseng for another few weeks, meaning he would have been at Hogwarts still when Draco fell ill. And if that weren't enough, it had been Rigel's decision not to tell Snape that his godson was ill. Only Snape, Madam Pomfrey and Rigel had known that Acai was substituted for Ginseng in the potions, and only Snape and the Malfoys had known that Draco was allergic to Acai, so if anyone could have done something about the allergy before Draco had a bad reaction to the potions it was Snape, who knew both about the allergy and the Acai substitution. And Rigel hadn't told him. Now Snape was out of reach and Draco had three days before his magical core realized his body was not actually responsive and detached itself from him, and Rigel was left with the overwhelming and undeniable truth that she was to blame.

Just when she thought her heart couldn't sink any lower, Rigel sat down at the Slytherin table and realized that she was alone in the unofficial first-year section of the benches. Completely alone. She fisted her hands under the table tightly, and turned her head to scan the rest of the table, looking for one particular shade of blonde hair to prove her dreadful suspicion wrong. The look on Rookwood's face as she caught his eye was all she needed to know. Feeling as though she was choking on her own heart, which had suddenly risen from the pit of her stomach to her throat, Rigel pushed away from the table roughly, ignoring Rosier as he made an aborted gesture to stand and follow her—aborted because Rookwood pressed a firm hand on the other Slytherin's arm and shook his head resolutely.

Rigel ran out of the Hall and didn't stop until she was outside of the Hospital Wing. She paused, hesitating for only a moment, not sure if she wanted to see Pansy laid up like a limp little doll in the too-bright hospital light, but a second later she passed unchallenged through the Quarantine wards and pushed open the doors to the Wing.

It was silent, more so than just the rows of eerily quiet sleeping children could account for, and after a quick glance Rigel realized Madam Pomfrey wasn't anywhere in the expanded room. The nurse must have been in her office, perhaps eating dinner. Rigel was grateful for the privacy as she crossed the ward to walk along the half-filled row that held the most recent patients. At the very end of the row lay Pansy, next to a Hufflepuff third year who must have fallen ill after Blaise.

Pansy looked like an angel, serene and innocent, with her halo of blonde hair spread out beneath her head, except that no angel should ever be so still. There were bare signs of life, a slow, almost inaudible breath here and the slight flush of fever there, but what struck Rigel most of all was how young Pansy looked in her enchanted sleep. She'd always seemed to Rigel like a mini grown-up, just a smaller version of Narcissa Black, but in sleep Pansy truly looked her eleven years, and Rigel was reminded how much bigger this sickness was than them, no matter how much it felt like she, Pansy, and Draco were in the centre of the maelstrom. This sickness wasn't about them, wasn't really about any of the children who had succumbed to it. They were just chips to be gambled in a political bluff by the S.O.W. Party (at least that's who Rigel thought must be behind the sickness). And yet, for all the first-years' insignificance to the big players in the game, it was they who would be most affected by this mess.

Draco had two days before the life-sustaining spells could no longer disguise his body's unresponsiveness, and if the worst were to happen…Pansy would take it hard, and Rigel had to admit that she would too. Not to mention Draco's parents and—Rigel's gut clenched—Snape, if Draco were to pass before his godfather returned and even discovered he was ill. Because Draco would die, if his magical core separated itself from his body. The shock to his major systems would surely kill someone so young, especially without his mind aware enough to override his body's reaction to the sudden loss of magic in his system.

Rigel left Pansy's bedside and went to stand by Draco's. Did he look a bit thinner already? No, of course not. Madam Pomfrey would keep him manually hydrated and nourished for as long as she could. He did look a bit feverish though. It was a strange sort of fever. Draco didn't toss and turn or mutter as patients normally did under the influence of a fever. It was purely a fever of the body, and the mind remained untouched. Or perhaps a better explanation was that whatever was happening in Draco's mind was causing the fever, but not caught in the fever itself. Either way, the result was that though Draco's temperature was continually trying to rise, and he had to be fed Sweat Inducers to cool his body down as much as possible, he remained perfectly still, seemingly unaffected by the discomfort the fever must have been causing his body.

Rigel gazed down at her friend and felt something that was probably a pale comparison to what Archie must have felt watching Aunt Diana slowly fade away before his eyes. She felt defeated by this sickness. So many promises were going to be left unfulfilled in its wake. She'd told Pansy she would keep helping Snape as much as she could, but here she stood, not helping anyone at all, drained and weary. Snape would be disappointed in her too, and probably angry when he realized she'd deliberately held back information from him, as if she were in a position to decide what her Professor could or could not handle being told. What a joke her best efforts were turning out to be. But letting down Pansy and Snape was nothing compared to letting down Draco. She had promised everything would be okay, that he would be okay, and she'd promised his parents to do everything she could to help their son.

But what can I do? Rigel gritted her teeth with frustration, I can't invent a new potion in three days, and I can't substitute a substitution, and even if I could Draco would still be sick.

It was a very rare moment in her life when Rigel didn't know what to do. Things that would be stone walls to other people—Hogwarts' pureblood-only policy, a broken wrist—were just obstacles to her, and every minute of her life was spent moving forward, always forward toward one goal or another. Here she was well and truly stonewalled. A sickness like this was not an enemy to be fought, a spell to be figured out, or an upperclassman to be bargained with. Rigel could understand completely Archie's desire to be a Healer if only it meant she would never feel so helpless against something again.

Rigel was about to go in search of a chair, so that she could sit by her friend's side a bit longer, when she felt it.

It was a tickling sensation that niggled her awareness, a creeping that she felt with one of her senses she didn't use in the physical world. Something was brushing against her mind. She fell into meditation mode automatically, turning her consciousness inward to view her mindscape. She was certain that's where the uncomfortably foreign feeling was coming from. If she hadn't been so familiar with her own mind after so many meditation sessions, she likely wouldn't have even noticed anything, let alone been able to do anything about it. As it was, she swept through the fog in her mind cautiously, searching through the gloom for the intruder she knew had to be there.

She reached the great white mountain without seeing anything unusual, but when she stopped there and turned her inner eye around, her physical body inhaled sharply with what she saw. The foggy mists around the periphery of one part of her mind, usually white or at most a light grey, were infected with black tendrils of…something that was steadily creeping through the air toward her mountain like a great insidious black weed. She shivered in a way that had nothing to do with the chilly mindscape and backed away toward the mountain, moving down its face and slowly heading for the illusion of an ice wall that protected the inner sanctum of her mind. She could not tell if the black stuff had any way of sensing its surroundings, or if it simply moved forward on magic-bred instinct, but she moved as stealthily as possible through the ice wall so that she wouldn't draw its attention just in case. She felt the warmth of the cavernous potions lab behind the ice illusion just as she saw the black tendrils reach the peak of her mountain fortress. Her physical body shivered as the black thing felt about the tip of the mountain, clinging to it and slowly spreading further down the face, but when she entered the underground cavern fully she could feel her physical body no more, and instead she had a second awareness of what was happening at every level of her mind, from the Foggy Mists to the Space Room.

Using this awareness, she kept track of the inky black substance that was slowly taking hold of more and more of her mountainside while her avatar that represented her consciousness moved through the decoy potions lab and to the trap door beneath the great rug that lay before the fireplace. She dropped down into the tunnels beneath the lab and mentally willed the trapdoor to close behind her and the rug to return to its place. By the light of the green crystals embedded in the walls, she moved confidently through the web of tunnels that branched from the third path from the right and a few minutes (in mental time) later arrived at the door that sealed off her Space Room. The door was a new addition, from her last meditation session. It had no discernable handle or latch and fit smoothly into the rough rock surrounding it. It only opened to a password, and that password relied on knowledge that only people she trusted would have. It was fitting, she thought, to guard her memories and secrets with a door that could only be opened if one already knew the most closely guarded of her secrets.

She cupped her hand around her mouth and whispered to the door, "My name is Harry Potter, and I am not a boy."

The door slid sideways into the carved stone wall, and Harry stepped through into the infinite impossibility that was her Space Room. The door closed behind her as she pushed herself off of the ground and floated lightly around various memories, which were all trapped and focused into little stars and planets. The memories didn't orbit the sun in the centre of the great space, and instead drifted freely in any direction they pleased. Harry did the same, floating aimlessly as she concentrated on her sense of the other portions of her mind to check on the black creeping invader.

It had settled like a cloak over most of her mountain, and Harry felt a bit ill as the sensation of tar-like sludge rolled over her mindscape. It would not be long before the black tendrils found their way past her ice wall illusion, for the thing seemed to be relying on touch more than sight, and the illusion wouldn't hold up against direct contact. When she had designed her mindscape, it was with the assumption that any intruders would be at least humanoid if not wizards themselves, and would be using eyes as their primary source of information about surroundings, and Harry was only now realizing how much of a liability that was.

She knew what the black thing was, or at least had a pretty good guess. It was the sickness, finally come for her. Just as Snape had postulated, it spread mind to mind, and Rigel suspected that the other kids affected by it hadn't had any mental awareness of it until it had completely taken over their mindscape and wrested control from them. Since she had experience with her mind through meditation and rudimentary Occlumency training, she had been alerted when the sickness first targeted her, though now that she was aware she wasn't sure what she could do about it. Harry would have to rely on the safeguards she had already put in place, having no idea how to fight a mental enemy head on yet. That, she assured herself, would be the next thing she studied when she got out of there.

If she got out of there. Harry was keenly aware that in retreating from the black sickness, she had well and truly trapped herself in her own mind. She had never built another exit from her mind, and wasn't sure it was even possible, especially now that so large a part of her mind was under the control of the creeping blackness. The only way she knew to get out of her mind was to go back out of the mountain and leave through the mists, and with the mountain and mists now swallowed by the sickness, that really wasn't about to happen. She didn't want to know what would result from her consciousness coming into contact with the black stuff.

She could feel the black stuff sliding through the illusion now and into the bright, cheery cavern that held her decoy sanctum. It didn't seem to be in a hurry, and it didn't seem to notice that the scrolls of potions recipes it was smothering with its black feelers weren't her real memories, but mere mental constructs. In fact, the sickness didn't appear to be terribly clever, and Harry wondered if that was because it wasn't a part of a being with a real consciousness or if it had simply engineered to be that way because it was meant to target children. After all, it wouldn't suit the S.O.W. Party's purposes if the sickness really did become an epidemic and infected adults as well as children. A wizarding world in chaos did no one any good. So it must be that the sickness was only supposed to be effective against children, who hadn't come into the full mental awareness that came with growing up and really learning and knowing themselves.

If that was the case, Harry thought hopefully, then the sickness wasn't invincible—it wasn't bred to be. She just had to figure out a way to beat it. Not in herself, no. Harry frowned determinedly; she had to find a way to beat the sickness in Draco. He was the one really in danger, because even if it meant her secret came out, Harry could be kept alive at least with Snowhit and Aurora's Breath until the sickness lifted. Draco would die if the sickness kept its chokehold on his mind for very much longer, and nothing, not even her deepest secrets, was worth a friend's life.

But how was she going to help Draco while she was trapped in her own mind? Should she fight off the sickness in her mind first, and then try to help Draco after that? No, her avatar shook her head, sending her long black hair floating weightlessly about her, she didn't know how much time was passing in the physical world. Her mental time could be moving faster or slower, and there was no way to get a good read on her physical body unless she was out in the first layer of her mind, on the mountainside. Here she was too deep in her mindscape, and didn't even know if she was still standing, frozen by Draco's bed or if she'd collapsed on the Hospital Wing floor.

So she somehow had to get to Draco, or more specifically to Draco's mind, from within her own mind. She didn't know Legilimency, and was pretty sure it wouldn't work if you were already in your own mind, and besides that Snape had said that the sickness made Legilimency on its victims impossible.

Harry drifted close to her sun and basked a little in the warmth it gave off. She really did like how her magic felt in her mind. It was fiery and strong, but reassuring in a dependable kind of a way. Like the sun. Here in her mind she felt connected to her magic in a way that she didn't while dealing directly with her magical core.

Wait. Harry stopped drifting and spun midair to stare thoughtfully into the sun at the centre of the Space Room. Connected. Connections. That's it!

Harry let a crazy smile bloom across her face as the plan came to her in a rush of insight. She didn't have to get to Draco's mind from the outside. She just had to forge a connection from the inside.

Pausing a moment to assess the situation in her own mind, Harry nodded in satisfaction. The sickness was still lumbering about in the main cavern, and even if it discovered the trapdoor and the caverns beneath it, she had fleshed out the tunnels in the last few meditation sessions. It would take a long time for it to fill up all of those tunnels, and it was unlikely that it would sense the Space Room by touch alone. Even if it did, there was no way an entity without a consciousness could get through the door that protected it. If nothing else, her memories and magic were safe.

Fueled by that assurance, Harry dove into the sun.

Connections, connections were the key. She couldn't believe she'd almost missed the most obvious one. Hadn't Snape told her when he'd explained about magical cores that usually a magical core was spherical? Each one was different, but the secondary level of the magical core, the true core, was what represented that person's magical power most appropriately for who they were. Her primary layer was coils, ropes and tendrils and twisting bits of magic all wrapped up around the centre, but she'd never looked close enough to discern what her true core was. Yet it was so obvious.

If magic made events in the mind real, then it stood to reason that what was true about magic in the mind had some connection with what was true of the same magic in the 'real' world. Hadn't she created the Space Room specifically because she'd found the sun already burning at the centre of her mindscape? If she didn't make her magic take the form of the sun, then it was a natural form for her magic to take, which meant that her true magical core must be something like a miniature sun. And that wasn't all. How did she use the energy of the sun to enact changes to her mental landscape if the sun in her mind wasn't somehow connected to the sun in her magical core? She couldn't. Every time she'd used magic before, the magic had traveled from her magical core to her hands to either the wand or the stirring rod she was using to conduct the magical energy. It didn't just manifest in the wand itself or in the air around her, though she supposed theoretically one could pull magic from the wild magic sources in the world like the ancient druids…she pulled herself back on track, feeling the warmth of her own personal sun singing along through her consciousness as she delved deeper and deeper into the ball of magical energy, following the heat and pushing through what felt like tangles of energy until—

Yes! She emerged, breathless (though of course as a product of her own consciousness she didn't strictly speaking need to breathe), on the other side and found herself staring at the outside of a very familiar coil-covered magical core. She'd been right. Magic couldn't be transmitted without a pathway, and if there was a magical core in one place and the exact same magical core in another 'place' then it only made sense if those two magical cores were in fact one, connected and simply manifesting in different ways and spaces, one physical and one mental. It made perfect sense…if she didn't think about it too hard.

Harry flexed her senses once more—magical, mental, and physical, as since she was no longer in the inner recesses of her mind she was peripherally aware of her physical body as well—and took stock of the situation. She was out of her mind, and that realization alone made her glow with success. She could still feel the blackness creeping about in her mind, but it was a distant sort of revulsion and her more immediate senses were concentrated on 'where' her consciousness was and what her physical body was doing. She was at the nexus of her magical core, like she'd been the day Snape had taught her how to perceive a magical core, and she could feel the warmth of the core on her consciousness the same way she could feel cool tile beneath her cheek with her physical senses. Turning her awareness outwards, she tried to perceive what was going on in the real world without breaking her own meditative trance. It was difficult. Using her five regular senses made her automatically tend towards operating on the conscious level, so she had to hold on to her mental and magical senses while at the same time focusing on her physical senses. The process was distracting, but what she heard when she concentrated on listening in the physical sense caught her immediate attention and made focusing much easier.

She was no longer alone in the Hospital Wing.

"Don't touch him," a voice said sharply. Harry recognized it as Madam Pomfrey, and wondered who she was talking about until she remembered that while she was completely herself in her conscious manifestation, in the real world most people thought her a boy named Rigel. She had separated the two parts of her life so completely that it was a bit jarring to witness from the outside while being aware of both parts. Like watching a movie.

"But surely he must be moved," that voice was Narcissa Malfoy, "The boy is obviously uncomfortable, particularly if he's been sitting there since dinner, and if he's succumbed to the sickness—"

"He hasn't," Pomfrey said briskly, her tone brooking no argument, "If he had, he would be in a magical sleep like the others, but he is not asleep. He is not even truly unconscious."

"Then what exactly is he doing on the floor?" Mr. Malfoy's drawl was too distinctive to mistake.

"He appears to be meditating," Pomfrey said, and Harry could almost see her lips pursing, though she couldn't open her eyes without snapping herself out of meditation completely.

"On the ground?" Narcissa asked dubiously.

"I doubt he was expecting it," the nurse said, "No doubt he was struck by the sickness rather suddenly."

"You just said he wasn't—"

"Oh, he hasn't succumbed," Pomfrey said, and Harry wondered if Malfoy's eyebrow twitched when he was interrupted like Draco's sometimes did, "I wondered why Mr. Black hadn't fallen ill before now, considering how many friends he has in other Houses, but I chalked it up to his having so little time to spend with his friends once he began brewing with Snape for the students falling ill. It appears he must have some rudimentary training in Occlumency."

"Occlumency?" Mr. Malfoy's voice sounded tight, and Harry silently grumbled at having one of her most carefully cultivated skills revealed so carelessly. She knew nurses were trouble for people with secrets.

"Hmm, yes," Pomfrey said, "The sickness is spread mind to mind, on the loose mental pathways that are constructed through close acquaintance, and to an experienced Occlumens the sickness would pose no threat, as it preys on unprotected minds, preferably the open minds of children. Since Mr. Black is neither an experienced Occlumens nor completely unprotected mentally speaking, he likely fell into meditation immediately upon detecting the threat the sickness represented in his mind."

"Will he be able to fight off the sickness?" Narcissa asked, "Now that he is aware of its presence, I mean."

"Impossible to tell," Madam Pomfrey said, in what was probably her lecturing voice, "From what we can tell, the sickness usually takes the mind unaware, clamping down once it has the mind under its own control and snapping up a barrier to prevent any communication into or out of the mind, so that the mind can't send signals to the body and can't be reached through the use of Legilimency. Once the child's consciousness is trapped within its mind by the sickness, the child might choose to fight back, which is what we believe causes the fever we see in some of the children. As to whether catching the sickness before it has complete control will give Mr. Black a fighting chance, well, it depends on how good his Occlumency is, frankly."

"Either way, he will be of no further help with Draco for the foreseeable future," Mr. Malfoy said coldly.

Narcissa spoke softly, but firmly, "Come now, Lucius. Neither of us really expected the child to be able to help. Letting him try and come up with a solution was more for his peace of mind than for ours. We must hope that Severus receives our message in time."

Harry curled her consciousness closer to her magical core, seeking reassurance from the warm sun rays coming off of it. Was she really so useless that her best didn't even merit the benefit of the doubt? She shook off that thought impatiently. She would help Draco. She promised she would, and she had a plan now. She just needed to know how much time she had.

As she turned her attention back to what was going on outside of her, she heard Narcissa say, "Can't we at least transfer Mr. Black to one of the beds? If he does wake from this fight on his own, he should not be rewarded with a stiff neck."

"We will have to move him very carefully," Pomfrey said, stressing her words to emphasize that she didn't think moving her the best course of action, "If he is distracted physically, it could upset the meditation."

Harry silently agreed; if she hadn't known it was coming, the sudden, though gentle, feeling of disorientation as her physical senses registered a change in surrounding that was not self-orchestrated would likely have pulled her consciousness back. As it was, she braced her consciousness by focusing hard on the mental and magical senses and ignoring the weird sensations coming from her physical senses as her body was picked up by unfamiliar hands and moved sideways toward the row of empty beds. Belatedly, she realized that being moved too far away from Draco would make the next part of her plan much harder, and she desperately clung to her non-physical senses even as she willed her vocal cords to vibrate and her mouth to say "Draco." It was difficult, and came out more like 'Drayo,' which she thought had something to do with a good portion of her mind being infiltrated by the black sickness, though she didn't know exactly which parts of her mind controlled her body. She hadn't designated a portion of her mind to her physical body, though now that she understood how connected the two were she would remedy that, so she guessed motor control and communication in general between her mind and body would be tied generally to her consciousness, but still affected by the sickness to some extent.

She felt her body stop moving in the real world, and split her concentration as much as she dared between getting the words she needed out and remaining within the meditative state that was keeping her consciousness out of the sickness' reach. She knew instinctively that if she let her mental avatar dissipate and came back to her body, the sickness would have full control over her mind and body, though it wouldn't get to her memories or magic, which were protected in the Space Room even without her there. She felt her lips form the words, though she didn't know how much was her actually getting her body to do what she wanted and how much was her magic helping to make her will manifest. Magic and willpower were funny things, and Harry didn't pretend to understand them very well.

"Stay. Drayo. Help. Drayo." There. That made sense. Or at least it was the best she could do, so hopefully they understood. She didn't have any more time to waste, as she still didn't know how much time had passed while she was meditating. She had been naïve to think one of them would conveniently mention the time of day, though she gathered it was still the same night. That meant she had less than two days to get into Draco's mind and help him get the sickness out of it. Harry vaguely felt her real-world body being moved closer to Draco's once more, and was grateful that they weren't making her task harder, but she didn't have energy left to waste on the real world at that point. Instead, she pushed her physical awareness back to the part of her consciousness that held her mental awareness and turned her attention to her magical senses. The next part of her plan was all theoretical, and she was relying a lot on sheer willpower to make it work, but it had to be done.

Harry asked her magical core for its cooperation in what she was about to do, and it thrummed happily, sending little pulses of warmth at her that she took for a wordless yes. Trying to remember how Snape had done it several weeks before, Harry coaxed one of the coils around her magical core into unwrapping itself while she extended her magical awareness in the same way she extended it when she needed to imbue a potion. Except she wasn't searching for the placid, passive receptor for magic that an unimbued potion was. She was looking for the active magical core belonging to Draco Malfoy.

There were four magical cores in close proximity to her, and other magical cores just a bit further away, but Harry zeroed in on the closest and smallest magical core, which had to be Draco's. She flung the coil of magic that had unwrapped from around her true core out toward the foreign magical core, willing it to forge a connection. She felt it latch on to the other magical core, like a jigsaw piece fitting into place or perhaps more appropriately like the sear of flame hitting dry ice, and she sent out a pulse of magic like Snape had taught her to feel out another's magical core, ignoring the guilty feeling that reminded her she was supposed to ask permission before establishing this kind of magical pathway. The magical echolocation pulse returned to her and she digested the information it had recovered for a moment. The core she'd forged a connection to was definitely Draco's. It felt like him, in a way that only made sense to her magical perception. Draco's core, however, was nothing like her core. Quite the contrary. Where her core was coils of magic around a brightly burning sun, Draco's core felt like a little ball of ice. Her magic stung a bit where it met his and it was constant work to keep the connection up.

Harry steeled herself once she was sure it was Draco's core she was connected to. Then, instead of sending another magical pulse down the connection, she sent herself down the magical pathway. There was no time for doubts as her consciousness sped along the current connecting her core to Draco's, but Harry was fairly confident this would work. After all, if she could project her consciousness inwardly to both her mindscape and her magical core, and travel between the two using innate magical pathways, and she could send magic outwards to create more magical pathways, there was no reason she couldn't project her consciousness along those magical pathways as well, as long as the pathways all stayed connected. And if that logic failed, then if she had learned nothing else her first year at Hogwarts, it was that magic was good at breaking rules.

She felt strange, the links to her own mental and physical senses stretched thin and largely indecipherable to her as she moved closer to Draco's magical core, and she hoped her mental defences would hold, as she imagined the only thing worse than being trapped in her mind by the sickness would be being trapped out of her own mind by it.

She could see Draco's core up ahead of her now, and she slowed until she was approaching it cautiously. It was one thing to poke at Snape's core while Snape was aware and in control of both his magic and the connection. It was another to blindly send her consciousness careening into another person's magical core while that person had no awareness of it. She didn't want to provoke an instinctive and likely defensive reaction from Draco's magic by appearing overly hostile.

His core looked like just how it had felt. It was a ball of blue ice, significantly smaller than Harry's was. Was this how big most first-years' magical cores were? Or was Draco's simply more condensed than hers was? She thought his core looked unnaturally still, but on the other hand she was used to thinking of magic as semi-independent moving energy, as her sun-core reflected. The more she thought about it, the more the ice core seemed to sort of suit Draco. His magic never did anything unexpected, after all. He used it for spells and the rest of the time it lay pretty dormant as far as Harry could tell. Perhaps his core reflected that. It certainly looked dormant.

The ice was unmoving, unyielding. She took a moment to consider it, seeing that she would have to modify her approach somewhat. Her theory was that if her mind was connected to her magical core naturally, then other people's cores must be connected to their minds in the same way. Even though Draco's mind was shut from the outside by the sickness' Occlumency-like barriers, his magical core was still connected to his mind from the inside. It had to be, because if that connection had been disrupted, his magical core would have immediately detached itself from Draco's body and dissipated. Since according to Pomfrey it would take his magical core three days to realize that Draco's body was only responding as living due to artificial magical influence, that realization was probably being delayed by the continued existence of the connection to Draco's mind. So her plan was to take the projection of her consciousness along magical pathways one step further, and send herself through Draco's magical core, and into his mind that way.

The idea was to do the same thing Legilimency did, which was to send one person's consciousness into another person's mindscape, except she would send her consciousness into Draco's mind by establishing and traveling along magical pathways instead of mental pathways. Several things could go wrong with this plan, and Harry was excruciatingly aware of all of them. She could be mistaken about how far one could extend their consciousness from their body before it snapped back. She could be wrong about the connection between the magical core and the manifestation of that core in Draco's mind being still connected. It could also turn out that while traveling through her own magical pathways was possible, traveling through someone else's would do something unspeakably horrible to her.

It didn't help that Draco's magical core was made of ice. Harry's magic didn't like it one bit. Still, needs must.

Before proceeding, Harry asked her magic to please make her avatar look more like Rigel did in the real world. She felt the magic tingle across her eyes and assumed it had turned them grey once more, but her hair remained stubbornly long. She shrugged, thinking that her consciousness was probably too deeply embedded for her to change her manifestation of herself very much, and figured that long hair wasn't too unusual for a boy. Archie Black used to have long hair anyway, anyone who knew him could support that.

Harry moved forward to lay a hand on the outside of Draco's magical core. The ice shivered a bit, but didn't budge. Sorry, Draco's core, but I'm afraid I'll have to insist. She pushed a bit more firmly, asking her magic to help her. The ice sizzled and melted around her hand and Rigel felt a strange rush of energy as she slowly melted a hole in the ice big enough for her to squeeze through. The ice was thick, and even when she'd gotten her whole body into the tunnel she was digging, she still couldn't see Draco's true core. She noticed the ice re-solidifying behind her and began to move faster, using both hands to push and mould the ice away from her. Strangely enough, she wasn't getting tired at all. If anything she felt more energized than she had before. All of a sudden, her hand burst through the ice and hit something on the other side that was definitely not air.

It was water. Harry took an automatic gulp of air before the tunnel flooded with water, and then she realized that she didn't need to breathe, and shook her head at her own foolishness. She swam the rest of the way out, looking back to see the water in the tunnel already turning to solid and smooth ice once more. She looked around curiously as she swam deeper into Draco's true core. It was like being in a swimming pool, in that there was no vegetation growing along the edges and no fish swimming around in the core, just pure, light blue water all around, trapped by a thick layer of ice.

At the centre of the true core there was a whirlpool. It spun too fast for Harry to see beyond it, but she could only assume that this was the wellspring of Draco's magic. Indeed, it seemed to be pushing water out of it instead of sucking water in, so she concluded that this was where Draco's body regenerated magic when it was used. It was also the connection between Draco's magic and his mind, if she was right. She began to swim toward it, but the current suddenly whipped up around her and pushed her back once more. She tried again, with no better results.

She growled with frustration. "Let me in!" Bubbles came out of her mouth and dispersed like a starburst in different directions, sticking to the underside of the ice layer and slowly absorbing into it. The whirlpool seemed to slow, or maybe it was just her imagination. "Please," she tried reasoning with it, "Draco needs help. I want to help him, but I need to get through here to do so." The whirlpool was definitely slowing down now. The lip of the swirling water seemed to tip toward her invitingly, and Harry gave it a dubious look, but shrugged, thinking, Here goes nothing.

She propelled herself into the whirlpool, and the world became a dizzying mess of rushing water before her vision went black.

Draco POV:

Draco was cold. Well, okay, not really, he admitted to himself as he idly tossed the ball of snow he'd been playing with for the last…how long had he been in here? Ah, well. The point is he should have been cold, considering his surroundings, but he really wasn't. He was sitting on a small iceberg, afloat in a little pond of ice-blue water. If this was real life, his legs would have been numb in the first few hours, but Draco didn't think he was in real life anymore. He didn't think he was dreaming, either. For one thing, he had never had such a boring dream before, even though it had been a little exciting at first, when the black octopus had chased him onto this iceberg. Or maybe it hadn't been chasing him. It hadn't seemed too concerned when Draco had escaped from it, swimming out into the pond, which seemed to be the only thing untouched by the black tar-monster. Lucky this iceberg was here, really. Or had it been?

Draco hadn't seen the iceberg when he started swimming. It was only after he'd gotten tired of treading water and looked for a place to rest that the iceberg had appeared. He thought maybe he'd made the ice appear, because he could sometimes make other things happen in this place if he tried hard enough. That's how he'd gotten his snowball to play with when the boredom had become too much. There were things he couldn't do, though, no matter how hard he tried. He couldn't wish the black stuff away.

Draco tossed the snowball once more and pretended it was a very fat and lazy Snitch. He had given up figuring out a way to leave, and he was having doubts as to where exactly he was, in any case. He remembered talking to Rigel, and being particularly fed up with the boy's workaholic tendencies. His friend was nearly as bad as his father when it came to work, and that was saying something. He remembered telling Rigel to take it easy, and then Rigel telling him he couldn't, and then…had Rigel cursed him? No, Draco didn't think so. Rigel never got mad at anyone, much less used magic on them. The boy actually seemed to avoid using magic whenever he could, though he'd stopped making strange things happen by accident, so maybe his magic was settling down after all. Rigel was probably just a late bloomer, with a little accidental magic left over from his childhood that was working itself out.

If Rigel didn't curse him, though, how did he end up here? His vision had gone black, and the vertigo he remembered made him think he'd fallen unconscious somehow. The most obvious answer that he really didn't want to think about but probably should was that the sickness had gotten him. Everyone at Hogwarts knew by now that the sickness had no symptoms until the kid collapsed, so if he had blacked out without warning it was probably because he was sick now, too. If that was the case, then maybe he was dreaming, since he'd heard rumours that the sickness made kids sleep for eternity.

He had a momentary flash of panic where he nearly missed catching his ball as it came back down. Would he be stuck in this place forever? He brushed that thought aside impatiently. No, of course not. Someone would get him out of here. If not him specifically, they would at least cure the sickness eventually and then he would get out of this boring dream by default. Not that he really thought it was a dream.

Draco sighed. He had a pretty good suspicion as to what was really happening to him, but he didn't like to acknowledge it. It was too horrible. His father had sent him a letter a few weeks ago that was very cryptic, even more so than usual. Draco could still remember the exact words his father had written at the bottom of the page.

Your mind is your greatest advantage. Keep your thoughts close, son, and your friends at a distance.

Draco scowled even now just thinking about them. At the time, the words had made no sense. As if thoughts could be anything but close. And Draco knew that although he wasn't an idiot like some of his less fortunate classmates, his mind wasn't his greatest asset. If anything, that would be his Malfoy good looks. He chuckled, and it echoed weirdly across the water. Seriously though, he was much better at doing magic than thinking about it. Pansy was better at theoretical problems. And distance himself from his friends? Draco had thought his father approved of Rigel, and he knew his father liked Pansy.

In retrospect, and in light of the sickness, it all made much better sense. He was to keep away from his friends because the sickness spread from friend to friend. That much was clear just by observing the pattern of the kids who fell ill. Draco hoped Pansy and Rigel hadn't fallen ill because of him. Keeping his thoughts close sort of made sense, if it meant keeping his mouth shut about the things he thought, but Draco had a feeling it meant more than that. It had to do with his mind being a great advantage—not asset, but advantage, his father had said. If he thought about the sickness in light of his father's warnings about his mind, things began falling into a discomforting picture.

The sickness made a kid's body go to sleep, but Draco didn't feel asleep, even though he knew he must have contracted the sickness. That meant that it looked to the outside that the kids were asleep, but on the inside they weren't. So his body was asleep, but his mind was not, and if he wasn't asleep, then he must be in the only part of him that wasn't asleep: his mind. From that conclusion, it was easy to guess that the sickness affected the mind, and that keeping his thoughts close was some sort of vague reference to protecting his mind, like Uncle Severus did. But how could a mind be an advantage when that was the vulnerable point the sickness attacked?

Maybe it's an advantage because it's my mind, Draco speculated, Like a home-pitch advantage. That suggested that he had some kind of advantage over the sickness within his own mind, which also supported the conclusion that Draco was, in fact, trapped in his own mind.

The downside to figuring all this out, Draco realized morosely, was that there was now no hiding from the fact that there was something slimy running around in his mind. Draco hadn't ever been told so exactly, but he was pretty sure Malfoys did not let boorish black octopi run amok in their mental landscape. It was entirely too uncouth. As soon as he got out of there he would demand that Uncle Severus teach him the mind arts during summer break. The black sickness-monster covered almost everything as far as he could see, and though he had never seen the inside of his mind before, he didn't have to be a Master at Occlumency to know instinctively that it wasn't supposed to be there.

At least the pond was safe. Draco relaxed against the iceberg he floated on and once again noted how strange it was to not feel cold, even though he was dressed in the summer clothes he wore to play Quidditch when he was home at the manor. And he was barefoot. Draco guiltily hoped his father would never find out about that, but he couldn't bring himself to wish for shoes. He loved going barefoot, even if Malfoys were not really supposed to.

He sat up and wriggled his toes off the edge of the iceberg, watching the ripples he made in the pond, and was surprised to see the water begin to tremble. A moment later, it was churning and roiling and Draco snatched his toes back from the liquid as a whirlpool began to form in the centre of the pond, just a few feet from where his iceberg rode out the waves calmly, much more stable than a normal iceberg should be.

The whirlpool began to swirl faster and faster, and Draco thought he saw a black hole forming in the middle, but the next moment something was projected out of the whirlpool's centre like a cannon ball and hurled, spluttering, straight onto Draco's iceberg. Draco backed up quickly until he was on the very edge of the iceberg and stared, disbelieving, at the soaking wet person who had just been spectacularly spat out of his pond. Whoever it was wore dark robes that looked like the ones Uncle Severus used when he brewed. The person had long hair like Severus did, too, but they were too, well, small to be Severus.

The new addition to Draco's island groaned and rolled over, muttering something about people with unnaturally wet magical cores. He thought he heard the name Malfoy somewhere in the litany of complaints, but before he could question the newcomer the person turned over, sat up, and caught sight of him.

"Draco!" the dark-haired person said happily, scrambling across the ice to fling themselves at Draco and squeeze the life out of him.

Draco just sat there, completely shocked by the fact that there was someone else in his mind with him. Someone hugging him, no less. Very few people hugged Draco Malfoy, and none of them had long, dark hair, excepting Uncle Severus, and he had already ruled him out.

"You're getting me wet," Draco said mildly, really not sure if this other person was a figment of his imagination or not. He didn't know why he would imagine someone glomping him, but he couldn't think of a different explanation for the presence of another in his mind. Though with the sick black thing roaming around…Draco supposed anything was possible at this point.

"Sorry, Draco," whoever it was laughed. "It's your fault for having a lake of water for a true core anyway."

"I don't know who you are, and I certainly don't know what you're talking about," Draco put on his best derogatory sneer that he mostly reserved for people who insulted his parents and Weasleys, "But if you don't tell me what you're doing in my mind this instant I'll kick you out of it."

Draco didn't know that he could actually do that, but it did seem to have some effect on the person currently dripping water all over him. It wasn't making him cold or really all that uncomfortable, but it was the principle of the thing. The newcomer sat back and stared at Draco with wide, blank eyes that seemed really familiar.

"Dray? It's me," the other person said, and Draco blinked to show he still didn't understand. The other kid raised an eyebrow, saying, "Well, that'll teach me to help out a friend in need. I come all the way here to get you, and you don't even recognize one of your best friends."

Best—? Draco narrowed his eyes at the other kid and looked more closely at them. The eyes were just a shade darker than his own grey, and they were widened in a falsely earnest expression he really should have recognized instantly.

"Rigel?" Draco frowned into the now-familiar face, "Why do you have long hair? I didn't recognize you at all."

"That's alright," Rigel said, shrugging a bit, "I think the manifestation of my consciousness still sees itself as having long hair, even though I cut mine eight months ago. Look at you, you're not in Hogwarts robes."

Draco looked down at his summer outfit once more and nodded. It made sense that the way people saw themselves was not always the same as the way others saw them.

"Well, how did you get in here?" Draco asked, a bit more excited now that he knew just who had invaded his mental space, "And what did you mean you came to get me?"

"It's sort of a long story," Rigel said, "I'll tell you all about it later, but right now we need to get you out of here, or get the sickness out of here, as soon as we can. It's very important."

Draco studied his friend carefully, and Rigel gazed back at Draco just as blankly as he always did, as if there was nothing whatsoever going on behind his flat, grey eyes. Draco knew better though, and so he said, "Why are you here, Rigel? I'm glad you are," he assured the other boy, "But why you? Why not Pomfrey or Snape or even my father?" Draco guiltily clenched his bare toes again, but held Rigel's eyes steadily as he waited for an answer. He'd noticed that whenever Rigel said something that Draco thought was probably a lie, Rigel's eyes flickered with pained regret for just a moment before he steeled himself and said whatever it was he wanted Draco to believe. Draco had never mentioned this to Rigel, not least because it was useful to be able to tell the difference, and Draco didn't even really mind that Rigel lied to him sometimes. He'd as good as said he would, after all, the night he agreed to be Draco's friend. Draco just wanted to see if Rigel was lying this time.

The other boy took his time in answering, but Draco saw no unease or regret flash through Rigel's eyes before he spoke, "You're sick, Draco. More sick than the others. We need to get the sickness out of you before it's too late."

Draco sucked in a breath slowly, digesting that information for a moment. "What's wrong with me?" he finally asked, feeling strange asking such a question about himself, "And it still doesn't explain why you."

"So many kids got sick," Rigel said, and Draco was thankful that his friend's voice was so calm and even. It made him feel like nothing could go wrong as long as he was there to help, "We ran out of Ginseng to put into the Snowhit and the Aurora's Breath. We had to start using Acai to substitute, because there was no Ginseng left anywhere in the country."

"I'm allergic to Acai," Draco spoke his thoughts out loud, "Oh. I see." And he did see. Without those potions, his body would waste away the longer he was in a coma. He'd already been there for…how long? A day? Two? "I'm dying," Draco tested the words, grimacing at the taste of them on his tongue. They tasted like failure, like weakness, and he wanted to spit, but he couldn't bring himself to in front of Rigel.

"You're not," Rigel said firmly, and Draco dragged his gaze, which had been wandering over the blackened landscape beyond his pond, back to his friend's face, "That's why I'm here. To make sure you don't." Rigel put his hand on Draco's shoulder, and it felt like a fire was burning under Rigel's skin. Though Draco hadn't been cold before, he was suddenly warm and feeling very calm and sure. Rigel looked very seriously at him, "Draco, I know you didn't hear me before, because you were already asleep, but I promised you everything was going to be okay. Maybe it wouldn't have been if things just kept on as they were, but we're not going to just let the world do whatever it wants, are we?"

Draco shook his head mutely.

"Good," Rigel nodded firmly, "We'll make sure everything turns out okay then. First we have to get you better, though."

"How?" Draco asked, wondering where on earth Rigel got his confidence from.

"Well, I'm not sure," Rigel said, and Draco looked incredulously at him.

"You somehow got into my mind, but you didn't have a plan for what you would do when you got here?" Draco shook his head, "Leave it to a Black."

"Hey!" Rigel said, mock affronted. It almost felt like they were back in their dorm, just joking around, except for the iceberg beneath their feet, "It's your mind, Draco, but if you want my opinion, I think we should try and use this pond to get rid of it somehow."

Rigel stood on the iceberg to get a better look around. Draco stood as well and surveyed the blackened wasteland his mind had become. The pond stretched about fifty feet across, and his iceberg was about five by five, though it wasn't really all that square. The shores the water lapped against seemed like they might be made of solid ice, but they couldn't see much of the actual terrain because the black tar from the sickness clung to absolutely everything. Draco couldn't see the edges of his mind either, though he thought he could make out black mists on the horizon in every direction he turned. Mostly his mind seemed to be a flat expanse of black-covered ice, with the light-blue pond in the middle, inexplicably untouched by the blackness.

"What are we supposed to do?" Draco turned to Rigel, frowning, "I don't think we have enough water here to cover the whole space, even if we could somehow just wash the black stuff away."

Rigel shrugged, "Your pond should re-fill itself, though slowly, and I can use some of my own magic to help I think." The other boy seemed to concentrate for a moment, then a ball of fire burst into life in his hand. Rigel grinned, "Between the two of us, we'll be able to get rid of it eventually. From what I've seen, it's not very aggressive." He frowned again, "The only problem is time. It's always hard to tell how much time is passing outside while you're in your mind, so we'll have to work fast."

Draco stared at the little ball of flame that was dancing in Rigel's palm. How did he do that? Draco cut his eyes to the snowball he'd been playing with earlier, which lay abandoned and smushed on one side of the iceberg now. He concentrated, willing the ball of snow to condense once more, and watched as it slowly became more rounded. Draco held out a hand and demanded the ball come to his hand. It flew upwards, and he caught it easily, noting with satisfaction that with a little extra effort he could make it harden into ice. He looked up at Rigel, who was smiling a little as he watched Draco control his snowball. Draco said, "I can make this happen because this is my mind we're in, but how can you control anything?"

Rigel blinked, and shrugged, "It's not really your mind that's making it happen. It's your consciousness willing your magic to effect changes in the mental landscape. Your magical core is water surrounded by ice, and it manifests itself here as a lake, with icebergs like this I guess." Rigel tapped a foot onto the ice they stood on and went on, "My magical core isn't water, it's more like fire, and even though I'm not in my mind anymore, my consciousness is still connected to my magical core even here. So I can effect changes on the mental landscape too, just like the sickness can, and I suppose like anyone else who broke into your mind could." Rigel looked embarrassed suddenly, "Uh, sorry about breaking into your mind uninvited, Draco."

Draco blinked. Rigel went off on the most unnecessary tangents sometimes. "No problem. Just keep the breaking and entering to emergency situations like this one, and I think I'll manage to forgive you."

Rigel nodded, "Well then, let's get started."

They turned as one toward the bank closest to their little ice raft. Draco swallowed at the sight of all that awful blackness, but then steeled his nerve. They had a long way to go, but Draco wasn't going to stop until his mind was completely his own again.

Normal POV:

Harry glanced over at Draco's determined expression and smiled. It was good to see her friend was just as he always was, even here in his own mind. Though she had definitely noticed the bare feet, it seemed that mostly with Draco Malfoy what you saw was what you got. That will probably change in a few years, she thought, One day I'll look over and I won't recognize this boy. She shook her head to clear the melancholy thoughts away. Time enough for that stuff later. Now it was time to do some serious spring-cleaning in Draco's mind.

"Can you make the iceberg move closer to the shore?" she asked Draco. He nodded and furrowed his brow in concentration, and their raft began to glide easily toward the blackened bank. When they were close enough, Rigel nodded to Draco and the raft stopped. "Don't let it touch you," Harry said softly, "I'm not sure what will happen."

Draco smirked at her, "Worry about yourself, Rigel. This can't be nearly as bad as one of Flint's early morning workouts."

Harry grinned back, "After you then, Dray."

Draco paused for a moment, then shrugged and stuck his hand out over the side of the raft and held it there, rigid, until a column of water began to rise from the lake toward his down-turned palm. "It's so weird trying to do stuff without a wand or a spell," he commented, then he jerked his arm forward and the column of water flew toward the shore, crashing against it and splattering in all directions. They watched as the water hit the blackness coating the shoreline. The inky stuff seemed to hiss, and then it was dissolving wherever the water touched it. Draco grinned broadly, "This is going to be like Quidditch without Bludgers. Too easy."

Harry rolled her eyes, but agreed, "It's not even fighting back. I feel silly for running from it now."

Draco glanced sideways at her, "Running from it?" His eyes widened. "Rigel, it's in your mind, too?"

"Yeah," Harry said sheepishly, "I just sort of left it there so I'd have time to come and get you before the two days was up."

"Well after we're done with my mind, we can do yours next," Draco said.

"Fine with me," Harry shrugged, "But I won't die if I stay in a coma, so let's get rid of this stuff as fast as we can, okay?"

"Right," Draco turned back and lifted another stream of water from the lake, sending it toward the shore.

Harry contemplated her own fireball. Fire was more destructive than water. Would she end up scorching Draco's landscape if she threw her magic around in it? She concentrated on what she wanted her magic to do, then moved the fire to the edge of their iceberg to test it. Nothing happened. Harry smiled. Magic really was all about intention. She didn't want the fire to melt any of Draco's ice, so it didn't. Now to see if her magic would work on the sickness like Draco's did.

She lobbed the fireball at the right side of the shore, since Draco was working on the left. It struck the black terrain and instead of dissolving the black stuff like Draco's had, it set it on fire. The sickness writhed where the fire burned it and Harry could see it melting away slowly under the flames. Though it was not as instantly effective as Draco's had been, the fire stayed and spread to the surrounding blackness, so that Harry only had to throw a few more fire balls and then wait while the fire did its work. When they had enough space, Draco directed the iceberg to land and they climbed off onto the mainland, which actually was made entirely of ice as far as they could tell. Harry was glad to note that none of the ice on the right side of their little semi-circle of cleared mental space looked scorched or melted. The mind was truly an impressive thing, Harry decided, surveying their work. She doubted anything like this would work in the real world, but here in Draco's mind, which was likely so flexible and open because of his age, there were very few rules that a pair of determined Slytherins with adept imagination couldn't bend or break completely.

They worked steadily, gradually moving further from one another as they each worked on their own flank, meeting in the middle and then moving further away once more over and over again as they pushed the sickness back with water and flame. The black thing wasn't fighting back—at all. Harry expected at least some resistance, but it seemed to not even notice that parts of it were being dissolved and melted away. It did seem to have an expanding instinct that kept it pushing back against them, but they worked much faster than the blackness could creep, so they moved forward inexorably, step by step, until a good portion of Draco's mind was plain, flat ice, unblemished by the sickness' sludge.

When they met in the middle once more, Harry tossed a grin at Draco over her shoulder and said, "Really gives a whole new meaning to the term 'brain-washing' doesn't it?" She gestured at Draco's water, which he was currently wielding like a whip to keep the black feelers at bay while his other hand directed a wave of water to crash down in front of him.

Draco laughed, a fierce sound that was really closer to a battle cry than a laugh, "I don't know why I didn't try this sooner! To think I was bored when I could have been doing this. Though," he paused to stretch his arm muscles, "It's really exhausting."

Harry nodded in agreement. Though her magical reserves had been up because she hadn't brewed anything for a day or so before the sickness invaded her mind, the constant use of magic was taking its toll on her as well.

They parted again to work on their own sides, and soon they had nearly a third of the visible mindscape clear of sickness. Harry didn't know what they would do when they reached the blackened mists, and she also couldn't tell how much time had passed. She called out to Draco to get his attention, "Hey Draco, can you feel anything from your physical body yet?"

Draco turned a quizzical look at Harry, "What do you mean? Can I do that?"

"You'll be able to whenever we clear the section of your mind that relates to control and communication with your physical self," Harry said, checking on the edges of the on-fire black goo with the corner of her eye while she spoke, "I'm not sure when that will be, though, since it won't be clearly marked or anything. You'll just have to keep checking I guess."

Draco nodded thoughtfully, absent-mindedly coaxing another load of water from the pond. "If I concentrate on the idea of my physical body, I can feel…something. It's weird. I can feel myself laying down, even though I know I'm standing up right here."

"It takes a while to get used to the dual senses," Harry agreed, "Try moving your hand."

Draco waved his hand in a nonplussed kind of a way.

"Not that hand," Harry said.

"I know," Draco frowned, "But whenever I try waving my hand, it just waves." He waved his hand again and Harry had to laugh at how silly he looked standing there in summer clothes, no shoes, and a pointlessly waving hand in the middle of a background that looked like Antarctica.

"Try concentrating on moving your hand, but also think specifically about not moving that hand," Harry suggested.

"How can you think about two things at once?" Draco asked incredulously.

Harry shrugged. It was just something you did; she didn't know how to explain it to Draco. It was how a potion brewer had to think, in order to correctly count the 28 stirs counterclockwise while also adding the exact number of Affilla Beans to a Winter's Luck Potion, for instance.

Draco sighed, "Watch this side for me." He frowned down at the ice to concentrate and Harry dutifully went to his side to keep the black stuff back while Draco was distracted. It took a few moments to catch because the edges of the black tar were still a bit wet from Draco's magic, but soon there was a slow fire burning on that side as well and Harry took a break to watch Draco try and connect with his physical body. The blond boy had a tendency to scowl at things when he was thinking very hard about something, even when he wasn't at all angry or upset. She wondered if he'd always done that, and had a sudden image of a little blond five-year-old scowling darkly at his first toy broom as he tried to figure out how to make it work. She barely contained an amused snort.

Draco looked up suddenly, "I think I did it."

"Really?"

"Well I felt my hand move, but my hand didn't move, if that makes sense," Draco said, looking rather cheerful despite the backdrop of burning tar and soggy ice.

"That's great!" Harry said, "If you can move your body around enough, maybe you can get someone's attention. Madam Pomfrey should be checking on you, and your parents were around when I went under too, I think. That way if the three days you had under the sustaining spells, well, two since I went into meditation, run out, they can take you off of the spells before your magical core realizes something is wrong. By then you should have enough of your mind away from the sickness that your body will breathe and pump blood on its own once more."

Draco nodded, "I'll try moving it again a few times, and then we can get rid of some more of this stuff."

Harry was about to reply when a new voice cut across the icy landscape, making the two first-years jump in surprise.

"There won't be any need for that."

They turned toward the source of the voice and gaped at the sight of Professor Snape gliding across the ice toward them, an unreadable expression on his face.

"Professor!"

"Uncle Severus!"

Draco and Harry exchanged a look of relief mixed with sheer disbelief.

"How did you get in here, sir?"

"Are you here to save me, Uncle Severus?"

Snape raised an eyebrow sardonically. Harry noticed that his mental avatar looked very much like his usual physical self. Same robes, same hair, same attitude. It seemed that Severus Snape was a man who saw himself just as clearly as he saw everything else, "Only the two of you would manage to do something so impressive without even realizing you'd done it."

Draco sent Harry a blank look, which Harry returned with a look just as uncomprehending.

Snape looked about two seconds away from rolling his eyes, "You destabilized the mental barrier that was preventing any Legilimency from accessing Draco's mind from without."

"How did we do that?" Draco blinked.

Harry turned her eyes toward the landscape with sudden understanding. There was only one entrance and exit from the outside of a mind. Sure enough, the fire they had left unchecked had burned a clear patch in the mists, which must have been what held the Occlumency-like barrier that protected the sickness from Legilimency.

Snape nodded as he saw where Harry was looking, "Indeed, Mr. Black. Even the tiniest flaw in a barrier is enough to allow a Master of the Mental Arts entrance to a mind. Once that part of the mists was purified, I could have come in at any time, but I didn't realize Draco's condition had changed until Narcissa noticed his hand move."

"See? I knew it worked!" Draco smiled triumphantly at Harry, who grinned back.

"So are you going to help us, Professor Snape?" Harry asked curiously, "We've gotten rid of a good chunk of the black stuff, but it's slow going. How much time does Draco have left on the sustainment spells?"

"It is currently Saturday at 6:43 am," Snape said in his emotionless drawl, "I am told that Draco fell ill Tuesday evening," here he shot Harry a look that made her wince, "Which means he was first administered the Aurora's Breath and Snowhit Wednesday around midday when his unconscious processes began to fail, and has consequently been on life sustaining spells for approximately two days and 19 hours."

Harry mentally calculated. If it had taken her a day and a half to make it this far, would they have enough time to eradicate the rest of the illness? Granted, she didn't know how much time had been spent just getting through Draco's magical core, but still…it was going to be close. "With the Professor here to help, surely we can get rid of it in time," Harry said to Draco, trying to sound confident.

Draco frowned, obviously doing some calculations of his own, and looked worried.

Snape snorted. "Stand back boys, and watch a real Occlumens at work."

Harry blinked, but took a step away from Snape as Draco hurriedly did the same. The Potions Master raised an arm out in front of him, hand flexed as if it were gripping something fiercely. The air around them seemed to hum for a moment, perhaps with anticipation, and then Snape clenched his fist and exhaled sharply, glaring at the blackness still covering two-thirds of Draco's mindscape.

To Harry's utter shock, the blackness twisted and writhed like a sea of inky worms, and then it was flung back from the ice it had settled on like it was tumbleweed and Snape had conjured up a tornado. If the black thing had a voice, it would surely have been screaming as it was hurled into the mists, and then, without so much as a shadow left behind, it was gone.

Harry felt supremely inferior, and realized just how ineffectual her and Draco's efforts had been compared to Snape's. Of course, it had seemed that they were accomplishing something really difficult, because Harry had very little real experience with Occlumency and Draco had none, but Harry now understood that the sickness truly was aimed at infecting and subduing children and children only, if this was the power of an adult Occlumens.

Snape smirked at the look of utter amazement both Harry and Draco were wearing.

"How did you—?" Draco couldn't even finish the question.

"You two did an admirable job," Snape said, and Harry could feel the smugness the older Slytherin was too reserved to show, "But I have had many years of experience in the mind arts, and that with wizards whose Legilimency makes this sickness look completely harmless. While the sickness created an impenetrable defence from the outside, it was nothing more than an irksome fly once its barrier was breached."

Harry nodded thoughtfully, "Because it wasn't designed to actually do damage to the mind it possessed, it is easily defeated from within once its occupant knows how to go about it. The problem is that children's minds are the ones susceptible to it, and most children aren't taught mind magics at such a young age, so they don't know what to do once they're trapped in it."

Harry didn't miss the sharp look Snape sent her at the way she described the illness as being designed for a purpose, but she ignored it with the excuse of paying attention to Draco.

"But you knew about the stuff I could do with mind magic," her friend pointed out, "And you still haven't explained how you even got in my mind, since even Uncle Severus couldn't get in until we broke the barrier from within."

"I would very much like to understand that as well," Snape put in, frowning at her.

Harry glanced between the two of them, "Well, can full explanations wait? We need to get Draco to wake up, though that shouldn't be hard now that the sickness doesn't have hold of his mind anymore. And I have to get the sickness out of my own mind after this too. I'm not sure how far it's progressed at this point, so for all I know I could wake up only to fall right back into a coma."

Draco frowned, "I guess I can't help you with your mind, since I don't know enough mind magic to move between minds. Sorry, Rigel."

"That's alright," Harry said, "Now that we know the trick, I'll just clear a path to the mists and disrupt the mental barrier the sickness has around my mind so that Professor Snape can get in to help me get rid of it. It shouldn't take much time at all, really."

Snape nodded reluctantly, "Very well. I will return to the physical world and explain the situation to Madam Pomfrey and Mr. Malfoy's parents. Mr. Black, you will return to your own mind…however you plan on doing that." Harry nodded easily. "As you will not be clearing enough of your mind to regain the physical control necessary to signal to me, I will simply attempt to breach your mind repeatedly until I am able to. Mr. Malfoy will wait until we have both exited his mind, and then attempt to wake himself up."

Draco and Harry both nodded to show they understood, and Snape nodded back. He strode on his heel back toward the mists and soon was gone from Draco's mind completely.

"Well, see you in real life then," Draco said cheerfully.

Harry gazed seriously at her friend. "I'm really glad you're going to be okay," she said, "I was so worried when I heard you—" she broke off, shaking her head. "I'm just so relieved, Dray. And you were amazing, picking up the mind magic so quickly like that."

"Only thanks to your help," Draco said, looking embarrassed. He glanced askance at her as he added, "Besides, what are you so relieved for? You promised everything would be okay, didn't you? Maybe you weren't so sure, but I never doubted you."

Harry didn't know what to say, so she just moved her gaze to the icy terrain that had been unveiled when the sickness left. "You should build something, Dray." Draco looked at her strangely, but she went on, "Not now, of course, but after you learn meditation and all that, you should do something with all this space."

"Maybe I will," Draco said thoughtfully, "Did you build something in your mind?"

"Yeah," Harry said, frowning as she wondered what sort of state she'd find her mind in when she returned, "Maybe one day you'll get to see it."

"I definitely look forward to it," Draco said, "But right now you need to get out of my mind and go clean up your own so Severus can make you better. I am not going to sit by myself at dinner this evening, and I'll just bet everyone else went and fell ill on us."

Harry laughed at how offended Draco seemed at the thought of eating alone and waved a hand as she turned and headed toward Draco's pond, "I can see when I'm not wanted. See you soon, Draco."

"See you, Rigel."

Harry took a deep, unnecessary breath at the edge of Draco's pond and silently asked his magical core to let her back out of Draco's mind, putting all of her will behind the request. A whirlpool began to turn at the centre of the pond, faster and faster, and when Harry caught sight of the black hole forming in the middle she jumped straight into the centre and let the confusing rush of water sweep her away once more.

She was spat out rather violently on the other side of Draco's magical core, and only saved herself from being smashed against the inside of Draco's primary core level by hurriedly bringing magic to her outstretched hands and blasting fire through the thick layer of ice to melt it out of the way as she hurtled through it. Once out of Draco's core completely, she sought out the connection between Draco's core and hers and thrust herself along it, speeding toward the familiar feeling of her own magical core.

When she arrived back at the ball of restless coils of magical energy that was her core, she asked her magic to sever the connection between she and Draco and began digging among the coils to reach the secondary layer. The coils of magic snaked around her playfully, tugging her this way and that until she sighed and asked her magic to please let her through to the true core. The coils parted and she caught a glimpse of the shining sun that lay beneath. Harry wriggled her way through the primary coils and let herself fall right through the centre of her molten true core.

Her mental senses returned to her all at once, and Harry had to pause for a moment to digest all the information streaming into her consciousness as she emerged from the sun in her Space Room. The sickness now covered everything outside of the Space Room. The mountain, the mists, the false lab and every branch of the many confusing tunnels was coated in a layer of black. Harry drifted toward the door to the Space Room. The hardest part would be getting out of the Space Room without letting any of the black stuff in.

Using the energy from her sun-core, which Harry noticed guiltily was burning a bit dimmer than it usually did, Harry decided to stand as close as she could to the door, and then create a barrier behind her that would seal off the Space Room completely, as if she'd created an antechamber between the door and the actual room. It would serve as a buffer zone in case any sickness leaked through when she opened the door.

With that precaution in place, Harry opened the door quickly and sent a burst of fire from her hands into the tunnel beyond. All she could see at first was blackness, but soon the flames were eating away at the creeping goop, melting it until it disintegrated. She stepped into the tunnel, closing the Space Room door firmly behind her after making sure no sickness had gotten through, and started flaming the blackness out of her way once more. It was slow work, but she cleared a path through the tunnel and out of the trap door, through the decoy Lab, which looked like a thick layer of soot had settled over everything in it, and out of the ice illusion to the mountainside beyond. Harry aimed for the closest patch of mist, and eventually made her way over to it.

She took a moment to re-gather her energy. Her magic was definitely not in top form. It felt like she'd been brewing Snowhit for hours or maybe days. She summoned another fireball with effort and hurled it just a bit vindictively into the blackened mists before her. The sickness seemed to evaporate from the air, and Harry sighed with relief. She sat down to wait, but it wasn't more than a few minutes later that Snape appeared out of the mists next to her. She could feel when he did so. It felt a lot like when the sickness had first entered into her mind, like a niggling pressure that felt foreign and unnatural, but the feeling faded once she had identified the intruder as Snape and classified him mentally as not an immediate threat.

"Hello, Professor," Harry said, somewhat cheekily, "Welcome to my mind."

Chapter 21

Harry felt decidedly self-conscious as she watched Professor Snape look around with interest at her mindscape.

"Usually it's much nicer," she told him as his eyes took in the huge mountain before them, "You know, when there isn't black tar all over everything."

Snape glanced at her, apparently unimpressed, "If you can still summon the energy to make obvious jokes, perhaps my presence is not needed here. Shall I leave you to tidy up around here by yourself?"

Harry backtracked quickly, "I wish you wouldn't, sir. Judging by the dimness of my magical core, I'd never get it all done myself."

"Where is your core?" Snape asked, looking around again, frowning in thought, "On the peak of the mountain?"

Harry shook her head, "It's inside the mountain."

Snape raised a brow, "You have built a passage into the mountain? That is to say, you have multiple levels to your mind?"

"Yes, sir," Harry said, "It seemed safest to get all the important things out of the open."

"Indeed," Snape's lips quirked for a moment, and Harry wondered exactly what the inside of Snape's mind looked like. "I need to see the sickness to banish it, so you will have to take me though all of the infected areas."

"Yes, sir," Harry agreed. She watched Snape concentrate on the blackened landscape once more and raise his arms imperiously. A moment later she felt her entire mind shiver, and some sort of power rushed through her mental awareness, like a strong wind blowing hair out of her face. The sickness was hurled out into the mists and beyond, at least all the sickness that they could see from that side of the mountain.

Slowly, Harry led Snape around to the other side of the mountain, then down to the base. She hesitated, not liking the idea of showing all of her mental tricks to someone else, especially a man that she knew she shouldn't really trust, for all that she respected him as a Potions Master. The fact was, Snape had spoken to Quirrell as if he were in league or at the very least working for whoever had sent the sickness to Hogwarts. That meant he was an SOW Party-liner, which meant he was against muggleborns and halfbloods to some extent, or passively okay with their mistreatment. In other words, he couldn't be trusted with her secrets. Still, Harry reasoned, she could always change her mindscape around after he'd left. Might as well get his help with the sickness as long as he's already here.

When they reached the ice wall, Snape stopped and looked at her questioningly.

Harry smiled, "It's just an illusion. Didn't stop the sickness any, but when I designed the place I wasn't expecting the intruder to rely on touch instead of eyes."

Snape smirked, "A valuable lesson in case you decide to pursue the mind arts further. A great number of wizards make the exact same mistake, and have mental defences that merely look impressive, instead of taking the time and effort to create more lasting protections."

Harry frowned, "Why would they rely solely on illusions? I only have the one."

Snape glanced at her, "Illusions in the mind take much less mental and magical energy to execute in comparison to solid creations."

"Oh? I hadn't noticed," Harry said absently, walking through the illusion to the cavern inside, "And what do you mean mental and magical energy? Isn't the energy the same, from the magical core, either way?"

Snape considered her question as he glanced around the black-coated potions lab, "When you create something with magic, be it in the physical world or the mental world, you use magical energy from your core, that is true. However, in each case you also expend mental energy. By that I do not mean that your mind actually produces any magical energy of its own, but that magic requires concentration and strong intent to wield, especially when attempting to create something from scratch instead of simply altering something existing. This mental requirement takes a toll on the mind; extended concentration tires the mind and strains it, whether you are cramming for an exam or building a log cabin in your mind, and over time the brain is able to concentrate less and less until it requires rest to recover. It is this loss of mental ability, or energy, that I was referring to, not physical energy as magic is generally seen as."

Harry nodded her understanding, "And it requires more concentration and mental power to create permanent structures in the mind than it does to create lasting illusions?"

"Much more," Snape said, looking like he wanted to shake his head at her and sigh, "Destroying requires the least amount of mental energy, illusions and tricks of the mind just a bit more, but solid creation is something extremely taxing…to most wizards. I don't suppose you've been studying Occlumency since you were about four?"

Harry shook her head bemusedly, "I just picked it up this semester, really."

Snape did sigh this time, "You are going to be a lot of headaches, Mr. Black."

"Sorry, sir," Harry said, not sure what else to say.

"Do not be," Snape said, "With any luck you will also bring much acclaim to Slytherin House. Merlin knows we need it these days." He muttered the last bit as he turned to look around the decoy lab once more, and Harry tucked that admission away for later.

"Do you need to stand at the opposite side?" Harry asked curiously, "So you can blow it out the door?"

Snape sent her an amused look, "No, I can evaporate it directly from here, it just requires more concentration."

Harry nodded and stepped back. Snape closed his eyes once more, and when he opened them Harry nearly quailed, thanking Merlin those eyes weren't focused on her at the moment. He looked determined enough to simply wish her out of existence if he wanted to, and a few moments later it seemed as though that's exactly what he had done to the sickness. It was gone so completely from every surface that Harry had trouble convincing herself that it had been there in the first place.

He turned to her, "A potions lab? Creative, but a bit obvious, don't you think? I suppose the recipe scrolls hold your memories."

Harry smirked, an expression she'd picked up from Draco and Pansy, "Entirely too obvious, sir." She walked over to the fireplace and nudged the rug out the way. She could see where the blackness had seeped under it and dripped down in between the cracks of the trap door to the tunnels below. She grasped the ring and levered it up to reveal the tar-covered ladder beneath. "After you, Professor."

Snape raised an eyebrow, "We may make a Slytherin of you yet, Mr. Black."

If only you knew, Professor Snape.

With a thought from Snape (or so it seemed to Harry watching), the blackness on the ladder and the part of the tunnel he could see was gone, and they traveled down into the pale green light emitted from the crystals embedded in the walls of the hewn rock. Snape glanced around curiously. "Do all of these tunnels lead somewhere?"

"No," Harry said, "But they are all covered with the sickness."

"Very well."

They traveled the tunnels with Harry as a guide, and eventually they had gotten all of them cleared except the one leading to her Space Room. She reluctantly led Snape along it and stopped when they reached the seamless door. He noted what was left of the path she'd blazed through the sickness on her way to the mists earlier.

"Your magical core is through there, then?"

"Yes," Harry said, "My…memories and such are through there too, but there isn't any sickness in there."

Snape regarded her carefully, "You are certain?"

"I am. I took precautions coming through, and there is no way for the sickness or anything else to get through by touch alone."

Snape inclined his head slowly, "Very well. I am not unfamiliar with the necessity of keeping certain things private. In any case, this explains how your physical body is still in meditation and not in a coma despite you leaving your mind unattended with the sickness for so long. You must have locked most of your physical controls away with your magical core and your memories, if perhaps inadvertently. You will inform me immediately if you sense any remnant of sickness within once I have gone, however."

Harry agreed. Snape eradicated what was left of the sickness, and the alien feeling that had been niggling at the back of her magical senses since she had first contracted the illness at Draco's bedside disappeared. She sighed with relief and led Snape back out of the confusing network of tunnels and up the ladder into the decoy cavern. "Thank you for helping me get rid of the sickness," she said as they walked through the ice wall and out onto the mountainside.

Snape turned serious eyes on her and said, "I would not have been able to, had you not broken through from the inside. That is especially true for Draco. My godson is…one of the few things I consider important in my life. It is I who must thank you for intervening as you did, though I expect a full explanation of just what you did when you get out of your trance."

Harry frowned slightly, "You shouldn't thank me. It was my fault to begin with. If I'd told you from the start that Draco was sick instead of trying to spare you the worry—"

"Then I would have rushed back, neglecting my important errand, and stood beside Draco's bedside just as uselessly as his parents and Madam Pomfrey did," Snape scowled at her the way he sometimes scowled at other kids in Potions class who gave answers that didn't make any sense whatsoever, "My expertise was not enough to save Draco or stop the sickness, and my knowing sooner would not have made any difference. You found a way when no one else did, and for that I expect you will have many people's thanks, including Lucius and Narcissa's. The other parents will be grateful if your method can cure their children as well, but the Malfoys almost lost their son and Heir today. They will not forget that, and you should not treat your accomplishments so lightly."

Harry didn't know what to say, a situation that was occurring more frequently the more time she spent at Hogwarts. Luckily, Snape went on to fill the silence.

"Do not worry about developing an inflated ego," he told her, looking down his nose at her, "I can spot one coming years before it swells, and the very moment I sense you to be valuing yourself more than you merit, I will be only too happy to intervene." Harry ducked her head to hide a small smile. "Now let's get out of here so I can dress you down properly for your numerous offences, beginning with omitting pertinent information from a report to your superior and ending with recklessly endangering another student's mind by mucking about in it without a licence in Mind Wizardry."

Harry winced, "Will this be before or after Madam Pomfrey chews me up for sneaking into the Hospital Wing behind her back?"

"After," Snape said easily, "But before Miss Parkinson wakes up and scolds you for once again heedlessly endangering your good health."

"Right."

Harry watched Snape fade through the mists of her mind, which were pristine and white once again, and breathed a sigh of relief. It was almost over. All she had to do was wake herself up and explain things so that Snape could cure the other students too. Then she could go back to her little Lab and brew potions that were actually on the first-year curriculum for a change.

With that thought in mind, Harry finally stepped forward into the mists herself, letting her physical senses drag her back to the real world and leaving the peaceful, sickness-free mindscape behind.

When she opened her eyes, she flinched back with a start at the sight that greeted them. Draco was hovering scant inches away from her face, staring intently. He leaned back with a smile and Rigel could see that the Hospital Wing was more crowded than it had been…two days before? Whenever she'd last seen it. She felt bleary, like she'd been swimming with her eyes open underwater for too long and forgotten what the world looked like without liquid obstructing her vision.

"He's awake," Draco said to nobody in particular, or perhaps to everyone in the room. Draco was perched on a chair next to the bed she was laying on. It was the bed Draco had been laid on when he was sick, between Blaise and a first year Ravenclaw Rigel thought might have a twin sister in Gryffindor.

Rigel levered herself upright, feeling extremely uncomfortable lying down in front of most of the people in the room. There was Draco, of course, and Snape, Narcissa, and Mr. Malfoy all standing near the foot of the bed. She was surprised, however, to see that Headmaster Dumbledore was there as well, and Professor McGonagall right beside him. Madam Pomfrey was also there, hurrying over from a patient she'd been checking on two rows away.

"Don't move about too much, Mr. Black," the nurse said crisply as she arrived, waving her wand at Rigel automatically, who tried not to cringe. She really didn't trust Medi-witches. "You've been in meditation for nearly two days, and your body will feel quite heavy and unwieldy because of it." She frowned and waved her wand again, "You also seem to have weakened your magical core somewhat, though the levels are not much below what is normal for a first-year."

"In that case, Mr. Black has weakened his magical core significantly," Snape drawled.

Madam Pomfrey raised her eyebrows, "Well that is more along the lines of what I would expect if half of the things young Mr. Malfoy has been saying hold any truth. One moment, and I will get you a bit of Pepper-Up. It's not as good as bed rest and quiet, of course," here she glared a bit at Headmaster Dumbledore, "But I daresay those things will have to wait until certain parties are satisfied."

She went off, muttering about people who put information gathering above a child's good health, and a moment later returned with a potion and a stern advisement to drink the whole dose.

Rigel did so, avoiding the curious gazes of the adults and Draco for a moment longer. When Madam Pomfrey had taken the empty vial back, Headmaster Dumbledore stepped forward, saying kindly, "Thank you, Poppy. Now that young Mr. Black is recovered somewhat from the trying few days he has had, perhaps he will be able to explain a few things." The Headmaster turned genial eyes on Mr. and Mrs. Malfoy, "If your family would be so good as to give us a few moments, I'm sure it won't take long. In fact, I doubt Draco need remain in the Hospital Wing any longer, as he is clearly free of the sickness."

Draco looked startled at Dumbledore's not-so-subtle attempt to get rid of his family, but Rigel privately understood and even sort of agreed with the Headmaster. If he knew what she suspected, that the SOW Party was behind the sickness, then it might not be wise to explain exactly how the sickness had been countered in front of one of the most notorious supporters of the SOW Party, namely Lucius Malfoy. From the look on Malfoy's face, however, he was not intending to go anywhere.

"My son does indeed appear to be free of this illness," Mr. Malfoy said smoothly, "A fact that I am most interested in understanding. I believe it is within my rights as a parent to know exactly what has gone on here, particularly as it seems to have involved infringement upon my son and Heir's mental sanctity."

Rigel winced inwardly and saw Draco frown out of the corner of her eye.

"Father, Rigel was helping me. He would never have gone into my mind otherwise. He even apologized for it already," Draco tilted his chin up with just a hint of defiance, "And I've said I've forgiven him. So he has no standing offence against me."

Rigel looked at Draco in surprise, knowing quite well he worshiped the ground his father walked on, but Mr. Malfoy seemed more amused than upset by his Heir's slight censure.

"I'm sure I will come to agree with you, Draco," he said unconcernedly, but with a hint of steel underlying his words, "Once I've heard the whole story."

If Dumbledore had been trying to get rid of the Malfoys, he certainly didn't show any disappointment at having failed. He smiled benignly, seeming to include everyone in the room with it, and said, "That's just fine, then. I can tell this is going to be quite a tale, though, so why don't we make ourselves more comfortable?"

He waved his wand in a gesture that seemed to be more for show than an actual wand-movement, and six handsome chairs appeared around Rigel's bed. She noticed that the beds on either side of her were moved back gently to make room for them, and shifted a bit uneasily as the six adults sat down around her with varying expressions of curiosity and impatience on their faces. There was something extremely strange and perhaps a bit morbid about sitting in a room full of comatose children, with a half-circle of people looking at her as if she'd called them there for story-time.

Rigel felt stronger physically after the Pepper-Up had kicked in, but she was still drained emotionally and mentally from the past couple of days, and she didn't know quite where to start. She glanced around at the adults helplessly for a moment, but Professor McGonagall must have sensed her predicament, for she said gently, "I think we all know what happened up until Thursday evening. Young Mr. Malfoy fell ill, and the Malfoys have explained that after discovering Draco's allergy to Acai and subsequent inability to rely on the usual potions you set out to try and find a way to work around the Acai. Obviously you were unsuccessful—"

Here Snape broke in sharply, "It is impossible to substitute a substitution, though a potions student of even Mr. Black's level would not have been expected to know that. There was nothing anyone could have done to make those potions work without Ginseng."

McGonagall nodded, lips pursed, "Of course, Severus, I meant nothing by it. Suffice to say that at some point Mr. Black gave up the search and came back here. It is there that the accounts become unclear."

The Gryffindor Head of House turned back to Rigel, who saw concern, but also kindness in her gaze.

Rigel nodded slowly, "Yes, I came to the same conclusion late Thursday afternoon. I went to dinner, and there I realized that sometime while I was working, Pansy had fallen ill as well. I came to the Hospital Wing—"

"How did you get into the Quarantine?" Snape interrupted.

Rigel held in a sigh. Clearly this was going to be one of those accountings where someone stopped her every other sentence and demanded clarification. "Madam Pomfrey escorted me across the line on Wednesday morning, when I brought potions to the Hospital Wing," Rigel said, "I think the line has a recognition memory of some kind, because after that it didn't refuse me access."

Snape sent a look to Madam Pomfrey, who pointedly ignored it.

Rigel continued, "I stood by Pansy and Draco's bedsides for a while, I'm not sure how long, just thinking, and when I was by Draco I felt something…strange with my mental senses. It was like something was poking at my thoughts, distracting me until I paid attention to it. Once I focused on it, I became sure that something was happening in my mind, so I fell into meditation automatically."

"You speak as though you meditate often," the Headmaster pointed out mildly.

Rigel nodded, already resigned to this particular secret coming out after she had overheard Pomfrey telling the Malfoys. "I began trying to learn Occlumency this semester."

"How convenient," Mr. Malfoy commented.

Rigel looked at him flatly, "Not particularly. It was actually Professor Snape that gave me the idea." Snape raised his eyebrows to indicate his confusion. "He's been helping me with my magic this year. I didn't have very good control over it and it had a tendency to react to my emotions, as Professor Snape explained." Snape's eyebrows raised a bit further at the way she stretched the truth, but he didn't contradict her, though they both knew her control was, if anything, too good, and her constant containment of it was what caused most of her magical issues. "Over winter break my cousin got me a book on Occlumency, because she'd read that Occlumency could be used to control the emotions, and so this semester I've been working on learning it."

"Alright, so you developed enough mental awareness to sense the sickness when it first attacked and go into meditation," Pomfrey said, writing on a clipboard as she spoke, "What did the sickness look like when you first encountered it in your mind?"

Rigel thought back, "It came through the mists first, turning them black." None of the adults seemed at all confused about what she meant by mists, so she continued, "The sickness itself is like a big, black…"

"Monster," Draco supplied, "Like an octopus, all fluid with tentacles."

"Yes," Rigel nodded, "It's a blob of tar-like blackness, oily and fluid, that slowly expands to blanket the landscape of a mind. The sickness appears to be mindless, and it moves almost automatically. Once it gains entrance into the mind, it spreads through the mists and I guess that's where it sets up the mental barrier to keep other Legilimency-users out. Then it creeps over the landscape in every direction, spreading like a liquid would, except it goes against gravity if it needs to in order to reach all the surfaces of the mind."

Madam Pomfrey nodded, jotting it all down, "What does it feel like?"

"Well, mentally it just feels wrong, and maybe a little slimy, but I never actually touched it with my avatar. When I saw the black stuff moving out of the mists and across my mindscape, I retreated," Rigel admitted.

"So did I," Draco put in, "I mean I touched it once by accident, and it just felt sticky. My magical core washed it right off though."

"Hmm," the nurse looked up, "Continue your account, please."

"I barricaded myself in the place I keep my magical core," Rigel said, speaking firmly so that no one would try and ask her for more details than that. "Once I was safe, I realized I was also trapped in my mind. Even though I was in meditation, and not a coma, I was still effectively cut off from the real world. This worried me because I knew that Draco only had another couple of days under the sustainment spells, and I was supposed to be helping him."

"You did help him," Narcissa spoke softly.

Rigel looked at the older woman and smiled, "I did. I was also very lucky, though." She hesitated for a moment more, still uneasy about explaining the 'cure' to the Malfoys, but the look of grateful concern on Narcissa's face decided her. The Malfoys didn't look to her like members of a political party. They looked like parents, worried and upset as any parent would be and many of the other kids' parents probably were. They, too, had been hurt by the sickness, no matter if they'd known of it beforehand or not. They, too, deserved an explanation. "Professor Snape had taught me earlier in the semester how to imbue potions consciously, because my magic wasn't stable enough to imbue them unconsciously, and he also taught me to sense my magical core. Because of this, I knew about true cores and about forming connections between magical cores. I just sort of put all of those things together and worked out a plan to both get out of my own mind and to help Draco get the sickness out of his."

She received a handful of blank looks and a couple of incredulous ones as well.

"I don't get it," Draco said, and since none of the adults tried to explain, Rigel went through it as best she could.

"I discovered that a person's true core manifests itself naturally in their mind," Rigel began, trying to sound as sure as possible, especially since Pomfrey seemed to be recording her word for word, "So from that I theorized that if my magical core was the same in my mind as it was in the real world, that is, since I could pull magical energy from the core in my mind the same as I could from my real core, then the two cores must be one and the same, connected, otherwise there would be no magical pathway for me to draw magic from my core into my mind. From there it was easy to see that my mind had a back door in the form of my magical core. So I could use that connection to get out of my mind."

"It is true that a person's mental core is a manifestation of their true core," McGonagall said slowly, "But I don't think I've ever heard of someone attempting to move between them."

"It is possible," Dumbledore said thoughtfully. "Because the magic moves from core to mind and back, a person's consciousness is able to move back and forth as well, with enough will power."

"Yes, but that does not apply to anyone else's magical core," Snape said, "It sounds as though you mean to say you projected your consciousness through your mental core to your physical core along the pathway that naturally exists between them. Then you used what I taught you about forging a connection between two cores to build a pathway between your core and Draco's, all while still maintaining your meditation status, I might add. While all of that would be theoretically possible if one ignores the fact that you are an eleven-year-old wizard who has had a wand less than a year and has been practising Occlumency for less than 6 months, that is as far as it goes."

Rigel frowned and opened her mouth to interject, but Snape held up a hand, "No, Mr. Black. I have many years of study in this discipline, and if you mean to suggest that you went on to project your consciousness into Draco's core, somehow using the natural connection between his core and mind to gain access to it, then I must disagree on the grounds of impossibility. Such a thing cannot be done."

"But that's what I did," Rigel protested. She felt the sting of betrayal as Snape once again refused to believe she had done something she said she had. "I forged a connection between our cores just like you did that one time, and then instead of sending magic along it I sent my consciousness. From there I moved through Draco's primary core to his true core, and then into his mindscape. It was the only way I could think of to get in to help him with the sickness' barrier still protecting it from the outside."

"I am telling you, it isn't possible," Snape said patiently, with a slightly apologetic look to his face that only someone who knew him well (which was pretty much everyone in the room) would catch, "You must have done something else. I don't mean to accuse you of lying. Perhaps you thought you went through Draco's core, but—"

"Now, now, Severus," Professor Dumbledore said cheerfully, "If this is what Mr. Black assures us is the truth, then we ought not to dismiss it too lightly."

"It is not for the sake of levity that I dismiss this," Snape said, glaring, "If Mr. Black had truly done what he said, the consequences would have been disastrous. For Draco."

Rigel paled and Draco looked confusedly between his friend and his godfather.

"Draco, cast a spell," Narcissa said abruptly. They turned to look at her, but she was staring very intently into her husband's eyes. Mr. Malfoy was glaring back, and the two seemed to be having some sort of silent argument. When Draco hesitated, Narcissa tore her gaze from her husband's and said, "Now, Draco. Any spell will do."

Mr. Malfoy clenched his jaw but turned to look at Draco as well. Draco straightened and pulled out his wand quickly. Apparently he had enough experience with his parents to know that now was not a time to disobey them. Draco pointed his wand at the cup that was sitting on the little side table next to Rigel's bed. A moment and a muttered incantation later, the cup morphed seamlessly into a silver snuffbox.

"Very nice," McGonagall commented approvingly.

Draco looked back at his parents, who were exchanging another long, though significantly less heated, look.

"Oh, for Salazar's sake, Lucius," Snape said, "I could have told you that Draco's core has in fact not been damaged. I was just in your son's mind, if you recall. That is why I maintain that Black could not have forced his way through it."

Rigel wanted to say that she hadn't forced her way through it, she had asked, but she didn't think anyone would listen to her at this point, and she didn't want to make herself sound crazier than she already did. She knew how other witches and wizards saw magic, after all; as a tool, not an entity in its own right.

"But that is what happened," Draco spoke up. Everyone turned to look at him, and he flushed delicately, "At least, that's what it seemed like. I was in my mind by myself one moment, and then the next Rigel was coming out of my magical core. How could have he gotten in there without going through it?"

There was silence as the others mulled that over.

"Well, putting that aside for now, perhaps Mr. Black should continue his story?" Madam Pomfrey suggested hesitantly.

"There's not much to tell after that," Rigel said, "After I got through Draco's core, I saw Draco, and together we fought off the sickness until Professor Snape arrived to get rid of it completely."

Draco nodded his agreement, "Apparently all that work we did was for nothing, though, because Unc…ah, the Professor sent it off in about a second."

"How exactly did you engage the sickness?" Madam Pomfrey asked clinically.

"We just sent our magic at it," Rigel said, "It's destroyed on contact when it touches magic, I think, which is probably why it left Draco's magical core alone even when it had covered the rest of his mind."

"You mean to say that you, too, could use magic while you were in Mr. Malfoy's mind?" Dumbledore clarified.

"Yes, Professor," Rigel said.

"Well, I'd say that certainly argues in favour of Mr. Black's actually being there, wouldn't you?" Dumbledore smiled at her, and Rigel blinked back, glad that someone believed her but not sure how genuine the Headmaster was in general. Then again, anyone who went along with one of the twins' pranks had to be okay, so she smiled slightly back.

Snape sent Dumbledore an exasperated look, "Albus, I want to believe Mr. Black. In fact I," he paused, and sent her a long look, "I have in the past dismissed his claims when they seemed fantastic, to my own detriment. But this time…it simply isn't possible. If wizards could go into each other's magical cores, affect them to the extent that Mr. Black proposes, they would. They don't, because it can't be done."

"Indeed," Mr. Malfoy was looking at Rigel as though he didn't quite know what to make of her, "A wizard's magic is one of the few things he can depend on in this world. If another wizard were to have free access to it as Mr. Black claims…well, the consequences would be enormous. Ordinary wizards wouldn't bother shooting spells at one another; they'd simply attack their opponent's magical core directly and be done with it."

"Perhaps," Dumbledore suggested, "Instead of enumerating the reasons Mr. Black's account cannot be possible, we should wonder instead how Mr. Black is able to do what is, for other wizards, certainly impossible."

Snape opened his mouth, but glanced at Rigel and snapped it shut again. His eyes pierced her, and he said, "It would not be the first time I have been mistaken when it comes to you, Mr. Black, and I doubt it would be the last. Instead of arguing about this, why don't we test it?"

"A wonderful idea, Severus," Narcissa said, looking rather glad to be sitting down during all this, "It's a wonder anything gets done around here with all you scholars waxing theoretical all the time." She smiled in a way that probably made a lot of people underestimate her as she spoke, and Rigel made a mental note to always assume Narcissa Malfoy was twice as clever as she acted, at least.

"How shall we go about it?" Minerva asked practically, "We didn't notice anything while Rigel was apparently in Draco's mind, and we were all sitting right here."

"Ah, my dear Minerva, we did not know what to look for before," Dumbledore said, "I think that this test will be most illuminating. Yes, now who shall we…?"

"Can I wake Pansy up?" Rigel asked immediately. Draco sent her an approving look.

"I don't see why not," Dumbledore agreed. "Let us adjourn to Miss Parkinson's bedside, then."

Rigel slipped from the bed, noticing as she did so that the only thing missing from her attire was her shoes, which were tucked neatly under the end of the bed. She moved down to Pansy's bedside and sat in the chair Dumbledore obligingly conjured for her.

"I don't know how long it will take," Rigel said, looking toward Snape, "Can you wait ten minutes, then try Legilimency every two minutes?"

Snape inclined his head, "Lucius, Albus, you two will monitor any magical connection formed between the two children?"

"Indeed, I know just the spell," Albus said, looking excited, "It was originally invented by a Russian puppet dancer who wanted to make his dolls come alive by transferring the consciousness of various people who came to his shows into…ah, right, well, the point is it tracks the consciousness it is directed at. If you will permit me…" He pointed his wand at Rigel and her whole body lit up like it was glowing a faint blue colour. "Now, if this works as you told us, the light should change so that it encompasses only your mind, then just your magical core, then to Miss Parkinson's magical core, and then to Miss Parkinson's mind, and so on. Ready, Mr. Black?"

Rigel nodded and relaxed her physical body as best she could. She fell into the familiar meditation mode, falling, falling into her mindscape. It was as chilly as ever on her mountain. Harry wondered vaguely why her mind was actually cold when Draco's didn't feel cold at all despite all that ice, but then she was moving as quickly as she could through her mind toward her magical core. She was careful to close the door to the Space Room behind her, in case anyone thought to take advantage of her being out of her mind, so to speak, and took a moment to make sure her eyes were a flat grey before she dove once more into the bright burning sun at the centre of her mind.

She followed the same path as before, but she didn't hesitate as much this time. Harry forged the connection between her core and Pansy's (and sent a pulse of energy along it to make sure it was, in fact, Pansy's), and then sent her consciousness shooting along the connection. She stopped at the outside of Pansy's core, which was shrouded in thick, green branches. Harry could actually smell pine and sap as she got closer, and the branches all seemed to be from different types of trees. She put a hand to the branches carefully, non-threateningly, and watched as the leaves curled around her hand and the branches parted just the tiniest bit. Vines wrapped around her and seemed to pull her in deeper. She leaned forward into the thick meshing of branches and leaves, seeing nothing but green all around her as she got deeper, and then, through the branches, she saw something else. The leaves around her grew silver as she stepped through them, and when they parted she came to a clearing, ringed by silver coloured trees all around. At the centre of the clearing was a pool of liquid that shimmered in non-existent light. It looked like a pool of mercury, or liquid platinum. It was thick and syrupy, and the trees around the clearing seemed to drink from it. She could see their roots dipping into the edges of the pool, and all of the trees that drank from it grew silver and shimmering too.

Fascinated, she approached the little pool slowly, projecting good intent as best she could. It didn't so much as ripple, even when Harry dipped a toe into the metallic substance. It seemed to absorb the motion calmly, and Harry thought it definitely suited Pansy to have such an accepting magical core.

"I need to get through here, to help Pansy," she said to the pool respectfully, "Will you let me through?"

In response, the pool shimmered and shifted until silvery liquid steps formed at the edge of the pool leading down into the well of magic. Harry thanked the pool and stepped forward onto the stairs. She walked down into the pool, which drifted over her head like she was going into a molten tunnel that led to the bottom of the pool. She walked until she couldn't see the entrance and only then did a light appear on the other side.

Harry emerged in a peaceful little enclave. The pool of quicksilver substance smoothed out again behind her once she'd stepped all the way off of the stairs, and Harry glanced around. The clearing she was in had lush grass growing on the ground. It was surrounded on all sides by a thick layer of trees and tree branches, so much so that she couldn't see what lay beyond them. A patch of daisies was growing on one side of the forest clearing, and lying next to the patch on her stomach, idly stringing daisies together in a circlet, was Pansy.

"Pan," Harry called as she stepped across the clearing. Pansy looked over and froze, before a huge smile broke out over her face.

"Rigel!" Pansy got to her feet and greeted her like she was hosting a picnic, "What a pleasant surprise. You've grown your hair out. How are you?"

"I'm fine, Pan, and this is just how my hair is for my mental avatar. How are you doing?" Harry grinned at her blonde friend.

"As well as can be suspected, I suppose," she gestured vaguely toward the line of trees that Harry guessed hid the blackened portion of her mind, "What are you doing here?"

"Getting you out, of course. Not that this place isn't lovely," Harry glanced around the picturesque clearing, "But Draco and I need you in the real world."

"Draco?" Pansy asked, smiling hopefully.

"He's just fine, and woke up not long ago himself," Harry assured her, "Now we need to clear a path to the mists that border the outer edges of your mind. If we get a section of the mists cleared, Professor Snape can come in and banish the rest of the sickness from your mind."

"You mean that awful black oozing stuff? Yes, please," Pansy sighed, "It's just ruining the landscape. What do we have to do?"

"Well, we've so far just thrown magic at it," Harry shrugged sheepishly, "So whatever your magic does will probably help."

Pansy thought for a moment. "Alright," she said, "My magic is that pool, correct? I've been able to do some things, like grow grass and these daisies, so I'll see what I can do."

"Great," Harry said, "Also, don't be alarmed." She summoned a ball of fire to her hand, "I promise my magic won't char your landscape. It will set the sickness alight though, so it might seem like everything is on fire, but it isn't."

Pansy blinked, "Whatever you say, Rigel. Shall we?" So saying, she stared very hard at a patch of branches enshrouding their clearing until they shifted and moved apart. Beyond them lay a forest, blanketed in black, and Harry watched for a moment as Pansy summoned some of the mercury-like substance from the pool and sent it toward the black stuff. It moved gracefully, and much like Draco's waves seemed to dissolve the blackness it encountered instantly. Unlike Draco's water, it did so gently, almost teasingly, moving along in a strange and erratic dance that sent splashes of the silver liquid all over the place.

Harry followed, sending her fire where they met with a particularly dense section of black tar, but following Pansy's lead as far as direction. Soon they made it to the edge of the woods where the mists began, and Harry poured fires into the mist to evaporate the sickness out of it quickly.

A minute or two later, Snape was there with them, taking charge and willing the sickness away from Pansy's mind completely. He insisted on watching Harry go back through Pansy's core this time, so Harry obligingly approached the pond, which seemed to sense her intent and re-opened the passage, complete with shimmering stairs, for her to walk into. Harry waved to Snape and Pansy over her shoulder, both of whom were watching her departure with interest, and traveled back along the pathways until she was in her own head again and could exit her meditative state by walking into her own mind mists.

When she opened her eyes, Snape was already explaining what he'd seen to the others.

"…nothing I've seen a core do before. It practically invited him through…"

Rigel tuned him out in favour of focusing on Pansy, who had opened her eyes and was staring at the people standing around her bed with polite confusion. Draco stepped forward to grin brightly into their friend's face.

"You're awake," he said brightly, "Good thing too, because we need more people of good sense in this Hospital Wing." He lowered his voice conspiratorially, "The adults are having a hard time grasping how we got rid of the sickness, even though they've just done a spell that proved to them that Rigel was telling the truth, not to mention Snape was there both times to witness."

Pansy's brow lifted, but like the poised and prepared pureblooded woman she was, she merely inclined her head to Draco to show that she understood the situation and turned to the Malfoys, who were standing on Pansy's left side, "Hello Narcissa, I hope the day finds you in good health."

"It is I who should be concerned for your health, dear Pansy," Narcissa said, a smile in her eye, "I am truly glad to see you are recovered."

"All thanks to Rigel and Professor Snape, it seems," Pansy said, smiling warmly at Rigel and sending a look of thanks to Snape, who had finished recounting what he'd seen and was now paying attention to Pansy once more.

"Indeed it does," Dumbledore said jovially, "Well, things have certainly been explained to my satisfaction."

Snape and Mr. Malfoy shared a look that said 'satisfaction' would not have been the word they chose, but neither interrupted.

"Now all that's left to decide is how to wake the rest of the children up," Dumbledore continued, "I'm sure we can get several Legilimens from St. Mungo's here to help our Professor Snape—"

"A fine idea considering the likely reaction of three-quarters of the afflicted students at finding Severus in their minds," Minerva muttered.

"—but it appears young Mr. Black will be working by himself on his end of the cure," the Headmaster finished.

Rigel frowned dubiously. She was exhausted even with the Pepper-Up Potion from all the energy she expended in Draco's mind, fighting the sickness the hard way.

Madam Pomfrey settled it by breaking in firmly, "Not until tomorrow afternoon at the earliest. None of the other children are in immediate danger, and Mr. Black requires at least a day of no magic usage to recover his core levels."

"I can leave the Hospital Wing, though, can't I?" Rigel asked. At Pomfrey's disapproving look, she wheedled, "I don't need to be Quarantined anymore, and it would reduce the chances of me catching the sickness again from one of my other friends in here."

Surprisingly, Snape spoke up for her, "The boy has a point. It would not help his magic recovery at all to have to fight off another bout of the sickness tonight."

"Oh, very well," the nurse said, "But you will check in with me tomorrow morning, and you will not do anything strenuous tonight. That goes for you two as well," she glared at Pansy and Draco, "And no Quidditch."

"Yes, ma'am," Rigel said, smiling slightly. Draco and Pansy nodded their agreement just as readily.

"Wonderful," Dumbledore said, "I have a few letters to send now that this business is all cleared up, so if you will excuse me. Minerva, I may require assistance, if you wouldn't mind? Splendid. Mr. Malfoy, Mrs. Malfoy, I trust Severus can see you out when you go." The headmaster gave a little wave and strode out of the Hospital Wing with a spring in his step and a whistle on his lips. McGonagall followed him out, and Pomfrey went off to file her medical report on the Malfoy case.

Snape surveyed them all for a moment, then said, "My absence has caused many things to pile up in my office. Come and see me before you leave, Lucius, Narcissa. Mr. Black, I will see you back here tomorrow afternoon to begin waking patients. Until then, no brewing, and no homework. I shall negotiate your missed assignments with your other Professors and inform you of which ones you will complete. The same goes for you two as well, Mr. Malfoy, Miss Parkinson." He swept off purposefully, leaving the Malfoys, Pansy, and Rigel behind.

"I should get going as well," Pansy said demurely, "There are a few people who should be informed of my recovery, and I must write to my parents. Good day, Mr. Malfoy. Lovely to see you, Narcissa." She turned to Rigel and Draco, "I'll meet you guys at dinner."

"Give your mother my best, Pansy," Narcissa said. Pansy nodded and rose gracefully from her sickbed. Rigel rose from her seat as well and made to follow her, but Draco put a hand on her arm and shook his head slightly. Perplexed, Rigel relaxed her stance once more and turned to face the older purebloods.

"Mr. Black," Mr. Malfoy began stiffly, "No matter how it came about, the fact remains that were it not for your actions, Draco would be lost to us. For that the Malfoy family owes you a debt, of equal value to the life of our Heir."

"You may call upon us to fulfill this debt day or night, now or twenty years from now," Narcissa continued, "A blood debt you have sown, and blood ties you shall reap. For safeguarding the life of our son where none other stepped forward, you, Rigel Black, shall be made a son in magic as though you were a son in blood, until such time as the debt that lies between us is fulfilled."

Rigel looked between the two adults. Narcissa's face was solemn and Mr. Malfoy's expression was harshly set. Both gazed silently at her, waiting for words she didn't know how to say.

"It means you're an honorary Malfoy," Draco leaned over beside her to explain quietly, "It's family tradition that when the life of either the Malfoy patriarch or the scion is owed to someone outside of the family, that person becomes a part of the family in spirit until the debt is fulfilled. You now have the informal social position of a Malfoy, and access to all of our connections and holdings." Rigel stared at Draco with what she knew was an expression of disbelief warring with overwhelming shock. He nudged her gently, "It's a matter of honour, and more importantly, blood. You have to accept formally. Go on."

Rigel turned back to Draco's parents and swallowed. She felt something hot in her gut that was part embarrassment, part shock, and part shame. Would they be so keen to appease their honour by inviting her into their family if she was a halfblood? And what would Sirius think when he heard that his son was rubbing elbows with the Malfoys? Then again…Rigel thought about the pained and almost desperate looks on the Malfoys' faces when Madam Pomfrey had told them Draco rejected the coma-sustaining potions he needed to last out the sickness. She thought about the good she might be able to do with the advantage of the Malfoy name. Archie could get a job in any Hospital he wanted with a Malfoy backing. The Black name was nothing to sneeze at, of course, but aside from volunteering in the children's ward from time to time, Sirius was a veritable recluse since Diana died. Rigel's uncle had nowhere near the connections the Malfoys had, and while Rigel didn't approve of the way the Malfoys went about acquiring those connections, she could not, as a Slytherin, deny their potential usefulness. And a life debt? Rigel was all too aware of how likely it was that someone in her position—that is, someone playing a dangerous game with even more dangerous people—would have a use for just such a debt.

"My actions were in the service of a friend," Rigel said carefully, "And not initiated with an ulterior purpose in mind. I accept the debt between us only with the understanding that I will never take advantage of your family's honour, and with the hope that I will not become a burden to the Malfoy name. It is my wish that this debt not hang between us, heavy and awkward, but rather that it be set from our minds and forgotten until such time as it becomes relevant once more."

Mr. Malfoy inclined his head slowly, "Well spoken, Mr. Black."

"Though your own family of course has the greater claim," Narcissa added, "We hope that you will come to naturally think of us as your secondary family. We don't mean to replace the ones already in your life, but instead to add to that life as best a family can."

Rigel's smile was small, but genuine, "Thank you, Mr. Malfoy, Mrs. Malfoy. In truth I have already begun to think of Draco as my brother, and surely no one could ask for a better second family than yours."

"Please, just call me Narcissa," Narcissa said, effectively breaking the tension in the room with a teasing smile, "All this Mr. and Mrs. doesn't feel very familial, now does it?"

"I suppose not, my lady," Rigel said, willing to forgo the Mrs. but not quite up to actually calling Draco's mother 'Narcissa' yet. "Well, I shall leave you to Draco, then. I hope the next time we meet is under more pleasant circumstances."

"Circumstances would be hard pressed to become worse," Mr. Malfoy said, and he seemed to have unfrozen just a fraction, "Good day, Mr. Black."

"Good day," Rigel told them, and sent Draco a 'see-you-later' grin before leaving the Hospital Wing as quickly as was polite. She had letters to write before a certain uncle of hers got any ideas about charging up to Hogwarts and checking on his son. Not that she thought he would be allowed to. She was pretty sure Dumbledore was keeping all the parents away with the excuse of the necessary Quarantine. The Malfoys were probably only let into the school because their son was in serious mortal danger, unlike the other children. Still, Sirius deserved a letter now that she was able to write one.

Dear Sirius—

No, no, that wasn't right.

Dear Dad,

I bet by now you've gotten some appropriately vague and unsatisfying letter from the school saying I was admitted to the Hospital Wing for the past few days or some such. I'm sure you've seen the papers, and to be honest I was briefly afflicted with the sickness that's going around the school. Don't worry though, I'm perfectly fine, and in fact they've recently figured out a cure for the illness, so all the other kids are going to be fine, too.

Okay, okay. To be even more honest, I was the one who came up with the cure. It was sort of an accident how it happened, but they're giving me credit for it, and I have to help out with waking the other kids up from their enchanted sleeps, too. It's going to keep me so busy—when am I going to find the time for a good prank? Feel sorry for me? You should. When I stumbled upon the solution for this silly sickness, I ended up saving Draco Malfoy's life in the process. Don't get me wrong, I like Draco, but his parents went and made me an honorary Malfoy on account of the life debt they owe me or something. I don't think it actually means anything, I mean, I don't exactly want or need a second family when I've got you, do I? Anyway, one good thing is that this means the Cow Party can't use the sickness to undermine Dumbledore, right? There isn't any proof that they're the ones behind it, of course, but maybe it would help if you put out the word that the sickness was cured. Hint that Dumbledore played a strong role in the discovering of a cure if you can. I'll back it up, and since I came up with the cure, who's to gainsay me? Let Aunt Lily and Uncle Potter and Uncle Remus know that I'm okay too, won't you?

I can't wait to see you in June. Unless I fail all my finals because of the course work I missed and they keep me in summer school, but hey at least everyone else in my grade will fail too. Maybe they'll cancel final exams altogether. If you wanted to write to the Headmaster expressing your concern as a parent for your child's academic progress, perhaps emphasizing how unfair you think it would be to test the first-years who've been asleep since February on material they never covered, I certainly wouldn't complain. Don't get any funny ideas about coming up here to check on me once the Quarantine is lifted though. I love you, dad, but it would be so lame if my father had to come personally check up on me—they'd think I really was a Malfoy, instead of a Black, who everyone knows can stand just fine on their own two feet.

Anyway, I miss you tons (no one appreciates a good joke around here, except maybe the Weasley twins), and I fully expect you to pick me up at King's Cross in your most embarrassing outfit to make up for not coming and checking up on me in person. Just please don't bring the snakes.

Give my best to everyone,

Love,

-Your son

P.S- what do you want for your birthday? I just realized I better have it planned out before I come home, since it's in mid-June.

There. Rigel stopped the Dicto-quill. She'd down-played the sickness, done damage control on the whole Malfoy-life-debt thing she was still trying not to think about, and played the embarrassed teenager card to make sure Sirius didn't come up to the school. Now all she had to do was send it. She would write to Archie as well, letting him know that everything was okay, but that could wait until later in the week.

Rigel stood from where she'd been sitting on her bed in the dorm room. Draco hadn't come back, so he was probably still spending some time with his parents. Theo, of course, was still in the Hospital Wing, but even so she retreated into the bathroom before changing into clothes she hadn't been wearing for three days straight. It wouldn't do to develop habits that weren't conducive to her secret-keeping after all.

She left the first-year dorms and was crossing through the common room to the false-wall entrance when someone called her name from a couch near one of the fireplaces.

"Black!"

Rigel turned her head. It was Flint. She slowed, then changed direction to walk over to him. He was sitting with Adrian Pucey and Lucian Bole, probably talking Quidditch. "What is it, Flint?" she asked, nodding to Adrian, who she knew, and giving Bole a polite look as well.

Flint smirked up at her, "Perhaps you can help us with something, Mr. Black. You see, not long ago we saw a girl who looked remarkably like Pansy Parkinson stroll through here. Now normally we would assume we were mistaken, as it is common knowledge that Miss Parkinson fell prey to the sickness on Thursday afternoon, but this girl was walking with Aldon Rosier and Edmund Rookwood, who are known to be close associates with Parkinson."

Rigel looked at Flint rather blankly, knowing what he wanted her to say, but not going to say it until he asked.

"So you see our conundrum," Flint went on blithely, "How is it that a girl who should by all rights be laid up in Quarantine is walking around the school with a skip in her step when Adrian here saw her collapse himself?"

Rigel smiled very slightly, "Why Flint, didn't you know? The sickness has been cured."

"Cured?" Pucey leaned forward with interest, "Are you sure?"

"Quite," Rigel said, "I was there when Pansy woke up, and Draco's awake as well. The other kids will start returning to their Houses tomorrow, I believe."

"How was it cured?" Bole asked, his eyes narrowed thoughtfully, "Was it Snape? He's been gone for a while. Was he researching a cure?"

Rigel tilted her head to the side, "Yes, Professor Snape was instrumental to the cure. He went on a trip to get supplies for some potions he was brewing for the victims of the sickness, and when he came back the illness was cured." Technically, Rigel thought to herself, that was all true.

"Interesting that Parkinson and Malfoy would be the first two to be cured," Flint remarked, a mocking glint in his eye.

"Yes," Pucey said, "You'd think they'd wake up the ones who'd been under the illness the longest first."

"Snape wouldn't want his godson to be afflicted a moment longer than he had to," Bole said dismissively, "And I hear Snape is good friends with the Parkinsons too."

"If that's the case those poor Hufflepuffs will never be woken up," Pucey said sadly, fighting a grin.

"A shame the sickness was stopped before it had time to infect the whole Ravenclaw Quidditch team, eh Flint?" Bole added.

Flint grunted, "No need. We'll crush them in the final match either way. All the better if they're conscious enough to see it."

Rigel lifted a mental eyebrow. She hadn't been paying much attention to Quidditch since she started brewing for Snape, but she supposed the season would be coming to a close soon.

"Oh, and Black?" Flint brought her out of her thoughts, "That letter you were supposed to send for me? Don't worry about it."

Rigel frowned, but quickly realized he meant the assignments she was supposed to be completing. She thought she was caught up, but there were probably a bunch due on Monday that she hadn't even gotten from him yet.

"No, I'll send it," she said, "Just remind me tonight."

"Didn't you hear me?" Flint frowned, "I said you don't need to—"

"I'll send it," Rigel said firmly. She wasn't going to give him any wriggle room in the Vows they had taken, whether he meant to be kind or not, "Really, Flint, I said I would do it so I will. A Black doesn't go back on his word."

Flint narrowed his eyes at her, but Pucey and Bole were beginning to look at them strangely, so he shrugged, "As you will, Black."

"If that's all?" she asked, "Actually I'm going to the Owlery now if you want to get your letter." It was a bit of a risk handing off the assignments in person, but if she wanted to get them done by Monday she should get started tonight. Who knew how long she would be working with Snape and Pomfrey tomorrow.

"Alright," Flint said, getting up, "Wait here." He stalked off to his dorm room and came back quickly with a roll of parchment tied securely. Rigel tried not to fidget under the curious stares of the other two Slytherin Quidditch players as she took the scroll and tucked it into her robes.

"See you around, Flint. Pucey. Bole," Rigel nodded to each of the upperclassmen, who either nodded or waved back, and left the common room, heading for the Owlery.

Rigel spent the rest of the evening, save dinner which was a very uncomfortable affair involving numerous stares from the people around Draco, Pansy, and Rigel who didn't know the sickness had been cured, working on Flint's assignments. There were indeed several due on Monday, and Rigel thanked Merlin she had kept up on the extra essays she did for Flint before she'd gotten sick and subsequently spent two days in meditation. She hadn't missed one, but if she'd waited until the weekend was over to get those assignments she would have missed three. She was lucky Flint reminded her, and she told herself she would keep up on the assignments in the future so that if something unexpected came up again she wouldn't risk reneging on their agreement by default.

She managed to finish all three essays that night, though she relied heavily on the Map to make it back from mailing the assignments in the Owlery without running into any teachers after curfew.

The next morning, she, Pansy and Draco met up at the Hospital Wing to get checked over by Madam Pomfrey. The nurse reluctantly proclaimed them fit, and Rigel was told to come back that afternoon to start helping Snape wake up the other students.

"Let's go outside," Draco said suddenly as they were walking out of the Wing, "We've been cooped up too long. I don't know about you guys, but I don't think my mindscape counts as fresh air."

"Good idea," Pansy said, "We're probably all due some vitamin D no matter what Pomfrey says. Especially you, Rigel. You haven't been out of the potions lab much in the past few months."

Rigel nodded agreeably. It would be nice to get out of the castle and remember that the rest of the world still existed beyond the sickness.

They strolled across the grounds, not going anywhere, just enjoying the sun and one another's company.

"You know my parents have invited you to the manor this summer," Pansy remarked to Rigel as they walked, "Draco will be over several times I imagine, but my father invited you specifically, Rigel. I wrote him about how you cured me of the sickness, and he is very interested to further his acquaintance with you."

"What exactly did you tell him?" Rigel asked uncomfortably. Snape had told her not to downplay what she'd done, but on the other hand every ounce of attention on her added to the likelihood that someone would see through her pretense. Pansy's father had struck her as an extremely intelligent and frankly ruthless kind of man, and that was exactly the kind of a man she didn't want to get to know too well.

"Why, the truth, of course," Pansy said innocently, "That you were fulfilling the promise you made over Christmas break to look after my best interests admirably."

Rigel didn't remember actually promising to do anything, but she did remember Mr. Parkinson saying something about her duty as a friend to Pansy, and she supposed she'd tacitly agreed. Still. "Pan, I'd rather not make everyone think I'm some kind of hero, or super-powered wizard, or genius or something. I was lucky Snape had taught me enough this semester to guess my way through the whole thing, and I'm afraid if people make too big a deal out of this they'll expect me to be something I'm not."

"Something you're not?" Pansy raised her eyebrows, "Rigel, you are all those things, though maybe not in the way you mean. You did save Draco's life, on purpose or accident, so you're a hero by default. You also did something that apparently should have been impossible, twice, so technically you do have some sort of power that most wizards would consider extraordinary."

"And everyone knows you're a genius at potions," Draco put in, "How many first-years are competent enough to take over for Snape when he's out of the country?"

Rigel shrugged, "I guess. I just want to make potions, though. I don't want to be some great famous wizard, and if people start expecting things like that from me now, they'll only be disappointed later on."

"So let them be disappointed," Draco said like it was the most obvious thing in the world, "Who cares what they think? Just live your life how you want, Rigel, but don't deny something when it's so obvious. You are great, whether you like it or not."

Rigel smirked and simpered, "Aww, Dray, I think you're great too."

"Me too," Pansy giggled, "So great."

"Shut up," Draco scowled, but the corner of his mouth was twitching.

They laughed, teased Draco, and laughed some more. Pansy told them she had finally gotten her mum to agree to let her take cooking lessons over the summer, and Draco said his father was going to get him the new Nimbus broom before September. Rigel promised she would try and convince her dad to let her see them that summer. They were outside so long that when they came back in, the Great Hall was already empty.

"We missed lunch," Draco frowned.

"Madam Pomfrey's not going to be happy with us skipping meals," Pansy added.

Rigel cocked her head, considering, "You know, I just realized you guys have never been to the kitchens."

"Have you?" Pansy asked curiously.

"Come on," Rigel said, turning and heading for the stairs that would take them to the basement level, "I should have shown you anyway."

"Yes, you should have," Draco said, looking torn between curiosity and indignation, "You never tell us anything, Rigel."

"It's his nature," Pansy patted Draco's arm sadly, "Unless he's been hit with a jelly-brains jinx, our Rigel is as closed-mouthed as a clam."

Rigel ducked her head, not thrilled to be reminded of that particular incident.

Draco chuckled, "I remember that." He put on an incredibly wondering tone and said, "'The sky is going to rain honey tomorrow.'"

Rigel rolled her eyes a bit, "I did not say that."

Pansy joined in, snickering, "You did so. 'Oh, are you an angel, Malfoy?'"

Rigel nudged them each with an elbow, "Alright, you two. We're here, so stop making fun of me or you'll embarrass me in front of Binny."

"Binny?" they repeated blankly.

Rigel shook her head and reached up to tickle the pear. She turned the doorknob and led the way through the portrait hole. There was a moderate amount of activity, mostly centred around the sinks, and Rigel supposed they were cleaning the dishes from lunch. Draco and Pansy climbed in behind her, looking around with interest at the cavernous underground kitchen.

Rigel had barely closed the door behind her when a familiar house elf with a necklace of champagne corks skipped up to them.

"You is back, Young Sir!" Binny said cheerfully, smiling up at her before turning to the other two and sweeping them a curtsy with her pink doily, "Welcome to the kitchens, Young Miss and Young Sir. I is Binny. Is you needing anything today?"

"I'm afraid we missed lunch today on accident, Binny," Rigel explained, "Is there any food left?"

Binny giggled, "There is always food. Come and sit, Young Sirs and Miss." She gestured them over to a long table before bustling off to find food for them, and Pansy and Draco sat with raised eyebrows.

"Come here much, do you?" Draco said wryly, "I always thought you were so skinny because you skipped meals, but if you've been coming here to get food you must be naturally miniscule."

"You're only about an inch taller than me, Draco," Rigel pointed out, "And I'm taller than Pansy."

"Pansy's a girl, no offence Pans," Draco said.

Pansy shrugged, "Why would I take offence? It's a compliment to be a recognized female. He does have a point though," Pansy eyed Rigel sceptically, "You really should eat more or something."

Rigel smiled, "My aunt Lily will fatten me up when I go home, don't worry." In truth, she was frowning inside. She didn't think she was that small for her age, but she knew that in the coming years the difference between herself and the other boys her age would become more obvious. She made a mental note to think on that problem over the summer.

Binny came back with a selection of meats, cheeses, and for Rigel a salad with a side of strawberries. "Is you wanting anything else?"

"This is lovely, thank you, Binny," Pansy said politely. Draco looked at her askance and Pansy stepped on his foot beneath the table.

"Oh! Ah, yes, Binny, everything looks great," Draco fumbled, shooting hurt looks at Pansy.

"Young Miss and Sir is being too kind," Binny said happily, "You is coming back often, yes?"

"We shall certainly try," Pansy said, "Though the school year is almost over."

"Binny is being here always," the house elf shrugged, "If you is coming next year, then I is seeing you next year. Good day, Young Sirs and Miss."

"Bye, Binny," Rigel said, "Thanks."

The house elf waved off her thanks and went back to the sinks. The three first-years dug into their late lunch and chatted about the end of the Quidditch season coming up. Draco suggested that Rigel could win the game single-handedly for them by making her patented baby-owl face at the Gryffindor team, and Pansy suggested Draco could win the game single-handedly by distracting the Gryffindor team with a well-timed fainting spell, to which Draco hotly replied that perhaps if Pansy would work on her feminine wiles a little more she could be the distraction. Rigel was really going to miss her friends when she went home, though she had to admit she was looking forward to the end of term.

After they'd eaten, Rigel and her friends parted and she headed up to the Hospital Wing to meet Snape and Pomfrey. She walked into the Wing to find the two adults already waiting for her.

"Ah, Mr. Black," Pomfrey bustled her over to the far end of the Wing, where the patients who'd been there the longest were sleeping, "Good, now we can begin."

Snape explained what they would be doing. Rigel was to use her ability to cross through people's magical cores to go into each child's mind and first explain to them what was happening if they were confused, then help them clear a path to the mists. Snape would wait five minutes then begin periodically checking the mental barriers the sickness erected for weakness, so that he could enter the child's mind and clear the sickness out completely. Once they had a better idea of how quickly she worked on average, he wouldn't have to check so often, and once Rigel got the hang of things Snape would go back to his work as a Potions Master and professor and they would call in an Occlumens from St. Mungo's to help Rigel wake the rest.

Rigel was once again excused from classes for the duration of her work in the Hospital Wing, and she wondered how she would ever catch up in her classes for finals in a couple of months if she missed so much school.

So every day for the next two and a half weeks, Rigel went to the Hospital Wing and broke into people's minds. The first day was the worst. The children she woke first had been trapped in their minds the longest, over two months for most of them, and as a result were rather skittish when she suddenly appeared in their mindscape. Most of them didn't understand what was going on, as when they had fallen sick no one really knew much about the sickness, so they weren't even aware of what had happened to them. Rigel had to explain everything, as calmly as she could, which took a lot of time. She then had to convince the students that she was trustworthy, or in some cases even real, because unlike Draco and Pansy, these kids didn't know her and had no reason to let her toss fire around in their mindscapes without an explanation. Usually they were more at ease once Snape appeared and banished the blackness from their minds, but getting to that point took more out of her than actually fighting off the blackness with her magic did. She was getting tired of explaining the same thing over and over, despite how necessary it was to be as kind and patient with the poor confused students as she could be.

That's not to say it was a boring job. In fact, it was fascinating. Each and every one of the students had a different magical core, and a different mindscape. Even kids she'd never talked to in any of her classes before seemed like good acquaintances by the time she exited their minds. She just felt like she knew them after experiencing their magical cores and exploring their mindscapes, though she knew most of them didn't recognize her in her mental avatar form, and were very surprised to find she was a Slytherin first-year upon waking up.

One Ravenclaw had a magical core that felt like a windstorm, with a tornado at its heart. A second-year Hufflepuff had a mindscape like a tropical island, with a huge volcano in the centre that was the link to her magma-core. She'd been in her mindscape so long that she had actually mostly beaten the sickness back to the water's edge of her island, and used her magic to plant bright, colourful flowers along the sides of her volcano in complicated patterns. Another Ravenclaw told her blankly that the 'black stuff' crawling all over his mind didn't really bug him. He'd created a thick cloud with his magic and spent his time lounging about on it, occasionally tossing a lightning bolt, the manifestation of his magical core, down to the ground beneath him for fun. She got to see Neville's carefully tended mental greenhouse, which he proudly told her was blooming already, though he'd only started building it out of boredom a few weeks ago. Rigel met Ron in his scorching mindscape, which was a great desert. He told her that he'd gone to Egypt to see his brother at work a year before and had loved the desert immediately, though his actual core was a water element, manifesting in a little oasis.

Some kids, like Ron, or like Millicent, had figured out how to manipulate their magic against the sickness already, but had been unable to eradicate it fully because they lacked the stamina. These she merely had to point in the right direction, and they did most of the work clearing a path to their mists for her. Others had little or no conscious control over their mental magic and sometimes created things on instinct or out of extreme boredom, but were mostly no help in disrupting the mental barrier around their minds from within. Nevertheless, no matter how much or little help they were, no matter how easy or difficult it was to get their cooperation, Rigel kept at it. She treated each and every kid whose mind she entered with respect and patience, and by the time she was waking the last students up at the end of the two and a half weeks, word had spread throughout the school that the youngest Black, first-year Slytherin, was the one who'd been curing everyone of the sickness.

Everywhere she went, classmates and even a few teachers stared. It wasn't that noticeable when she was still working in the Hospital Wing with Pomfrey and Gina Whitefield, the Occlumens St. Mungo's had sent to replace Snape, but when Rigel finally resumed classes with the other first-years, the attention became obvious. Mostly the stares were curious, excited, grateful, interested, or some combination thereof, but Rigel didn't miss the looks that were puzzled, sceptical, calculating, and cautious either. There were whispers that she must have some kind of strange power, to be able to do something none of the teachers could do, and suggestions that her innocuous appearance was all a mask, but in spite of the suspicions of a few, most of the school was in better spirits than it had been all semester, and the prevailing opinion, according to Pansy, was that Rigel Black was to thank for it. And thank her they did.

She no longer received nasty looks when she went to the Gryffindor common room looking for Percy to study with, and more than a few of their Ravenclaw and Hufflepuff classmates found time to stop by Rigel's desk or table and thank her personally for helping them get rid of the sickness. Even upperclassmen would sometimes send her serious, thankful looks or nods, as it seemed almost everyone in the school had known someone in the younger years who had fallen ill, be it a team-member, younger sibling or cousin, or just a fellow Housemate.

All the attention was, quite frankly, driving her mad.

Rigel didn't want to be the school's latest darling. She didn't want people she'd never met before coming up to her in the hall and patting her on the back fondly. She didn't like the way Headmaster Dumbledore twinkled at her merrily as he awarded Slytherin House sixty points for her assistance in ridding the school of the miserable sickness for good. Rigel especially didn't like the way even her own Housemates had begun treating her differently. Draco and Pansy didn't, of course, but the others all changed their attitudes toward her just slightly after they'd woken up. Davis and Greengrass avoided her entirely. Blaise sometimes sent her intense, brooding looks when he thought she couldn't see him staring at her. Millicent and Theo had started treating Rigel like a general or advisor of some kind, always asking her opinion on things and taking every word she said very seriously, as if she were some wise old guru. She was sick of the way people always looked at her when something interesting or challenging came up in class, as though she should be involved somehow.

When she couldn't take it anymore, she turned to the only thing that ever made sense to her. Potions. Rigel went to her lab and brewed whatever potion came to mind. Potions weren't complicated, she told herself soothingly as she worked. There was nothing abstract or unpredictable about them. When you got the recipe right, it worked, and when the formula didn't mesh, the potion flopped. Simple, reliable, and not at all extraordinary.

It wasn't that Rigel didn't want to be extraordinary. She did. She wanted to be the greatest Potions Mistress there ever was, and that would be something quite extraordinary indeed. What she didn't want was extraordinary attention and expectations before she'd even gotten to the point where she could let herself be extraordinary. Right now she was vulnerable. A minor, a liar, weaving a dangerous fiction over every inch of her life, and a criminal in the most technical definition of the word. She couldn't afford attention now, when someone looking too close would have such disastrous effects, and so she retreated into her potions lab, made excuses about missed schoolwork and studying to isolate and protect herself from all but her closest friends, and waited with bated breath for the school year to end. She just wanted to be Harry again, just for a little while. She wanted to talk to her mum, whom she hadn't exchanged two words with since Christmas unless they were relayed through Sirius. She wanted to talk magical theory with Remus and relax with Archie in his dad's courtyard (even with the snakes) and play Quidditch with her dad and Uncle Sirius. She needed a break from all the confusion and intensity that hovered about her at Hogwarts. She needed to go home.

So she brewed, and stewed, and waited.

Near the end of April, she finally got a letter back from Sirius. She took it with her to the Library where she needed to check out a few books on advanced Herbology for one of Flint's essays. It burned a hole in her concentration all through the half-hour she spent looking up information on the chemical composition of flesh-eating pest repellant, and it was with trembling hands that she shut Caring For Your Crops and took out the roll of parchment sealed with the Black family crest.

If Sirius had decided to come to the school regardless of her wishes, she was done. She had a stash of Polyjuice for June that she could use, but anyone besides her father would immediately realize she didn't look quite like Rigel. She and her cousin looked a lot alike, especially with the short hair and the contacts, but the difference was still noticeable, and there was no way she would somehow be able to see only Sirius and no one else while Sirius was here. It just wouldn't work. What she needed was some sort of conditional illusion, where a person saw different things depending on how the illusion recognized and targeted them, but she hadn't learned how to do anything like that.

Rigel broke the seal with the thought that even if Sirius expressed his intention to come and see her in person she'd have time to at least get out of the school and meet him on her terms to explain. Better to be expelled than to be revealed and put into prison. She took a steadying breath, mentally prepared to meet whatever was in the letter with all the cunning and guile that got her into Slytherin.

Hey Arch,

I won't pretend I'm not upset with you. When I read that article in the paper I was scared half to death. The only thing that stopped me from storming the school and screwing the Quarantine was the fact that it was the Prophet that reported it. Everyone knows you can't trust what that old dishrag says, and Malfoy's endorsement convinced me even less. I thought, if there really was something to be concerned about, Archie would have told me. After what we went through with your mother, I thought you of all people would know better than to keep something like a sickness to yourself. I understand that you didn't want to worry me, but I ended up being worried anyway and it would have been better if I could have at least had the comfort of knowing my son had been well enough to write to me. All of us were upset and confused when we got your letter. Dumbledore didn't send us any sort of letter about you getting sick, so to hear about it from you after the fact, once it was too late to do anything about it, was very upsetting. What if you hadn't been able to write to us? What if you hadn't gotten well? Would we have only heard of your death after the fact, too? I sent a few letters back and forth with Dumbledore and he explained things to me. I get now that you didn't actually ever succumb to the sickness, and since you didn't appear to be in danger Dumbledore didn't feel the need to inform me, but dammit Archie I shouldn't have to rely on the headmaster like all the other parents with crappy relationships with their kids do. I should have heard it from you. We expect this kind of thing from Harry, but you've always told me everything. I don't know what's happened since you went away to school, but I hate the feeling that we've grown apart so much that you don't even tell me when you're in trouble. I want to help you, Archie, but I can't do that if you pull away so much.

I'm not trying to lecture you, pup, you know I'm no good at that. I'm sorry it took so long to write back to you, but I needed some time to get my words straight. I was really frustrated when I read your letter, but Moony helped calm me down. James tried to help, but I admit I didn't listen to him as well as I should have. I guess I'm a bit jealous to be honest. He and Lily get letters from Harry every week, and I keep thinking how unfair it is that going away to school has improved their relationship with their kid, but it's done just the opposite for us. I know you didn't want to go to Hogwarts, Arch. I'm sorry, okay? The whole reason I didn't want you to go to America was that I was afraid of letting you get too far away from me, but I guess that was for nothing if you feel like you can't talk to me anymore. So here's the deal. I'm not angry, and I'm really only a little disappointed in you. I just want you to know that no matter how far apart we get, you can always tell me anything. You know that, right? I know you're growing up, and that's fine with me (though I'm sure I don't know why you would want to), but just know that you can always turn to me if you really need help. Even if you don't really need help. I'll be here.

I also want you to know how proud we are that you're finding ways to use your interest in Healing to help others even though you didn't get the Healing program you wanted. I believe you can do anything you put your mind to—you and Harry both, no matter where you go to school, and you've proven that by curing this sickness and saving your friend. The life debt with the Malfoys…well, we can discuss that this summer. It'll have some repercussions I'm not sure you've thought out, but I would never tell you it would have been better if you hadn't saved a life. I've been dropping certain conjectures into a few ears here and there, and I've hinted at Dumbledore's involvement too. I even gave an interview with the Prophet, so look out for that even though normally I'd tell you to stay far away from that trashy tabloid.

I'll be at King's Cross to pick you up from the train. Can't wait to see you this summer and check you over for alien probes. You can never be too careful. The snakes miss you. Moony sends his scolds, and also his exasperated look—no, wait, that one was for me. See you soon,

-Dad

Rigel rolled up the letter with a sunken heart. She felt worse than she had since Draco had fallen ill. How could she have been so stupid? Of course Sirius would expect more from his son, and of course she couldn't just pretend to sound like Archie in the tone of her letters and expect Sirius to be nice and fooled. Sirius and Archie were close, which was part of the reason Archie had to hide his going to America in the first place, and it wouldn't be enough to be falsely cheerful in her letters if she 1) only sent those letters every few months and 2) didn't include anything really important and personal in the letters. In acting like herself while pretending to be Archie, she'd hurt Sirius really bad, and probably strained Archie's relationship with his dad as well.

She took a shuddering breath and cradled her red-wigged head in her hands. She had to fix this somehow, and that meant writing a long letter to both Sirius and Archie. To Sirius she would explain that she still thought of him as her closest friend, didn't mean to hurt him, and apologize profusely, promising things would be different (or rather the same again) when she got home that summer. To Archie she would apologize as well, and tell him what she'd inadvertently done, hoping he'd forgive her. Rigel felt hot shame pool in her gut as she thought about her mistakes in the past couple of months. She should have told Sirius about the sickness immediately. She knew exactly how sensitive both Blacks were about illness of any kind, and keeping Sirius in the dark before springing it on him had been cruel and thoughtless.

But if she'd told him, he would have dragged her out of school before the Quarantine went up, she reminded herself. Sirius would have completely freaked out, understandably, and the ruse would have been over just like that. She really didn't want to worry him, and she'd only sent that letter because she'd figured Dumbledore had already sent one. Rigel supposed she hadn't technically ever fallen into a coma, so maybe Dumbledore had been justified in keeping Sirius from knowing, or maybe he knew as well as she did how Diana's death had affected Sirius, and didn't want to hurt him any more than she did if he didn't have to.

Still, Sirius was a grown man, for all that he acted with the exuberance of a child, and he deserved to be respected as such, and given the opportunity to make his own decisions. She'd done the same thing to Sirius that she'd done to Professor Snape—tried to spare him worry and pain and ended up treating him like a child. Dumbledore could get away with making decisions like that. Rigel could not.

Rigel rubbed her eyes beneath the fake glasses, feeling her contacts sticking slightly in her eyes. She'd have to put in a new pair soon, along with the numerous other things she was supposed to be doing. She stowed the rolled up letter in her bag and was about to stand and re-shelve the Herbology book when a sudden voice cut through the silence of the Library.

"Aha!"

Rigel glanced up with surprise to find a small finger pointing about an inch away from the bridge of her nose. She looked down the finger to the hand, arm, and person it was attached to and blinked up into the face of the second-year Ravenclaw she'd first met in March, and then again just a few weeks ago when she'd woken the girl up from the sickness. Rigel recalled that the girl's mind had been mountainous, but unlike Rigel's White Mountain, the Ravenclaw had several smaller mountains in her mind, interspersed with grassy knolls, and covered with wild wood orchids.

The Ravenclaw was pointing at her with what looked like elation and frustration mixed together, and Rigel raised an eyebrow at the older girl's accusing stance. She stood carefully, grabbing her bag and readying herself in case she had to run. Madam Pince was already looking over at them with a murderous glare.

"Cho Chang, right?" Rigel said, a polite note of question in her words.

"Yes, that's right," Cho said, retracting her pointing finger but still looking fiercely at her, "And just who are you?"

Rigel shifted, a bit taken aback. She'd thought the girl had recognized her, and if she hadn't then why was she talking to her?

"I'm Reggie," she said, "We met a few months ago—"

"Don't give me that!" Cho snapped, her long dark hair trembling slightly as she glared at Rigel, "I've been looking all over for you since that day you were so nice to me, but I couldn't find you anywhere!"

Rigel glanced over, and sure enough Madam Pince was standing, clearly about to come and throw them out. Rigel held up her hands placatingly and smiled at the fearsome librarian. She took Cho's elbow and whispered, "Come on, let's continue this discussion more quietly, not in the middle of the Library."

"Why?" Cho hissed, "Afraid someone else will figure it out?"

"I'm afraid Madam Pince will come kick us out," Rigel said, steering them to the secluded biography section, "Now explain what you're so worked up about, please."

The Ravenclaw took back her elbow and flipped her hair back huffily, "Why did you lie to me when I asked you your name? Who are you?"

"What makes you think I lied to you?" Rigel asked carefully, "I mean, just because you haven't seen me around doesn't mean anything. I mostly stick to my common room anyway."

"Oh, please," Cho rolled her eyes, "Do I look like a Gryffindor to you?" Rigel wondered if she should take offence on principle of the Gryffindor robes she was wearing, but Cho kept talking, "After I couldn't find you for a couple of weeks I checked the school registry Professor Flitwick keeps in his office. I checked all the grade levels, even though I knew you couldn't be more than a third year, and there is no Reggie anything in the whole school. There's a Reginald Turnblatt, but he's got blond hair, and he's a Hufflepuff besides. There's a Roger Davies in my House, but he looks nothing like you. I even thought it could be a nickname for a last name, but all the close R-names like Rochester and such have dark hair. The closest red-head is Ronald Weasley, but he has way more freckles and is significantly taller than you."

Rigel was looking at Cho in sheer shock by the time she'd finished, "You did all that research just to find somebody who you talked to once?"

She smiled a bit smugly, "Never underestimate a Ravenclaw. Ravens are notoriously tenacious when it comes to curiosity, as well as naturally opportunistic. Besides," her face lost some of its smugness and looked troubled for a moment, "You were really nice to me. I wanted to thank you properly, at least until I realized you'd lied to me about who you were." She was scowling again, "Seriously, what is up with that?"

Rigel sighed, scratching the back of the red wig she had on, "Well, it's sort of a long story."

"I like stories," Cho said bluntly.

"Ah, okay then. Well, as you've deduced my name isn't Reggie, and the reason I lied about that is because this isn't what I really look like. I'm here in disguise, and I didn't want to have to explain the whole reason why when I told you my real name, because it looks a bit suspicious for me to be walking around in robes that don't belong to me or even my House, disguising myself…" Rigel glanced sheepishly at Cho, who raised her eyebrows but gestured for him to continue. "So, the thing is Madam Pince sort of really hates me."

"What did you do?" Cho asked, frowning, "Did you do something to one of her books? Because you really shouldn't treat books so—"

"I didn't do anything!" Rigel exclaimed quietly, "I just walked in the first weekend of term and when she found out my name she flipped out. It turns out my father may have set fire to a few…rows of Divination books while he was here, and Pince decided to bar me from the Library on the suspicion that I would follow in my dad's footsteps. The problem is, I do a lot of extra studying, so I need to come into the Library, so I came up with the idea to disguise myself so that Madam Pince wouldn't recognize me and throw me out. I still can't actually check out books, because as you realized Reggie doesn't exist, but I can come here and look things up now."

Cho looked like she wasn't sure if she should laugh or not, "You're skulking around in disguise…to study? Are you a Ravenclaw?"

"No, I'm not a Ravenclaw," Rigel said nervously.

"You must be a Slytherin, then," Cho said decisively. "A Gryffindor would be brave enough to do it, and brash enough too, but you already admitted those weren't your real robes, so you must be a Slytherin."

"Uh, yeah I am," Rigel admitted. She winced a bit, waiting for Cho to stomp off, well aware of how Slytherins were perceived by most of the school.

"Huh," Cho said, "A Slytherin who's not afraid to waltz around in lion's robes. Interesting."

"You're not mad that I'm a Slytherin?" Rigel asked blankly.

Cho shrugged, "It would be pretty stupid to be mad at a quarter of the school just for being what they are, but I know what you mean. Normally I would be a bit leery of a Slytherin in disguise, because I really don't think you guys need an excuse to be sneaky, but a Slytherin did me a good turn recently, what with getting me out of my own head and all."

"So you're not going to rat me out to Madam Pince?" Rigel asked.

"I won't if you tell me your name," Cho said.

"I'm starting to think Ravenclaws are just the ones who were too smart for Slytherin," Rigel sighed, "You are one tricky girl."

"Thank you," Cho said.

"I'm Rigel," she told the older girl finally, "I'm a first-year Slytherin, and—"

"You're Rigel Black!" Cho exclaimed, staring at her, "Let me see." She reached forward to take off Rigel's wig with a snatch that tugged at the tucked strands of hair and made Rigel grit her teeth on a wince. Before she could recover, Cho plucked the glasses from her face and tilted her head interestedly, "Huh, well what do you know. You looked different with long hair, though."

"I cut it all off right before school started," Rigel said, "But I still kind of picture myself with long hair."

"I can't believe you're Rigel Black," Cho said, sounding almost disappointed, "You were so cool in my mindscape, like calm and collected, and here you are running around with red hair and Gryff robes and… did you draw those freckles on yourself?"

Rigel flushed and snatched the wig back from the Ravenclaw, "Maybe."

Cho laughed heartily, but reached forward to help Rigel straighten the wig once more and handed back her glasses nonetheless, "Man, that's too funny."

"Don't go telling people, please?" Rigel said, "I don't want it getting back to Pince."

"Oh, I won't," Cho said lightly, "I have a feeling this is going to be the kind of thing I'll want to be able to hold over your head when you're all grown up and famous."

Rigel rolled her eyes, "Why does everyone think I'm going to be famous?"

Cho looked at her incredulously, "Because you already are, at least here at Hogwarts. Every single kid who got sick, which is most of the first through third years at the school, knows exactly who woke them up and got them better."

"Professor Snape and a Mind Healer?" Rigel mumbled halfheartedly.

"We know who made it possible for us to be cured," Cho said seriously, "And none of us are ever going to forget that. Just you wait, Rigel Black. Your name will go down in history one way or another."

Rigel didn't say anything. She couldn't deny what Cho was telling her, but she was uncomfortably aware of how easily her name could go down in history 'another' way.

Rigel said goodbye to Cho and left the Library. She had several serious letters to write, and she'd promised she would help Draco with his Quidditch game after dinner. Thoughts of fame and infamy could wait.

On the sixth of May, Rigel was pulled into a very serious conversation with a very unlikely group of Slytherin upperclassmen.

Alesana Selwyn caught her elbow as she was walking through the common room and effectively hauled her over to a corner by the far fireplace where Rookwood, Rosier, and Flint were sitting on a couple of couches that had been pulled close to face one another, bent over something on the table in the centre and talking in low voices. "Come here, young Black, you might find something to interest you."

Rigel would like to say she allowed herself to be pulled toward the group, but in truth Selwyn was significantly stronger than she was, so there was no 'allowing' about it. Yet another thing she'd have to fix if she was going to pull off being a boy in the long run. The three older boys looked up at them as Selwyn, and Rigel by default, reached their group. They leaned back enough that Rigel could see what they were bent over. It was a newspaper, the Daily Prophet to be exact, and they seemed to have been discussing an article with great interest.

"Alice, so nice of you to join us," Rosier said smoothly, "And you've brought Mr. Black as well, how fortuitous."

"Why is that, Rosier?" Rigel asked politely.

"It's because we were just talking about you, Black," Flint grunted with amusement, shaking his head at Rosier's lofty manner.

"Surely three such interesting upperclassman such as yourself have something better to talk about," Rigel said rather dryly, "Don't you have final exams to study for or something?" Probably she should be more respectful, but she was running out of her infinite patience as the school year drew to a close. She just wanted to rest for a moment away from all the lies and intrigues. Usually it didn't bother her, but the idea of three upperclassman who were all Heirs to an intimidating amount of political and social power pooling their information to discuss her made her want to groan with frustration. She knew Flint wouldn't give her away—couldn't—but it was still unnerving that they would even want to talk about her. None of them were stupid, and no matter how well she'd covered her tracks there was always a trail somewhere to her secrets.

The other three exchanged amused looks at the very idea of studying for something as trifling as an exam, and ignored her question completely.

Selwyn sat down on the couch between Rookwood and Rosier and stared pointedly at the other couch until Rigel sank into the seat next to Flint. "Show Black the article," she said, nudging Rosier in the arm.

He slid the paper over toward Rigel, who picked it up to skim.

THE HOGWARTS MALADY: AN IN-DEPTH EXPOSÉ

It looked to be an entire write up, from beginning to end, on the sickness, written, of course, by Rita Skeeter. There were little subtitles like: FEARFUL BEGINNINGS: THE JONES CASE and A TROUBLESOME TURN: ALLERGIES CAUSE A SNAG IN THE TREATMENT. Rigel sighed and began reading through it. Surprisingly, most of the information was, as far as Rigel knew, correct.

It detailed the sudden appearance of the sickness, how it struck the youngest Hufflepuffs first, and slowly spread by House and age as people got their friends sick despite the Quarantine. It went through the symptoms, referencing notes that Madam Pomfrey had given the Healers at St. Mungo's, and it was remarkably on-target with what the illness actually did. There were short quotes from a few anonymous students who had fallen ill, describing the blackness that invaded the mind, and Rigel recognized a few of her own phrases and assumed the kids had just repeated what she'd told them when she explained how the sickness had erected a mental barrier that could only be broken from the inside, which kept them from being woken as long as it was in place.

They were all, Rigel was dismayed to see, quite adamant that it had been Arcturus Rigel Black who saved them from the sickness, with help from a Healer or Professor Snape once Rigel had taught them how to break through the barrier from the inside. Rigel groaned, "They make it sound like I'm some sort of super Legilimens."

"It gets better," Rosier said cheerfully, "Just keep reading."

She did, and he was right…if you stretched the meaning of the word 'better' until it came out looking like 'worse.'

Good readers, this reporter was shocked as well, but after a little more digging it was revealed that Arcturus Black was in fact the one responsible for the cure. That's right, Arcturus Black, first-year Slytherin and Heir to the Noble and Most Ancient House of Black, somehow accomplished what several anonymous Healers at St. Mungo's agree should have been impossible. How is it that Young Mr. Black was able to break through mental barriers that stopped even the strongest of Legilimens, but was not able to completely eradicate the sickness from the minds of those he helped without assistance? It sounds to this reporter as if Mr. Black is not a Legilimens at all, but something else entirely, someone able to overcome mental barriers with a skill of his own. Surely the Headmaster will take measures to ensure Mr. Black's classmates' mental privacy, should that be the case. In any event it seems that Young Mr. Black is proving to be a very gifted young man.

Some, however, would disagree with this assessment. This reporter interviewed Young Mr. Black's infamous father, co-founder of the Marauder practical joke line and well-known ladies man in his youth, Sirius Black. Mr. Black had this to say about the accounts of his son's involvement in the sickness: "My son is no Mind Master," he laughs, "When I sent him off to Hogwarts he was just like any other eleven-year-old. He's always had an interest in Healing, that's true, but he's never been trained in it like you're probably imagining. Anything he's learned that aided him in discovering a way around the sickness was picked up at school. You mark my words, Dumbledore knows what he's doing at Hogwarts. He's teaching those kids right if a boy who's been learning magic there for only a year can find a solution to such a formidable illness."

Mr. Black has certainly given us some food for thought. If, indeed, Young Mr. Black has no special talents of his own, then we can certainly be proud of the education our youth are receiving at Hogwarts, but on the other hand does it seem likely that if a student succeeds where his teacher fails he was relying solely on his teacher's teachings? Only time will tell if Young Mr. Black is more than meets the eye, but for now parents everywhere can rest safe knowing that the Hogwarts Malady has been cured, the children safely awoken, and the Quarantine lifted. There are even rumours that the Headmaster is planning a complete reform of the medical operations at Hogwarts, which will offer safer, more efficient Healing services to the students and staff. All in all, things are looking up at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.

"How in Merlin's name did Skeeter manage to make an entire article that was supposed to be on an illness about one eleven-year-old boy who didn't even have the illness?" Rigel muttered, scowling. She really didn't want this kind of attention, though at least Sirius had warned her he was speaking to the paper in his letter.

"You should be proud, Black," Flint said, a glint to his eyes, "If your dream is to be a Healer, I mean. After this any Hospital would be mad not to hire Arcturus Black."

Rigel grimaced ruefully. Archie's career as a Healer would definitely be helped by this article in the future, but she knew Archie would hate the idea of taking credit for someone else's work. "It has nothing to do with Healing," she said, "I didn't Heal anyone, I just used what Professor Snape taught me to help him cure the sickness, which wasn't even really a sickness. It didn't make anyone sick. It was more like a contagious curse, so if anything what I did was creative curse-breaking, not healing."

Selwyn laughed, "Poor little snake. Not much for attention, are you?"

"I can't see why anyone would be," Rigel said, "All it brings is trouble."

"Says the honorary Malfoy," Flint smirked. Rigel's eyes widened and Flint chuckled, "Oh, yes, we've heard about that as well. Draco Malfoy seems to be under the impression that you saved his life, and that you're now his brother by magic as well as his cousin by blood."

Rigel looked down at her robes uneasily, "The Malfoys are too kind."

"But not mistaken?" Rosier's golden eyes shone eerily in the firelight, "So you did save Draco Malfoy's life. How could that be when from your own account the sickness isn't even really an illness at all?"

Rigel shifted under his gaze, "Draco was an exception. He had an allergy to…one of the ingredients in the potions he needed to stay stable under the coma. I sort of saved him by default, by helping cure the sickness before the time he had on the life-sustaining spells ran out."

"So you weren't trying to save him?" Rookwood clarified.

"Well, I guess I was," Rigel said, "But I would have done it for anyone. I didn't need to be adopted by the Malfoys. They're great, but I have a family."

"But you did save their Heir," Selwyn said.

"I saved my friend," Rigel corrected.

"Well whoever you saved or didn't save," Rosier broke in, "The fact is that it ended the sickness, and as a result Dumbledore's credibility is higher than ever. Now that the children are safe again, no one wants to admit they ever doubted the Headmaster."

"And with this article suggesting that Dumbledore's teachings are what gave you the power you needed to cure the sickness, most people are of the opinion that the Headmaster should keep doing what he's doing, in all areas of his doings," Flint added.

"In other words," Selwyn concluded, "Dumbledore's opinion is good as goblin gold in the wizarding world right now, and rumour has it that his opinion is very much against a certain set of laws that were supposed to come up for discussion before the Wizengamot this summer."

"The mixed-blood marriage laws," Rigel said flatly, "You think they'll be voted against in the Wizengamot now that Dumbledore's faction has the advantage once more?"

"Oh, I very much doubt the SOW Party would be foolish enough to push the laws into consideration while the political winds were not at their backs," Rosier said breezily.

"So they'll table the laws until they have the support they need," Rigel said, understanding dawning. In other words, the threat the laws presented was postponed, not defeated. The Cow Party would just keep the laws from being voted upon until they were sure they could win the vote, and since they were the ones proposing the laws, they could wait as long as they wanted with the excuse of still working on the draft. That meant they could suddenly push the laws through at any time, as soon as they had the support they needed to pass it.

"No one wants to risk losing when they don't have to," Selwyn said vaguely.

"No doubt the SOW Party will be very interested in how exactly the sickness that so fortuitously arose in Dumbledore's school while the law Dumbledore would have so venomously opposed was being introduced came to be cured miraculously by a mere first-year," Rosier said quietly, "I know I'm interested. And you, Edmund?"

"It certainly is interesting, Aldon, that the truth about the cure is so muddled. Most Slytherins are under the impression that Professor Snape played a significant if not dominant role in stopping the sickness," Rookwood said mildly, not missing the slightly guilty look on Rigel's face at that. She might have given several Slytherins that exact, and not precisely false impression. "Most of the younger students, particularly those afflicted by the sickness itself, would say that you, Mr. Black, were primarily responsible for their recovery, with only supplemental help from the Mind Healers. Other reports say that Professor Snape was in fact out of the country when Draco Malfoy fell ill, and of course the Prophet article suggests that Dumbledore played a part in the cure."

"All anyone knows for sure is that somehow Rigel Black got involved—and what a first-year who wasn't sick was doing in the Quarantine no one seems to know—and that the first-year ended up curing the sickness, acquiring a life-debt from the Malfoys, and becoming solely responsible for curing the rest of the patients as well," Rosier continued. Rigel was slowly sinking further into the low-backed couch, wondering how exactly Rosier and Rookwood had gotten so good at double-teaming a person.

"Your involvement can of course be explained by what Selwyn has told us—namely that you were brewing an exorbitant amount of potions for Professor Snape as far back as February. Presumably Snape had you brewing for the sickness and so just let you continue brewing for the Wing while he was out of the country. If he was indeed gone while Draco Malfoy was ill, then it would make sense that you felt you needed to become involved, both because Malfoy is your friend and because you were given a position of powerful leverage as Snape's replacement," Rookwood said, "What doesn't add up is why you personally had to help awaken every single student. It can't be because Dumbledore didn't want to involve anyone else, because he hired a Healer from St. Mungo's to take Snape's place in the cure."

"On the other hand," Rosier said, eyes gleaming cheerfully, "It does add up if for some reason no one else could cure those students. In other words, the only solution is that you, Rigel Black, were able to do something that no one else could do. Something that couldn't be taught, couldn't be passed off to someone older, and therefore something that had nothing to do with Snape or Dumbledore. And that is certainly interesting."

"What's also interesting is that you were so dismissive of the illness actually being an illness," Rookwood said, "That suggests you have Healer training or knowledge of some kind, though your father denied it in his interview and you yourself seemed impressed and curious when I healed your wrist last semester. Not to mention the fact that by your own admission you hate hospitals and Mediwizards. In short, the anomalies are beginning to add up, Mr. Black."

Rigel glanced back and forth between the two of them, "Are you finished?" At their amused nods, Rigel took a breath and said, "First of all, you have figured out most of it. I cured the sickness by doing something that I am told no one else can, though it doesn't seem so difficult to me, only a little confusing. Snape taught me some of the things I used to get around the sickness, though he didn't put them together the way I did, and that's why I said he influenced the cure heavily. Dumbledore facilitated the cure, and since it's his Potions Master that taught me what I needed to figure out a cure, what was said about his school being responsible for the cure is true too. I have self-training for Medi-wizardry, and I only started that after the winter break, precisely because I didn't want to have to rely on other Mediwizards and hospitals. Did I get everything?"

"Everything but the actual cure," Selwyn said, rolling her eyes, "Aren't you going to tell us exactly what you did?"

"What do you think I did?" Rigel asked innocently.

"In other words, no he's not," Flint grunted.

"Fine, then," Rosier sighed, "Keep your talents secret. One day we will figure you out entirely, Mr. Black."

"And until then we will be watching closely," Rookwood said in his mountain's rumble.

Rigel nodded her acceptance, knowing that any protestation would only make them more interested. She left the four upperclassmen to make of the situation what they would. She just wanted to get home for the summer.

The final Quidditch match was played in the third week of May. Unlike the first match, Rigel and Pansy sat with their classmates in the Slytherin section, cheering on their team and just letting off some of the energy they'd pent up while studying for final exams. Slytherin won, and the cheers in the actual student section were nearly deafening. The entire House glowed with pride for the rest of the week, though the boasting was kept to a tasteful amount by most of the upper years at least.

The afterglow didn't last long, however. Soon finals were upon them, and the students who'd been struck by the sickness were especially stressed out over the prospect of the exams. Though Dumbledore had made an announcement that any student who failed the exam due to sickness would still pass and be able to take extra tutoring in the fall to bring themselves up to curriculum, no one wanted to be stuck in extra lessons the following year.

Rigel wasn't too worried. She knew she could at least pass the finals, and she had so many other things to do before summer that studying was something to be done when there was nothing else to be done. She was keeping up with Flint's assignments, and her own of course. She was studying Healing as much as she could, trying to bring herself up to where Archie would be, and therefore where her parents would expect her to be by the end of the first year at AIM. Her Occlumency could wait, but Rigel knew Lily wouldn't be able to keep James and Sirius from demanding to see some Healing for the whole summer, no matter the laws about underage magic.

So she studied the textbooks she'd taken from the Potter Library and by the first of June she was confident that she could heal a minor bone fracture (she'd only healed a bird's wing so far, and bird bones were very light and thin, but she had the basic concept down), which was right on schedule with where Archie would be, though he would be faster and more confident than she was and have a better understanding of the theory behind it. Rigel was learning Healing like most muggles learned algebra. She could follow the situation-specific formulas and come out even at the end, but she had no idea how or why the equations worked the way they did.

She was also sending letters back and forth to Archie, coordinating their return trip home, and so it was that the first Wednesday in June saw her writing yet another letter. This letter was unique because she was writing it with a handwriting charm instead of a Dicto-quill. Usually, Rigel dictated her letters to Sirius, Remus, and the rest, so that her handwriting wouldn't give her away, and only wrote her letters to Archie because it didn't matter if it was her handwriting on those, since no one in America would be able to tell. This time, she was writing to Archie with the new handwriting charm she'd learned so that he could compare it to his own and approve it before she tried it on Sirius. The charm was two parts. First you cast the charm over the sample of handwriting you wanted to imitate, then you cast the charm over your dominant hand, and everything you wrote with that hand would be in the sample handwriting for approximately one hour.

She leaned back on her dorm room bed and admired her work. It really did look like one of Archie's letters. She was about to seal it when Theo spoke up from the bed next to her.

"Hey, Rigel, can you help me with this?"

Rigel looked over. Theo was sitting on the foot of his bed, both feet on the lid of his trunk, which sat just below him, and was clearly trying to get the over-sized trunk to close.

"Are you packing tonight?" she asked curiously. They would finish their finals the next day, but they didn't leave for a couple more days after that, on the first Saturday of the month.

"I just need to make sure it all fits," Theo explained, huffing as he strained his muscles to push down on the lid, "Otherwise I'll have to donate some of my shoes to the lost and found or something."

Draco glanced over from his own bed on the other side of Rigel and grinned, "I think the fact that you're standing on it means that all of your things do not, in fact, fit in that trunk."

"I really think I can persuade it otherwise," Theo said good-naturedly, "Come on, Rigel, help me."

Rigel got up and went to stand by Theo's trunk, "What do you want me to do?"

"I don't know," Theo scratched his head, "Sit on it or something."

Rigel shook her head, but went to sit obediently on Theo's uncooperative trunk.

-_-Hp-_-

Draco's POV:

Draco watched as Rigel went to contribute to Theo's impossible packing methods. He would never participate in something so ungainly himself, but he had to admit it was pretty funny watching his roommates make fools of themselves for a piece of luggage. His eyes drifted back to the letter Rigel had been writing, which was now lying quite exposed on his bed. He couldn't help thinking there was something different about it.

Then he realized with a jolt of surprise that the handwriting was different. Why, it wasn't at all like Rigel's usual handwriting, which was generally small, unslanted cursive. Instead, the letter that Draco had just watched Rigel write was in a large, loopy handwriting that moved erratically across the parchment instead of in the neat, near-perfect rows Rigel generally took notes in. Was he more lazy in a letter home? Was the handwriting some sort of code that meant different things depending on—no. No, he was being silly. It could be anything. He generally wrote his father with a dicto-quill, Draco knew, so maybe it was because he secretly had really bad handwriting. A bad habit he consciously broke to take notes. Every. Single. Day. Draco frowned, thinking. He supposed it made sense if Rigel had been writing with a handwriting charm, but why would he? Draco shook his head and turned back to his own letter home. He would just add weird handwriting fluctuations to the growing list of really strange things he knew about his friend.

All in all it had been a very weird semester. He'd come to Hogwarts expecting…not exactly what he'd found. The Quidditch was pretty much what he'd thought it would be. Classes, too, were fairly straightforward. But other things…

His friends, for instance, were not at all what he had been expecting. He'd known Pansy already, the little blonde girl who always hung around his mother when Mr. Parkinson came to talk to his father. He'd really expected, however, that he would mostly hang around with Crabbe and Goyle, both of whom had been constant fixtures, rather like two ugly suits of armour, in his life before Hogwarts. Draco had fully expected to walk the halls of Hogwarts with his pseudo-bodyguards in the left and right wings, but then Rigel Black had walked up to that Sorting Hat and, completely ignoring other people's carefully thought out expectations of their time here at Hogwarts, gotten himself sorted into Slytherin.

Immediately, something changed. He would not be reporting on the Black scion from afar, like his mother had asked him to, but from the next bed over as a dorm-mate. And then Black had to make himself so interesting, and before Draco knew it he was Rigel, and Parkinson was Pansy, and they were all three best friends. Well, sort of. It was hard to claim to be someone's best friend while also being perfectly aware that they were keeping major secrets from you. Just like it was hard to claim that someone was your best friend when you were also sort of reporting on said best friend to your parents. Still, it was a Slytherin sort of friendship, like the kind Draco often suspected his father and godfather had, and that suited Draco just fine.

The sickness he had definitely not seen coming, and the thing with Lee Jordan trying to kill Rigel had come from complete nowhere. The strangest thing, though, was Rigel himself. The boy was, objectively speaking, odd. He was a vegetarian. He slept in his clothes. He had a strange, almost innate knowledge of the castle layout from the very first week. He spoke about his magic like it had a mind of its own, and all evidence that Draco could see seemed to support the theory that it did have a mind of its own. He was so good with potions that Uncle Severus had been immediately impressed. He could walk through people's magical cores. And despite everything he could do—levitating Longbottom in mid-air just a day after learning the spell, flying for weeks one-handed with a broken wrist, pulling a potions essay out of his own mind without references—he didn't care. Rigel treated everything he did like it was just something to keep him busy until he could brew potions again.

It drove Draco crazy, and even Pansy, Miss Patience herself, grew extremely frustrated with Rigel every now and then. How could someone have so much sheer ability and just not give it a thought? Magic was an inconvenience to him, and yet it was his unique way with magic that allowed him to save Draco's life. His father had made Rigel a Malfoy, and Rigel had just blinked like he didn't get why they would do something that he saw as being so unnecessary. Rigel Black was exasperating, confusing, and Draco knew he hardly agreed with anything Draco said or believed, though Rigel never actually came out and said it. But even though Draco had always imagined friends as people who supported and agreed with you no matter what, Rigel was undeniably one of the best friends he'd ever had. Pansy was the other best friend he'd ever had, and most of what made her so great was that she was the only other person who understood just how weird Rigel really was.

So even though Pansy was a girl, and even though Rigel lied to him all the time, Draco was pretty sure those things didn't matter, because after the year of craziness they'd had, Draco thought maybe friends weren't the ones who agreed with you. They were the ones who saved your life and then listened to you complain about how aggravating your life-saving friend was. Draco rolled up his letter to his father carefully, knowing that any smudged ink would be remarked upon, and thought as he tied it closed that even though it hadn't been what he expected, his first year at Hogwarts was one he would never forget.

Regular POV:

Their compartment was completely full on the train ride home, and they didn't hate anyone in it. Millicent had taken the empty sixth seat, and so they spent the ride talking and making promises to write, visit, and meet up over the summer completely sans the usual train-ride drama. The Weasley Twins came and said their goodbyes, along with Ron and even Percy, prompting Draco to mutter half-heartedly about their compartment becoming infested with Weasels. Neville stopped by too, and surprisingly Cho Chang, whose appearance was unexpected enough to have all of Rigel's classmates looking at her with varying expressions that said 'who-are-you-and-why-do-you-know-all-these-people-who-aren't-Slytherins?' Rigel shrugged noncommittally and a collective eye-roll (except for Pansy, who didn't roll her eyes) went around the compartment.

Rigel had never been so glad to see the outline of King's Cross station in the distance. She wanted to be home so badly it ached. Though her first-year at Hogwarts had been both everything and nothing she'd expected it to be, she was so tired. It wasn't magical exhaustion like when she'd been brewing Snowhit for Snape, and it wasn't mental exhaustion like when fighting the sickness in Draco's head. It was pure, soul-deep exhaustion that came from the strain of constant lying, constant deception, constant pretense. Her soul was wrung out, and she didn't think she could be Rigel for one more minute. She needed Archie. She needed Remus. She needed to see her mum and dad and Sirius and have them see her for her, Harry, not Archie or whoever she was pretending to be anymore.

She needed a break from the person she was at Hogwarts, even if just for a week or so before she'd visit her friends as Rigel again. She would sleep in her pyjamas, see green eyes looking back at her from the mirror, and not talk about Harry Potter in the third person even once. She would brew all day long, she thought dreamily, and not have to pretend she cared about other classes and assignments.

Rigel stood as the train began to slow. "Well, it's been a great year, guys. I'll miss you all, and don't forget to write. I'll see you in September," she said. She waved in a show of exaggerated cheerfulness, and left the compartment before any of her dumbfounded friends could react to her abrupt departure.

Rigel ducked into the nearest bathroom and locked herself in a stall while she took out a vial of Polyjuice Potion from her pocket and the fresh lock of hair Archie had mailed her at the end of May. She downed the dose and gritted her teeth against the uncomfortable twisting sensation in her gut. A few minutes later she emerged as Archie's twin and went to stand by the doors so that when the train stopped she'd be ready to go. She had her trunk in her pocket, along with enough Polyjuice doses to last her until midnight, and when the Hogwarts Express finally stopped completely Rigel hopped onto the platform with a step as light as her heart. She was almost there.

Sirius was hard to miss, and it wasn't because of the pink-and-yellow top hat he was wearing. It was his expression, half-hopeful and half-anxious, that was so out of place among the crowd of cheerful, waving parents and guardians. Rigel smiled as wide as Archie's mouth would allow her to and took off toward her Uncle at a run. His face registered a moment of surprise, and then he was holding out his arms to catch her as she rocketed through the air toward him.

"Dad!" she landed on him with all the finesse of a flying rhino, but Sirius caught her anyway and used her momentum to twirl her in a circle like he was wont to do to people. She hugged him tight, but not as tightly as Sirius held her.

"Archie," he breathed with relief. He set her down carefully and looked searchingly into her face, "How are you?"

"Great now that I'm back!" she said. She grabbed Sirius's arm and began towing him out of the platform, determined to get away before her friends came looking. "It's so great to see you again, Dad. I'm sorry I didn't write more, but you won't believe all the things I have to tell you! No, really, I don't think you'll believe me at all, which is why I didn't bother putting it in a letter, but I'm going to tell you anyway. So much stuff happened this last semester! Did you know Slytherin won the Quidditch Cup? Ravenclaw won the House Cup, but the Quidditch one is the only one that really matters. Draco didn't play, but Adrian Pucey did, and he helped me with my Herbology homework once."

She chattered on and on and on as they made their way through the winding streets of London to an apparition point. Sirius didn't once interrupt her, instead just watching and listening with his smile getting bigger and more relaxed the more she talked.

"And I'm pretty sure I passed all my finals, but Binns had us write three feet on a goblin rebellion he only mentioned like once in October. Three whole feet! And—"

"Woah, there, pup," Sirius broke in with a laugh, "You can tell me everything when we get home, and then again when we go to Godric's Hollow for dinner. Just tell me this," here he looked at her with a more serious expression, "Did you like Hogwarts? I mean, really like it?"

Rigel looked into the grey eyes that would always be brighter than what a contact could imitate and answered as honestly as she could, "Hogwarts was wonderful, Dad. It was everything you'd told me and more, but nothing is as good as coming home."

Snape's POV:

The office of Severus Snape was unusually bare. Some might say that it was always rather Spartan, and that the odds of it somehow becoming more so were so long as to be rather impossible, but after spending most of the day packing up his office for the summer break, even Severus Snape had to admit, looking around, that his office was quite bare. Gone were the shelves of embalmed ingredients that served as both a macabre decoration for his admittedly offbeat sense of humour and as deterrent for any non-Slytherin student ornery enough to attempt a visit longer than the time it took to completely dismiss them. Gone was the comfortable chair that usually sat behind the desk. Gone were the papers almost always sitting on top of the desk, and as soon as he cleaned out the last drawer he, too, would be gone. Away from meddlesome old men with beards too long to be sanitary, away from children who didn't know the right end of a stirring rod from the sharp end of their sub-standard steel knives. Away from teaching and grading and worrying about how many of his students were going to cause near-fatal accidents because they couldn't be bothered to read the directions before tossing ingredients around like they were tossing around their mother's spice rack. He would have three months of peace to brew, research, and experiment—in other words, to relax.

First, though, he had to pack away this one last drawer. The first thing on top was the bag of medi-balls he'd given Black to train his magic with. A quick look in the bag confirmed that every single one of them was as bright, steady green as the day the little brat had handed them over to him. As if they didn't understand the concept of naturally declining magical energy at all. He shook his head. Was nothing that child did normal? Severus really didn't know what to make of Rigel Black. If someone had asked him at the beginning of the school year if he'd be taking the son of one of his enemies on as his trial-apprentice, he'd have taken 100 points from Gryffindor for asking such an impertinent question, because really only an idiotic Gryffindor would ask something so clearly ludicrous of a man like Severus Snape, who so clearly did not have time for lunacy.

Of course, that was before Rigel Black had gotten sorted into Slytherin and showed himself to have a stubborn will and an eye for potions—and more importantly, a heart for potions.

Severus packed the bag of medi-minis away in the box and pulled a few other odds and ends that always seemed to collect in his office when he had nowhere else to keep such things out of the drawer. The last thing, tucked into the very bottom of the drawer against the back, was a silk-wrapped bundle that he froze upon seeing. He sighed and pulled it out, lowering himself to the ground to sit and look tiredly at the bundle.

The Potions Master gazed at the innocuous little bundle and wondered how it had come to this. He unwrapped it slowly, and there, in the silk, was a pile of perfectly preserved ginseng. It didn't look like much, and indeed in the grand scheme of the sickness it wouldn't have been much, but it was enough to keep one child supplied with Snowhit and Aurora's Breath for several months at least. Severus Snape stared at the bundle for a long while. There was nothing special about the ginseng itself, but rather what it represented.

The ginseng symbolized a lie, his lie to be exact. There was nothing remarkable about the fact that he had lied—Severus Snape lied for a living, as many, many people would attest. It was this particular lie, however, the why and how of it, that merited deep contemplation.

He had lied to Rigel Black, lied in the boy's own mindscape, when he told Black that his telling Severus about Draco's illness would have made no difference. In truth, Severus had set aside this ginseng and preserved it the very moment he realized they were running low. He had looked over Draco's allergy list himself when Lucius had turned it in, and he had known that it was only a matter of time before his godson fell sick as well. So he had made sure that when Draco fell ill he would be taken care of. Of course that plan only worked if he was made aware of the fact that his godson was ill, but instead of telling Black that, instead of explaining about the hidden ginseng, he had lied.

He told the boy that he hadn't made anything worse with his mistake, and let the boy go on believing that Draco's life truly was still in danger even though Severus had only stopped by the Hospital Wing to check up on Draco before getting started on brewing him the necessary potions when Narcissa had noticed Draco's hand twitch. He let Black think he'd saved Draco when nobody else could, let Draco and even Lucius and Narcissa think it, not telling his oldest friend of the stash of ginseng he'd prepared, though he knew what that would mean to them in terms of the Life they felt they owed the boy.

Severus could have easily justified his actions by saying that if he'd told the truth the sickness might never have been cured. If Black didn't think his best friend was in mortal danger, he wouldn't have tried so hard to save him. But the truth was that the sickness was cured the moment Black had gotten into Draco's mind, and he had done that before Severus had shown up and lied to him.

So why had he lied? It was simple, and yet it was so complicated he could scarcely fathom it. Severus Snape simply, and impossibly, didn't want to hurt the boy. Black had felt guilty already for what he thought he'd done, and he'd done much for Draco, despite the fact that his godson would have been okay without Black's help. He didn't need to make the boy feel worse after the fact, so he'd invented a fiction in which Black really had saved Draco from certain death. If Severus thought about it long enough, it really wasn't much of a lie. Black had been operating under the assumption that Draco was going to die, and even if he was wrong, he had still done a hero's work, for a hero's reason. Surely, then, it wasn't so much to ask that he receive a hero's reward. Narcissa and Lucius could afford the Life Debt—Severus knew Black was not the kind of boy to demand an impossible payment, or more likely any payment at all. No one got hurt, in the end, and his pseudo-apprentice gained both confidence and acclaim, both of which would help him later.

The trouble was that Severus Snape had shown sympathy and even kindness for someone who was not just a student, not just a Slytherin, but a Black. A Black. He hated the Blacks. Hated the whole, diseased family. Sirius Black was a name etched with hate on Severus' every schoolyard memory, and to behave in such a way toward his son—to show kindness and go out of his way to avoid hurting the child—such a thing even Albus would have considered beyond him. Yet so it was.

Severus wrapped the bundle of Ginseng back up and placed it in the box with the rest. He stood and hefted the box under an arm, using the other to douse the lights and lock up behind him. As he walked the dungeon corridors for the last time until September, he couldn't help but shake his head at the way the year had turned out. Last August he never would have imagined that he'd find the perfect heir to his potions expertise in the child of his most bitter childhood enemy. Things were changing. He was changing. Only time would tell if the world could really change for the better.

Epilogue

Lucius Malfoy was never nervous. Nervousness was an affliction of people sensitive to fear. Lucius had nothing to fear, because he belonged to that elite group of men in the world that truly are untouchable in the realest possible way. So if his heart beat a little faster in the presence of one Tom Marvolo Riddle, it was not because he was nervous, anxious, or otherwise suffering from fearful anticipation. He could not deny that he was in suspense, bent nearly double in a bow lower than any he would give outside of his leader's presence. He had reported to Riddle as soon as he'd quit the Hogwarts anti-apparition wards and was waiting for Riddle's response, whatever it may be.

It was true that Riddle would probably not be happy with the news Lucius had come bearing. Lucius himself was not quite as disappointed as he might have been, but his son's life had, after all, been in grave and unforeseen danger because of the sickness that had so recently been thwarted. And that was just it. The sickness had been cured.

Lucius wasn't sure how Riddle was going to take that news. He knew how long his leader—he hesitated to use the word Master, both because a true Malfoy had no master and because that wasn't really the sort of image the S.O.W. Party wanted to give off—had worked on the sickness. It had been perfect—or so they had thought. Draco's reaction was of course, unanticipated, and Riddle had apologized for the event already, though of course it was not Riddle who was at fault. When Lucius found out who had been buying up the ginseng crop he would see to it they paid dearly. Still, the sickness was formidable. To think that a boy of eleven had developed a cure, and such an unconventional one at that, well, Lucius was not at all certain what Riddle's reaction would be.

His spine was slowly stiffening, but he remained with his head and shoulders bowed, staring at the elaborate Indian silk carpet beneath his booted feet until Riddle spoke. To Lucius' immense surprise, when Riddle bade him rise it was with a soft laugh—a laugh!

"Stand up, Lucius, and come closer so that I don't have to shout across the room to be heard," Riddle said, and when Lucius looked up it was to find a smile playing across Riddle's mouth. Not a politician's smile, though he was very good at those, but a real one.

Lucius moved forward until he was directly before the golden throne Riddle sat upon in the middle of the cavernous reception room. It was a private joke among the upper tier of their Party that Riddle was King of the Cows. Oh, they knew what their opponents called them. The fools knew nothing. Lucius had had the throne encrusted with emeralds for Riddle's last birthday, and they winked at him in the light of a hundred candles as he approached his leader.

Tom Riddle was an impressive specimen of a wizard, Lucius could admit that freely and without insecurity. He was tall and well formed, with a politician's perfect hair and a card sharp's piercing gaze. Yes, Tom Riddle was impressive in every sense of the word. Then again, Lucius himself was rather impressive if one believed his wife when she was at her most revealing. It was not his physique or political charm that had drawn Lucius to the man and allowed him to bow before him when none other would do. It was his magic. Riddle had the magic of Merlin himself; of this fact Lucius would swear to Mordrid. It was wild, it was powerful, and it was wielded by the most capable political mind of the century. Lucius would go far at Riddle's side, oh yes, he would go very far indeed, just as his father might have were it not for his untimely demise.

Lucius looked Riddle in the eye and said, "Yes, Mr. Riddle?"

"So a first-year was able to get around my little bug's defences, is that what you're telling me, Lucius?" Riddle asked, that strange smile still tugging at the edges of his mouth.

"Yes, Mr. Riddle," Lucius said.

"Interesting," Riddle drew out the word as if tasting it for potency, "Yes, very interesting. I admit, I did not think that anyone would be able to penetrate the sickness until I called it back. Not even Severus should have been able to lift the mental barriers from without. I made sure of this, of course, as I knew that his position under Dumbledore's watchful eye would prompt him to attempt it. Yet from your account this child was able to unravel the defences from within?"

"That is correct, Mr. Riddle," Lucius said, "The boy demonstrated this unusual ability in front of my wife and I. It appears that he is able to enter the mind through a person's magical core, however ridiculous the idea seems to common logic."

"Common knowledge is sometimes the least reliable," Riddle admonished gently, "This ability is most suspect, however. You have felt the boy's magic?"

Lucius faltered, "Sir, since you have taught me how to sense the magic around a person I have met with great success in my exercise of the ability; however…I have felt nothing from the boy."

"Nothing, Lucius?" Riddle gazed at him with half-lidded amusement, "We both know that cannot be so."

"Yes, Mr. Riddle," Lucius said quickly, "I am sure that something is preventing me from accurately assessing his power levels, but through secondary sensing alone I can detect nothing around the boy. I have met him thrice, and each time it is the same. There is none of the wild aura of magic a child of eleven would usually have, especially a magically strong child who does not yet know how to control his power. However…"

"Continue, Lucius," Riddle said, "Speak your thoughts."

"The boy intimated that he learned primary sensing from Severus in an effort to learn conscious potion imbuing earlier in the semester," Lucius said, "So it is likely that Severus has a better understanding of the child's magical depths."

"I shall be having a chat with Severus very soon, it seems, though I know how he dislikes being pulled from his summer experiments," Riddle chuckled softly, "In any event, the boy does not appear to be a threat to us at the moment. You say he is primarily focused on school work at this time?"

"Yes, sir," Lucius said, "My son reports that the boy does little besides read about and brew potions when he is not completing his other school work. I, too, believe he is of no danger to our goals at this time."

"Time, indeed," Riddle said thoughtfully, "Time is very much on our side. Lucius, you will see that the legislation is tabled for the moment. I have a few changes I'd like to make to the proposal while we have the chance."

"Yes, Mr. Riddle," Lucius paused, "And the boy?"

"I very much desire to meet this young Slytherin lad, this Rigel Black," Riddle said, gazing off to the side as he thought, "You will arrange it, Lucius."

"Of course, sir. What are we to do about Dumbledore, Mr. Riddle? He has gained a great amount of support in the wake of the sickness' cure," Lucius ventured.

"Dumbledore?" Riddle laughed softly again, "Do not trouble yourself about the good Headmaster. Plans are already being made for September. Not even Dumbledore's phoenix will be able to rise from the ashes of the next storm I send his way."

Chapter 1

Sirius Black decided that his 33rd birthday party was going to be a pool party. Did he have a pool? No he didn't. Did he rent out a muggle pool or perhaps host the party at the house of someone who did have a pool? Of course he didn't.

Harry Potter, Sirius' niece, sighed heavily as she gazed down at what had once been a perfectly good, if admittedly unused, potions laboratory. The Black Family Potions Lab was now looking a lot like the Black Family Underground Tropical Getaway, and while Harry had never actually needed her uncle's lab, having a perfectly good one at her own house outfitted with everything she could ever want, she still thought it a sorry state of affairs when a potions lab was ruined to this extent.

"Cheer up, Harry," Archie, Harry's cousin and Sirius' son, told her as he stepped up beside her at the top of the basement steps, "You're always saying how labs need proper lighting."

Harry grimaced. Proper lighting indeed. Sirius had taken his inspiration from the Hogwarts Great Hall when designing his party grounds, and charmed the ceiling to look like an open sky instead of the dull grey stone it was made of. Unlike the Great Hall, however, the clear cerulean expanse with its golden sun beaming down on them was definitely not a sky to be found anywhere in the United Kingdom.

"It's supposed to be Aruba, I think," Archie said, squinting up against the bright sunlight.

"It's as hot as Aruba in here," Harry said, "If there were any actual ingredients around they'd be dried up and ruined in about ten minutes."

"Lucky you raided any salvageable ingredients when you were about seven, then, isn't it?" Archie grinned, "Though I don't think the ingredients would need to worry about drying out, as they'd be completely submerged in water as well."

Harry looked down into the basement lab, which was filled with about thirty feet of sparkling blue water, and smiled back ruefully, "It is a rather clever charm, I suppose."

"Why thank you, Harry," Sirius bounded up beside them, floating a cooler of drinks behind him, "It warms my heart to know that a potions enthusiast like yourself approves of my state-of-the-art improvements to the lab."

"You're welcome, Uncle," Harry hugged him briefly, "Happy birthday, Sirius."

"This is really cool, Dad," Archie said, "Are those treasure chests at the bottom of the pool?"

"Of course they are. What else is the Black Family gold good for?" Sirius swept by them and went down to where the water line stopped halfway up the stairs. He conjured a red floatation ring and secured the cooler inside of it snugly before sending it away to glide across the homemade pool. "Remus helped with the spells to keep the water insulated, and of course James transfigured most of the rafts, but the ceiling was all me."

"Who did the temperature charms?" Harry asked.

"Lily," Sirius said, grinning, "Her birthday present to me was an entire day of quiescence. No arguing and no scolding, and she also agreed to help however she could with the party decorations." Sirius grinned unrepentantly, "I've got her rounding up the snakes as we speak."

Archie and Harry exchanged a look.

"Can the snakes swim?" Archie asked dubiously.

"That's what we're going to find out," Sirius said, clapping his hands together, "Now go get your swimsuits on, kids, the party is about to start!" He headed back toward the kitchen to collect the food and Harry and Archie retreated to Archie's room to change.

Examining her swimsuit-clad form in the mirror, Harry couldn't help but think that she was experiencing a level of novelty most normal almost-twelve-year-old girls really shouldn't feel. Her swimsuit wasn't pink or frilly, but it was so clearly a girl's bathing suit just by virtue of having a top that Harry felt awkward wearing it. She'd only been home from school a week and a half, and the idea that she didn't have to hide her sex was one she wasn't quite used to yet. She still got a mild shock every time she saw her bright green eyes staring back from her reflection, and there had been times when she forgot to respond to the name 'Harry,' but overall she was so glad to be home.

"You done staring at yourself yet?" Archie called from outside the bathroom door.

Harry opened the door, purely so that she could roll her eyes at him, not because she was giving in to his pestering, but the earnest look on Archie's face stopped her.

"What?" she asked, resisting the urge to shift self-consciously.

"You really have to stop doing that," Archie told her, "Staring in the mirror every chance you get is starting to get kind of noticeable. I think your parents are putting it down to puberty or something, but try not to look so surprised when you catch sight of yourself in every reflective surface, okay?"

Harry sighed, "Yeah, sorry. It's just weird."

"Yeah, I've been thinking about that," Archie lifted one foot to rub his other in a nervous gesture he'd perfected over the years, "I'm not sure we'll be able to keep going as we are for six more years. How long will it be before one of the people who know you at school wants to meet both you and someone who actually knows what I look like at the same time?"

Harry nodded, "You're right. I'm working on it, sort of. I'll tell you after the party, okay?"

"Alright," Archie shrugged, "I figured you had something up your sleeve—you're the girl with the plans after all."

Harry thought to herself that she didn't feel very much like a girl with a plan, but Archie probably didn't need to hear that, so she smiled in what she hoped was a confident way and followed Archie back down to the basement.

The rest of the party guests, meaning the rest of their unofficial family including Remus, James, and Lily, were lounging about on the rafts James had transfigured when Archie and Harry finally arrived. Sirius had all of the snakes on his raft, and from what Harry could pick up from their disgruntled mutterings none of the reptiles were pleased with the situation. Sirius tossed Harry a bottle of sunscreen, and Harry glanced questioningly at Remus, not sure if Sirius was joking or not.

The werewolf shrugged from where he was lounging on his raft under an umbrella, "We're actually not sure if the charm gives off UV rays, so better safe than sorry in this case."

Archie laughed, "Someday when I'm a grown up I'm going to perform magic that I don't really understand, and no one will yell at me for it."

"Not on your birthday, at any rate," Lily muttered into her tropical beverage. Archie claimed a raft with an umbrella, but Harry picked a plain raft to sit on. She figured some sunshine would do her good after all those months practically cloistered in potions labs.

"Speaking of birthdays," Sirius said once they'd all settled in, clapping his hands together, "I know I've set the bar pretty high this year, but I don't want you two to think we aren't celebrating yours just as well when the time comes this summer. Is there anything in particular you want?"

Archie glanced over at Harry and then shrugged casually, "We'll think about it."

Harry nodded her agreement. She and Archie had been born just a few days apart, and as such always celebrated their birthdays together to save effort. It only made sense considering they invited the same four people. This year, however…

"You should invite some of your friends from school," Lily suggested, "It'll make a nice change to have other kids around the house."

Lily often said 'around the house' when she really meant in or around the three houses their pseudo-family frequented. Each house unofficially belonged to all of them in a way.

Harry coughed slightly, "I'm not sure who I'd invite. Most of my friends from America actually live in America, and it's a long way to come for just a birthday party. International floo is so expensive."

Not to mention, Harry thought wryly, that all of the people that 'Harry' knew in America thought 'Harry' was a boy.

"What about that Hermione girl you're always writing home about?" James asked, "She lives in England, with her parents the dentists, right?"

"Oh yeah," Harry said weakly, "Right. I'll see what she's doing the last week of July."

"What about you, Archie?" Sirius prompted, "It would only be polite to invite the Malfoy boy after his family offered you a life debt."

"And if Pansy Parkinson is anything like her mother Rose, I'm sure she's a lovely girl," Lily chimed in, "We'd love to have them, regardless of politics and the like."

Archie curled his toes nervously over the side of his raft, "I would like to invite them, but I'm not sure their parents would let them come. You know how it is with the dark purebloods. It's unlikely they'd send their Heirs off to a pureblood's home they aren't familiar with."

"Oh, right," Sirius said, looking disheartened. Harry winced. He was still feeling the rift she'd inadvertently caused between him and his son by not sending letters as often and as honestly as she could have. No doubt he was thinking Archie would resent him for making the Malfoys and Parkinsons uncomfortable with letting their kids play at Sirius' house.

"It's no big deal, dad," Archie said cheerfully, "I saw them all year. I'd rather just spend my birthday with you guys like I always do."

"Still," Sirius said, though he looked a little more chipper, "A kid should have friends over for his twelfth birthday."

"What's so special about twelve?" Harry said idly, "We can have a big party when we turn seventeen or something."

"You just don't want party preparations to take away from your brewing time," Archie teased good naturedly, though Harry could see the slight relief in his eyes at the change of topic. Friends were a tricky subject when you were lying to and about them.

"Of course," Harry shrugged, "So what?"

"Careful there, Harry," James put in with a grin, "It's a wonder you made any friends at all this year with that kind of outlook."

"Maybe she didn't," Sirius flicked water at her from his raft as he floated by, "Maybe our Harry just wrote home about friends so we didn't worry, but really she's been hiding in the potions lab at AIM all year."

Harry shrugged, a smile tugging on her lips, "I guess you'll never know."

"You do look a bit pale," Lily said, pursing her lips, "You have been getting out, haven't you? James and I were surprised when you said you weren't going out for a Quidditch club this year."

"I just didn't think I'd have time," Harry said reasonably, "The Healer tract isn't exactly easy, and I'm keeping up with my potions work in my spare time as well. I want to be able to get a Mastery by the time I finish school."

"In which one?" Remus said, surprised.

"Both," Harry shrugged, "Though I'll always enjoy potions more."

"Then why did you decide on the Healer tract?" James asked concernedly, "If you want to gain a Mastery so soon, you should go into the potions tract. Don't you just have basic potions classes in the Healer tract?"

"There are a couple of advanced classes later on," Harry said, "Because a lot of Healing has to do with Potions, even if the Healers don't brew them personally, but there's actually another reason I decided on Healing." She glanced toward Archie very obviously and said, as apologetically as she could, "I've actually been learning Healing so I could teach it to Archie. It was his dream to go to AIM and get Healer certified, so I'm helping him make it come true."

There were exclamations from all the adults.

"Oh, Harry," said Remus seriously, "It's wonderful that you're helping Archie, but what about your dreams?"

"I've got it covered," Harry said firmly, "Frankly, I don't need to be in the Potions tract to gain a Mastery by the time I leave school. My potions studies are progressing rapidly, and if I was in the potions tract I'd probably be bored with the level my classmates were at. This way, I learn something I don't already know, which will be useful to my potions work anyway, and Archie gets to learn Healing too. He's really good, you know."

Sirius turned surprised eyes to his son, "You've begun already?"

"Yes," Archie said carefully, "Harry and I are about at the same level, actually, because Harry writes me letters with instructions and assignments, and we found copies of the textbooks in the Potter Library. I didn't tell you because I didn't want you to think I was ungrateful of the teachings I can get at Hogwarts—I'm not. I'm learning a lot at Hogwarts, and I'm glad you insisted I go there. I've made so many friends. This is just extra, so that I can follow my dreams no matter where I am."

"I think it's wonderful," Lily said, smiling at the both of them proudly, "You've both matured so much, helping one another and working so hard." She looked around at James, Sirius and Remus, "We've done a great job with these two."

"What are you talking about?" James sighed dramatically, "It's a disgrace!"

"Indeed," Sirius chimed in forlornly, "The next generation Marauders and they're doing extra studying for fun? Where did we go wrong, Prongs?"

"I blame Moony," James said sadly, "He gave little Fawn her first ever junior potions kit, and if she wasn't so far ahead she wouldn't have time to teach extra things to Pup, now would she, Padfoot?"

"I agree," Sirius said solemnly, turning his head toward Remus' raft, "Sorry old friend, but you've crossed an un-crossable line. Get him!"

Sirius and James moved as one and launched themselves onto Remus' raft. The werewolf barely had time to "oof!" before he and his attackers fell arms over ankles off the raft and into the clear, blue water. The three grown men sank and thrashed about, wrestling in the water, and Lily ignored them with the ease of long practice, calmly sipping her drink and continuing the conversation as if there had been no interruption.

"Harry, I know you're rather advanced for your age, but are you certain you can learn all you need to without help? I was friends with a Potions enthusiast once, and I understand there are many things you can't learn from books," Lily said worriedly, "I think what you and Archie are doing is great, of course, I just want to make sure you've got everything figured out."

Harry nodded slowly, "Actually, I was going to talk to you and Dad about this eventually, but I guess I'll tell you now. I was thinking of participating in a couple of summer classes, to help me with my extra studies, you know? Would that be okay?"

Her mother blinked with surprise, "Summer courses? Where at?" She frowned at Harry a bit sadly, "You know most places in England discriminate based on bloodlines, and your father and I were really looking forward to having you home for the summer."

"I know," Harry said, ignoring the confused looks Archie was sending her, "I was thinking more along the lines of an owl-correspondence program." At Lily's sceptical gaze, Harry rushed on, "It's true that most of them aren't very reputable, but they'll take any student who pays their fees. I've found a really good one, I think, and I'd be able to do all of the work from home."

"I suppose extra classes never hurt," Lily said finally, "I'll talk to your father later tonight."

"Speaking of," Archie said wryly as the three men finally surfaced, all three releasing their Bubble Head Charms with loud popping noises. They climbed back up onto their respective rafts and collapsed in boneless heaps while Archie, Lily, and Harry watched.

"Who won?" Archie asked with interest. All three of the participants grunted and waved their hands around tiredly in a way that conveyed no coherent answers whatsoever. "Ah, conceding the battle to Aunt Lily then? Good choice."

After a collective groan went up from the men, Lily laughed and said, "Alright, enough of that, when are we going to have cake?"

Sirius jumped up, starting the snakes, who had just begun to dry off once more, up hissing again, "Right now!" He dove off of the edge of his raft and started swimming in long strokes to the basement stairs. Archie and James dove off after him, and even Lily decided to jump in and swim the distance to the 'shore.' Harry shared a look of agreement with Remus, who grinned and lifted his hands toward the water behind their rafts. After a moment's hesitation, the water began rippling, pushing against the rafts, and propelling them forward toward the exit.

"Hey Remus?" Harry said, watching the water lap against the rafts insistently.

"Yes, Harry?"

"How do you do that? Magic without a wand, I mean," Harry asked, "And without words, too."

Remus tilted his head as he considered the question, "Well, wordless magic you'll probably learn your sixth or seventh year at school. It requires great focus, and usually a very good familiarity with the spell you want to cast. Wandless magic, on the other hand, is much more difficult. To do magic without a wand requires extremely good familiarity with your own magic, to be able to direct it without a medium."

"But anyone could do it, couldn't they?" Harry asked, thinking back to her first Flying lesson, when she'd slowed Neville down without her wand, or in Transfiguration that one time, when she'd turned the match into a needle without words, "As long as they had focus and determination, I mean."

Remus frowned slightly, "Well, in theory every witch or wizard has the capacity to achieve it, but in practice most never do. It's not something like apparition, which about sixty percent of wizards learn how to do just by practising it long enough. Wordless and especially wandless magic requires something that most wizards never bother to gain; that is, it requires an understanding of magic that doesn't come from copying the correct incantations and wand motions until a spell works."

"You can do it, though," Harry pointed out. They were at the bottom of the stairs, but neither made to climb off their rafts just yet, "Did you learn it yourself, or did someone teach it to you?"

Remus smiled a bit, "Well, I picked up what I know from my post-graduate studies in magical theory, though I wouldn't ever claim to be proficient in it. I can work a bit with raw elements, which is the easiest kind of wandless magic to do. Magic is, for lack of a better word, freer in nature. The sense of wildness that magic has in the elements, like water and fire and such, allows for easier manipulation without a wand or staff. I couldn't try and move a chair, for instance, without a wand."

"What about a person?" Harry said casually, "They're made up of elements, aren't they?"

"Oh, no," Remus said seriously, "It's very difficult to use magic on another person without a wand—that is, if you're talking about a witch or wizard. Muggles, maybe, but wizarding folk have too much magic of their own—shaped magic, not wild magic like is found in nature. The other wizard's magic would interfere with wandless magic, which lacks the focus necessary to retain its properties when it comes into contact with shaped magic, which seeks always to shape new magic in turn. Does that make sense?"

Harry frowned, "Sort of. So the magic in wizards isn't the same as the magic in nature?"

"It starts the same," Remus explained, "Every magical core is born of wild magic, but as a child grows he or she develops a barrier of shaped magic, ordered magic, around the wild magic core, and that shaped layer is what interacts with the magic of the world. A wizard's magic needs order and shape in order to function properly; without it, his magic would simply disperse without purpose, without effect, whenever he tried to use it. Because of this, all magic used by wizards is ordered, structured in a way that keeps the magic from going wild, bound by words and wands. Without the words, and especially without a wand, which channels the shaped magic, spells are usually ineffective, because there is not enough willpower in the wizard to force the magic to keep the shape it needs to work."

Harry nodded slowly, "I guess that makes sense, but what if a wizard didn't have a wand, but was desperate or scared enough to make magic happen anyway?"

"Like a child's accidental magic?" Remus clarified.

"Sort of, but if the wizard isn't a child anymore."

"Well, accidental magic works because a child's magical core hasn't fully developed the secondary layer of shaped magic yet. Because their magic does not have a stable form yet, when the magic manifests itself forcefully it does so without the constraints that adult wizards need to make their magic work for them," Remus said, "For an adult, accidental magic like that is very rare. Only an unstable magical core could produce such a result, I believe."

Harry chewed her lip thoughtfully, "Okay, thanks Remus."

"Of course, Harry," Remus said, smiling, "I do enjoy our conversations, you know."

"Me too," Harry smiled back, "Let's go get some cake before it's all gone."

They made their way to the kitchen in silence, Harry thinking hard. In light of Remus' information, things were making a bit more sense. The reason wizards had primary and secondary layers to their cores must be because of the way their magic worked. The true core would be the wild magic. As Harry thought about it, most if not all of the true cores she had seen when she was helping cure the sleeping sickness had been elemental in nature. Fire, water, air, earth, or some variation therein. The outer layer of the core would then be the ordered magic, given more stable shape to allow the witch or wizard to utilize their magic in everyday life.

And her spontaneous bursts of magic from her first semester at Hogwarts could be explained by the fact that her core was still unstable at that time, like Remus said. She hadn't had a working wand, the magic in her core was unusually high, and if her core had still been a bit unstable or underdeveloped, that would explain the accidental magic she exhibited.

Or would it? Was it possible that her core was really underdeveloped then, when just a few months later Snape told her she had overdeveloped her magical core in her efforts to suppress her magic manifesting? She didn't know. She also didn't know why so many people spoke of magic like it was an unruly pet, to be forced to act a certain way, or a bar of clay, to be moulded into the shape a wizard wanted. Harry had started out that way, of course, but as soon as she realized how much energy she was wasting trying to browbeat her magic into submission she'd changed her tune. Why didn't other people just get along with their magic? Or maybe they did, and they just spoke in terms of forcing the magic to do something out of long habit.

What about that time in Snape's office, though? Harry still hadn't figured that out, though she tried not to think about it much. From what she now knew of Legilimency, it was nothing like what she'd done at that time. She'd somehow felt everything Snape was feeling, and made him feel what she was feeling, just by wanting it and concentrating on it. That didn't seem like accidental magic, because it wasn't really done out of fear or great need, and it also didn't seem like the kind of wandless, wordless magic Remus had described as possible, because she wasn't familiar with either her own magic or the magic that she'd been performing at that point. She still wasn't sure what she'd even done, come to that.

All in all, she still didn't understand a lot about the way magic worked, but she supposed she had enough to be getting on with.

Luckily, the horde had saved them two slices of cake apiece (singing was forgone in favour of just eating the cake already), so Harry and Remus joined their family at the kitchen table and dug in.

When everyone was finished, Sirius cleared his throat and placed his napkin down pointedly on the table, sending meaningful looks at James and Lily, who in turn sent uneasy looks toward Harry and Archie, both of whom looked to Remus questioningly. The werewolf sighed in turn and gestured toward Sirius, who, upon having everyone's attention once more, began speaking.

"Normally I'm not one to tarnish occasions involving cake with serious talk, though of course if people want to talk about me, who am I to—" Sirius broke off as Lily kicked him under the table, "Yes, well, anyway, Harry, Archie, you two are already aware of what the S.O.W. Party has been most recently planning, are you not?"

"The new anti-muggle-blood legislation," Harry said.

"Including the Marriage Law," Archie added, "Which makes it so that halfbloods can't marry anyone except purebloods."

"That's right," Sirius said, "And you also know that it was tabled after the sleeping sickness was cured, because Dumbledore's faction, which was against the laws, was supported so strongly." They nodded, so Sirius continued, "What you don't know yet is that the legislation is undergoing revisions while it is tabled, and from what Frank Longbottom has gleaned, it's going to be even nastier the next time it's up for ratification."

"Worse?" Archie frowned, "How?"

"Well, for instance there's talk of adding a clause that prevents a halfblood from turning down an offer of marriage from a pureblood," Sirius said. Lily pursed her lips angrily, but didn't say anything, and James took her hand comfortingly.

"But surely if they make it worse, it'll get even less support," Harry said, "Maybe if they get too carried away it won't pass at all."

"Maybe, though you have to remember that halfbloods are only about 25% of the population, muggleborns much less than that, so the majority of witches and wizards simply don't care either way," Sirius said tentatively, "And maybe the Sow Party has got something worse than the sleeping sickness up their sleeves."

Harry blanched. What could be worse than comatose children?

"We don't know for sure that they were the ones behind the sickness," Remus said cautiously, "It could have been very inconvenient timing."

"But you don't think so," Archie said, looking from face to face, "You think they'll do something next year to make Dumbledore look even worse, and that they'll push the laws through after that."

"So we have a year before they possibly get approved?" Harry asked, thinking of all she would have to do in that year. She needed to read the laws carefully and see what they would forbid halfbloods from doing career wise. Usually the Potions Guild didn't allow the government to interfere with them, but then again they were a bunch of stuck up sexist snobs, so who knew if they'd recognize the new legislation or not.

"Worst-case scenario, yes, we have a year," Sirius said.

"But, Harry," James said quietly, "We don't want you to ever be put in a position like this law is trying to force you and others like you into."

"Are you going to fight the law?" Harry asked, "Isn't it against the ICW Equality Accords or something?"

"We are going to fight it, though the Equality Accords generally only recognize sex, race, and personal beliefs to be possible sites of illegitimate unequal treatment," Lily said, "But the thing is, Harry, we want you to be protected in the event that the laws do go through somehow."

"How is that possible?" Harry asked, confused, "Everyone knows I'm a halfblood."

"Oh, little Fawn, we'd never ask you to try and change or hide who you are," James said, reaching across the table to ruffle her short hair comfortingly.

"There is a loophole, of sorts, in the legislation," Lily said, "Particularly the laws related to the Marriage Law. If a halfblood is already…spoken for, then they cannot be claimed by another pureblood."

"So, you want me to find a husband before the laws go into place?" Harry asked incredulously. No way could she pick a pureblood to marry within a year.

"No, Harry, of course not," Lily said gently, "In fact, you won't have to marry anyone. We've been discussing it, however, and the best option at this point is to have you engaged to someone—not with the true intent to marry, just to make you off limits to other purebloods, if that makes sense."

Harry bit her lip, "And I suppose this would be a very long engagement. Since I'm so young, of course."

"Of course," Remus said, a smile tugging his lips, "No one could expect you to marry for at least another, oh, six or seven years."

Archie began to smile too, "Oh yes, you wouldn't want to rush into anything, especially before you come of age."

Harry grinned, "Okay, so I get a pretend engagement for the next six years, and surely by the time I'm seventeen we'll have either repealed the laws or I can find someone to marry for real."

"Yes, exactly," James said, "Are you okay with this? We just want you to be as safe as possible."

"I'm okay with it," Harry said, "Archie?"

Archie laughed at the surprised looks on the adults' faces, "Well of course, who else would put up with you for six more years?"

Harry flicked a small bit of icing from her fork to Archie's cheek, but he just laughed and wiped it off unrepentantly.

"So you two are really all right with all of this?" Remus asked, looking tentatively relieved.

"Well don't get us wrong," Archie said, glancing at Harry and wrinkling his nose, "It's totally gross, and if I really did have to marry her I'd probably move to Japan."

"Archie!" Sirius admonished, grimacing.

"Likewise, I assure you," Harry sniffed, her lips twitching as she spoke, "I couldn't ask for a better brother, but a boyfriend…yeah, Archie's not exactly my type."

"You have a type?" James asked, turning alarmed eyes on her.

Oops.

"What? No, of course not, Dad. I hate boys. I was just using a figure of speech," Harry said, smiling innocently at her father.

"Oh, good then. Yes, Harry, boys are evil," James said, nodding judiciously.

"So predictable," Remus muttered.

Lily smacked her husband upside his head, "Don't forget who it was that proposed to me the first time when he was eleven."

"That was different," James said, highly offended, "I loved you."

"You didn't even know my name at that point!"

"Love is not hindered by the mere absence of a name," James said airily.

"Or an absence of brain cells, apparently," Sirius added.

"You really don't like any boys though, do you, little Fawn?" James turned his pleading gaze on her, and Harry sighed with exasperation.

"Oh please," Sirius scoffed, "Isn't it obvious that living with the Marauders has ruined her for any other man?"

"I'm sure you didn't mean that as creepy as it came out, Sirius," Lily muttered, shaking her head.

"So anyway," Harry said before the conversation could deteriorate further, "Do we need to sign a betrothal contract? I mean, just telling people we're engaged won't be enough, will it?"

"You'll definitely need a contract," Remus said, "I'll talk to the goblins at Gringotts. They should have some templates we can choose from, and alter if necessary."

"Yes," Lily said, "We need one that is binding until their seventeenth birthday, but which doesn't require chastity or exclusivity of the prospective bride and groom."

"Eww, Aunt Lily," Archie said.

"You'll thank me when you're older," Lily smirked.

"It should appear to be a loose but seriously intentioned contract," Remus said thoughtfully.

"With a clause for unsuitability that comes into play at seventeen, so that neither of them can break the contract before they are of age, to keep people from trying to break them up uselessly, but so that they can break it at seventeen if one deems the other unsuitable," Sirius added. He was well versed in pureblood laws and customs.

"What are possible grounds for unsuitability?" Harry asked.

"All kinds of things," Sirius said, waving a hand negligently, "If need be we'll make something up, but the point is that a clause like that puts the power to dissolve it in your hands, though not until you're both seventeen."

"That sounds good," Harry said. "This should solve the problem of the Marriage Law, at least for now."

"There's more," Lily said, "If the laws go through, a lot of things—jobs, housing opportunities, magical insurance and that sort of thing—will be out of reach for muggleborns and halfbloods. The only good thing is that if a halfblood is married to or betrothed to a pureblood, then the restrictions don't apply to them."

"So by being temporarily engaged to Archie, I have the legal benefits of a pureblood?" Harry said incredulously.

"Yes," Sirius said, "This means that from the moment the laws go into effect, provided you sign the contract, you will for all legal purposes be pureblooded."

"We're not ashamed of our blood," Lily said firmly, "But we don't want bureaucrats standing in the way of your dreams, Harry."

"Unfortunately this doesn't apply to Hogwarts," James said carefully, "Most schools are run separately from the government, and the Hogwarts board of governors wrote the pureblood-only restriction into the school charter independently from the Ministry of Magic's stance on blood status."

"That's okay, Dad," Harry said, smiling to show she wasn't upset, "I'm really okay at AIM. I have friends, and I'm learning Healing, which means Archie is learning it as well. The engagement will be enough to make sure I can get a job. Thank you guys, Mum, Dad, Remus, Sirius, and especially you, Archie. Thank you for doing this for me."

"You deserve it, Harry," Remus said simply, "You and Archie deserve every chance you can get. I know both of you will do extraordinary things one day."

"Besides," Archie said, pulling Harry's second piece of cake toward him with a winsome smile, "What's a secretly-fake betrothal contract between friends? You weren't going to eat this, were you?"

Harry shook her head, though she had, of course, been planning to eat that. What was the loss of a little cake when compared to the enormous gain that was her family? She forgot sometimes that other people were looking out for her too, and that she didn't have to do everything alone, or work out the whole future on her own. She didn't at all mind the reminder.

The next afternoon Harry found Archie in the Potter Library. Archie looked up as she entered, toting a bag of books with her, and put a bookmark in the medical journal he was reading through.

"What's up?" Archie asked, taking in Harry's determined face.

"I need you to tutor me in Healing, if you have time," Harry told him, plopping her books down on the Library table Archie was sitting at.

"Yeah, sure," Archie said, "I thought you said you were caught up, though."

"I am, at least in practice," Harry said, sitting down, "But I don't understand the theory behind what I'm doing."

Archie gave her a strange look, "How do you perform it in practice if you don't understand the theory?"

Harry grimaced, "My magic is weird."

"Explain," Archie said, raising his eyebrows, "Or do you just mean how it was acting out a bit around Christmas?"

"Not that," Harry said, "Though I guess it starts with that. Not long after school started up again, I came to a kind of accord with my magic. It stopped doing things I didn't want to do, or not doing things I wanted it to do, and now it's almost like magic comes too easily to me."

"What do you mean?"

"I can perform almost every spell I try on the first attempt," Harry whispered, leaning closer to Archie so they wouldn't be overheard, "Everything from Potion imbuing to Healing bruises—as soon as I ask my magic to do it, it just happens. That's not normal, is it?"

"It doesn't sound normal," Archie admitted, "You sure you're not just a super genius or something?"

"Definitely not," Harry said, "It's not that I easily understand everything I try to learn. It takes me as long as it would take anyone else to learn theory and remember things. I study theory vigorously to comprehend it all. But actually doing the magic…it's like breathing. I just imagine it happening, ask my magic, and it happens. I'm pretty sure I don't even need to know a spell for something for it to work, though of course I don't just throw the magic around without learning the spells first if I can help it."

Archie grinned, "You're like a classic superhero, Harry. Always so afraid of what you can do, determined not to abuse it."

"It isn't fair if I just do the magic without understanding it," Harry said, frowning, "It's like I'm taking advantage of it, and cheating with it."

Her cousin sighed, "Harry, it's not cheating in any way I can see. So you're really good at magic. So what?"

"It's not that I'm good at magic," Harry protested, "It's that my magic is good at…magic…if that makes sense."

"Not really," Archie said wryly, "So you're still sure of the idea that your magic has a mind of its own, and that your magic is the one responsible for doing all the, well, magic you do?"

"Yes," Harry said firmly. She didn't care what other people said. Her magic was separate from her, independent and an entity in its own right. She could feel it.

"Hmm," Archie scratched his head in thought, "Is that how you cured the sleeping sickness? Because I know you already explained it, but it didn't make much sense to me."

"Sort of," Harry said, "It wasn't that I asked my magic to cure the sickness though—I'm not sure asking it something that vague would work anyway. I just asked the other kids' magical cores to let me into their minds, so that I could help them take down the mental barrier."

"And Snape and the others told you that no one else can do what you were doing?" Archie checked.

"That's what they said," Harry nodded, "It seems strange to me, because it doesn't feel like a great new skill I have. It's natural. Easy."

"Can I try?" Archie asked.

"I suppose so," Harry said slowly, "I'm not sure what will happen though."

"I trust you to stop things if something really strange happens," Archie shrugged.

Harry hesitated, not wanting to hurt Archie unintentionally. On the other hand, she couldn't imagine anyone getting hurt doing what she'd done. It was so simple, and somehow beautiful. Archie would be fine. Harry trusted her magic now.

She took a deep breath and said, "I'm going to forge a connection between our magical cores, okay?"

"Whatever you say," Archie grinned.

Harry retreated into herself, looking inward to the place where her magical core rested in her gut. The familiar ball of fiery, writhing snake-like strands of magic greeted her inner eye, and Harry projected her consciousness toward that place within her until she felt her avatar manifest itself just outside of her magical core. She requested a strand from the outer layer of her core and directed it to shoot out toward the nearest magical core—Archie's. She felt the connection twang to life, and asked in her real-world voice, "Can you feel that?"

"Yes," Archie breathed wonderingly, "It's like a tug to the gut. What is it?"

"It's the connection. The place you feel that tug coming from? Turn your mind to that place and concentrate on seeing it, on feeling it, and on taking yourself to it," Harry said with her physical voice.

"Okay."

There were a few moments of silence, then Harry felt something brush against the connection between their cores tentatively. Harry smiled and sent her consciousness streaming along the connection until she reached the source of the experimental prodding. She looked around and, spotting Archie's avatar shifting uncertainly by his magical core, waved at him. He waved back, staring at her.

"You have long hair," he said, "Do I have long hair?"

He twisted around as if he could see the back of his head and Harry smiled, "No, you don't. I think I have long hair mentally because I associated my long hair with my girl self, my real self. To you it was probably just a hairstyle, so the cut assimilated into your consciousness more easily."

"Sure, Harry," Archie laughed, "So this is my magical core?"

They turned to look at it. The core was shrouded in soft blue mists that curled and swirled in a slow, playful pattern as they watched.

"It's kind of cool," Archie said.

"Let's get closer," Harry said. She walked forward until she could feel the cool air of the mists against her skin. "Will you let us in?" she asked the core. The mists began parting immediately before them, and Harry could hear the sound of running water up ahead.

Archie whistled, "Magic really just does whatever you want it to."

Harry shrugged, "Come on, I want to see your true core. It sounds like water."

"Water?" Archie moved forward through the swirling blue mists with her.

"All true cores seem to be pretty much elemental," Harry told him, "At least that's all I've seen. Water, fire, lightning, wind, or some variation of an element, like metal or magma."

"What's yours?" Archie asked.

"Fire," Harry said, "Look."

The mists parted completely and they could see Archie's true core. It was like a river, or more closely a babbling brook, but it flowed in a circle, forming the sphere-like shape that most cores took on. The water was a pretty cerulean blue and flowed lazily around and around the core, cool and tempting. Archie reached forward to touch it, and laughed with delight at the first touch of his hand to the moving water.

"It feels like magic," he said happily.

"It is magic," Harry smiled.

"I mean that I feel this when I do magic," Archie said, plunging his other hand into his magical core as well, "I just never realized what it was until now." He stayed there, up to his elbows in his magic's stream, until he took a deep breath and let it out on a peaceful sigh, "I feel better all of a sudden. Relaxed and soothed, and almost rejuvenated, you know?"

"Yes, my magic does the same for me," Harry said.

"So now what do we do?" Archie pulled his hands away reluctantly, marveling at how they were completely dry.

"Just like I projected my consciousness toward your magical core, you're going to do the same for mine," Harry said, stepping backwards from Archie's core and turning to move back toward the connection. The mists swirled back into place behind them, and when they reached the outside of the core once more Harry held out her hand, "Come on, I think I can pull you along with me."

Archie moved forward and took her hand without hesitating. Harry concentrated on moving back toward her magical core, but also on tugging Archie's consciousness along with her. They floated together through the connection and came out at Harry's core safely. Archie looked around with interest, examining the churning outside of Harry's core from different angles.

"Interesting," Archie said, "Your core is much more restless than mine is. The surface is moving faster, I mean, and I can feel the energy output even though I'm not very close to it."

Harry blinked with surprise. Now that she thought about it, compared to Archie's softly flowing stream and gently curling mists her magical core looked rather violent. It seemed as though the coils of magic on the surface, which so reminded her of snakes or ropes, were thrashing about mindlessly, constantly in motion, wildly shifting and twisting with abandon. In fact, thinking back over the other cores she'd come into contact with, she couldn't think of any that had moved as fast as her magical core moved. Even the core that was lightning surrounded by storm clouds hadn't seemed so restless and unpredictable, and though she had encountered a core that was a tornado at heart, and had been moving pretty quickly, the winds had all been blowing the same way, in a circle, ordered. Her magic looked rather a mess in comparison, as if it had the barest seeming of order to hold it together.

"I suppose you're right," Harry said, "But try doing what I did to your core, so we can see if the adults were right."

"I don't know," Archie looked dubiously at the ball of roiling fire-snakes before him, "My magical core wasn't nearly so intimidating."

Harry frowned, "I know it looks sort of wild, but it feels like the warmest, most comforting fire, like a snug blanket or like Dad's most worn-out cloak." She put her hands to the core and felt the immediate tug as the coils wrapped around her wrists and fingers. They bathed her with light and Harry felt content, supported and protected, as well as energized and confident. She looked back, but Archie had not come any closer. She could tell he was struggling not to pull her back from the fire.

"I know it's strange, Arch, but remember when you pulled your hand back from the stream of magic and it wasn't wet? That's because it's not real water, just like this isn't real fire. It's just magical energy, manifesting as an element because of its affinity with the wild magic from nature."

"Magic can be just as destructive as fire," Archie pointed out, but he moved forward nonetheless, "So how did you make my mists move out of the way?"

"I didn't make them move," Harry said, "I asked."

"Okay," Archie approached her magical core determinedly, "Hi, Harry's magical core. I'm Archie, a good friend of Harry's." The core seemed to pulse toward him with interest, so he went on, "Would you mind moving out of the way? I'd like to see what Harry's magical core looks like underneath all this…lovely ropey stuff. I promise not to—ouch!" He jerked his hand back and hissed in pain, "It bit me!"

Harry whipped her head around to stare with confusion at her core, which was sure enough retracting a coil back toward the surface. It must have snaked around Archie's other side where Harry couldn't have seen it and zapped him or something. She glared at it, "Why'd you do that? He's my friend!" Harry turned to Archie, who was rubbing his hand irritably, "I'm sorry, Arch, I didn't know it would do that."

"It's okay, Harry," Archie said, "This is probably why other people don't try and do what you did to cure the sickness. I'm also starting to think you weren't exaggerating about your magic. It's sneaky."

"I thought we were getting along fine now," Harry sighed, "Does it still hurt?"

"Yes, but not as much. I think it was just warning me off," Archie said.

"Sorry," Harry said again, "I guess Snape was right about this at least. Good news is he had a legitimate reason for not believing me about it. Bad news is I'm officially a freak of nature."

"There are worse things to be," Archie said with a brittle kind of cheerfulness, "Let's go back to my magical core. I have a feeling if I put my hand back in my own core's river it will heal right up."

Harry forced a small smile, still feeling horribly guilty for hurting Archie, "Trust you to have a magical core that heals things."

"Better than a magical core that burns things," Archie teased. He closed his eyes and projected himself back along the connection to his core, and missed the pained flinch Harry gave at his words.

Is that true? Harry wondered as she broke off the connection between them, Is fire really only good for burning things?

When they got back to the Library, Archie shrugged off the incident as a failed experiment. He began going into the theory behind the Healing she'd been learning, teaching her faster and less painful applications of that theory in practice all afternoon. Learning to Heal properly, not just asking her magic to knit this and repair that without understanding what was happening, was tedious and mind-numbing work, but it made her feel that maybe a person's magical core didn't define them. If she could do good things, soft things, as well as scary destructive things with her magic, then the element at her core didn't really mean anything. Did it?

Harry went looking for her father in his study the next day to see if her mum had talked to him about the owl-correspondence classes she wanted to take. It was essential to her plans for the future that her parents agree to the classes, to throw off suspicion for the next part of that plan. She needed a reason to seem busy over the summer, because she was going to be very, very busy if everything worked out like she hoped.

Her dad's study looked more like a broken toy shop, because it was where all the products for the Marauder joke line were born. James, Remus, and Sirius were always moving in and out of the study in their free time, depending on who was working on the latest and greatest pranking tricks at the time. She found her dad hunched over something she couldn't see in his hand when she walked cautiously through the door. Her caution was justified by the number of times she'd walked into a demonstration of a new product, and this time was no exception—though it was certainly more literal than usual. She only took one step in the door before she ran smack into an invisible barrier of some kind and was repelled backwards onto her butt rather rudely.

James looked up and grinned apologetically. He reached over to snag a remote control off of his desk and clicked it twice. "You can come in now," he said, "Sorry about that."

Harry rubbed her backside ruefully, "I can't tell if that was an item from a new prank kit or your Auror's kit, Dad, but it definitely works."

Her dad laughed, "Doesn't it though? It's a remote-controlled mobile barrier. Sirius and I designed it. The joke is that you plant this on someone," he held up an ordinary, two-holed button, "And when you're out of the barrier's range, you activate it. It's completely invisible, but it repels anything with a magical core, so basically any witch or wizard, away from the button if they come within five feet of it. Imagine, you put this in your friend's pocket, turn it on, and anyone who gets five feet from him is knocked backwards instantly. It looks like he's the one doing it, but he can't control it because you've got the remote. Pretty funny, huh?"

"What will you call it?" Harry asked curiously. She could think of a few other uses for such a button.

"The Barrier Bubble Button?" James suggested, "Hmm, maybe Lily will have some ideas—she's good at naming things. Anyway, did you come here for something?"

"Yeah, did Mum ask you about me taking owl-correspondence courses over the summer?" Harry asked.

"She did," James said, setting the button and remote in a desk drawer absently, "I think you work way too hard, but I'd definitely get the worst parent of the year award if I forbid you from educating yourself when that's what you want to do. Just take the gold you need for the classes out of the account we set up for you when you started school last year. We'll consider it an educational expense just like textbooks for AIM and potions ingredients."

"Thanks, Dad," Harry stepped forward to hug her father tightly, "I really appreciate it."

"Hey, no problem," James said, wrapping his arms around her just as firmly, "You're my little Fawn, and if you want to change the world with a cauldron, well, I think that's just as good as changing it with a wand. In fact it's more impressive, because everyone uses wands, but not many people can brew like you can."

Harry looked up at her dad in shock. He almost never complimented her potions work. She knew it was a leftover from he and Sirius hating Severus Snape all those years, and by default viewing everything associated with his school rival with distaste, so she'd never blamed him for not supporting her quite as much as Remus and Lily had. For him to say this though…

"You're really okay with it?" she asked seriously, "I know it's not what you and mum were best at in school, but I really can't imagine myself doing anything else."

"Of course I'm okay with it," James said, smoothing her hair down reflexively, "I'm sorry I haven't been more involved in the past. I half-thought that you were only so interested in potions because it was the only magic you could do without a wand. I sort of thought once you went to school and learned about all the other kinds of magic, you'd get bored of potions, which you already knew so well, and become more interested in learning new kinds of magic. It was silly of me, though, and I can see now that it means much more to you than an interest or a hobby. If you need anything to help you reach your Mastery, just ask, okay?"

"Okay," Harry smiled, not a little smile, but a big, bright one, and leaned up to kiss her dad on the cheek, "You're the best dad ever."

"I know," James grinned, "And don't tell anyone, but you're my favourite daughter."

"That means a lot to me, Dad," Harry said solemnly.

They shared another smile, and then Harry stepped back.

"I'm going to sign up for the courses I want to take, then," she said, "Thanks again, Dad."

"Thank your mother, too," James called after her retreating form.

"I will," she promised, and she closed the door behind her.

Phase One: complete success.

Harry went in search of her mother and found her in the kitchen, charming the placemats different colours.

"Harry, is that you?" Lily smiled as she looked up from her work, "Oh good, come here and tell me what you think. I'm tired of the old pattern, but I can't decide on a new one."

Harry walked over to the table and looked at all the patterns Lily had laid out on it. Mostly they leaned toward blues and greens. She guessed her mother must really be tired of the old one, which had been a deep burgundy.

"I like this one," Harry said, pointing to a pale blue pattern with bronze flowers dancing along the edges, "The dishes are bronze, so it won't clash."

"Good point," Lily tilted her head, twirling a strand of her beautiful red hair around her finger, "That one it is, then." She waved her wand and turned all the placemats on the table to match the pattern Harry had picked out, and then tucked the wand in the sleeve of her robes. "So what's up, Harry?"

"Just wanted to thank you for talking to Dad about me doing extra school work this summer," Harry smiled gratefully and Lily patted her cheek.

"Of course, dear. What classes were you—" Lily was cut off by the kitchen door being flung open suddenly.

Archie came bounding into the kitchen, dusted with enough soot that Harry thought he probably hadn't bothered to brush himself off after coming through the floo.

"Harry, are you in here? I just got a—oh, hi, Aunt Lily," Archie faltered at the sight of the older woman, "How are you today?"

"I'm just fine, Archie," Lily said, crossing her arms over her chest and staring the boy down, "And what exactly has you running so excitedly into my kitchen?"

"Oh, um," Archie glanced anxiously at Harry, "I just wanted to tell Harry something."

"Something that you can't say in front of your dear Aunt Lily?" Lily asked reproachfully.

"Of course not, Aunt Lily," Archie said, laughing weakly, "I just didn't want to take up your free time with something so trivial. I know how hard you work during the week."

"Well, now I'm curious," Lily said blithely, "So tell us what's so exciting."

Archie swallowed, "Okay, sure. Well, I got a letter today from my, uh, friend Draco. He's invited me to a party next month, and I just wanted to tell Harry about it so that she could help me find something to…wear."

"You wanted to ask Harry, our Harry, for…fashion advice?" Lily repeated sceptically.

"Hey," Harry put in jokingly, "I didn't do so bad on those placemats, did I? Besides, you know Archie's learned everything he knows about fashion from Sirius. He might go in purple pinstripes if we don't help him."

Lily laughed, "Well, when you put it like that."

"Yep, I'm hopeless," Archie said, nodding, "You'll help me find something, won't you guys?"

"Of course," Lily said, "May I see the invitation?"

Archie took a gilded square of parchment from his pocket and handed it over. Harry leaned in to read it as well.

Arcturus Rigel Black

Is cordially invited to

The Malfoys'

Annual summer garden party

July 15

In addition

Mr. Draco Malfoy

Will be celebrating his twelfth year on this date

Floo and Apparition coordinates enclosed

Harry raised her eyebrows, but it was Lily who let out a shocked gasp.

"The Malfoys' Summer Party? You've been invited to this, Archie? Oh my, that's really unexpected," Lily ran a hand through her hair as she gave the invitation back to Archie. "The Malfoys must be taking the life debt they owe you much more seriously than we'd anticipated."

"What do you mean?" Harry asked, "It's just a party invitation."

Lily shook her head, "No, this is a formal invitation to a formal dark pureblood party. In the past, select light-sided families also received invitations, but since the Split no light family has attended a dark pureblood event, and vice-versa. Society is supposed to be completely separated at this point, except for those families that remain neutral, of course."

"But since they made Archie a Malfoy in name until the life debt is fulfilled, Archie is considered to be a dark pureblood as well as a light pureblood, socially speaking," Harry said, understanding suddenly why Lily was so surprised. "The fact that the Malfoys actually invited him to the event as if he were a dark pureblood means that they're sticking by their words and treating him like a Malfoy, ignoring the fact that he's the son of a light-sided pureblood."

"Yes, exactly," Lily said thoughtfully. "I suppose it probably helps that you were sorted into Slytherin, Archie. People will be less likely to put up a fuss if you go. If you were Arthur Weasley's son…well, let's just say it would be a different story."

"If he goes?" Harry said, slightly alarmed, "He has to go. Surely it would be really rude to refuse. It is Draco's birthday party."

"Uh, yeah," Archie said, "I really do want to go. Do you think Dad will let me?"

"I'm not sure," Lily said, "I'll invite everyone over for dinner tonight and we'll discuss it, okay?"

"Okay," Archie said.

Dinner that night was an awkward affair.

"I don't like it," James said, stabbing a carrot rather violently with his fork, "Sending Archie into the hornet's nest, that's what it is."

"Darling, it's an extremely public event. No one would try anything in the open like that," Lily said soothingly, "Archie will be perfectly safe there, I'm sure."

"Maybe," James allowed reluctantly, "But you can't be too careful with dark purebloods."

"It won't be all dark purebloods," Remus pointed out fairly, "A lot of ministry officials are invited every year, and those aligned with the ministry tend to stay out of light and dark politics by remaining neutral."

"All my friends will be there," Archie said tentatively after a pleading look from Harry, "It's Draco's birthday celebration after all, and Pansy, Theo, Millicent, and Blaise will probably all go."

Sirius toyed with his vegetables while he thought, "I don't want to keep you from your friends, Arch, I'm just worried about sending you by yourself, surrounded by political enemies, where I can't help you if you need it."

"Is it so different from sending him to school in the Slytherin dorms?" Lily said tentatively, "Those children are all dark purebloods, but Archie's made good friends of them."

"It's not the same as letting him go unchaperoned to a gathering of adult, fully-fledged dark witches and wizards," Sirius said apologetically, "There are teachers at school to watch out for trouble, and kids aren't nearly so ingrained in their prejudices and hatred as adults are."

Harry thought it was time for her to speak up, "Weren't we just the other day saying it was too bad Archie couldn't have his friends over for his birthday, because we didn't think their parents would trust our families to look after their Heirs? Now we're doing the same thing. Trust has to start somewhere, doesn't it? Why can't we be the bigger people, and trust that Archie's friends will watch out for him? Flint will probably be there, and Archie has known him forever. We can trust him to look out for Archie at least."

The part about Flint was a complete lie, as he wasn't exactly the protective older brother type, but Harry thought the rest of it was actually a good point.

"Archie also admitted he didn't really need to see his friends, because he's seen them all year," James protested somewhat half-heartedly.

"I said I didn't need to have my friends with me on my birthday," Archie corrected, "But that doesn't mean Draco should have to spend his birthday without one of his best friends because my family doesn't trust me to take care of myself."

"It's not that we don't trust you," James said quickly, "It's them we're worried about."

"How can we ask them to trust us if we don't trust them?" Archie said firmly, "It's like Harry said. If we want to tell ourselves we're different from the dark purebloods, then we have to act differently. Let me go as a gesture of goodwill, if my going to my best friend's birthday party has to be something political."

Harry took a bite of potatoes to hide her smile. Archie was really persuasive when he wanted to be, and he wasn't afraid to play dirty in a debate, like insinuating they didn't trust him and playing the 'kid who just wants to go to his friend's party' card.

Sirius sighed, "Do you promise not to make friends with any politicians?"

Archie whooped and Harry smiled victoriously.

"I promise," Archie said immediately.

"Then I guess you can go, but you're taking the emergency portkey," Sirius said firmly.

"Good idea, Dad," Archie said happily.

Harry spoke up before anyone could change their mind, "If Archie gets to go to his friend's house, I want to go see Hermione that day, too."

"That seems fair," Lily said, looking bemused at Harry, "You could have asked anytime if you wanted to go and see her, though."

"I want to spend time at home first," Harry shrugged, "But by July I'll probably want to see Hermione."

"Well, that's settled then," Remus said cheerfully, "Sirius, this lobster is delicious, did you add something to the sauce?"

Harry and Archie shared a smile across the table. She would have to remember to get Archie something really awesome for his birthday this year.

Archie interrupted Harry's studying Occlumency in the Black Library the next day and dragged her outside to the courtyard. The snakes hissed their greetings and Harry stroked a few of them absently while Archie geared himself up to talk.

"Harry," he said finally, "I've been thinking, about everything, and I'm a little worried."

"Okay," Harry said, "I can't blame you for being concerned about what we're doing, but what exactly are you worried about?"

"It's just, this whole deception could be so easily unveiled as soon as someone really looks," Archie said, sitting down in the grass and plucking some of it absently, "I feel like it's only been successful so far because no one would think to look for such a deception."

"In a way, you're right," Harry said, "A lot of this depends on the fact that no one would expect a halfblood to ever dare to do what we've done, and they definitely wouldn't expect a pureblood to help a halfblood, which is the only way this could work. Even so, that hasn't changed. It was always true, so why are you worried now?"

"Before we were anonymous. No one wondered if Rigel Black was all he seemed, because why wouldn't he be? But now you've cured the sleeping sickness. You've said Professor Snape, one of the smartest men I've ever heard of, has taken an interest in you. The Malfoys owe you a life debt, for Merlin's sake." Archie brushed a curious snake away from his robe sleeve impatiently, "Now that people are looking, what if they notice something's off? Maybe we can get through this summer without anyone in our family getting suspicious that we only want to meet our friends on the same days, but the next summer? And the one after that? And what about the school year? How long can you keep pretending to be me—to be a boy? You're going to start your girly changes soon. And do you really think no one at AIM in seven years will hear that Harry Potter is a girl? All it would take is one person, one person who sees us both at school and not at school, and from there everything else is obvious."

"Is it?" Harry said, taking Archie's hand to stop him from ripping up more grass, "Is it obvious? Or does it only seem obvious to us, because we know exactly what's going on?"

"What do you mean?"

"I've been thinking about things too," Harry said, "And I've got a few things worked out. There are several major problems we're going to face, but I've got a plan to address each of them, okay? First is the problem of our lives at home and our lives at school being noticeably different. What if one of us got our picture in the paper? Either our friends from school or our parents would immediately know something was up. This would be easier if we were twins instead of just cousins who sort of look alike, wouldn't it?"

"Yes, I guess if we looked the same it would be easier to trade off personas," Archie said, frowning.

"Then that's what we have to make happen," Harry said, "I've been toying with the idea for a while, and this summer I'm going to start experimenting. I want to create a potion that will…blend our appearances, sort of, though not equally. It's hard to explain, but it would be semi-permanent in theory and it would allow us to look exactly alike in the end, which would mean that if someone saw us out of our usual context we could still get away with our pretense. I'll explain it further once I get it more figured out, but if the potion works it would also solve the problem of me starting to look noticeably feminine in a couple of years. It would blend our physiques in a way that made me look more masculine. I'll give you the full write up later, but suffice to say it would go a long way toward helping our plan work."

"Okay, you're the potions girl, so I'll let you handle that," Archie said, shaking his head, "Just so long as I don't actually have to become a girl."

"No, too many people know you as a boy at AIM already," Harry waved him off, "But that's okay. The second major problem comes if somebody finds out, right?"

"Yeah," Archie agreed, "If they figure out what we've done, you'll go to Azkaban."

"Yes, if they find out that Harry Potter took your place at Hogwarts, I'll go to prison," Harry said, "But if they find out any other possible combination of the truth, everything will be okay."

"How's that?"

"I have a back-up plan," Harry said, smiling slightly, "That's why you've been so worried, I think. The only thing this plan was missing is a plan B, to make sure that even if something goes wrong, we're still okay."

Archie nodded thoughtfully, "Security would be nice. So what's the back-up plan?"

"It's horridly complicated," Harry said cheerfully, "Feel free to be impressed. There are several phases to the plan. In the first phase, I enroll now in an owl-correspondence school. Wait, don't interrupt," she said to Archie's sceptical looks, "Just listen, it will all make sense. Mum and Dad think I'm enrolling in summer classes, but they've given me leave to pull the money for the classes out of my school account, which draws directly from their main vault, meaning they won't know or care how much money goes toward tuition as long as the goblins are sending it to the correspondence school they've approved of."

"So you're not just taking summer classes?" Archie guessed.

"I'm enrolling as a full-time student," Harry said proudly.

"You're sort of already a full-time student," Archie pointed out.

"Exactly. I'm not going to actually learn anything from the owl-correspondence school," Harry explained, "I can learn way more at a real school like Hogwarts. I'm just going to receive the materials in the mail, pretend to learn them, and send the assignments and tests back to get credit for the work. Since I'm already learning everything at Hogwarts, doing the assignments will be cake, but I'll have records saying that Harry Potter has been home schooling herself since she was eleven, get it?"

"Sort of," Archie said slowly, "So if someone finds out I'm at AIM taking your place and wonders where you are, you can say you're home schooled."

"Yes, but that's not enough," Harry went on, "Because our parents and anyone who knows our parents will know that I am not, in fact, home during the school year. That's why I'm going to answer this."

Harry reached into her pocket and pulled out the worn advertisement from the Daily Prophet she'd been carrying around for a few days. She smoothed the creases and handed it to Archie, who read over it with mild bewilderment.

"It's an ad for an apothecary," he noted, "They need a basic potion brewer."

"Yes," Harry said, taking the ad back and stowing it in her robes once more, "I'm going to apply for the position tomorrow, and if I get it I'm going to use the money to buy an apartment."

"An apartment?" Archie stared at her.

"Well, rent one anyway," Harry said, "I'll take a really cheap place out in my name, pay the rent on it during the school year, and if Harry Potter has an apartment and a home-school record while Rigel Black is at Hogwarts how can they be the same person? Especially if no one finds out that Rigel Black is a girl, and if the potion works then the minute we're caught I change back to my real appearance and Rigel Black disappears!"

Archie was silent for a whole minute. "Disappears? Will people buy that?"

"I actually got the inspiration from Marcus Flint," Harry said, grinning, "When he realized I wasn't you I thought we were done for, but he didn't immediately think—oh that must be Harry Potter. Of course he didn't. He thought I was just some random halfblood who you got to take your place so you could go to AIM. Why does Rigel Black have to be you or me? He doesn't. He'll just vanish if anyone figures out the truth, and Harry Potter will have been there all along, home-schooling herself in a little apartment so that her cousin Archie could take her place at AIM and fulfill his dreams of becoming a Healer."

"That's…really brilliant," Archie breathed, "If we're found out, I get a slap on the wrist for pretending to be you—it's not a serious crime to pretend to be a halfblood, and I'll just pay a fine and have all my records as Harry Potter transferred over into my name. Rigel Black, the real criminal, can't be punished because he doesn't exist."

"And we have complete plausible deniability. Better yet, our family has plausible deniability," Harry said earnestly, "You say that you did ask someone to take your place at Hogwarts—a pureblood from somewhere on the continent who was too poor to afford the tuition himself. You offered to pay his way if he pretended to be you at Hogwarts so you could go to AIM without your dad knowing. He wasn't on the list for Hogwarts because he isn't from Great Britain, and you don't know who he really is. You definitely thought he was a pureblood though, so you can't be blamed as an accomplice to blood-identity theft. Our parents can honestly say they had no idea you were in America and I was being home schooled, and that they don't know who Rigel Black is either."

"It's practically air-tight," Archie admitted, letting out his breath with a whoosh of air, "But you know it's going to be nearly impossible to pull off. You can't take money for the apartment from your account because it's clearly not an educational expense, so you'll have to come up with the money solely through working. But if you're going to be completing home-school assignments and experimenting with an entirely new potion…I don't see how you'll have time for all of this in one summer."

Harry just smiled, "You'd be surprised how many things I can juggle at once. This past year has been excellent practice. Brewing is easy and I can set my own hours. I'm not actually learning anything, just completing busy work for the owl-school, which leaves me plenty of time for experimentation."

"Well, you sound pretty sure," Archie said, relaxing back into the grass at last, "If you need any help, you know you only have to ask. In the meantime I'm going to try and find a way to make money too, so I can help pay for the apartment that neither of us will actually be living in." He smirked, "At least our utility bill will be cheap."

"So we're agreed on this cover story?" Harry asked, "When we get the plan in place, as soon as one of us is found out, the other has to be ready to implement the back-up plan. As long as both Harry Potter and Archie Black are accounted for when the game is up and Rigel disappears, it'll be next to impossible for anyone to prove anything for sure."

Archie agreed and they shook on it. Archie then went to read up on Occlumency, since all of their work would mean nothing if someone just plucked the secret out of their heads, and Harry went to enroll herself in owl-school.

The next day Harry told her parents she was going to Diagon Alley to pick up a new order of potions ingredients. This was a common occurrence for Harry, who went through potions ingredients like nobody's business when the mood struck her, so her parents just reminded her to use her school account to pay for them (if it was an educational expense they could write the galleons off in their taxes), and asked her to pick up a new pot of floo powder while she was out.

Harry flooed into the Leaky Cauldron and set off down the familiar street to the apothecary she usually frequented on Diagon Alley. It wasn't the apothecary that had advertised for a brewer, but she really did need to pick up an order of ingredients that had come in, so she stopped there first.

The man behind the counter perked up as she walked in. He was large and burly, with curly brown hair pulled back into a messy ponytail. He wore an apron that bulged at the pockets from being stuffed with various things he picked up around the store throughout the day and never bothered to put back down again. She had never seen him when he was anything less than jovial, and sure enough he smiled broadly as his warm brown eyes caught sight of her and called out in a cheerful manner, "There she is; I knew I'd be seeing my favourite little customer today!"

Harry smiled back and closed the door politely behind her so that she sunlight didn't get into the shop too much. Certain ingredients could be rather sensitive to sunlight, and though those ingredients were always kept away from the doors and windows, it never hurt to be careful.

"Hello, Mr. Tate," Harry said, approaching the counter, "It's good to see you too."

"Always too polite, Miss Potter," Mr. Tate wagged a finger at her good naturedly, "I have your order though. Got it just this morning and I just knew you'd be here to claim it before the day was done."

"You know me too well, Mr. Tate," Harry said, smiling slightly, "I despair of ever surprising you."

"That's one of the things I like about you, Miss Potter," Tate chuckled, "Surprises are only interesting for the young."

"Were there any troubles with the order?" Harry asked.

"No, no," he reached under the counter to pull out a well-packaged box, "Everything came in just fine. I double checked on the soil for the flitterbloom like you asked, and the greenhouse we order it from was very helpful. They gave me a list of the components, which I included with the rest of the order for you to look over when you get home. They did tell me to tell you that the formula for their soil has a magical patent, so don't try and reproduce, blah blah you get it."

"Yes, thank you," Harry grinned, "I'm not going to be entering the soil market at this time."

"Is this all you're picking up today?" Tate asked as he rang up her order.

"You sell floo powder here, don't you?" Harry asked, looking around.

"We have the generic brand," Tate shrugged.

"That'll work," Harry said, "Can you ring it up separately? I'll pay for the floo in coin, but I have to pay for the ingredients—"

"With your school account, I know, Miss Potter," Tate smiled kindly, "Sure thing."

He rang her up and Harry paid, putting the floo powder into the box of ingredients to make it easier to carry.

"Anything else I can help you with today, Miss Potter?"

"Actually, could you give me directions to the Serpent's Storeroom?" Harry asked.

Mr. Tate frowned cautiously, "Is there an ingredient you're having trouble finding, Miss Potter? You know I'd order anything you want, no need to go all the way over there."

"Oh, no, Mr. Tate," Harry smiled, "I'm not taking my business there, I assure you. Everyone knows the best ingredients come through Mulpepper Apothecary. I found this in the paper, though." She pulled out the notice from the paper and showed it to Mr. Tate.

"Oh, looking for a summer job, are you?" Mr. Tate said, looking a bit more relaxed, "Well, I guess I can see how this would appeal to you. The Serpent's Storeroom, though…it's not exactly a place I'd like to be sending you, Miss Potter. The shop's okay of course, but the location…"

"I understand, Mr. Tate," Harry said, "I just really need the money for a personal project I'm working on. I'll be very careful, I promise."

"Alright," Tate huffed, "I suppose it's not really that far into Knockturn Alley. You go straight there and straight back to Diagon Alley, okay, Miss Potter?"

"I will," Harry promised.

"Good," Tate said, "You know where Knockturn Alley branches off from Diagon Alley?" Harry nodded. "Well, when you turn down the alley, go past Borgin and Burkes to the first alley that intersects Knockturn's main alley. Turn left and the Serpent's Storeroom is the first shop on your left. It has a dark red sign with black letters and the Staff of Asclepius on the window."

Harry smiled gratefully, "Thanks, Mr. Tate. I'd hate to wander around looking for it."

"No kidding," Tate sighed, "Well, best of luck Miss Potter. In fact," he reached over and plucked a business card from its holder on the side of the desk, "Take this and tell that sourpuss Edgar Krait that Caleb Tate recommends you."

"Really, Mr. Tate?" Harry blinked in surprise as she took the card automatically, "Thank you very much. I promise I'm a good brewer, so you won't be wasting your recommendation."

Tate laughed jovially once more, "Oh, Miss Potter, nothing spent on you is wasted, be it time or ingredients, that much I know."

"Thanks again, Mr. Tate," Harry picked up her package, "I'll be by sometime next week to make another order I expect."

"Looking forward to it, Miss Potter. Good luck on your job application."

Harry smiled once more and put the box of ingredients under her left arm so that her right would be free to open the door—and more importantly free to draw her wand should it become necessary. If nothing else, she had learned a pretty mean shield charm that year, no thanks to Professor Quirrell.

Knockturn Alley was everything she'd ever heard it was. Dirty, creepy, smelly, and dark, shadows lurked everywhere, though it was the middle of the day. Harry walked calmly but purposefully down the alley, staying to the middle of the road where there was at least a semblance of afternoon light. She passed Borgin and Burkes and turned left like Mr. Tate had told her, and sure enough there on her left was the gloomy Serpent's Storeroom Apothecary.

Harry didn't linger in the little side alley long. She entered the shop and paused for a moment to adjust her eyes to the incredibly dim lighting. There was a counter to the left, raised up on a platform that would give anyone standing behind it a very good view of the narrow aisles of stock to her right. There were also mirrors positioned all over the shop, and Harry thought a shoplifter would be hard put to get away with anything in here. The aisles closest to the door held what looked at a casual glance to be the cheapest of ingredients, with more expensive, more rare ingredients sold in the middle aisles. The aisles at the back held completed potions in decorative bottles.

Harry turned toward the counter and took in the man sitting behind it, counting armadillo scales into a jar. He was tall even sitting down and had thick blond hair slicked back from his face. His frame was thin, but hard, like a habitual fighter's would be, and he had a scar along his jaw line that disappeared into the collar of his plain lab robes.

"Are you Mr. Krait?" she asked as she reached the counter. Because it was elevated, she felt at a distinct disadvantage looking up at the man behind it.

"Who asks?" he drummed his free hand on the counter as he spoke.

"I do," Harry said, thinking it would be best to get straight to the point with this man, "I'm here about the brewing job. Has the position been filled?"

"No it has not," the man, who she assumed was Mr. Krait, said without even looking up from his scale counting, "But I don't see what my staff shortage has to do with a brat like you."

"I am a potions brewer," she said.

"Says who?" Krait grumbled absently.

"Says Mr. Tate," Harry said shortly. Krait finally looked up at her with eyes that were an earthy green. "He recommends me," she added, pulling out the card Tate had given her and passing it over. Mr. Krait took the card and threw it into the trashcan behind the counter without ever taking his eyes away from her face.

"What can you brew?" Krait asked, leaning over the counter as if he could inspect her brewing ability by staring down at her intently enough.

"If I have a recipe?" she shrugged, "Probably about anything you'd need me to. I assume you brew all the top-level potions yourself."

"Hn," Krait grunted, "Sure you can. Look, this ain't grade-school cooking lessons, got it? You can't just add the ingredients together and stir if you want to—"

"With respect, Mr. Krait, I know how to brew," Harry said evenly.

Krait raised an eyebrow, "Can you consciously imbue? And if you say 'what?' to me I swear I'm gonna kick Tate's arse into next week for sending you over here."

"I can," Harry said.

"What's the highest level potion you've ever brewed?" he asked, looking only a little less dismissive.

"Snowhit Draught," Harry said; it was definitely the hardest thing she'd brewed, requiring both the most concentration and the most magic.

"Not bad," Krait rubbed his chin, "If you're not lying, that is."

Harry opened her mouth to speak but he waved her silent.

"Tell you what, kid. I'll give you a list of potions and a crate of my bottles. You buy the ingredients, brew and bottle the potions, and bring whatever you finish back here. I don't care which potions you make. I need them all done sooner or later, so just brew whichever you think you can." He drew out a remarkably thick tube of rolled up parchment from a drawer behind the counter and handed it over. "I'll pay you by the bottle, thirty percent labouring fee guaranteed for you. If it takes you ten sickles to make one dose, you'll get thirteen sickles from me, with a bonus if it's magically grueling. I'll sell them at two galleons to cover the bottle and make a profit, and if your potions sell good enough you get an additional bonus. Any questions?'

Harry unrolled the stack of parchment he'd given her and saw that the first sheet was a list of potions and the rest of the sheets were recipes. "How much of each potion do you want?"

"Don't care," he said, "If you can only brew one of those potions, bring me back a crate of that."

Harry nodded and said, "Give me two crates of bottles."

Krait fixed her with a stern eye, "You run off with those bottles and I'll hunt you down, kid."

"Understood," Harry said, though she wasn't sure how he expected to do that without ever having asked her name.

Krait glanced around the store to make sure there were no customers before ducking quickly into the back to fetch the crates of potion bottles. Harry stacked the crates and added her box of ingredients to the top. Next time she thought she ought to bring Archie with her, as walking down Knockturn Alley with her hands full was probably not a good idea, but for now she just walked as quickly as she could back to the relative safety of Diagon Alley.

Harry didn't relax fully until she was back in the Leaky Cauldron. She set the crates briefly on the ground while she tossed some floo powder into the grate, and soon enough she was back at the Godric's Hollow house, storing the crates and ingredients in the potions lab that she had unashamedly claimed as her own despite it technically belonging to her mother. Lily didn't use the lab nearly as much as Harry did, and most of the actual ingredients in the lab were Harry's, though her mother had bought the cauldrons and equipment.

She went to replenish the floo powder supply with what she'd bought and stopped by the kitchen to pick up her mail on the way back to the lab. Her parents usually left owl post on the kitchen counter, and Harry smiled as she spied a thick letter from Sphinx Correspondence School of Magic with her name on it. She took the letter down to the lab with her and slit it open with her finger as she claimed a metal stool.

She skimmed the contents. It was a basic introductory letter, followed by the first year learning curriculum and a syllabus spread out over the next ten months. Harry would be cutting that down to two months. Her goal was to finish the first year's curriculum by the end of the summer, so that she wouldn't be distracted by it during school, when she would be completing Flint's assignments as well as her own, and also so that no one at school would catch her doing the work. The whole point of doing this was that the correspondence school was something Harry Potter did that Rigel Black did not.

She would finish the assignments for the first units that weekend. For now, Harry was ready to brew. She unrolled the list of potions Mr. Krait had given her with an expression that was nearly gleeful. Thankful that no one was around to see her childish excitement, she read over the list carefully.

Agnes' Ageless Agent

Befuddlement Draught

Blood-Replenishing Potion

Calming Draught

Deflating Draught

Dreamless Sleep Potion

Forgetfulness Potion

Gasnik's Gastric Solution

Hair-Growth Potion

Invigoration Draught

Mind-Sharpening Potion

Numbing Potion

Pepper-Up Potion

Shrinking Solution

Telbert's Tincture

Westfield's Wart Remover

Harry raised her eyebrows at the list. Most of it looked like what you might find in any witch or wizard's medicine cabinet. She smiled a bit at her foolishness. What had she been expecting, deadly poisons? Of course he wouldn't give recipes for poisons to a kid, even if he did sell them in the open where anyone from the ministry could pop in and see.

She glanced over the crates. There were two dozen bottles in each crate, meaning she could make three bottles of each of the sixteen potions if she wanted to fill the crates. Unfortunately, one cauldron usually made about 5-6 doses of a potion, so she didn't have enough bottles to make a cauldron of each potion on the list. Instead she would pick eight potions to start with and make a cauldron of each. She would try the second half of the list once she got more bottles.

She started with Blood-Replenishing Potion, something she knew a lot about but had never actually tried brewing. After treating her cauldron with the necessary oil, she got to work hand-filtering the raw dragon's bile she kept in a tightly sealed container to prevent leakage.

Blood-Replenishing Potion turned out to be easier than she was expecting it to be. In fact, she found herself almost bored as she waited between steps, probably because she was so conditioned from the last semester to be making as many potions as possible at one time. She finished stirring the last turn and checked the final result against the recipe's description. It was a rusty red the consistency of water just like it was supposed to be, but Harry felt a vague feeling of unease about the potion still. Thinking it was probably that she hadn't imbued enough magic after all, she reached out with her senses to re-forge the connection between her core and the potion once more to double-check. Through the connection, however, she knew immediately that the potion was magically speaking complete. In actuality she thought she'd put a bit too much magic in the potion, though of course that wouldn't hurt a blood-replenisher.

Still, something wasn't right. She reached out with her senses to look over it again, and this time she noticed something that surprised her considerably. The current connecting her core to the potion was telling her that the Blood-Replenishing Potion was complete magically, but incomplete physically. That had never happened before—not after she'd finished the recipe at any rate. What did it mean? Had she skipped a step? She sharpened her connection to the potion, trying to figure out what the magic was telling her. It was like the potion knew what was wrong, if only she could understand. She checked the recipe. She'd completed every step perfectly, that much she was certain of, and yet there was a problem. Though the potion looked to her eyes to be all right, to her magic it felt as though it were a puzzle that had come with a piece already missing, so even though she'd used all the pieces, the picture wasn't quite right.

It was the recipe, she realized with dawning incredulity. The recipe itself was wrong…or, maybe not wrong, but incomplete ever so slightly. Not enough to change the appearance of the potion, but enough that it irked her magical senses. Harry shook her head agitatedly. Honestly, what fool of a Potions Master had come up with this recipe? Bonagage? Professor Snape had never given her a recipe that was less than perfect. Harry supposed she could write to Snape and ask for his recipe for Blood-Replenishing Potion, but something was telling her she could figure it out herself. She just needed to think.

It felt like it needed more of something, Harry mused, concentrating her senses on the different layers of the potion. Everything mixed just fine, but if there was just a bit more of…something, it would mesh completely. Harry frowned, reaching with her senses further into the potion and sort of magically poking around. It almost felt like it needed more bloodroot, but that couldn't possibly be right. The bloodroot was in perfect proportion to the vervain, which had to stay at a constant 3:1 ratio with the hypericum flowers. She couldn't change the number of hypericum flowers because it had to be a prime number, and the next prime number after 13 was 17. If she added 4 more hypericum flowers she could need 12 more vervain leaves, which would make the amount of bloodroot needed way too much. She needed a tiny bit more bloodroot, not a whole additional bushel.

So it couldn't be the bloodroot. And yet it was. The potion felt like it needed more antiseptic, and also something that would bond the dissolving St. Stewart's Bane with the Hypericum flowers more closely. Bloodroot did both of those things, but it was too potent. Adding even the tiniest bit more would upset the whole potion. Harry blinked suddenly. It was so obvious. Hadn't she thought all those months ago when she was helping Percy with his Potion Fusion homework that feverfew was pretty perfect for a Blood-Replenishing Potion? Harry smiled victoriously, she didn't need to substitute feverfew for bloodroot though, she needed to add feverfew to the bloodroot. Both would play pretty much the same role in the potion, but feverfew was three times weaker than bloodroot, and adding it wouldn't mess with the ratios of the other ingredients. In addition, feverfew kept platelets from clumping. The only reason it hadn't been in the Blood-Replenishing Potion already was probably because bloodroot was so much stronger and easier to cultivate.

Harry hurried to her A-F storage cupboard and dug out the jar of ground feverfew from the bottom shelf. A pinch was all it took, and after a few stirs the potion felt…satisfied, for lack of a better word, to her magical senses. Harry grinned and broke off her connection to the potion gently, then ladled it carefully into six of Krait's stasis bottles. She labeled each one, and after cleaning her cauldron and preparation materials she put a check mark beside Blood-Replenishing Potion on her list, feeling more self-satisfied than she had in weeks.

Harry spent the rest of the night brewing. Out of the eight recipes she tried, five of them were ever so slightly off, needing more of one thing or less of another, and one of the recipes was so blatantly wrong she was sure it had been copied incorrectly. Honestly, who would put ginger leaves in a Mind-Sharpening Potion? While ginger was a mental stimulant and energizer in the right mixtures, its properties came from the root and stem, not the leaves. In addition, besides the fact that the recipe called for the Chinese variety, which was much less potent than the African variety, the juice in the ginger leaves would have interacted with the rosemary seed oil and caused severe and likely permanent long-term memory loss. Harry immediately guessed they'd meant to write thirteen ginkgo leaves, which came from the Chinese Maidenhair tree and were known to improve memory functions.

She noted each change she made to the potions diligently, in case Krait should ask, and by midnight she had filled and labeled every bottle in the two crates she'd been given. Harry felt better than she had in weeks, despite the late hour. She had forgotten the joy of brewing just for the sake of making a potion. Too often in the past year it had been about making the grade, impressing Professor Snape, or saving students' lives. Sure, she was technically brewing for money, but she wasn't worried that if she messed up she wouldn't get the money. She was confident in her ability to produce enough potions to satisfy Krait, and she could try as many times as she needed to on the off-chance that she couldn't brew a potion right the first time, which hadn't happened often since she'd gotten the hang of imbuing. Harry could brew at her own pace, her own impetus. She could choose how long to brew, what order to brew the potions in, what changes to make until she was satisfied with the potions, and no one would say anything about it. It was freeing, relaxing, and thoroughly enjoyable.

Before going to bed. Harry drew up a schedule that would allow her to finish the first year's worth of owl-correspondence schoolwork in the nine weeks she had left of the summer. The program was self-paced, though the recommended timeframe was ten months on and two months off for each school year. She was given a list of books to read, most of which overlapped with the textbooks she already had for Hogwarts, and each of the six core subjects (Charms, Transfiguration, History, Defence, Potions, and Astronomy) had five units per semester. She would in theory learn the first five units for each class, take her midterms, then learn the next five units for each class and take her finals. In actuality, Harry would complete the mandatory work for the first five units, take the midterms, then do the mandatory work for the second five units and take the finals. There wasn't much she'd really need to learn.

When she started each unit, they would mail her a series of worksheets and suggested activities for each class to help her learn and understand the material. These worksheets and activities were entirely for her own benefit. Harry wouldn't be completing any of them. Instead, all Harry would be doing was writing the required research essay for each unit in each class. It was open-topic, as long as it pertained to the course, and the quality of her research essays would determine one third of her course grade for each class. The midterm and final made up the other two-thirds of each grade. That meant for Harry to pass her first year of owl-school, she had to complete six research essays per unit, or 60 essays in total, and take twelve exams. Her goal was to write six essays each week, taking a week off each for the midterm and finals, and finishing the first-year curriculum in eight weeks. That gave her an extra week to relax and prepare for her second year at Hogwarts.

While she was writing about an essay a day, a feat she had no trouble imagining possible considering the essay requirement for a first-year in the owl-school consisted of a mere 10-inches and two outside sources, she would also be brewing every day. Looking over the list of potions she was given, she averaged the cost of brewing a cauldron of them to be about three or four galleons each, meaning that each dose averaged about eleven sickles each. That meant she'd be getting about fifteen sickles per dose from Krait. That was a 96-sickle profit per crate, about five and a half galleons.

She figured she could rent an apartment for about 60 galleons a month, so she would need 570 galleons to cover the whole school year. That meant she needed to brew about 103 crates of potions that summer, or roughly 12 crates a week. That was doable if she brewed two crates a day.

However, that was only true if Harry was truly eating the cost of the potions she'd be making herself. Simply put, she was not. When her parents had set up an educational-expense account for her at Gringotts, it was with the understanding that she would charge all her potions expenses to that account. Her parents were incredibly wealthy, something she tried not to take for granted, but something that meant that they would not even notice the increase in her expenditures as long as they continued to come from apothecary orders and the like. So because she was buying the ingredients with her parents' money (she mentally argued that she was technically learning a lot by brewing all the new potions) and putting all of the 20-galleon reward per crate toward her private housing fund, Harry actually only needed to brew enough for thirty or so crates all summer.

So she was not, to be honest, overly concerned with the amount of work she'd taken on over the summer. Harry planned on having plenty of time for her experimental brewing, not to mention hanging out with Archie and her family and completing her Hogwarts summer work as well. By the time her mother came down to yawningly tell Harry to get her butt in bed, Harry had everything about her summer plans figured out. All she had to do was put them into motion, and really, what could go wrong?

The next day Harry went back to the Serpent's Storeroom with her crates of potions. Archie had left early that morning with Sirius and James to go to Zonko's and check on the Marauder joke line sales, so Harry went to Diagon Alley alone again, though she kept a careful eye out for any suspicious characters on her way from the Leaky Cauldron to the dingy little shop.

Mr. Krait was busy with a customer when Harry entered the shop, so she stacked the crates behind the counter and waited patiently for him to finish showing a stooped old witch with a hacking cough where the antimony was stored. Mr. Krait came back to the counter and saw Harry standing there. He stopped in front of her, crossing his arms and setting his feet apart as he looked her over. He was so tall she had to lean her head back a bit to look at his face.

"Well, I won't pretend I'm not surprised to see you here," he grunted, the scar along his jaw line flexing as he worked his mouth, "I half-expected to never see you again. What are you doing back so quick? Lost my bottles, have you?"

Harry shook her head, "No, sir. They're behind the counter. I'm here to pick up more bottles, and to collect my payment for these, unless you pay at the end of the month."

Krait's eyebrows shot upwards toward his slicked back blond hairline. He strode around the counter and hefted the crates easily up onto its surface. Krait scanned the labels in the crates and shot her a look, "You made eight potions yesterday? Eight different potions?"

Harry refrained from saying 'Obviously.' Barely.

"Yes, sir," Harry said instead, keeping her tone on the respectful side of stating something readily apparent, "I thought it would be a waste to do all sixteen when I didn't have enough bottles to hold all the doses."

Krait shot her a look that clearly said he caught the implied lip and didn't appreciate it. The Potioneer sighed and said, "I don't know what to think of this, kid." He gestured to the crates of potions on the counter. "If I didn't know Potions Masters were a bunch of stuck up swobs with the collective sense of humour of a rotting toadstool I'd think someone was playing a practical joke on me."

Harry thought at that moment that it was probably best that Krait didn't know who her father and godfather were.

"I mean," Krait rolled his shoulders as if he was working out a kink, "I just gave you these recipes yesterday, and somehow you have viable examples of eight? Ignoring the fact that it usually takes a brewer at least a week to work the kinks out of a recipe they aren't familiar with, most of these potions require upper-medium levels of magical energy to be imbued in them, and Dreamless Sleep is enough to knock the average wizard on their arse for a good four hours alone with the level of magic required to fuse the ingredients. You're what, ten? No way you have the magical core necessary to make all these potions in 24 hours."

Harry thought that was a bit unfair to assume, but Krait wasn't finished.

"Plus," he said with an incredulous snort, "Making Pepper-Up and an Invigoration Draught would use about a pound of Piper betel. Who the heck has that much betel just lying around? Your parents own a greenhouse or something?"

"No," Harry said honestly, "I just brew a lot of potions. Our cupboard is well stocked."

Krait narrowed his eyes, "Well-stocked my arse." He sighed deeply, "In spite of the fact that I think this is an elaborate setup, it remains that the potions are here and you didn't steal my bottles. I'll test these later on, and you can come back when I do my books at the end of the week for your payment."

"Can I take more of your bottles with me today?" Harry asked, choosing not to comment on the rest of the man's ridiculous theories.

Krait grimaced, "Sure, why not."

Harry took that as an invitation into Krait's back room and quickly grabbed three crates of empty bottles. She was almost to the door when Krait called her back.

"Wait, kid," he snapped his fingers at her imperiously and she paused, lifting an eyebrow inquiringly. He pulled out a sheet of parchment from a drawer and brandished it at her, "You'll have to re-do the Mind-Sharpening Potion. I discovered a clerical error in the recipe this morning that would have rendered anything you produced with it useless. It was my fault, so I can cover the costs of the ingredients if you want."

Harry shook her head, not moving to set the crates down and take the parchment, "No need. You're talking about how it read ginger leaves instead of ginkgo leaves, right?" Krait blinked, but nodded. "I corrected for it when I made the potion."

Mr. Krait put the recipe back in the drawer, shaking his head, "Alright, kid, just do whatever you're going to do then. I'll pay you at the end of each week for whatever you've brought in."

"Thanks, Mr. Krait," Harry smiled sympathetically at the man, "See you tomorrow."

Krait sighed, and waved her from the shop.

Harry shook her head, grinning a bit at the silliness of adults. No imagination. You present them with something even mildly unordinary and they immediately seek complicated explanations or assume they're being tricked rather than accept that they don't know everything after all.

Harry made her way slowly down Knockturn Alley with her three crates balanced steadily before her. The extra crate made it a little hard for her to see ahead of her, but by walking slowly in the middle of the alley she was visible enough that the other witches and wizards saw her coming and skirted around her. She was almost past Borgin and Burkes when trouble came, from not before her, but behind.

A dirty hand grasped her right bicep harshly and yanked her sideways into the shadow of a building's overhang. Harry gasped and hauled her weight against the movement, tilting the weight of the crates to the left as well to help counter-balance her accoster's pulling. The man who'd stopped her just pulled harder and brought another hand up to fist in her robe collar and keep her from twisting away. The potion crates were dislodged and fell to the alley with a dull thud that didn't stop anyone else in Knockturn from ignoring the situation that Harry was rapidly finding herself in. With her hands now free, she struck out at the man and tried to push him away from her. She could see him clearly now. His hair was as long as any pureblood's, but ratty and crusted with something that flaked. He was broad-shouldered and slightly overweight, with hands like meat hammers and eyes half-lidded with a violent disorientation, making her think he'd been drinking. When his grip on her collar and arm proved too strong, Harry lashed out with her feet, using the guy's hold on her to keep her upright as she pushed off the ground and kicked him with both feet as hard as she could. Her right leg was a little high from being turned more toward her attacker, but her left foot got him square in the groin.

The man doubled over clutching himself, his mangy hair falling into his face and his grip slackening instantly. Harry thrust herself away from him and backed quickly toward where the crates had fallen. She stacked them up hurriedly, thanking Merlin for the foam packaging that encased each bottle in the crates and would have, she hoped, prevented any breakage from occurring. She had the crates stacked, but before she could pick them up a hand clawed at her nape, jerking her off of her knees and up, until she was dangling with her toes just scraping the earth in front of her very pissed off attacker. His dark hair swung forward into her face and she could see every rip in his tattered black robes. His breath was foul with something sickly sweet and his teeth winked at her like yellow stars from behind the heavy, graying beard around his mouth.

"You'll pay for that one, brat," he wheezed into her face, "I'm gonna—"

But whatever he was going to do, Harry never found out. At that moment a fist came from over Harry's shoulder and struck the man in the face before either of them could blink. Her attacker went reeling backwards from the blow, his hand falling away from Harry's neck, and Harry dropped toward the ground like a stringless puppet. Just as she should have landed hard on the ground, an arm caught her firmly around the middle and towed her backwards into a muscled chest. She blinked, her equilibrium thrown off by the events of the last several seconds, and craned her head back against her captor's robes to look up into his face. With the way things were going it would be some other shady, smelly guy who was only fighting off the first man so that he could sell her organs on the black market himself.

And yet, she thought as she caught sight of the guy she was being held against, no face that handsome would ever need to sell a spleen to make a living. Bright hazel eyes glanced down at her above a straight nose and a strong jaw. His teeth were even, she noted as he grinned briefly at her before turning his attention back to the man sprawled out on the alley dirt, and his face was lightly tanned, as though he occasionally worked in the sun but didn't bask in it. He was young, too, she realized when he spoke. His voice had an easy, pleasing quality to it that set her nerves instinctively at ease.

"I need you to stand behind me," the guy said softly into the top of her head, "That won't keep him down for long, and when he gets up I need you to be standing somewhere you won't get caught up in the fight, okay?"

Harry found herself nodding automatically, though she personally thought the better option would be to leave before the man picked himself up off the ground. Her defender's arm around her waist loosened and he nudged her gently until she moved behind and away from him. She backed up until she stood over where the crates still sat on the floor of the alley and watched, a bit transfixed, as the guy who was helping her settled into a relaxed fighting stance and the man who'd tried to grab her stumbled to his feet.

Her protector looked about sixteen or seventeen. He was taller than she'd realized, though not quite as tall as Mr. Krait was. Probably he was about 6 foot. He was certainly taller than his opponent, who stooped awkwardly and growled before launching himself at the younger man. The young man simply turned around the other man's attack, using one foot to trip the man up and slamming an elbow down into the small of his opponent's back. The older man crumpled again to the ground, but instead of trying to stand he fumbled with his robes until he brought out a thin but sharp-looking dagger and swiped it toward the hazel-eyed guy's ankles. The young man jumped over the knife and aimed his landing to be directly on the knife-wielder's wrist. A cracking sound Harry was all too familiar with told her the man's wrist was broken. The knife fell from an unresponsive hand and the younger man, who was standing with his hands in his pockets as if he'd done nothing more arduous than kick an errant soda can to the side, nudged the knife out of his opponent's reach.

He needn't have bothered, Harry thought, as the man who'd originally attacked her was now curled up around his wrist, rocking and cursing sloppily at them. Her saviour turned around and walked over to her, his face so relaxed Harry thought perhaps he often strolled down notoriously dangerous alleys and beat slovenly characters into the dirt. He tilted his head curiously at her while she looked him over just as curiously through lowered lids. His hair was a dark brown that would have been unremarkable if he wasn't so generally good looking. He was built like a dancer and moved like a street fighter, all wiry muscles and agile grace. The lines of his face weren't rugged, but neither did he have the delicate look most of the pureblooded families favoured.

He leaned a bit closer to Harry, as if he were about to impart a secret, and said, "All right there, lad? I'm not complaining or anything, but usually this is the part where you thank a body for helping you out."

Harry flushed slightly, both because she had been rude to stand there staring after he'd saved her, and because he, like many others, had mistaken her for a boy. She supposed it was the short hair. Of course the plain black robes she favoured for their resilience against visible stains didn't help gender her to the casual eye either.

Deciding to let it go, she said, "Thanks for your help."

The guy laughed lightly and ruffled her hair, "Plain-spoken little thing, aren't you?" Harry finally looked up to glare reproachfully at him and he did a double take, murmuring, "Would you look at those eyes?" Harry blinked, taken aback at the blatant observation, and resisted the urge to reach up and pull her bangs into her eyes nervously. He turned and lifted the stack of crates she'd been neglecting and held them easily with one arm, "Where were you headed, then?"

Harry frowned slightly, "There's no need to escort me or carry my things. You've done enough already."

He smiled easily down at her, "Headed to Diagon Alley, I bet," he said, putting his free hand on her shoulder and propelling her slowly toward the mouth of Knockturn Alley, "I'll walk with you. I think it only fair I know the name of the person I just yanked from the jaws of death."

Harry had no choice but to walk along next to the older boy, who was seeming stranger to her by the minute. "You don't know he was going to kill me," she pointed out, "He might have only wanted a kidney."

The boy laughed, "Very true, I suppose you really don't owe me anything in that case."

Harry grimaced, "Sorry. I meant to say thank you again, and my name is Harry."

"I'm Lionel Hurst, but everyone calls me Leo," he told her.

Harry glanced up at him out of the corner of her eye, "So you make a habit of patrolling Knockturn Alley, Mr. Hurst?"

He favoured her with a look of his own, "First of all, don't ever call me Mr. Hurst again. It's Leo. And I could ask what a sprout like you was doing in that alley as well, but it looks to me like you were coming from the same place I was going." He gestured to the crates, "Krait take you on as a messenger boy or something?"

"Something like that," Harry said, "So you were headed to the Serpent's Storeroom? Why are you escorting me in the other direction?"

"Truth?" Leo turned to look her in the eye, "I'm not sure. There's something about you, though, and when I passed your little predicament my magic was suddenly screaming at me to sit up and pay attention. Never felt anything like it. I figure there's got to be a reason, so maybe if I stick by you long enough I'll figure it out."

Harry shrugged uncomfortably, "Well you've got until the Leaky Cauldron, but how do you know you weren't supposed to help out the other guy?"

Leo laughed again, "My magic hasn't turned on me yet."

"You talk about magic like it's sentient," Harry said cautiously.

"It is," Leo said without pause, "Don't let anyone tell you otherwise."

Harry smiled to herself. Leo was strange, but she liked the way he thought. "What were you going to the Serpent's Storeroom for?" Harry asked curiously, "A potion?"

"The Apothecary doesn't sell any potions I couldn't make myself. I was actually picking up an order for my father," Leo said, "He's too busy with his research to pick them up personally."

Harry turned surprised eyes to her companion, "Is your father Malcolm Hurst? The—"

"The Aldermaster of the Potions Guild, yeah," Leo said, a bit embarrassed.

"Oh," Harry said, blinking, "I was going to say the man who wrote the introduction to the most recent edition of Moste Potente Potions, but he made Aldermaster? That's great." Harry really should follow the politics of the Guild more closely, but it didn't interest her as much as the potions work did.

Leo looked down at her with surprise, "That's right, he did write that a few years ago."

"Yes, I got a copy of it for my eighth birthday," Harry said, smiling a bit, "The introduction was the best part of the whole book. Mostly it was poisons with incredibly unlikely ingredients and one decent recipe for Polyjuice Potion."

"I think I remember my father saying something similar," Leo said with a grin, "You're a rather unexpected person, Harry No-last-name."

"Thanks, I guess," Harry said, "So do you go to Hogwarts?" It would be a disaster if he did, though she didn't remember seeing him around the castle.

"I'm home schooled," Leo said. "My father tutors me in Potions, and everything else I pick up where I can. I'll be taking the NEWTs next May, so I guess I'm what you'd call a seventh-year."

Harry let out her breath slowly in relief, "Interesting. Are you going to pursue a Potions career?"

"Probably," Leo said, though he didn't look at her while he said it, "I learn the other stuff because my mother insists, but there is nothing more interesting than potions that I've found so far. Who knows? Maybe I'll end up the greatest Potions Master of all time." Leo winked at her cheerfully.

"If you say so," Harry said politely. They'd reached the Leaky Cauldron and Harry held her hands out for the crates, "Thanks for your help, Leo. Sorry to take you away from your errands."

"Not at all," Leo said, "Although…I fear I've failed in my original objective. You've learned much more about me than I have about you. Still, something tells me we'll meet again soon." He handed the crates to her carefully, "In fact, I intend to see to it."

Harry looked up with surprised wariness while taking the crates in hand, "And how could you possibly ensure such a thing?"

"Why, by following you home, of course," Leo said mildly. At her look of utter alarm he broke into a laugh and shook his head, "Kidding, of course, my young friend. Instead, I shall insist upon accompanying you the next time you attempt to traverse the streets of Knockturn alone."

"Won't that get a little inconvenient?" Harry asked dryly.

"Nothing in the name of friendship is inconvenient," Leo declared, "Besides, I'm at the Serpent's Storeroom a lot picking up and dropping off for my father. It won't be any trouble to schedule my next trip with yours."

Harry wasn't convinced, "Unless your next trip was going to be tomorrow—"

"Tomorrow it is," Leo smiled winningly, "Shall we say the Leaky Cauldron at noon?"

Harry blinked, "Really, Leo, there's no need. I can bring someone else next time to—"

"I would be grievously insulted if you did, Harry," Leo said solemnly, his bright hazel eyes shining with mirth beneath his short brown hair, "See you tomorrow."

He walked off down the alley before Harry could accept or decline. She sighed, shifting the crates of bottles awkwardly. What a strange man, she thought, then frowned, Or is it that I've been around subtleties and intrigue so much that I don't appreciate straightforwardness anymore?

Either way, she was determined not to pay any heed to Lionel Hurst's declaration, yet somehow the next day she found herself ready to go to the Serpent's Storeroom at almost exactly noon. Leo met her as she flooed into the Leaky Cauldron and took her now-full crates from her immediately.

Harry just gave up trying to talk him out of it, instead thanking Leo for the help. He laughed as if she'd said something delightfully funny and they'd kept up a casual conversation—mostly about Leo, since Harry didn't really want to talk about her complicated life—all the way to the apothecary. No one bothered them in Knockturn, though Harry, without the crates to distract her, noticed they were getting several curious glances from other people in the alley. This wouldn't be unusual in Diagon Alley, since shoppers were often curious about other people as they went about their business, but in Knockturn people generally made it a point not to be too interested in one another. Harry supposed Leo did sort of stand out. His personality, the way he moved and gestured, was like a bright ball of light in the gloomy street, but she had the strangest feeling that they were staring at her because she was with him.

They reached the Serpent's Storeroom and Harry held the door so Leo could manoeuvre the crates into the shop. Krait looked up from his accounting books and his eyebrows shot upwards when he saw them there.

"What's this then, Leo?" Krait grinned with an incredulous sort of humour, "Slummin' as hired muscle today?"

Leo set the crates down carefully, and spoke slowly in response to Krait's joking question, "I'm sure I don't know what you mean, Edgar. You know I'm always happy to help out my friends. It seems young Harry here ran into some trouble on the alley yesterday with a drunk. I couldn't have that, could I?"

Harry glanced at Leo in surprise. His voice was as light and pleasing as ever, but there was a deadly serious quality to it that she hadn't heard even when he was fighting off that thug the other day. More surprising was Krait's response.

"Of course, of course, your—ah, Leo," Krait looked a bit flustered and glanced at Harry awkwardly as he spoke, "So, Harry's a good friend of yours, is he? Good, good. I'm sure he won't run into any trouble with you by his side."

Leo flashed even, white teeth in a playful grin, "Your faith in me is heart-warming, Master Krait."

"Yes, well, so you've got the potions then, Harry?" Krait turned to the crates and began checking the labels.

"Yes, sir," Harry said, not knowing what was going unsaid between them, but letting it go for the time being, "The other eight potions plus extra Calming Potion, Dreamless Sleep, Blood-Replenishing, and Pepper-Up, since those are the four you sell most often."

Krait looked at her with mild surprise, perhaps wondering when she'd taken the time to notice that his shelves were always a bit low on those four in particular, "Good, good. Is this the pace I can expect all summer?"

Harry nodded, "I don't see any reason for it to fall off."

"In that case, wait just a moment," Krait grabbed a sheet of parchment from under the counter and began scribbling.

While he wrote, Leo captured Harry's attention with a curious, "So you run bottles for one of Krait's potion brewers, Harry?"

Harry hid her amusement with a polite smile, "Indeed, Mr. Krait hired a new brewer just a few days ago, and I've been in and out of this shop every day since."

Krait made a badly disguised choking noise, but didn't look up from his scribbling.

Leo glanced at him curiously, but turned back to Harry almost immediately, "This new brewer sounds like a lucky find if he brews twelve potions in one day."

More like one morning, Harry thought wryly. She'd settled into an easy routine in the past couple of days. In the morning she brewed, making three or four cauldrons an hour by brewing simultaneously at several stations. In the afternoons she did her owl-school essays, and in the evenings she experimented until her eyes started crossing. She took meals with her family and so far none of them besides Archie even knew she'd landed a summer job. They just thought she was brewing for fun like she always did, and her parents were at work too much to notice her frequent comings and goings.

"I'll tell him you said so," Harry said.

Krait snorted, but simply thrust the parchment he'd been writing on at her. It was a list of potions. "If I'm going to be getting this many potions a day, I may as well diversify my stock a bit. Tell my brewer," he rolled his eyes a bit at this, "To find recipes for these twelve potions and alternate between these and the original sixteen I gave him, alright, kid?"

"That won't be a problem," Harry assured him. In truth she was glad she'd have a more interesting selection to brew from. Maybe if she made enough of these she could convince Krait to take on even more potions. Of course, she supposed it would depend on if people showed any interest in buying the potions.

"Good," Krait grunted, "You know where the empty bottles are."

Harry nodded and rounded the counter to duck into the storeroom, but Leo beat her there.

"How many do you want?" he asked with a friendly grin.

Harry hesitated. If Leo was carrying them, she could probably take four. The problem was that if he wasn't there the next day, there was no way she could carry four crates of full bottles back to the Serpent's Storeroom on her own. She didn't know how to ask him without being presumptuous though. When he raised an eyebrow at her dithering, Harry blurted, "Four." If he wasn't there the next day she would just make sure Archie came with her to help her carry.

"Four it is," Leo hefted the requested number of crates without batting a lash. They bid good day to Krait and headed, once more, toward Diagon Alley.

Over the next few weeks, Harry brought potions to the Storeroom every weekday, deciding to skip weekends and concentrate solely on her experimental brewing and spending time with her parents. And every day Leo was there at noon to meet her, taking the crates and walking her to the Apothecary and back. Harry might have been more uncomfortable with it had Leo known she was a girl, but as it was she accepted that the older guy just had a strange and rather proprietary interest in her friendship. She was still mostly silent about herself when they conversed, not because she didn't trust Leo—it was almost impossible to distrust such a person—but because she wasn't sure which details of her complicated life she could reveal.

Should she be Harry Potter around Leo, and tell him she went to AIM and wanted to be a Healer? She couldn't tell him she was home schooled, too, because when she disappeared in the fall it would be a little obvious she was lying. And she certainly couldn't be Rigel—Rigel had grey eyes, not the green Leo often told her he admired. So Harry just kept her personal history to herself, and Leo respected that and never pried beyond jokingly remarking that he didn't even know her last name every now and then.

On July 14th, Harry told Leo not to expect her the next day, the first break in their unspoken arrangement.

"Is your brewer taking a day off?" Leo asked with surprise, "The way you run these potions back and forth I'd have thought he never takes a break."

Harry smiled a bit sheepishly, feeling rather guilty that she'd been lying to Leo about who was really brewing the potions she delivered every day. Still, he probably wouldn't believe her if she told him, so she let him keep his assumptions, "Actually, I have to go visit a friend of mine tomorrow, so I can't deliver the potions. I'll probably have twice as many the day after tomorrow to make up for it."

"Ah," Leo said sadly, "I was afraid you might have other friends."

Harry scowled up at him good-naturedly. She'd relaxed quite a bit after seeing the older boy every day for weeks.

"I'm just messing with you," Leo looked as though he wanted to ruffle her hair, but had his hands too full of crate to do so, "See you the day after tomorrow, then."

"Yeah, see you."

On the day of the Malfoy Garden Party, Harry and Archie Polyjuiced as one another before the sun even hit the horizon. Harry would be wearing Archie's best summer dress robes, which were just a bit too small for him now that he'd grown over the summer. Lily had wanted to get Archie new robes for the party, but Archie said firmly that the robes he had would do just fine. Though the robes were snug while she was Polyjuiced, as soon as it wore off they would fit her just right. Archie was Polyjuiced as her, and dressed in a pair of muggle basketball shorts and a baggy T-shirt, so that he would look normal going to Hermione's when he changed back to himself. They'd both told their parents that they wanted to go to Diagon Alley that morning, Archie to pick up Draco's present and Harry to get a hospitality gift for Hermione's parents. They assured their parents that they would simply floo to their respective friends' houses after they completed their purchases.

In reality, they were going to floo to Diagon Alley, collect their packages from behind the bar where Harry had asked old Tom to keep them the day before, wait in an alley in muggle London for the Polyjuice to wear off, go back to the Leaky Cauldron, and floo to the Malfoys' and the Grangers'—who had connected their house to the floo just a week before—from there.

All in all, it was terribly complicated. Still, Harry and Archie were very good at complications by that point, so the plan went off without a hitch, unless one counted Sirius pulling Archie aside and telling him to use the emergency portkey if someone so much as looked at him funny.

Harry took a few minutes to duck into the bathroom and put in her grey contacts before flooing to Malfoy Manor, and when she emerged she was Rigel Black, ready to socialize with the dark pureblood elite. Or at least ready to hand Draco his gift and hide in a shadowy corner for the rest of the party if it came to that.

She waved goodbye and good luck to Archie, and stepped into green flames and roiling soot.

She came out sprawling at the other end of the floo connection. Rigel mused that she really shouldn't have expected the floo to be any more forgiving to her just because she was going to the Malfoys' party in her cousin's best summer robes. Luckily, the only one to witness her most ungraceful exit onto the dark green hearth rugs was the house elf waiting by the fireplace, clearly stationed there to direct people flooing in to the gardens.

The house elf approached her and snapped its little fingers at the soot covering most of her robes. It vanished, and Rigel sent a grateful smile at the elf, "Thank you."

The house elf's eyes grew wide and frantic, and Rigel looked at it with mounting concern. The house elves at Hogwarts hadn't been nearly so taken aback by politeness.

"Good wizard is being too kind to Dobby!" the elf near-wailed, wringing its hands and hopping from foot to foot agitatedly, "Dobby is not to be thanked. Dobby is not knowing what to say."

Rigel nodded in understanding, "That's alright, Dobby. Do you know where I'm to put my birthday gift to Draco?"

Dobby nodded so violently his bat-like ears flopped to and fro, "Dobby is knowing. You is to bring it to the gardens, and you is to place it on the gift table as you leave the house. Dobby is showing you."

The elf bowed deeply and motioned for Rigel to follow him. Dobby took her through the corridor from the reception room to a drawing room with large glass patio doors that stood open to let in the fresh air and sunlight. Dobby motioned her through the doors and onto a beautiful white stone patio. At the bottom of the patio steps was a large table piled with gifts, and beyond that the gardens began. Walking down the steps, taking in the view, Rigel could honestly say that she had never seen anything more magnificent in her life. The Gardens, and indeed she would need to capitalize them in her head from now on, sprawled out like a despoiled emperor before her eyes. They began simplistically, short hedges and flower beds interspersed with tables and chairs, open expanses of lush green lawn, and the occasional stone statues. This was where the main party would be, Rigel guessed. There was already a multitude of guests milling about in their summer best. The hats on the ladies alone were works of art, looking right at home among the lovingly tended flowers and trees.

Beyond the party grounds, however, the hedges grew taller and more intimidating. Trees went from elegant miniature bonsais to silent branching giants, strewing their delicate petals wherever the wind pleased. The flowerbeds became the path boundaries, and Rigel imagined it wouldn't take much to be lost in the great natural maze.

She had just barely set her gift, a small square box wrapped in dark green paper, on the table when she was grabbed by the shoulder and turned around abruptly. It was Draco. He looked resplendent in silver-trimmed white robes, and not even his royally annoyed expression could detract from how radiantly he shone even among the gardens and the throngs of beautiful people.

"I can't believe you!" he fumed, thumping her in the arm with his other hand to show just how put out he was, "You disappear on the train without saying goodbye, no letters all summer, and then you just show up at my birthday party like—like—well, how could you?"

Rigel extracted herself carefully, "I did say goodbye."

Draco batted her words away, "Barely."

"And it's not like the invitation had an RSVP on it," Rigel pointed out.

"Still, you're supposed to send an acceptance," Draco sighed, "Honestly, don't you know anything?"

"Apparently not," Rigel said, a bit sheepish, "So is it alright that I'm here anyway?"

"What? Of course! You're my best friend," Draco said, "Speaking of, Pansy's going to kill you. Come on."

So saying, he pulled her off to the left side of the party lawn, where Rigel could see most of their year mates lounging in the shade of an elaborate gazebo. There were many exclamations and admonitions at her approach.

"Rigel!"

"We haven't heard from you all summer."

"I'm surprised you showed your face after that stunt on the train."

The last was from Blaise, who winked at her as he said it to soften the censure a bit. Rigel looked toward Pansy, who was sitting in a seat next to the middle seat, which must have been Draco's. She hadn't said a word, and was pointedly looking anywhere except at Rigel. Thinking back to when they'd first become friends, back when Pansy used the silent treatment to correct Rigel whenever she did something wrong, Rigel approached her friend slowly, sinking down to her knee beside Pansy's seat. When Rigel put her hand on the arm of Pansy's chair, Pansy couldn't ignore her anymore and looked down at Rigel with reluctant amusement.

"I do like my boys on bended knee," Pansy said, her lips smiling ever so slightly.

"How about begging for forgiveness?" Rigel said teasingly, "I've behaved rather dismally."

"Abominably," Pansy agreed.

"And I feel terrible about it. I was so busy with my summer work I somehow forgot to pay homage to the very lady who makes the summer sun so warm and the days so beautiful," Rigel said, gazing with pitiful regret at Pansy, "My only shred of hope is that surely a lady so kind and grand as she who makes the moon grow round could find it in her bountiful mercy to forgive one so lowly and sorry as I."

"She who makes the moon go round?" Millicent snorted, "That's class-A stuff right there."

"I'm making this up as I go," Rigel said.

"It shows," Theo told her plainly.

Rigel stood up with deliberate dignity, "Well, I can see when true poetry is not appreciated. Pansy, am I forgiven?"

Pansy sighed and shook her head sadly, "I fear we've a long way to go with you, Rigel. But yes, you are forgiven for your unconscionable rudeness."

"Thank you," Rigel said, looking around them, "Is there somewhere I can pull a chair from?"

"Don't bother," Draco said, "Now that everyone is here we'll be expected to mingle." In silent agreement, Millicent, Theo, and Blaise rose to find their parents. Crabbe and Goyle ambled over to the food table, and Rigel just blinked at how quickly everyone had dispersed. "Don't worry," Draco said, looping his arm through Pansy's and gesturing for Rigel to walk on his other side, "We'll see them when we get around to their parents. For now, there are about a million people I'm supposed to introduce you to."

"Me?" Rigel said, taken aback, "I'm not sure I really should—"

"Of course you," Draco said firmly, "This is your first social appearance as an honorary Malfoy. Everyone will have heard by now, and if we don't introduce you around it's like we're ashamed of you."

"Besides," Pansy said, leaning forward a bit to speak past Draco's shoulders, "This will be an excellent opportunity to spread your political wings."

"I'm not sure I have a set of those yet," Rigel said, but her protests fell on selectively deaf ears.

A half hour later Rigel was sure she'd met everyone at the party. She'd met Blaise's beautiful mother, Theo's flirtatious father (who wouldn't stop hitting on Blaise's mother long enough to do more than smile politely at Rigel), and Millicent's impressively upright parents as well. She'd met people she'd only read about in the newspaper, and people she'd never so much as heard of before. She'd been introduced to so many people that there couldn't possibly be any strangers left in wizarding Britain. And yet there were. Just as she was being guided over to yet another person just dying to meet 'that darling boy who'd cured the sleeping sickness,' she was saved by the sound of an echoing violin, which was the signal, Draco told her excitedly, for him to start opening his gifts.

Draco's parents beckoned him with generous smiles and Draco walked quickly over to the gift table where they were waiting.

Pansy laughed at their friend's enthusiasm, "I got him a specialty servicing kit for competitive broomsticks. What did you get him?"

Rigel shrugged, "Just something I thought he'd enjoy. Nothing too serious. I'm going to get some water, do you want anything?"

Pansy shook her head, not looking away from where Draco was smiling and unwrapping a large, oblong present with Snitches printed on the paper. Rigel left Pansy to her viewing, but she didn't go to the refreshment table; instead, after making sure no one was watching her, she slipped behind a tall row of hedges and set off to explore the gardens.

Rigel wanted a moment of peace and quiet in between the endless rounds of introductions to people she couldn't care less about. She had yet to meet a single Potions Master, after all. Mostly the guests were Draco's friends' parents and Ministry officials. She also didn't want to wait around on tenterhooks for Draco to open her present. She didn't like watching other people open gifts she'd gotten them. Either they'd hate it and would awkwardly pretend not to for her sake or they'd like it and she'd feel uncomfortable with their gratitude. It was best to occupy herself with something else, and she had been itching to explore the gardens since she'd laid eyes on them.

The hedges were even more imposing up close, when she was surrounded by them. Rigel wandered for a bit, aimless in where she was going but paying close attention to where she'd come from, so that she could find her way back out again when she thought it had been long enough. She was about to round a neatly groomed corner when she heard voices and stopped, suddenly realizing that the gardens may not have been as secluded as she assumed. Clearly, others had skipped out on the present opening as well.

Harry asked her magic to muffle the sounds of her footsteps and promised herself she'd look up a real spell that dampened sound when she got home. She began walking carefully back the way she came, not sure the magic would hold up if she actually snapped a twig or something, but stopped again when she heard the word 'Hogwarts.' She knew she really shouldn't, but she was curious, so she crept just the tiniest bit forward to catch the rest of what the speakers were saying.

"—sure you'll find Hogwarts to be anything but dull in the coming year," the first voice said smoothly. There was something about that voice that Harry recognized but couldn't place, like something from a commercial she'd heard over the Wizarding Wireless.

"A pity. With all the excitement of last year I had hoped for a year of peace—relatively speaking, of course." That voice Harry knew instantly. It was Professor Snape.

She found her feet moving forward without her really thinking about it, and soon enough she was able to shift ever-so-slightly around the edge of the corner hedge. She didn't though. Rigel was not one to stick her neck out into unfamiliar situations so foolishly. Instead, she reached down and quietly pulled out the timepiece Archie kept in his robes. He'd insisted Rigel take it with her, and the gold backing was reflective enough to serve her purposes. She angled the side of the watch around the corner and used it as a rudimentary spying glass, squinting against the glare to try and make out who Snape was talking to.

"Oh, Severus, I'm afraid you aren't nearly old enough to bemoan the folly of today's excitable youth," the first voice said. Rigel could almost make the speaker out in the shiny metal mirror. He was tall and had thick dark hair, but he was standing with his back to her, facing Snape.

"I'm sure you would know, sir," Severus said dryly, prompting the other man into an appreciative chuckle.

"Why ever do I let you stay in that dreary old school all year, Severus? I forget how entertaining you are when you're away so long, you know," the first man leaned toward Snape conspiratorially, "I think the others are too afraid of me to make jokes."

"I can't imagine why," Snape drawled.

The first man laughed again, "Yes, exactly, Severus, exactly. So, tell me of this boy of yours. Lucius has been most disappointingly unforthcoming."

"He's not my boy, I assure you, sir," Snape said in a neutral tone.

"Come now, Severus, I know how little you think of the most recent generation. If you've taken an interest in one it can't be without reason," the man said, and though his words were still teasing there was now a harder edge to them.

"Oh, the boy is talented," Snape said, "There's no doubt about that. He is one of a kind, if I may be so trite. I was merely clarifying that the relationship between the boy and I is not the surrogate father bond you might have been hoping for. He is my student, and I know of him only what any teacher knows of their students."

"I am not interested in his favourite colour," the first man said dismissively, "It is precisely the sort of talents a professor would be aware of that I seek to discover. Already the boy has done what no one else could do, and yet I am told he has no magical presence to speak of. How can this be, Severus?"

Rigel was feeling more uncomfortable the longer she listened. She just knew the first voice was familiar, and it was seeming more and more as though the student they were talking about was her, as vain as that thought undoubtedly made her. If it was her they were talking about, she didn't know if she should be offended that Snape spoke so distantly of her or grateful that he wasn't as eager to divulge information about her as he could have been.

Snape took a careful breath before saying, "Perhaps you should discover that for yourself, sir."

Before Rigel could blink, Snape's wand was out and pointed at the other man—no, not the other man: her! Snape had sensed her presence somehow and was about to reveal her to his companion. Rigel went to snatch her hand back from around the corner, but before she could do so the spell Snape had sent from his wand wrapped around her wrist like a lasso and dragged the rest of her abruptly out from around the hedge. The spell-rope tugged at her again to jerk her toward Snape and she stumbled forward a half step. She yanked futilely at the spell for a moment, but soon realized the folly of resisting, especially considering she was already well and truly caught out. She sighed and walked the rest of the way to Snape's side of her own volition, tucking the pocket watch away as she did so.

Rigel opened her mouth to apologize to Snape but snapped it shut again when she finally got a good look at his companion. It was Riddle. Leader of the Sow Party, notorious muggle hater, the genius politician himself, and here she was caught red-handed eavesdropping on his conversation with her professor. Rigel groaned internally. Way to keep a low profile.

Snape set a heavy hand on her shoulder, squeezed hard enough to let her know she'd probably be getting one heck of a lecture from him later on, and said, "Mr. Riddle, this young man is my student, Rigel Black. Mr. Black, allow me to introduce you to Mr. Riddle."

Rigel bowed as deep as she dared with Snape's hand still digging into her shoulder, "One thousand apologies, Mr. Riddle. In truth I recognized my Professor's voice from a distance and was curious to know just whom he was talking to. I had not realized it was you until this moment."

Riddle took his time looking her over. There was something all-too-knowing in his gaze, as if he knew a great secret about the world but was too polite to mock you for your ignorance. When she had fully straightened once more, he said, "Curiosity is a wonderful thing in one's youth. I hope yours was satisfactorily appeased."

Rigel blinked with surprise into Riddle's handsome face, "I'm afraid that as the offended party to my wrongdoing you are too kind, Mr. Riddle. Please, let me know what it is I can do to atone for such impertinence."

"So polite," Riddle murmured, "I can see why Severus likes you. Don't be so quick to owe me a debt, though, Mr. Black. I tend to collect them rather abruptly."

"A possibility that should have crossed my mind before I stuck my ears where they weren't invited," Rigel said evenly, "As it is, I can only hope you allow me the chance to redress this mistake as soon as I am able."

"Well, how about right now?" Riddle said, deceptively amiable. At Rigel's cautious nod, he went on, "Since what you were trying to steal from us was truths we were perhaps not prepared to tell you, that is what I shall ask for in return, sound fair?"

"Many things sound like what they are not," Rigel said vaguely, "Would you clarify your request, Mr. Riddle?"

"Very well, Mr. Black," Riddle said plainly, "How long were you listening to us?"

Rigel thought, "Perhaps two and a half minutes."

"Then I will ask you questions for two and one half minutes, and you will answer them as if you were having an unguarded conversation with someone you trust," Riddle said, smiling a bit at her, "Does that seem to be a fair trade to you?"

Rigel said, "It is for you to decide, of course, but yes, I do think that is a fair compensation, sir."

"Then let's begin," Riddle said, "And believe me when I tell you that I will know if you are lying to me." Rigel nodded, and Riddle asked, "Was it you who cured the sleeping sickness?"

"It was."

"How?"

Rigel frowned, "Nothing that seems to me to be so impressive, though I am told that others are unable to recreate my methods. The sickness was impenetrable from the outside, but from the inside it merely needed to be disrupted. I entered the other children's minds by means of their magical cores, and proceeded to direct their magic to destabilizing the barrier until a Legilimens like Professor Snape could enter the mind and clear the sickness out for good."

Riddle tilted his head thoughtfully, "And this ability to pass through others' magical cores does not interest you at all?"

"Not really," Rigel shrugged, "My only interest is in potion making."

Riddle looked unconvinced, but changed topics, "Why is it, Mr. Black, that you have no magical presence? I was not able to sense you around that corner at all, though it seems Severus was."

"I recognized his Occlumency shields at the periphery of my senses, not his magic," Snape offered tonelessly.

"I'm not sure what you mean by magical presence, Mr. Riddle," Rigel said honestly.

"Most wizards, children especially, have an aura of magic that leaks from their cores and tints the air around them with a taste of their magic. If one is adept at reading these auras one can tell a lot about a wizard by the way his magic feels around him," Riddle explained curtly, "You, however, have no aura to speak of, Mr. Black, and since you are not a squib I would like to know how that is."

Rigel thought for a moment, "Can one suppress the magic they leak, stop it from leaking, I mean?"

"If one is purposely dampening or controlling their magic, yes," Riddle said.

"Then my guess is that I am unconsciously suppressing any magic that would normally leak out. I have a very tight hold on my magic," Rigel explained, "One of the reasons I learned to imbue potions consciously so quickly was because I was incapable of imbuing them unconsciously. My magic simply does not emit itself unconsciously."

"Interesting," Riddle commented, seemingly to himself, "Tell me, Mr. Black, what are your political leanings?"

Rigel fumbled at the non sequitur, "I haven't any, sir. I'm afraid politics don't interest me much."

Riddle laughed, "You're lying, Mr. Black, but I suppose as my minutes are up it is within your rights to do so."

"You are too kind, Mr. Riddle," Rigel murmured.

"Kind is one thing I am certainly not, Mr. Black, though you should pray you never have to verify that statement firsthand," Riddle said, "Now, I think young Draco will be quite put out with me if I keep his friend from his party any longer. Let's adjourn to the front lawn, shall we gentlemen?"

So saying he began walking at a brisk yet refined pace through the hedge maze, Snape and Rigel at his heels. Rigel risked a glance up at her Professor's face, but his features were too blank to give anything away. When they reached the party grounds Rigel saw a couple of house elves clearing away wrapping paper and Draco looking around the throngs of guests with a slight frown on his face. His eyes lit upon their group coming out of the taller hedges and his eyes grew wide and a tad bit concerned. Feeling guilty, Rigel waved discreetly to him, smiling to show that everything was all right. Her friend came toward them slowly, as though approaching a muzzled bear.

When he reached them, Draco bowed deeply to Riddle and nodded respectfully to his godfather. "Good day, Mr. Riddle. Hello, Uncle Severus. Do you mind if I steal Rigel away for a while?"

"I wouldn't dream of denying you a request at your own party, Mr. Malfoy," Riddle said, smiling in a way that Rigel supposed would be considered charming, "It was interesting to meet you, Mr. Black."

"I'm sure I was the least interesting participant in our conversation, Mr. Riddle," Rigel bowed politely once more, "Thank you for the company, and for keeping me from getting lost in Draco's intimidating hedge maze."

"The pleasure of the company is mine, Mr. Black," Riddle said, nodding to her, "I trust we'll meet again soon."

"It will be as you say," Rigel said, "Good day, Professor Snape."

Snape inclined his head, "Mr. Black."

Draco bowed once more to Riddle and then practically dragged Rigel away from the older two men.

"You really can't be trusted for even five minutes, can you?" Draco muttered as he towed her to where his parents were standing, "Honestly, I turn around and you're strolling through the Gardens with Riddle like you don't know what the man does for a living."

Rigel chose to ignore that comment, thinking she hadn't really had a lot of choices besides give Riddle whatever he wants so he doesn't get angry and run for the hills.

"Get any good presents, Draco?" Rigel said, changing the subject.

"Yeah," Draco said, rolling his eyes, "Yours. I love it, which you would have seen firsthand if you'd stuck around to watch me open it."

"Oh," Rigel said, "Good."

She'd gotten Draco a potion for his birthday. It was a variation on the Weightless Draught, and she'd made it because sometime in early February, Draco, Rigel, and Pansy had had a long conversation about what wandless superpower they'd want if they could pick one. Pansy had wanted telekinesis and Rigel said she would like to be invisible, but Draco declared he wanted to be able to fly without a broom. So Rigel had set about creating a potion that would let him do that.

The Weightless Draught did pretty much what its name implied, making the drinker weigh very little. Unfortunately, gravity still acted on the drinker perfunctorily so you couldn't fly with the Draught unless someone on a broom was holding your weightless form in the air. Rigel had wanted to make the potion into a sort of self-regulated Wingardium Leviosa, so that one could not only float with it, but control their movements as well. The potion had turned out to be surprisingly easy to tweak. Instead of changing the ingredients in the potion, she had changed the kind of magic she imbued into the potion.

Usually when Rigel imbued a potion she asked for magic straight from her core to flow into the potion through the connection. This time, Rigel shaped the magic before it left her core, working from what Remus had told her about wild vs. shaped magic and theorizing that if one could imbue formless wild magic into a potion to mesh ingredients together then one should be able to imbue shaped magic into a potion, not to help stabilize the ingredients, but to add properties to a potion that the original ingredients didn't have. So when making the Weightless Draught, Rigel asked her magic to shape itself like it would when performing the Levitation Charm, then imbue that shaped magic through the connection into the potion on top of the unshaped magic that the potion itself needed to mesh. In this way, the final potion would when drunk act like a combination of weightless and levitation magic. Since the shaped magic had melded with the neutral potions magic, it would no longer be Rigel's spell, instead acting as if Draco had cast the spell on himself, making him the one in control of the magic. Also, being imbued in the potion would make the magic last longer than the intent of the spell, so Draco would in theory have about two hours of flying time with the potion. To be safe, she'd written that he not use it longer than one hour.

Draco just shook his head, "Come on, you have to thank my parents for having you, okay?"

Rigel nodded, "I can do that."

They waited until the Malfoys had moved away from the guest they were talking to, then approached them.

"Draco, darling, you've found our wayward Mr. Black," Narcissa said, smiling down at Rigel genially, "Are you finding the party to be diverting?"

"Only by virtue of your attendance, my lady," Rigel said, bowing over Narcissa's hand gallantly, "I must beg your pardon for not notifying you of my intention to attend today's gathering, and thank you and your husband for putting up with me all afternoon."

Narcissa laughed and waved her words away with an airy hand. Rigel noted that Narcissa was probably where Draco had picked up that habit.

"Not at all, Mr. Black," she said graciously, "We were relieved to see you'd decided to come. Draco particularly enjoyed your thoughtful present if the look on his face was indication enough, didn't you Draco?"

Draco flushed a bit at his mother's teasing, "I already told him, Mother."

"I own you have my curiosity piqued, Mr. Black," Mr. Malfoy spoke up, "Where did you acquire such a potion?"

"He made it himself," Draco said immediately, "I recognized his handwriting on the label."

"Indeed, I should have clarified," Malfoy inclined his head toward his son in acknowledgment, "Where did you come across the recipe for the potion you gifted my son? I have never before heard of such a potion."

Rigel tilted her head, "I guess I invented it. Though really I just made a few changes to the Weightless Draught."

Malfoy frowned, "Is it safe for my son to ingest?"

"Yes, sir," Rigel said, "I tested it myself several times, with no complications or side effects other than a slight disorientation not unlike when one returns to dry land after gaining sea legs."

"If you say it is safe, then we trust you, Mr. Black," Narcissa said, "After all, you are as good as family now."

"My wife is right," Malfoy said, smiling a bit in apology, "And in that vein I don't believe you've met everyone here, Mr. Black. Allow us to rectify that."

Rigel summoned a smile with difficulty and followed Mr. and Mrs. Malfoy to a nearby group of people whom, she was shocked to discover, she had not in fact yet been introduced to. Joy.

The Malfoys knew everyone, as one might expect given that they were the hosts, but it wasn't just that the Malfoys knew their guests' names. Every time the Malfoys approached someone new, they would give Rigel a little tidbit of information about the person. So-and-so owns this Quidditch team and sometimes cheats on his taxes. Such-and-such a person works for their father but sells his secrets to his father's competitors to cover his gambling debts. By the time they'd gotten around to the Parkinsons again, Rigel knew more things than she'd ever wanted to know about complete strangers. Thankfully, the Malfoys and the Parkinsons appeared to be good friends, so Rigel wasn't privy to any uncomfortable secrets about Pansy's family. Instead, they chatted amiably about what one another had been doing over the summer and what their plans for the fall were.

All too soon they were interrupted by a couple of Ministry officials on the Wizengamot. Rigel wasn't paying much attention to the elderly witch and wizard, instead choosing to stare out over the expansive gardens, wondering what it must be like to live with so much space.

Something glittered at the corner of her eye and Rigel twitched, turning to look for the source. She couldn't see anything, so she turned back to the view she'd been taking in, but—there it was again. A shimmering at the edges of her vision that sent shards of discomfort into her brain. She rubbed her forehead and looked toward where she'd caught the glare but once again the subtle light disappeared the moment she looked for it. The next time Rigel caught sight of it in the corner of her eye, she didn't move. Instead she focused on her peripheral vision to try and see where it was coming from. When she pinpointed it, she swiveled her head around in alarm.

It was coming from the glass of punch in the elderly wizard's hand. Rigel stared at it for a moment, but couldn't see anything immediately wrong with the drink. She turned her head slowly until she could see the glass only in the corner of her eye, and sure enough it took on a very distinctive mother-of-pearl sheen.

Rigel turned to the wizard and interrupted his conversation with Mr. Parkinson rather rudely, "Sir, is your drink alcoholic?"

The wizard drew himself up abruptly, peering down at her forbiddingly, "I beg your pardon, young man?"

"Excuse me, sir, but it's very important," Rigel said quickly, "Is that drink you're holding meant to be an uninhibitor?" She asked because sometimes Nimue's Breath, which she suspected was in the elder man's punch, was added to a drink as a relaxant, and she didn't want to jump to conclusions.

"Certainly not, you impertinent child," he said, disgruntled, "I do not partake of alcohol or anything of the like."

"There is no alcohol being served at this party, Mr. Black," Narcissa added tentatively, looked confused and a bit worried.

"Then, I would strongly suggest you don't drink that, sir," Rigel said firmly, ignoring the disdainful looks she was receiving from the guests who could overhear their conversation.

"And who are you to suggest such a thing?" the man said dismissively, "I don't see anything wrong with this drink." So saying he leant close to sniff experimentally at the liquid in his glass.

"No, don't—" Rigel started, but it was too late. He'd inhaled.

A pleased, dreamy look overtook the old man's face, "You see? Nothing wrong with this drink. It's my favourite, you know." He brought the cup to his lips to take a sip, but Rigel darted forward and clapped a hand over his mouth, trying to wrest the cup away from him. The older wizard was strong despite his age, however, and fought back, struggling away from Rigel and toward the drink in his hand, panting and gasping as he attempted to get at the liquid that Rigel knew was calling him so urgently.

The guests around them gasped in shocked disapproval, some demanding that such an impertinent child be removed from the party at once. Rigel ignored them.

"Someone help me," she gasped out, still struggling to keep one hand over the drugged wizard's lips and the other over the top of the cup, all the while keeping her face turned away from the drink, lest she inhale the fumes herself, "Get the cup away from him."

Just when she was certain no one was going to help her, Draco was there, using both hands to pry the cup out of the old man's grip, and then Pansy was taking control of the cup, holding it far away from her own nose while Draco and Rigel together managed to hold the elderly Wizengamot member back from diving after it. It was at this point that Mr. Malfoy stepped in.

"Clearly something has affected Mr. Ogden," he said, loudly and clearly enough that his voice carried over the noise of the excitable guests, "We will deal with it presently. In the meantime could I invite the rest of you to view our newest addition to the hedge maze? Narcissa?"

Narcissa immediately took charge of the curious guests, herding them easily to a different part of the gardens to give Mr. Ogden a little privacy while her husband sorted everything out. Most of the guests left agreeably, content to gossip about what they'd already witnessed, and those that stayed behind were understandable: Mr. Malfoy, Pansy's parents, and the elderly witch who had been accompanying Mr. Ogden.

"Mr. Black, allow Mr. Parkinson to take charge of Mr. Ogden for the moment," Mr. Malfoy said curtly, "I would like an explanation."

"As would we all," a smooth voice interjected. Rigel looked over to see Mr. Riddle, closely followed by Snape, making their way toward their group from the direction of the back patio.

"Mr. Riddle," Malfoy nodded respectfully, "There seems to be a little trouble with Mr. Ogden's drink. Mr. Black was just helping us sort it out."

"Were you, Mr. Black?" Snape did not look terribly surprised, "Why is it that you are always in the thick of things?"

"I've no idea," Rigel said blandly. She handed Mr. Ogden off to Mr. Parkinson, who was looked at her very intensely, and crouched down to retrieve the small knife she carried in her boot for harvesting potions ingredients. Moving slowly and non-threateningly—she really didn't want to startle any of them into cursing her—Rigel ran the blade of the boot knife along her left wrist, just deep enough to draw a line of blood. She sheathed the knife just as quickly and strode over to Pansy with her wrist outstretched. To Pansy's credit, she didn't flinch away or make a face in disgust at the bloody appendage coming her way. Instead Pansy looked at her with concerned determination, and held the goblet out for Rigel to drip her blood into the drink.

Almost immediately, Ogden shook himself and slumped back into Mr. Parkinson's grip.

"What?" he gazed around him in a lost sort of way, "What happened?" He spotted Rigel accepting Pansy's handkerchief to staunch the shallow wound on her wrist and spluttered, "You—you—what did you do?"

"From the looks of things, saved whatever was left of your life," Snape said sardonically. He took the cup of ruined punch from Pansy and brought it to his nose, inhaling deeply. Snape immediately moved the glass away from his face and said, "Nightshade. Without the masking agent to cover the smell it is quite apparent. Not even a bezoar would have saved you had you been unfortunate enough to ingest even a drop of this mixture."

Rose Parkinson put a trembling hand to her mouth and reached out to clasp Pansy with the other, "Masking agent?" she repeated questioningly.

"Nimue's Breath," Draco said quietly. Everyone turned to look at him and he flushed a bit under the scrutiny. His father in particular looked mildly surprised that he had identified it, "It was nullified by having blood spilled over it, but when active the flower causes logical thinking processes to shut down, encouraging the victim to happily drink whatever poison the flower's scent is covering. Is that correct?"

Rigel smiled slightly, remembering that she had dictated one of her essays on the flower out loud in front of Draco once.

"It is, Draco," Snape said, "Well spotted. And quick thinking of you as well, Mr. Black, for spilling blood over the glass before Mr. Ogden could be further affected by the Nimue's Breath."

Rigel nodded and turned to Ogden, who was leaning heavily on Mr. Parkinson still, taking in everything said with a kind of dazed wonder, "Forgive me, Mr. Ogden, for behaving so rudely before. When you told me the drink was not meant to be a stimulant I was afraid poison might be involved. I did not mean to alarm you, nor accost you, sir."

Riddle seemed almost sardonically amused. "Too polite," he muttered to himself.

Ogden shook his head at Rigel slowly, "No, young man, it is I who must apologize for not taking you seriously from the start. I might have saved myself a good deal of embarrassment if I hadn't sought to smell the drink and ascertain the truth of the matter myself. It was foolish of me. I know the dangers of Nimue's Breath, and it should not have been left to a child to apprise me of the threat."

"Yet he did," Riddle commented. Rigel turned to see him contemplating her over the rim of his own glass, "How interesting that a boy your age is so attuned to assassination attempts."

Rigel glanced at Draco and Pansy, who were looking at her with sympathetic understanding.

Pansy spoke up tentatively, "Rigel has been especially sensitive to the possibility of goblet poisoning since the events of last Halloween, Mr. Riddle."

"Pray, enlighten those of us who were not present for the events you refer to, Miss Parkinson," Riddle requested.

Pansy looked troubled, and glanced at Rigel questioningly. Rigel smiled in encouragement, so she said, "The pumpkin juice in Rigel's goblet at the Halloween feast was replaced with corrosive acid. Rigel very nearly drank it, and ever since he checks everything he drinks for tampering. I'm not surprised that Rigel out of all of us noticed the poisoning first."

Rigel blinked. She hadn't known that Pansy watched her so closely. She did check everything she drank, but she did so discreetly—or so she'd thought.

"But who would want to kill you, Tiberius?" the elderly witch asked in a shaken tone of voice.

Ogden shook his head, "I don't know, Griselda, but I do know that I owe this young man a great personal debt." He turned to Rigel, "I am Tiberius Ogden, child, elder of the Wizengamot. Thank you for the service you have rendered me today—I shall not forget it. A life debt is owed to you and such a debt is yours to claim."

"It's an honour to meet you properly, Mr. Ogden," Rigel said, bowing slightly, "I am Rigel Black, and the service you speak of was merely my duty, one wizard to another."

"Well, I disagree," the older witch replayed, setting a hand on Ogden's arm, "I am Griselda Marchbanks, also an elder of the Wizengamot and Governor of the Wizarding Examinations Authority, and you have saved the life of my oldest friend. I now formally consider myself to be an equal party in the life debt just incurred. If you do not claim it from Tiberius, you must claim it from me."

Rigel bowed once more, "A pleasure to meet you, Madam Marchbanks, but truly I require no payment for such an act."

"Nonetheless you shall one day receive it," Marchbanks said firmly. She looped Ogden's arm through her own carefully, "Now, I think it wise if Tiberius and I retire from this lovely party. Mr. Malfoy, we will not blame you of course for this unfortunate incident, but we will have your word as a gentleman to investigate the matter thoroughly."

"Of course, Madam Marchbanks," Malfoy bowed to the elder, "Everything that can be done to discover the perpetrator of such a crime against one of my guests will be. I will send you a copy of the report."

"Please do," Marchbanks said, "Come, Tiberius, let's get you home."

The elders left and there was a moment of silence in which Rigel thought to herself that she was really racking up life debts a little too quickly. She hadn't the faintest idea what she would do with them all.

"Well," Mr. Parkinson said, moving to put his hands comfortingly on his wife's shoulders, "That was a bit more excitement than I had counted on for the afternoon, but I suppose one must learn to expect the unexpected at your parties, Lucius."

Mr. Malfoy frowned the slightest bit, "We can only be grateful to Mr. Black that the excitement did not turn tragic. As my wife would say, an attempted murder is good gossip; a successful murder is poor security. It seems our debt to you is compounded, Mr. Black."

Rigel winced, "Please don't, sir. I acted instinctively, not for any perceived gain. Can't we pretend this didn't happen?"

There were many raised eyebrows in the group.

"A life was saved here today, Mr. Black," Rose Parkinson said softly, "Why would you want to pretend otherwise?"

"I just meant I would appreciate it if my involvement were kept as quiet as possible," Rigel said, swallowing against her dry mouth.

"We can say Uncle Severus saved Mr. Ogden, can't we?" Draco said suddenly, "After all, Father, if Rigel's dad hears about how close Rigel was to what happened today he might not allow Rigel to come back."

Well, thought Rigel, that much was certainly true.

"While I do not seek to deny young Mr. Black the credit, perhaps it would be best if his name was kept out of the official report," Snape said shrewdly, "Whoever was responsible for poisoning Ogden's drink may seek retaliation for the foiled plan, and as a target I am better suited to handle any attempts at revenge."

Rigel did not like Snape putting himself on the line for her sake, but accepted that it was his right to do so. "Thank you, sir," Rigel said, "Also, would you mind if I took the poisoned drink with me when I leave today?"

Snape raised an eyebrow and Mr. Parkinson frowned openly, but it was Pansy who asked, "Why?"

"I'm sure Professor Snape could neutralize the poison and dispose of it easily," Rigel said, "But I have spilled my blood into this mixture willingly. I would not like it to fall into unfriendly hands accidentally."

Riddle quirked an amused grin, "What would you know of blood magic, Mr. Black?"

"Just enough that I would prefer to dispose of the mixture myself, Mr. Riddle, if no one has any objections," Rigel said evenly.

Snape nodded and pulled a flask from the holster he wore beneath his outer robes. He tipped the liquid in and corked it firmly before handing it over to Rigel without ceremony. Rigel nodded her thanks, tucking the flask away carefully.

The adults went off to gather the rest of the guests back from the hedge maze and Draco, Pansy, and Rigel went back to the now empty gazebo to say their farewells. The party was nearly over in any case, and Rigel had to meet Archie in Diagon Alley to take the Polyjuice once more before going home and switching back.

Pansy hugged Rigel and said, "You'd better not go the rest of the summer without writing."

Rigel smiled, "I promise you'll hear from me before the train at least. I don't know if I can see you guys in person again though, I'm really busy this summer."

"Just don't get into too much trouble before the fall, okay?" Draco hugged her briefly, "You're entirely too apt to find yourself in the middle of every problem that comes your way."

"No promises for that one," Rigel said, "But trouble or no trouble, I'll see you two in September."

"Yeah," Draco said, "Thanks for coming, Rigel, even though you didn't answer the invitation properly."

"Thanks for being my friend, Draco, even though I'm so socially inept," Rigel said.

Pansy laughed, "We'll make you into a gentleman someday, Rigel Black, though I really must talk with you about how one properly advises another about an attempt on their life."

"I must have skipped that chapter in Etiquette for all Occasions," Rigel rolled her eyes.

"I'll send you an updated copy for your birthday," Pansy sniffed.

They laughed, and bade farewell.

When Rigel went over the day's events that night as she waited for sleep to claim her, she couldn't help but shake her head with bemusement. The summer was only half-over and already she was looking forward to the break she'd get in the fall. Compared to the last few weeks, an uneventful school year would make a nice vacation.

Provided it was uneventful, of course.

Chapter 2

Harry's head was spinning. Again. She was bent over her notes on the Polyjuice Potion in the Potter Library, trying as she had been for weeks to crack the input variable restrictions. She had to get around them somehow, if her idea was going to work.

There were different types of shaped magic, as Harry had been learning in her studies. There was the kind of magic that did relatively the same thing every time to the nearest thing it encountered—like a warming charm or the Expelliarmus spell, just point and shoot. Then there was magic that relied on parameters, variables, which were supplied in the case of a spell by the wizard's intent and in the case of potions by ingredients added after completion. In the case of Polyjuice, the basic pattern of the shaped magic was inlaid in the recipe, but the exact effect of the potion depended on the input variable—the hair of the wizard one wanted to turn into, which was added after the potion was complete. At first Harry thought the potion simply 'read' the DNA encoded in the strand of hair and produced a copy in the wizard who drank it. But then, Harry did a little more research.

If DNA was the only thing the magic was 'reading' when a wizard took Polyjuice, then it wouldn't account for things in the appearance that DNA had nothing to do with. For instance, if Polyjuice only read DNA and you took a hair from someone who dyed their hair you'd wind up with their original colour. If someone was malnourished as a child and had grown up shorter than they were 'supposed' to be given genetics alone, you'd end up taller than they were under the influence of Polyjuice. If your target had lost their leg in battle, you'd end up as them with the leg, because nothing in the DNA accounted for environmental influences throughout a person's life.

So Harry had reasoned that the potion wasn't analyzing the DNA, or at least not the DNA alone. It was as if the strand of hair somehow represented the person it belonged to as they were at the moment the hair was plucked. She wasn't sure how that could be, so she had done more research on biomagic, the magic that affected the body. Archie had helped her a lot in that area; Healing was pretty much all biomagic, and even though she was technically on-par with Archie's level as an AIM first-year, Archie had been reading medical journals and checking out books on Medi-magic for years. His stores of knowledge in the field far outclassed hers, and the information he came up with was very helpful.

It turned out that hair didn't just contain DNA. Archie explained that even muggles were aware of this. They used hair to test if a person had been taking illegal substances, because hair absorbs chemicals like arsenic and smoke from the environment. Also, even the DNA that was in hair was not actually nuclear DNA unless the hair was plucked from the root. Regular, shed hairs only contained mDNA, or mitochondrial DNA, which wouldn't have the full genetic code needed to copy the exact physical characteristics even barring any environmental influences. So in other words the potion wasn't actually taking DNA from the hair put into it. It was taking something else.

That something else turned out to be magic. As Archie explained, hair not only absorbed physical chemicals and toxins from the environment, but in the case of a wizard, hair absorbed magic as well. In retrospect, this piece of information explained a lot. Most adult wizards and witches wore their hair long. Harry had always chalked it up to pureblooded custom, but what if it was more than that? As Draco and Pansy were always telling her, purebloods did nothing without a reason. Archie said that a wizard's hair was constantly absorbing magic, and the closest and most frequently absorbed magic was the wizard's own magical signature. When the hair was added to the potion, the strongest magic in it would be its owner's magical signature, meaning that what the hair likely added to the potion was the magical signature.

From there, Harry researched what sort of information could be gleaned from a magical signature. She knew that magical signatures were highly specific, and as such were used for identification purposes in the Ministry, much like a fingerprint, hence the 'signature' part. They were also nearly impossible to falsify, which is why high-level wards were keyed to magical signatures rather than to a pass code as lower-level security wards were. Harry knew that Polyjuice changed only a person's physical appearance, meaning that the taker's mind and soul remained his own, but she discovered that not even Polyjuice could copy another wizard's magical signature. Otherwise anyone could get through top-clearance wards with the potion, which was simply not the case.

So the potion wasn't copying the entire signature, but some part of the signature was what gave the potion the input it needed to copy. Therefore, Harry thought, there must be physical data stored in a magical signature about the person it belonged to. Yet, she couldn't imagine why that would be, or what part of the signature the physical data would be found in.

This was important for her to understand, because she was trying to change the input parameters slightly to modify the potion. The recipe was too delicate to be meddled with—and honestly, she wasn't skilled enough to even try. What she planned on doing wasn't changing the potion itself so much as it was changing what went into it. Harry wanted to make a variant of the Polyjuice that wouldn't copy one form or another exactly, but instead allow for a blending of two forms. She wanted to blend her and Archie's looks and create a middle ground that they could both Polyjuice into, thereby looking exactly the same, or at least exact enough to fool everyone. In truth, Harry was not, repeat not, changing either of their sexes. She really didn't want to actually become a boy for six years, and she was pretty sure Archie would just plain refuse.

Instead, she wanted to create a form that would appear to be a slightly delicate male. In Archie's case it would actually be male, and in hers it would only look male, with her girl features vastly understated. Narrower hips, broader shoulders, pretty flat chest, and taller than she would probably grow to be naturally. To do this, she needed to somehow isolate the components of a magical signature that revealed the physical characteristics of the wizard it belonged to, so that she could blend she and Archie's signature in a way that selected for the characteristics she wanted. Then she had to find a way to get the Polyjuice to accept the blended signature instead of a natural signature.

Of course, this was not the only thing about the potion she'd have to change. She also needed the potion to last longer. Harry knew she was probably not the first to wish Polyjuice lasted longer than an hour, and indeed she had read a lot of research on the possibility of the subject—some credible and some not so credible. One article had actually suggested that one should eat live dung beetles once every new moon to make the transformation last longer. Utter rubbish, in Harry's opinion. Yes, there had been much speculation done on the possibility, but all of the articles she'd read had proposed changes to the recipe. Harry had brewed the Polyjuice recipe three times in the nearly two months she'd been home, and each time her mind and magic were telling her the same thing. The recipe was perfect.

Harry saw, and more importantly felt, nothing wrong with the recipe as it was. It sort of…clicked, magically speaking. Everything fit together in a way that was delicate yet elegant, and Harry was sure the key to adapting the potion was not in changing the actual recipe. It was in the variables.

The input variable of the hair was obvious, because the outcome of the potion changed depending on whose hair you put in it, but Harry thought the time-sensitive portion of the potion was just as variable. As far as she could tell, none of the ingredients that caused the change in the drinker were subject to time. That is, the things in the potion that turned you into someone else weren't the ones that made it only last an hour. It was the ingredients that made it temporary that were time-sensitive, so the reason it only lasted an hour was because of the ingredients that changed you back to yourself. Those were designed in the recipe to become effective in an hour.

Harry supposed the idea was that it was better to have a shorter working time than to be stuck in a different form forever.

Or was it?

Harry had a tentative plan to get around the annoying need to take Polyjuice every hour. It revolved around the fact that the Polyjuice recipe was so air-tight. Every ingredient had a purpose and was carefully measured against all the other ingredients. In this way, the finished potion was entirely neutral. It wouldn't react with anything until drunk, which meant anyone's hair could be added safely, but that also meant that anything else could be added safely as well. Harry was at this point playing with the idea of adding an ingredient to make the change permanent. Not irreversible, of course, but permanent in that the transformation would not reverse itself naturally. It wouldn't be practical for anyone who wanted to become someone else for a day, but for six years? Harry thought it was a rather good idea. She would simply add the ingredient that would ensure permanence at the same time she added the modified magical signature. Of course, that meant that she had to figure out how to blend the signatures correctly first.

Harry found that it helped to think in terms of colours. Right now she was red and Archie was yellow. They wanted to both end up as a sort of yellow-orange. It would be all too obvious, however, if they were both to become yellow-orange overnight. Instead, the plan would actually involve a series of permanent Polyjuice Potions, individualized for both Harry and Archie and spread out over at least half a year. In the first dose, she would change slightly, and with each dose after that she would be more orange-red, then more orange, and eventually she would reach the yellow-orange at the same time Archie would. She hadn't yet decided how many doses it would take to change them slowly enough that those who saw them every day didn't notice anything, but that was the general plan.

Or it would be, if Harry could just figure out how to differentiate the parts of a magical signature.

Harry sighed and closed the book she was reading. It hadn't told her anything the other twenty books hadn't already said. She needed to start brewing for Krait anyway if she wanted to have the crates filled before noon like usual. Harry checked the clock-face on the Library wall. It was already eight in the morning.

She shelved the books carefully before going down to the lab. There wasn't a crazy librarian to give her the evil eye if she left them out, but she didn't want one of the adults to see what she was reading up on. Better that they thought she was in the library studying for her owl-school classes. Harry felt marginally better by the time she'd gotten the cauldron off of the drying rack and set it up. She was starting a new potion today, after all, and there was no way to be morose while doing that. She read over the recipe for the love potion Krait had given her the day before carefully.

She had never brewed a love potion before, and Krait had never stocked them before either, but his sales had been up since she started, a combination of having a wider stock available and the fact that Leo was apparently quite popular with the residents of the alley. Harry guessed Leo had been frequenting the alley for a long time, fetching potion ingredients for his father and whatnot, and had made a lot of friends. Now that Leo was accompanying her to the Serpent's Storeroom, it seemed many people were curious to know what the fuss was about. More interest meant more customers, meant more demand for potions, and more for Harry to do.

So she was trying her hand at a love potion this morning and praying Archie never heard about it. He would tease her into the next century, especially after she swore up and down after reading a critique Professor Snape wrote about another Master's work with love potions when she was nine that she would never go near the silly things.

Harry got out the ingredients the recipe called for and began preparing them. Once the base was simmering, she connected her core to the potion and began imbuing. She was getting better at telling ahead of time how much magic a potion would need, and she raised her eyebrows as her senses expanded. Apparently the amount of magic needed to brew a love potion was more than two Snowhit Draughts combined. Harry wondered if all love potions needed so much magic to be stable, and theorized that maybe it was that way because potions that worked on the compulsion of the mind needed greater magical input than potions that merely affected the body. She then wondered how much magic a potion like Amortentia or Veritaserum would take to make. Perhaps she wouldn't attempt those for a few more years.

Everything was going fine, until she got to stage three. The moment she dropped the dried chimera eyes she knew something was wrong. The potion looked fine to her eyes, but through the connection she was pouring magic into, it frothed and boiled. She could feel it, at first just a little bit off to her magical senses, but growing more unstable by the moment. It felt wrong, and unbalanced, and—and dangerous. Harry backed away from the potion rapidly. It was just barely starting to bubble ominously on the outside as Harry spat out the emergency sequence as loudly and clearly as she could.

"Code Omega! Station three! Pass code: Sunset Bravo!"

At her words, the built-in safety precautions Lily had insisted on when she agreed to let Harry brew alone sprang into action. Thick, magic-reinforced shields rose from the ground and formed a secure dome over the unstable potion. A few seconds later, the potion erupted, taking chunks of the cauldron with it. It splattered with a violent shake against the clear glass of the domed container and Harry shakily sat on one of the thin metal stools to give her heart rate a chance to settle.

Five seconds later, James and Remus both tore down the stairs of the lab. They skidded to a halt when they saw Harry sitting, unharmed, well protected from the explosion, and both panted heavily.

"You…okay…Harry?" James puffed out between breaths, "We heard…the alarm."

"I'm okay, Dad," Harry said, smiling a little crookedly, "Just surprised, that's all."

"You got the shield up, though," Remus said, looking relieved, "Good job."

James reached out and tugged Harry off the stool into a strong embrace, "Scared the life out of me, Fawn. What happened?"

Harry hugged him back tightly, "It was the chimera eyes."

"That means nothing to me," James laughed out, with just the slightest hint of hysteria to it.

"Sorry," Harry muffled a laugh in her dad's arm, "Bad recipe, I think. I didn't know enough about the potion I was making to spot the error. I'll be more careful from now on."

"Well, you're all right, and that's what matters," Remus said, eyeing the mess behind the cauldron barrier uneasily, "I'll help you clean it up tomorrow, okay? Lily will want to see it when she gets home. Why don't you take it easy for the rest of the day?"

Harry nodded, detangling herself from her dad to hug Remus as well, "Thanks for coming so quickly to my rescue you guys. My very own knights in shining armour."

James smiled awkwardly, "Yeah, someday I'll figure out you don't need saving."

Harry shook her head, "Someday I really will need saving, and I'll be glad I have you there."

At her father and Remus's insistence, Harry took the rest of the morning off. They were convinced it was her tendency to over work, not the faulty recipe, that was responsible for such an unprecedented occurrence in her lab. It was true that Harry had never actually blown up a cauldron before, but at least they knew the safety precautions worked.

At noon, Harry flooed to the Leaky Cauldron, for once empty-handed. Leo stood from where he'd been lounging against a wall and smiled incredulously at her.

"Aren't you forgetting something today, sprout?" He eyed her empty hands meaningfully.

Harry smiled ruefully, "I'm afraid not. No potions today. I just came to tell you I didn't need an escort. Not that I ever need one, mind you, but whenever I suggest you stop inconveniencing yourself to ferry my potions about—"

"I tell you that nothing in the name of friendship is inconvenient," Leo finished, walking over to ruffle her hair.

"As you say," Harry sighed, patting the unruly curls back into place, "Though I don't think I'll agree that this is okay until you request something similarly inconvenient from me."

Leo shook his head at her, "You're too honest for your own good, Harry. It's like you're inviting people to do whatever they please to you."

"I'm not," Harry frowned uncomfortably, not sure which part of that statement she was protesting. She wasn't honest at all, but she couldn't tell Leo that, "I said you should request something of me if it's to be an equal friendship, not that I would let you run over me if you asked."

Leo just looked humourously down at her and changed the subject, "So why no potions today? Your brewer finally taking a much-needed day off?"

"Not exactly," Harry said, "One of the recipes Krait gave me last time was bad. A cauldron blew up, making a huge mess in the lab, so no potions."

Leo looked troubled, "Were you in the lab when the explosion happened?"

Harry shrugged, "Yes, but the lab is very well equipped in terms of safety. The shields contained the explosion, it's just a pain to clean up."

"Even so," Leo said, "It wouldn't have happened with a better recipe."

"I suppose that's true," Harry said, not really paying attention as she moved out of the way to let a large group of witches in magenta robes pass, "But a Potioneer takes that risk when trying out an unknown potion recipe. There is no committee that releases standard recipes for potions, you know. Potion Masters just publish books with the recipes they use in them. Those recipes might have been passed down to them from their mentors, or they might be changed and improved upon by the Master himself. There's no way of knowing how good a recipe is until you try it, unless there is significant research already published about a particular recipe."

Leo ran a hand through his brown hair distractedly, "Yeah, I guess. Still…"

Harry took a step toward the door, saying, "Sorry you coming here was even more unnecessary than usual today, Leo. I'll see you tomorrow I expect."

Leo raised an eyebrow, "Where are you going, then?"

"I'm going to see about getting a better recipe from the boss," Harry said.

"Alright, let's go," Leo said, his laid back grin back in place, "I've got to have a few words with Mr. Krait myself."

Harry sighed, "I really don't need any protection today, Leo. My hands are free."

"You don't believe me? I'm crushed. All right, young Harry. No protection, then. How about a friend?" Leo said, holding the back door of the pub open expectantly.

"I suppose one always needs friends," Harry said, smiling slightly. She glanced up at Leo as she walked out onto the alley, "Friends help each other, though, so start thinking of ways I can repay you."

Leo just smiled, and they walked the familiar route to Knockturn Alley companionably. When they got to the Serpent's Storeroom, Mr. Krait greeted them with the same nonplussed resignation he always did.

"Back again, Harry? Oh, look, Leo's here too. What a surprise," Krait yawned theatrically, waving them to the back. "Just set the crates over—hang on. No potions today?" He lifted his chin from his other hand and looked between the two of them expectantly, "Didn't run into trouble on the alley again, did you?"

"No, Mr. Krait," Harry said, "I'm afraid the recipe you gave me for the love potion was faulty. It blew up the cauldron, unfortunately, so I was wondering if you had a different version somewhere."

Krait sat straight up, frowning, "Faulty recipe? I'm sorry, kid, are you okay?"

Harry nodded.

Leo scowled, "Harry was in the lab when it happened."

"Well of course he was—ahem," Krait coughed amusedly as he caught himself. He seemed to enjoy pulling one over on Leo, and had yet to correct him about who was brewing the potions, "I suppose as the, ah, assistant you got the brunt of it?"

Harry shook her head, "I'm fine. The lab has shields that we can activate when a cauldron is unstable."

"Well, I do feel bad about it, though," Krait scratched his chin, "It wasn't my recipe. I don't deal much with love potions and the like. With all the new customers coming in I thought to expand a bit, so I got the recipe off an old friend. Perhaps he wasn't as friendly as I thought. Blew up the cauldron, you say? That's not an easy feat, though of course they don't make cauldrons like they used to. Bottoms are all thin and weak."

Harry shrugged, "I understand how it is with unfamiliar recipes. Usually I'd catch something so out of place, but I'm not familiar with love potions either. Now I know not to add chimera eyes at least."

"Dried chimera eyes?" At Harry's nod, Krait's eyes grew wide and he paled abruptly, "I should have looked at that recipe. I'm really sorry, kid, I could have caught that if I'd looked. Dried chimera eyes," he shook his head, a bit shaky, "Those should only be used in the most basic and least reactive potions. Violent ingredient, they are, one of the few that react with large amounts of magic. With the magic involved in a love potion, I'm very surprised you got out of the blast zone in time, kid. That kind of reaction would have had almost no visible warning signs."

Harry shifted uncomfortably, "Just luck I guess."

At her words, Leo blew out a breath harshly. She turned to glance at him and nearly stepped back in surprise. Leo's face was dark with suppressed emotion. He was glaring at Krait so fiercely Krait actually winced.

"Who gave you that recipe?" Leo asked in a voice that was dangerous and low, "Tell me it wasn't one of ours." Harry couldn't believe such a sound was coming from Leo. Even when he had moments of seriousness, her friend's voice only acquired a firm edge. This was different. Leo sounded like a general whose subordinate had directly disobeyed him. He was angry.

Krait swallowed heavily, "It was Claw, your—Leo. Claw gave the recipe to me. He was supposed to deliver it from Solom, who got it off a traveling potion brewer at the Dancing Dragon, but I'm thinking Claw might have changed a few things in the delivering."

Leo let out a breath slowly, still visibly upset, "Couldn't have been Solom, you're right. Claw though…I don't know as much about him as I'd like. I'll look into it, Edgar."

"As you like, Leo," Krait said, "Now, Harry, you'll send me the bill for the new cauldron?"

"It's not exactly your fault, though, is it?" Harry said dubiously, "Why don't I send the bill to this Claw person?"

"Because Claw eats little kids like you for breakfast," Krait snorted, "I'll take care of it, brat. I should have looked at the recipe before handing it over in any case. That'll teach me to let my guard down, won't it?"

"Do you think this guy was trying to kill you, Mr. Krait?" Harry asked, eyes wide. Why was Krait not more alarmed at the idea?

"Who knows?" Krait said gruffly, "Could be me, or if he knows I contract out it could be one of my brewers who was the target. No way of knowing, since I don't advertise who makes what potions unless a customer specifically asks."

"I see," Harry said, "Well, let me know if you get a better copy of that potion you wanted, Mr. Krait."

"Will do, kid. Just keep making the old ones for now," Krait said.

Harry bade Krait good day. Leo left the shop with her. He was still frowning, brooding about Claw or the phony recipe or something. Harry kept glancing at him as they walked back toward Diagon Alley. She felt like she should say something, anything to make Leo snap out of his black mood. It wasn't like him to be upset for so long, at least as far as she knew. Come to think of it, Harry didn't know too much about Leo, besides that his dad was Malcolm Hurst and his mother was some kind of Healer who worked at a wizarding clinic. Probably she should learn a little more about Leo, if they were to be friends. Then again, that would be a little hypocritical of her. She hadn't exactly been very honest or forthcoming with Leo.

Perhaps it was time to change that.

When they reached the main alley, Leo turned toward the Leaky Cauldron, but Harry snagged his elbow and turned him the other direction, toward Gringotts. Leo allowed her to tow him forward a few steps, a bemused eyebrow rising as he looked down at her.

"Are we not going to the Leaky Cauldron today?" he asked.

"We are not," Harry said, "I am taking the day off while the lab gets cleaned up and you are taking the day off from…whatever you do with your days because you are not fit company for anyone at the moment."

"Permit me to point out a couple of flaws in that plan," Leo said, though he didn't stop her from steering them down the alley, "If you are the assistant, shouldn't you be the one cleaning the lab? Also, it is strange of you to volunteer to accompany me this afternoon if I am not fit company."

"It's true that normally such an act would be bothersome," Harry said loftily, "But I have found that nothing in the name of friendship is truly inconvenient. I shall bear with your towering temper if only so that no one else shall have to."

"Towering temper?" Leo said incredulously, "I'm not that upset."

"Well you won't be upset at all after this," Harry said.

"After what?" Leo frowned, "Where are we going?"

"You mean, 'where have we arrived?'" Harry corrected, stopping and turning Leo to look at the brightly coloured shop front before them.

"Fortescue's?" Leo glanced sideways at her.

"Ice cream makes everything better," Harry said, adding, "Except potions," as an afterthought.

"How old are you?" Leo asked, amusedly.

Harry frowned inwardly at the jab at her age, but at least Leo wasn't scowling darkly any more.

"Old enough to appreciate the good things in life," she said, pushing the older boy by the small of his back into the ice cream parlour, "Besides, it's not just ice cream I'm giving you today."

"Oh?" Leo laughed at her insistent manoeuvring and held his hands up to show that he'd go quietly to the counter.

"Yes," Harry said seriously, "Today you get information."

"About you?" Leo glanced at her sharply, "A rare thing indeed. What's the occasion?"

"Your grumpiness," Harry said teasingly, "Also, I think we've reached the point where it's clear you're not going to just go away. If I don't tell you now, it'll be ugly when you find out later, and I guess I don't have a real reason to keep it from you." Besides habit, she added silently.

Leo looked down at her smugly, "Finally. All right, I want two scoops of strawberry and one of chocolate."

Harry spluttered, "Wha-? You're the almost-grown-up! You're supposed to pay."

Leo shook his finger at her, "A-ah, Harry. You invited me, and you're the one with the job. You should pay."

"But—but I'm saving my money for—"

"For?" Leo pressed, interested.

Harry blew air at her bangs in annoyance, "Okay, fine, I'll pay. But you're only getting two scoops."

"Stingy," Leo sniffed, then grinned at her. Harry grinned back. Ice cream was definitely a good idea.

She ordered their ice cream and handed over the sickles with good grace. She really wasn't worried about having enough money for the apartment come August. She was making plenty with all the potions she was brewing for Krait. They sat outside so they could people-watch while they ate. After a while Leo began pointing out people who passed by and telling Harry about them. It was rather like listening to the Malfoys tell her about their guests at the Garden Party, and yet, it was nothing like that. The people milling about Diagon were completely different from the sharp and sparkling purebloods who frequented Malfoy Manor.

Also, Leo didn't tell her about people's dirty secrets. Instead, she learned that the woman who worked at the bakery across the street was dating the blacksmith's brother, who was planning on proposing to her on their four-year anniversary. She learned that the boy who swept the feathers up at Eeylops Owl Emporium was the son of the chef who cooked for the kitchens at the Dancing Dragon. She learned that the boy's name was Jason, and that he wanted to be a toy-maker when he grew up. Apparently Jason's woodcarvings were already very well known about the alley.

Harry listened and watched as Leo's face came alive. He talked about these people like they were all a part of his family. His hazel eyes shone with sincere fondness when he told her about the man who'd sold a priceless ruby for a dragon's egg, which had turned out to be a dud. The man had then sold that very dragon's egg to some rich bloke from the continent and used the money to set up shop as an apothecary. That man, it turned out, was none other than Mr. Mulpepper—Mr. Tate's boss! Harry had quite a laugh over that one.

Eventually, though, Leo turned his eyes from the street to her face, "So, now that I'm all cheered up again, weren't you going to give me something?"

Harry pushed her empty dish away from her with resignation, "Three questions. No promises, though—I'll pass on a question I don't want to answer."

Leo smiled, "More than enough. Okay, first: I know you and Krait are keeping something from me. What is it?"

Harry winced, "Maybe this wasn't a good idea. I don't want to de-cheerify you already."

"I promise not to get upset by anything you tell me," Leo said, "I'm too happy you're telling me to care that you lied to me for so long."

Harry smiled a little, maybe if she was lucky everyone would react that way in the end, "Your interest in me cannot possibly be healthy."

Leo looked a little bit ill, "Well, when you say it like that…" he grimaced, rolling his shoulders as if to banish an uncomfortable feeling, "Just answer the question."

"You're right," Harry admitted, "Krait does sort of know something you don't. It's not that we were lying to you, though. You just assumed, and we never really corrected you."

"About…?"

"Well, the reason I won't get in trouble for taking the day off while the lab is such a mess is because I'm not actually a lab assistant," Harry said, "I'm a Potioneer. I'm the one who makes the potions I bring to Krait every day, so the boring old potion maker who you're always saying needs a day off is actually…me. Surprise," she finished weakly.

Leo leaned back into his chair, blinking slowly. He cleared his throat, "I'm feeling a bit…sheepish. You really made all those potions?"

Harry nodded.

"I guess I can see why you didn't tell me," Leo said, laughing a bit, "I'm not sure how many people would believe a sprout like you was working as a potion maker. On the other hand, that sounds exactly like Krait to hire the first person who answered his ad, regardless of age or experience. Besides," Leo considered her with careful eyes, "I don't think you're lying. Something about you seems trustworthy today."

"Just today?" Harry asked.

"No one is trustworthy all the time," Leo said.

"Isn't that what trustworthy means?" Harry shook her head, "If someone isn't trustworthy all the time, then they aren't trustworthy."

"But then no one would be trustworthy," Leo said blankly.

"Maybe no one is," Harry muttered.

Leo frowned, "What a negative way of looking at things. Where's your youthful sense of naïve optimism?"

"Hidden behind my sense of reality," Harry said, "We're off topic though. Ask your next question."

Leo pursed his lips, thinking hard, "Now that I know you're the potion brewer, I have more questions, not less. Hmm, what to ask? I know! What's your last name?"

Harry winced, "Should have seen that one coming."

"Yes, you should," Leo said unrepentantly, "Come on, tell me. I won't spread it around."

"Promise?" Harry looked imploringly at him, "You can't tell anyone. My parents don't know I have a summer job, much less one on Knockturn Alley."

Leo frowned, "So no one knows where you go every day? What if something were to happen to you? That's not safe, Harry."

"My cousin knows where I am," Harry said.

"So you have cousins now, too?" Leo teased.

"One cousin," Harry said, "Only he's not really my cousin. We just grew up together, and his dad is like my uncle, so we call each other cousins, that's all. Because our fathers were practically brothers when they were young. Though…I guess technically we're related because my grandmother was his great aunt or something. It's too distant to really count."

"Interesting, but you haven't answered my question," Leo said, leaning forward, "I'm afraid if you pass on this one it will be most suspicious, Harry."

Harry swallowed, but really, what harm could it do? He already knew she was called Harry, and she didn't really have to pretend to be Rigel over the summer. Harry the girl liked potions too, after all. She'd just give him the usual cover story; she was Harry Potter, halfblood who attended AIM during the year, interested in Healing and Potions. Nothing complicated about it, except it felt complicated, because in reality she was Harry-Rigel-Potter-Black who dressed as a boy during the school year to masquerade as her pureblooded cousin at Hogwarts. Still, Leo didn't have to know anything about that. For Leo, she could be uncomplicated.

"My name is Harry Potter," she said, "Krait didn't ask for my full name when he hired me, so I didn't tell him. I was afraid he wouldn't hire me if he knew…" Harry shrugged uncomfortably.

"Knew…" Leo leaned back suddenly, his face slack with surprise, "Holy Merlin, you're a girl!"

Harry flushed as several patrons turned in their seats to look curiously at their table, "Leo! Quiet, will you?"

"I can't believe—you—" Leo blew out a breath and ran both hands roughly through his hair, "Harry Potter, of course. The only daughter of James and Lily Potter, Heir to the House of Potter. Black hair, green eyes. Your Uncle is Sirius Black, childhood best friend of James Potter, and your mother works for the private company that the patent office at the Ministry contracts out to, testing experimental magical inventions, including potions. No wonder you have access to a state-of-the-art potions lab."

Harry was taken aback, "You, um, know an awful lot about people you've never met."

"I know a lot about everyone," Leo said absently, staring at her without blinking, "I can see it now, kind of. I did think you were a little scrawny for a twelve-year-old boy. The short hair though…it threw me off, I admit. Usually I see clearer than most, but I guess that's what happens when you let your expectations run away with your common sense."

"Don't feel bad," Harry said comfortingly, "Nearly everyone assumes I'm a boy, unless they've known me forever, like Mr. Tate. I didn't want to tell Krait because he hired me thinking I was a boy. You probably already know, since your dad is the Aldermaster of the Guild, but the potions community can be a trifle…sexist at times."

"No kidding," Leo snorted, "Bunch of bigoted twits, barring a select few."

"Yeah," Harry said, "So, are you going to give me away?"

"Not even Krait knows you're a…" he lowered his voice, "girl?"

Harry shook her head warily.

Leo laughed, "Good. Not that I think he'd fire you at this point, but now we're the ones keeping a secret from him. Serves him right. I won't tell anyone."

"Thanks, Leo," Harry said, "So has the shock set in yet?"

"Any minute now," Leo rubbed his chest theatrically, "Lucky I'm a young man or my heart would have stopped from all the surprises I'm getting in one sitting."

"You should probably forget about the last question, then," Harry said seriously, "It's not worth endangering your health, after all."

"Not a chance," Leo flashed even teeth at her, "I'm even more curious about you now, Harry."

"Don't be," Harry laughed weakly, "After all, you've already found out my best secrets, so everything else will be rather anti-climactic, I bet."

"Only one way to find out," Leo said cheerfully, "Last question: you said you were working for Krait to save money for something. What were you saving your money for?"

Harry tensed. "Pass."

Leo lost his grin and raised his brows incredulously, "What, seriously? You tell me all of that and you're passing on this?"

"Yes," Harry said firmly, "Sorry, Leo."

Leo nodded slowly, "It's your right to keep your lips zipped. Just strange, that's all. Is it something illegal?"

"Is that your third question?" Harry asked evenly. She couldn't tell him she was going to buy an apartment for the school year because she wouldn't actually be in the apartment during the school year. Talk about suspicious.

Leo narrowed his eyes, "Yes. I want to know if what you're doing with your money is going to be dangerous or get you into trouble."

Harry thought about it, "What I'm doing with the money won't get me into trouble. It's perfectly legal. The reasons for it, though…maybe. I hope not, but I can't say it won't be bad if I get caught." She winced, "That's really all I can tell you, Leo. Sorry."

Leo waved her off, his face lightening though she noticed his eyes still looked a bit concerned, "It's enough, lass. Now, you should know that everything you've told me has only strengthened my reasoning for escorting you through Knockturn Alley."

Harry groaned, "Leo—"

"Let's see," Leo said, ticking his fingers as he listed reasons, "Young, female, practically nobility, rich (on account of the nobility), weak (physically speaking of course, no offence), innocent, gullible—"

"I'm not gullible!" Harry protested.

"But you admit you're all those other things," Leo said quickly, "It's settled, then."

"Says who?" Harry muttered half-heartedly. She should have known that if Leo wasn't offended and horrified to discover the truth he would use it as an excuse to treat her like—like some sort of glass that couldn't be repaired with a repairing charm.

"Says me," Leo said. He stood and collected their empty ice cream dishes and set them on the return tray, "Come on, Harry. It's about time I showed you something of my world."

Harry stood, following Leo to the door hesitantly, "Your world?"

"Just you wait, lass," Leo winked at her.

He led her back to Knockturn Alley, one hand on her shoulder to guide her steps. They walked past the alley the Serpent's Storeroom was on, past a woman giving out fingernail samples, down to the far end of Knockturn Alley, where it intersected with a street called Kyprioth Court, which was a long street with many branching alleys. The street dead-ended in a semi-circle, and that was where Leo seemed to be moving her toward.

Harry had never been so far into the heart of the Lower Alleys. She knew the streets behind Knockturn were the underbelly of Wizarding London—everybody knew that, and only the most confident or the most careless wandered the Lower Alleys without leave. Harry wondered idly which described she and Leo better, and stuck close to her taller friend as they wove their way along the street to the large inn that stood at the curved dead end of the street, a storey higher than all the other buildings on Kyprioth Court.

Music played from inside the inn, and the lights from the windows beckoned cheerfully to them, for though it was mid-afternoon, the alley was shadowed beneath overhanging roofs that seemed to have been engineered for the very purpose of keeping out light. The sign above the door depicted a dragon rearing onto its hind legs, its claws extended and its mouth open.

"A dragon rampant?" Harry asked curiously, wrinkling her nose a bit. How odd.

"Why not?" Leo shrugged. He stepped lightly onto the front stoop of the inn and knocked thrice. The door swung open on its own and Leo swept Harry a formal bow, "Welcome, young Harry, to the Dancing Dragon."

Harry raised an eyebrow at the introduction, but entered the inn anyway. It was a warm, inviting sort of place. The first floor was large and open, littered with big wooden tables that told Harry the inn was probably a tavern as well. A lone mop made its way slowly across the floor with lazy flourishes. A narrow wooden staircase led upstairs, and behind the bar a big door to what must be the kitchens was propped open, letting warm, fragrant air blow out into the main room. At the moment there weren't many people there, just a group of three men and one woman who were sitting around the table closest to the unlit fireplace, but Harry could easily imagine the place filled with lively customers, all shouting and singing and carrying on. It didn't seem like the sort of place she'd always envisioned a bar down Knockturn would be—dark and dim and filled with shady half-vampire things. From the obvious age of the well-kept inn and its place of prominence on what looked like the main court of the Lower Alleys, Harry guessed that it was a place steeped in tradition, a staple to the community, much like Gringotts Bank was on Diagon Alley.

Leo closed the door behind them and called out a hearty greeting to the four people across the room, who had stopped their conversation and looked up when they noticed Harry and Leo's entrance. The group made to stand, but aborted the gesture halfway and instead sat down again. Harry thought she saw Leo make a hand-motion of some kind out of the corner of her eye, but couldn't be sure.

"Solom! Just the man I was looking for," Leo said, putting a hand between Harry's shoulder blades and guiding her toward the group.

The oldest man, who looked to be in his late forties (though you never could tell with wizards), bowed his head to Leo respectfully as he flicked his wand a final time at the mop across the room and stowed the short wand up his sleeve, "What can I be doing for you today, Highness?"

Harry turned disbelieving eyes on Leo, who ignored her look with the grace of one who had been ignoring other people's disbelief for years.

Leo pressed Harry into a seat next to the woman, who was dressed in tight red robes that accentuated her every curve. She was very pretty, and smiled kindly, if a bit curiously, at Harry when she sat. Leo took the seat opposite her, next to a stocky man with an impressive goatee, and addressed the older man, who was sitting on the other side of the woman in the red dress, once again.

"Did you send a potion recipe to Edgar the other day?" Leo asked casually.

"Sure did," Solom said, shrugging.

"Who passed it along for you?" Leo asked.

"It were Claw, Highness," Solom said, scratching his head, "Did the blighter not give it to Ed after all?"

"No, he gave it," Leo said, "Only we reckon he gave Edgar a copy of the recipe, and took a little creative licence in the copying, if you catch my meaning."

Solom furrowed his brows angrily, "What a measly little bastard."

The woman next to Harry clicked her tongue and put her hands over Harry's ears, frowning disapprovingly at Solom.

The older man just grunted, "Come off it, Rispah. If His Majesty sees fit to bring the lad here, he best be expecting his ears to burn a bit."

Leo grinned, "The lad doesn't mind, does he?"

Harry rolled her eyes at Leo, who clearly thought her boyish looks were a great joke now that he was in on it, and said, "Thank you, my lady, but I fear I am used to such language by now." That wasn't precisely true, but Harry didn't want to spend the afternoon with hands on her ears.

Rispah removed her hands, but not before ruffling Harry's hair playfully, "Hear that? I'm a lady." Her voice was husky and low. She shook her long red hair back and smiled widely.

The man across from Solom snorted. He was tall and broad shouldered, with thick brown hair and an easy smile, "If you're a lady, then I'm the Queen of Egypt."

"I think the lad said you were his lady," the man with the goatee teased, "Isn't that what you heard, Marek?"

"Come to think of it, that is what he said, Aled," Marek said thoughtfully, "What bold young friends our Highness has today."

"Though of course it is heartening to see that the youth of today are as confident and bold as ever," Aled chuckled, winking at Harry with amusement.

Harry blushed, but otherwise didn't react to the ribbing. She supposed she deserved it. Pureblood manners were certainly out of place in this crowd—they just made her look uppity and rather foolish. Still, if she was going to pretend to be a boy, then she'd be a boy who respected women. It was the least she could do for female kind.

Rispah caught sight of her flushed face and laughed lowly, "Now don't go teasing the boy for having something the lot of you could do with from time to time. Good manners ain't nothing to sneeze at."

"Well said, Rispah," Leo inclined his head to her, "But we are getting a bit off track."

"Well what do you expect when you bring such a lovely distraction?" Rispah chuckled, running her hands through Harry's hair once more. Harry was starting to feel like someone's prize pet. "Oh, go on then, Leo," Rispah waved a hand at him, "What's the problem then? Ed's no slouch at what he does. He surely caught the mistake right off if it was as significant as you're implying, so we add another minus to Claw's character report and be done with it."

Leo shook his head, "It's nothing so simple, I'm afraid. Edgar doesn't brew most of the potions he sells anymore. He contracts them out to three different potion brewers."

"Three?" Marek, the broad-shouldered man, spoke up, "Thought it was two."

"Naw, he's got a new one now—goes on and on about him," Aled said absently.

"Yes, he recently hired a third," Leo said, "And the point is that the recipe went straight to the new brewer, who didn't catch the mistake before the cauldron blew sky high."

Solom looked disturbed, "What on earth did Claw do to that recipe? That sounds like an assassination attempt—a pretty poor one, but there you are."

"He added chimera eyes," Leo said, "But we don't know who it was intended for—it could be Edgar himself or it could have been any one of the three brewers."

"Either way, Claw's over-stepped himself," Aled grunted, fiddling with his goatee agitatedly.

"It were only a matter of time," Marek said, leaning over the table to make his point, "We all know Claw's trouble. No one knows where he came from, but everyone knows what he's after."

The four of them shared a significant look that went completely over Harry's head. She wondered if it would be rude to say something, but realized that she'd never know if she didn't ask.

"Sorry, but who's Claw? And what does he want?" Harry asked, looking from face to face apologetically.

"Why should we tell you?" Aled raised an eyebrow challengingly at her.

Harry bristled unintentionally, "Seeing as it was my cauldron that man destroyed, either intentionally or not, I now have a rather invested interest in his purposes."

Aled chuckled heartily and the others joined in, smiling at Harry as though she were quite amusing to them.

"He's just teasing you, lad," Rispah said conspiratorially, "Aled likes to tease the new folk, he does."

"But surely you're not the new brewer Ed's been going on about?" Solom leaned past Rispah to stare incredulously at Harry, "He's been chortling to all his customers how he's got the best brewer in all the alleys working for him. Fast and reliable, he says, and the whole time it were a mite no bigger than an anthill? What a laugh." The older man grinned widely at her and pounded a fist on the table to express how funny he found this and Harry tried not to look put out at what a great joke she was to these people.

"Careful now, Solom," Leo said, smiling at Harry's disgruntled expression, "You don't want to hurt the boy's feelings. Harry here takes his potions very seriously."

"Not as seriously as Leo takes himself," Harry shot back. Before she could wince and apologize for snapping, the men at the table broke into loud guffaws and Rispah slapped her knee smartly.

"He's got you pegged, Leo," the lady said, shaking her head of long hair back, "Well done, little one. I daresay Leo deserved that."

Leo grinned, "There, doesn't he fit right in? I'd say the least we owe him is an explanation, since he's dragged into this mess already."

"Fair enough," Aled said, "Well as to your questions, Claw is a man who showed up in the Lower Alleys not ten months ago. He's meaner than a wild boar and trickier than a barrel of hinkypunks. He petitioned to join the Rogue, and of course we don't turn folk away without a good reason, but it's been clear from the start he don't really have an interest in bettering the Court."

"He don't follow the Code," Marek growled, "The scum keeps for himself what he should pay to the Rogue. He don't look out for the alley folk, and you mark my words he's sold out a man or two to the tracking dogs at the Ministry."

"And if that weren't enough," Rispah put in, "Claw's got his eye on Leo's job. Nothing wrong with that, of course—Marek alone has challenged Leo a fair few times, but Claw don't do nothing by the book. He hides in the shadows, waiting for a chance to stab us all in the back."

Harry blinked, "Okay, but honestly…I'm more confused than I was. Code? Court?"

Everyone turned to look exasperatedly at Leo, who shrugged a bit sheepishly, "I, ah, hadn't gotten the chance to tell him yet?"

Rispah rolled her eyes, "So of course you brought the lad here anyway. Poor thing, no wonder you're confused."

"And no wonder he calls you 'Leo,' Highness," Aled said.

"Would you all stop confusing him further?" Solom broke in, sighing, "Look, lad, it's like this. You know what the Lower Alleys are?"

"The alleys in Wizarding London located beyond Knockturn," Harry said, "A mix of business and residential properties, I think."

"The poor alleys," Rispah said tartly, "You can say it like it is. The Lower Alleys are the wizarding underground. Home to the seedy parts of life no one likes to talk about. Everyone says it's naught but criminals and tramps, and everyone's silently grateful the disgraceful community is content to remain separate from the Wizarding whole for the most part. Aye, there's beggin' and thievin' and the like, make no mistake, but there's so much more." Rispah's face was alight with passion, and in it Harry could see a thousand stories she would probably never understand. "There's life in these alleys, lad. There's folk who spend their lives without two galleons to rub together and are happy despite it. This world, our world, is a place beyond blood and money, though there's plenty of the former spilt for the latter at times. It's about community, and family, and working and singing next to anyone who's got a ready smile and an open mind."

Harry stared up at the lady, this scarlet bird with such a lovely song, and thought that she would never understand life half as well as Rispah did.

Solom put a hand gently on Rispah's shoulder, "That was lovely, lass, but it don't really explain much about the way we work." Rispah smiled and gestured for Solom to get on with it then. "The truth of the matter is, the Lower Alleys and most folk in it don't really answer to any authority you've heard of. The Ministry and the Wizengamot have nothing to do with us—ashamed and in denial, they are—and we have as little as possible to do with them. Back before the Ministry and all that political nonsense we have nowadays, Wizarding Britain, like the rest of the civilized world, was ruled by a King. There was wizarding nobility, of course, who eventually became watered down into the most ancient and noble family houses you'd hear of today—the Malfoys and the Bones, the Blacks and the Goldentowers. With me so far?"

Harry nodded. She had known that the most wealthy and well-known houses were descendent from ancient nobility, and also that the practice of a Wizarding King had been abandoned after too many tyrants and subsequent uprisings had made the magical community unstable.

"Well, just as the nobles and middling classes had their King, we of the Lower Alleys had our King," Solom said, "Our King wasn't decided by birth and blood. He earned his crown by besting the other hopefuls in open combat."

"You mean free dueling?" Harry asked interestedly. Free dueling was mixed dueling. The fighters could rely on not just magic but potions, swords, knives, and hand-to-hand fighting as well, "I've heard of it, but never seen it done. It was banned from most official tournaments, wasn't it?"

Aled grinned, "Stick around long enough, lad, and you'll see it done. They can ban it all they want in their trumped up tourneys. It's tradition that the title of King is passed on by the outcome of open, or free, dueling combat. This is because part of the King's job is to defend his people. It's not so literal nowadays, of course, but so it stands."

"So what you're saying is that Leo is your…King?" Harry wasn't sure whether to laugh or frown, "I've seen him fight, so I guess I can see how it happened, but…aren't you a little young to be King?"

Leo grinned, "No rules about age, blood, race, or even sex—though I don't think we've ever had a woman King. Just Queens like Rispah here, who take care of the familial matters of Court."

"You're Queen?" Harry blinked up at Rispah, "Did you have to fight as well?"

Rispah laughed, "No, lad, the Queen is appointed by the King, though of course it must be someone who's been with the ladies of the Court a long time."

"Is that why you call him 'Leo' instead of 'Highness?'" Harry asked.

Rispah shook her head, "Nothing so formal. Leo's my younger cousin. I couldn't call him Highness with a straight face, considering I still remember changing his—"

"Yes, yes, Rispah," Leo broke in hastily, "I'm sure Harry doesn't want to hear about that."

"Oh, I don't know—" Harry grinned.

"Wouldn't you rather hear about Claw?" Leo suggested, his face flushing a bit at the laughter of his friends.

"I'd rather hear about this Code thing," Harry said, "It sounds important."

"It is," Marek said earnestly, "It's what holds all of us together."

"Us?" Harry clarified, "You mean everyone in the Lower Alleys?"

"The Court of the Rogue is all of us who make our living by our wits," Leo said, grinning, "The Rogue, you see, is just another name for the King down here. To keep him separate from the old Wizarding King, they called our King the Rogue or the King of Thieves. Of course, not everyone in the Court is a thief, and certainly not all those in the Lower Alleys work outside of the Ministry's Law, but those that make their lives here and pledge themselves to the Court must obey the thief's Code."

"So what does that entail?" Harry asked.

"Lots of things," Marek said, "Part of the Code says that no one can be King without beating the previous King in open, single, combat, which means that a person can't take the Rogue's throne by intrigue or secrecy. It keeps the Court from splitting into factions and taking sides. The Court always sides with the King, so long as the King upholds the Rogue's Code."

"The Code also says none of us can betray another to the Ministry's Law. We have our own justice, which can't be satisfied by the Aurors coming in and hauling our people off," Aled explained, "It's also against the Code to go after someone's family to try and harm them indirectly. If you have a problem with someone, you must take it up directly with them."

Harry nodded slowly. A lot of what they said seemed sensible for the kind of life they led.

"The King is bound by the Code as well," Leo said seriously, "He has to keep track of and look after his people, good times or bad. When the Aurors raid the Lower Alleys, the King makes sure his people are protected, and when the Ministry taxes basic goods to raise money for one thing or another, the King has to make sure those goods are still available to the poorest of his folk…one way or another."

Harry thought for a moment. She still didn't really understand everything—like why Claw had changed the recipe in the first place—but she summed up what she did understand slowly, "So this Claw is breaking the Code, because he wants to be King, but doesn't want to challenge Leo directly?"

"Exactly," Rispah said, "The man's a leech, but without proof…well, it just won't do for the Court to turn away one of its own without solid enough reason. Claw can easily say that the recipe was already written like that when he got it, or that someone must have changed it after he'd handed it over. The plausible deniability is too high, you see?"

"But we'll watch him," Aled said, "We'll not trust him with Rogue's business after this, and he'll not get away with that stunt a second time. Slowly he'll dig himself into a pit he can't get out of. Then we'll banish him for good."

Leo stretched and sighed, "Well now that we've got that out of the way, let's talk about something else."

"How about your new friend, Highness?" Marek looked over Harry appraisingly, "I'd heard rumours that you'd offered Rogue protection to a new kid, but I didn't imagine him so young." Marek grinned at Harry mischievously, "How'd you end up in such bad company, lad?"

Harry grinned back, "Ask Leo. He stalked me for about a month before I got tired of trying to get rid of him."

Leo sputtered and clutched at his chest in mock anguish, and Harry thought with amusement that he was not like any King she'd ever imagined meeting. It was surreal, in a way, to be sitting in the Dancing Dragon as if she was not all of those things that Leo's friends dismissed so readily—rich, descendent from nobility, educated, and upright. And yet, Harry suspected they all knew exactly what she was, and didn't care a lick. Like Rispah said, as long as she had an open mind they were content to take her as she was.

"Stalking is a little harsh," Leo said.

"That's true," Rispah said, "I hear it was more like Leo following the lad around like a lost puppy."

"Puppy?" Leo scoffed, "I saved the kid's life, you know."

"And to repay you the lad let you be his manservant, is that it?" Rispah laughed, "If he was a girl, I'd call you whipped, Leo."

"To be fair," Harry said, fighting a blush, "It was actually very kind of Leo to help me out like that. I wasn't very familiar with Knockturn when I started working for Mr. Krait, so it was lucky Leo was in the alley when he was, or I might be kidney-less."

"Kidney-less?" Aled raised an eyebrow.

Leo shook his head wryly, "He wasn't after your kidney, Harry. He was going to—actually, I'll tell you when you're older."

Harry scowled, "Either way, I still owe you quite a debt, Leo."

"Our Highness doesn't often collect his debts," Aled said, shooting Leo a look that made Harry think it was an old disagreement between the two of them.

"In that case, I'll have to decide the price and pay it by myself," Harry said, grinning, "Maybe I'll repay your kindness by following you around for a couple of months."

Leo laughed, "I'd like to see you try, Harry. I'm not an easy person to follow. Though, I might make an exception for you."

Harry opened her mouth to reply, but couldn't think of anything to say to that, and shut it again instead.

"Well, that explains a lot," Rispah said, smirking.

Leo stopped smiling and backtracked quickly, "Not what I meant, cuz."

"Even so," Rispah said in her husky voice, batting her brown eyes at Leo teasingly, "It makes sense if I consider things from that direction."

"What makes sense?" Marek asked innocently.

"Our King's infamously picky palate," Rispah said airily, "Turns out I've been offering him the wrong sort of dish."

"You certainly have not!" Leo exclaimed, "Merlin save me from nosy subjects. I'll not have you accusing me of preying on young Harry's virtue."

Solom choked and Harry flushed a bright scarlet that would have done Ron Weasley proud.

"Is that what you're going on about?" Aled scrubbed a hand over his goatee and narrowed his eyes at Rispah, "You keep your claws to yourself, you meddling matchmaker. His Majesty can find a lass in his own good time."

"Thank you, Aled," Leo said, "I knew there was a reason you were my favourite."

"Now I know the reason, too," Rispah said saucily, waggling her eyebrows.

"Are you now going to make disparaging remarks about myself in connection with every male of my acquaintance?" Leo asked forlornly.

"I think old Solom is safe from your designs," Rispah grinned.

"You keep me out of this," Solom mumbled.

Leo slumped disheartenedly in his seat, "Traitors."

"So the whole King thing is pretty much a formality, huh?" Harry observed.

"Pretty much, yeah," Marek grinned.

"Doesn't stop you challenging him for it every three months, Swift," Solom pointed out.

"Swift?" Harry raised an eyebrow.

"Oh, that's nice," Rispah frowned, "We never even introduced ourselves. I'm Rispah Cooper, cousin to Leo here on his mother's side, and Queen of the ladies of the Rogue."

Harry smiled, "Pleased to meet you, my lady. I'm Harry."

"Just Harry?" Marek snorted, "You don't have to hide your last name—we all know you're one of those rich nobs' kids. It don't matter to us, though. I'm Marek Swiftknife—hence the Swift."

Harry nodded, "Hello. And yes, it's just Harry. My parents don't know I have a job this summer, and it can't get back to them if no one knows who they are."

"Fair enough," Aled said, "I'm Aled Flint, the Armourer for this bunch of ninnies."

"Any relation to Marcus Flint?" Harry asked curiously.

Aled shrugged, "Sure, he's my cousin Herbert's son. You know him?"

Harry shook her head, "My cousin goes to school with him."

Aled nodded, "Not surprised. Good school, Hogwarts."

"So I hear," Harry said neutrally.

"Well I'm Solom," Solom said, "Just Solom. I run this inn. You ever get into trouble on the alleys and Leo ain't with you, run straight here, right?"

Harry smiled, "Thank you, sir, I will."

Solom waved a hand at her, grimacing, "Just Solom, lad, please."

"Don't worry," Marek grinned, "We'll scrub you of those cumbersome manners before long."

Taking a chance, Harry said, "If it's anything like the sort of scrubbing you do regularly, I think I'd be better off without it." She eyed Marek's dirty shirt and breeches meaningfully and the others laughed appreciatively.

"Well now that he's insulted Marek, it's official," Rispah laughed, slinging an arm around Harry companionably, "This lad's one of us."

"Why do you think I brought him here?" Leo asked smugly, "I knew he belonged the first time I met him."

Harry raised a sceptical brow, "Whatever you say, Majesty."

Leo frowned, "Now, now, none of that. These jokers can call me that if it makes them feel like they're posh or something, but I won't hear it from you."

"You don't make them call you that?" Harry asked curiously,

Leo scowled, "Of course not. Most of my other subjects do, out of respect, but I've specifically told my friends not to bother with it. They do it just to annoy me, I think."

"Not our fault it works so well, though, is it?" Aled chuckled.

Harry spent the rest of the afternoon and early evening in the Dancing Dragon. Other members of the Court came and went from the inn, most of them open and friendly, interested to meet the kid their King had been squiring about Knockturn. Harry still couldn't believe her friend Leo, the laid back son of the Potions Guild Aldermaster, was unofficial royalty of the Lower Alleys. How did she manage to find the most conspicuous people to become acquainted with? It certainly explained why Krait always treated Leo so strangely. Harry wondered if Leo was a thief, too. She didn't approve of thieving, but then again she could always afford to pay for things, so was her opinion really valid? She also wondered if Leo's parents knew what their son did during the day. She supposed being home schooled allowed for a flexible schedule, but surely Leo didn't have time to both run the Rogue and take full-time lessons.

Then again, Harry herself had two separate lives, didn't she? Perhaps it wasn't so fantastic a thought after all.

Leo walked her back to the Leaky Cauldron once the dinner rush started at the Dancing Dragon. Harry's brain was spinning with everything that had happened since she woke up that morning.

"What are you thinking about, Harry?" Leo asked as they passed the well-lit bookshop.

"Just how much we've learned about each other today," Harry said, "It's a bit overwhelming."

Leo grinned down at her, "We are a perfect pair, aren't we?"

Harry laughed, something she'd been doing a lot that day, "I don't know about that."

"No, really," Leo said, "We both have so many secrets, and yet are completely surprised when we find out the other has secrets of their own."

Harry flattened her hair absent-mindedly, "That's certainly true. I can't believe you're the Rogue. I didn't even know what the Rogue was!"

"Oh, yeah? Well how do you think I felt when I found out you were a girl?" Leo shook his head, "Kyprioth was playing me for a fool."

Kyprioth, Harry suddenly remembered, was an ancient god of trickery. She smiled, the Dancing Dragon being on Kyprioth Court made a lot of sense.

"Thanks for not telling your friends who I was," Harry said, "I really prefer to keep a low profile."

Leo shrugged, "Yeah, good luck with that."

"What's that supposed to mean?" Harry asked, "I'm a very low-key sort of person, you know."

"Impossible," Leo said simply, "Sorry Harry, but you're too interesting. Too…I don't know, something, to remain anonymous. People notice you, Harry, and the world seems to change suddenly when you're around, as if Magic herself was altering it to an unseen purpose. I bet you often find yourself in the middle of things without realizing how you got there, am I right?"

Harry looked away from Leo's knowing gaze, "Well, I'm trying to be low-key, okay?"

"Try all you like," Leo said, "I just don't think it's going to do much good. I have a feeling about it, and my gut's usually right."

Harry ignored her friend's words. Sure she had bad luck in the past when it came to getting caught up in messes not her own making, but this year was going to be different. Harry made a promise to herself then and there that this year she wasn't going to get involved in anything complicated or mysterious. She was going to spend time with her friends, write to Sirius, and generally just do what she came to Hogwarts to do—learn Potions.

When they reached the Leaky Cauldron, Harry said good night, but Leo hesitated. He looked very seriously into her eyes and said, "Why do I get the feeling I'm still missing something about you?"

Harry looked steadily back, "I don't pretend to know all of your secrets yet, Leo. Don't assume you know all of mine."

"But you'll tell me one day, won't you?" Leo asked. He looked frustrated, like he was halfway through with an important task but had been stopped in his tracks for a reason he couldn't understand.

"Maybe," Harry said, looking away from those bright eyes uneasily, "I'm still deciding if meeting you was a good thing."

Leo grinned slowly, "Liar. You're just scared because you know that it was."

Harry didn't say anything, but Leo didn't seem to need her to.

"That's okay, lass, you be scared all you want. But one day you will tell me everything."

Leo ruffled her hair once more and turned back down the alley. Harry watched him go, throat stuck closed with something that she assured herself was not the fear Leo spoke of. What did she have to be afraid of? Leo might be confident that he could pry her secrets from her some day, but Harry knew better. She could be friends with Leo, like him as a person, even, but she couldn't trust anyone besides Archie, and that would never change.

Chapter 3

Harry stepped out of the fireplace in her house's floo room and was immediately confronted with the business end of her father's wand. She inhaled sharply and froze; the dim illumination from James' Lumos Spell cast just enough light for Harry to see that her dad wasn't fooling around.

"Who goes there?" the elder Potter demanded, wand arm as steady as Harry knew his aim to be, "How did you get past the wards?"

Harry swallowed, realizing the remnant of the floo fire at her back was keeping her face in the shadows, "It's me, Dad. Harry."

"Harry?" James squinted against the darkness but didn't move forward or change the angle of his wand, both of which would have allowed him to see her better. He was too good an Auror to give up his advantage at the word of a potential intruder, "My daughter is in her bed—or she should be."

Harry winced. That was a fair point. She was out much later than usual for a Thursday night. Originally she had planned to be back from her errands well before her parents got home from work. They didn't exactly know what she did most of the day—though she was pretty sure they assumed studying took up a lot of it—and Harry wasn't one to explain things to her parents that she didn't have to. It was just easier that way. Today, though, Harry had been sidetracked from her agenda by an unexpected stroke of bad luck—followed, it turned out, by a bit of rather good luck, which was in turn followed by a spectacular heaping of really bad luck that spiraled into a situation that could only have been drawn from a nightmare. She felt her soul shiver with weakness and fear just thinking about it…

[Earlier That Day]

Harry finished unloading the last crate of potions in Mr. Krait's storerooms with a small sigh. Leo was busy doing something with the Rogue that day, though he had been rather vague about exactly what it was, so Harry had been on her own hauling the crates of potions from the Leaky Cauldron to the Serpent's Storeroom. She wasn't worried about the danger of walking down Knockturn alone anymore. Harry had been up and down the alley so many times that she recognized all of the usual faces that traversed the street and thought that most of them probably knew who she was as well. Or maybe not who she was, but what she was, at least. She was Leo's friend, and as much as being seen as the King of the Rogue's shiny new toy irked her at times, at least nobody bothered her as she went about her business. No, it wasn't the risk that had Harry sighing with relief once she was free of the last crate. She'd just forgotten how heavy they were.

Serves me right for relying on Leo to carry them for so many weeks, Harry thought with a fair bit of self-disgust, Not that I asked him to help, but now I've gotten all weak-armed.

She hadn't really had time for things like exercise lately. Archie asked her to play Quidditch about once a week, and Sirius still hadn't gotten rid of that pool in his basement, so it wasn't that she lacked the opportunity. There just always seemed to be more important things to do. Still, that would have to change. Every year she survived the delicate artifice she was enacting was another year the boys in her year grew taller, broader, and generally started looking less like effeminate boys and more like men. If she wanted to pass for one, she'd have to start keeping up physically.

"Oi, kid!" Krait's voice called through the open door to the storeroom, "Bring out a couple of those Blood-Replenishers while you're back there!"

"Yes, Mr. Krait!" Harry called back, stepping on one of the now-empty crates to reach the top shelf, where the Blood-Replenishing Potions were kept.

She carried the bottles out into the main room and glanced around for Krait. He was standing by one of the potion aisles, talking to a customer who had his back to her. Krait waved her over and she approached them.

"Thanks, kid," Krait said gruffly, taking the bottles and presenting them to the customer, "Take a look at these, then. What do you think?"

The other man took one of the potion bottles and held it up to the light coming through the dirty shop windows. He studied the bottle from all angles, and uncorked it to sniff at the contents with a considering frown on his face, "Good colour…hmm, yes, just the right consistency. The smell is…different, though, isn't it? You've changed the recipe, my friend. Go on, then, what did you put in it, Edgar?"

Krait smirked, "You tell me."

The other man raised an eyebrow and wafted a bit of the scent toward his nose once more. Harry looked between the two men, confused as to what exactly they were doing with her potion. The man handling the sample looked familiar to her, too. He was big and somewhat beefy, with a thin moustache under his nose and very little hair left on the top of his head.

When it came to her, Harry had to suppress the urge to whirl around and hide her face. It would only draw attention to her, so instead Harry remained very still and very calm. The man holding her Blood-Replenisher was the wizard Professor Snape had been talking to that night just before he left to find ginseng on the continent. He was the one whom she'd overheard telling Snape via floo-call about the ginseng shortage in England during the peak outbreak of the Sleeping Sickness. She recognized the tone of voice he used when speaking, like the kind you'd expect a savvy businessman to use: confident and gently cajoling, persuasive in a frankly experienced kind of a way.

"Well, it's definitely something new," the man, whose first name Harry thought was Horace, said thoughtfully. "It's faint, but there's a hint of citrus to it, am I right?"

"I wouldn't know," Krait said with a lazy grin, "Didn't make it."

"Didn't—" Horace what's-his-name scowled at Krait, "What the blazes am I inspecting it for, then? I thought you'd finally gotten me a B-R potion I can sell, and it's not even yours." The man shook his head and gave the potion back, "Shame, too, cause you know I hate buying from that Rotridge bloke. Let me know when you've got a potion like this in stock, Edgar."

"Now, now, Horace," Edgar said quickly, "I am looking to sell it. I just haven't made it myself, that's all."

"Ah," Horace gazed consideringly at the Blood-Replenishing Potion in Krait's hand once more, "Contracted out, have you? I don't usually buy through middlemen, you know. Messy business, working out cuts and all."

"Nothing like that," Krait said, glancing over Horace's shoulder to where Harry had retreated and was now watching, with no small amount of trepidation, the situation unfold, "You'd only have to pay me for the potions, as I pay the brewer separately."

"I see," Horace said, "Well, in that case I may just have to cancel my contract with Rotridge. Provided that the potions I can expect are all as good as this sample, of course."

"Of course, Horace," Krait said, "My brewer never delivers anything but the best."

Horace nodded his head seriously, "Good, good. Expect my owl in the morning with the paperwork. I'll pick up the first order in two weeks." He clapped a large hand on Krait's slighter frame jovially, "Great to be doing business with you, Edgar, as usual. Oh, and I'd very much like to meet this new brewer of yours when it's convenient. Sounds like a rare find if he has you changing your recipes after such a long time."

Krait blinked and shot Harry another look over Horace's shoulder, "Well in fact he's—"

Harry shook her head discreetly, eyes wide and pleading.

"—ah, well, he's accustomed to his anonymity," Krait finished weakly, looking confused, "I'm sure you understand. I'll talk to him about it, of course, but I can't guarantee anything."

Harry smiled slightly in gratitude, and busied herself re-organizing jars of bat brains a few aisles away until Horace took his leave of the shop.

"What was that about, kid?" Krait frowned at Harry when she came over to the front desk again, "Don't you know who that is?"

"Not really," Harry said, "Thanks for not telling him who I was."

Krait shook his head, "That was Horace Burke. He's an extremely influential businessman in Wizarding Britain."

"Burke, as in Borgin and Burkes?" Harry asked curiously.

"That Burke is Horace's cousin," Krait said, "Horace Burke is…well, I guess you'd call him a profiteer. He prides himself on being able to provide anything to anyone. Owns a bunch of warehouses in the Lower Alleys, and runs an owl-order company through them. You can order anything from Burke, and its quality and timeliness is always guaranteed. If he can't get it for you, it doesn't exist—at least not in Britain."

"I can see how he'd make money on things that are hard to find," Harry said slowly, "But who would buy things like Blood-Replenishing potions from Mr. Burke when they sell them in shops like these? Doesn't he raise the price to make a profit?"

"He does," Krait said, "But on the other hand I sell the potions to him cheaper than I sell them to customers, because his order is certain, while I don't always know if potions I put in the shop will sell. Also, you'd be surprised how many people are too lazy to go shopping around themselves. Then there are those who don't trust the quality in self-run shops like mine, and would rather pay more to have a product they know will work."

Harry nodded, "I guess that makes sense. So he's buying Blood-Replenishers through you now?"

"Looks like it," Krait said, looking smug, "He gets a few others from me, but always said my Blood-Replenishers were off a bit. Guess he likes your variation better."

"About that," Harry said, "Sorry for changing things without telling you."

Krait shrugged, "Can't argue with what works. A few of your potions have been selling significantly better than the old ones did—not with my average customers, but with the folks who come in with a distinguishing eye. I figured you must be doing something different, so I had Horace take a look and see if he liked the new version any better than the old versions."

"Well, I'm glad your sales are up," Harry said, "But could you keep my identity as the brewer a secret?"

Krait fixed her with a frank look, "That shouldn't be a problem, seeing as I don't actually know your identity, Harry No-last-name."

Harry shifted uncomfortably, "Yeah, thanks for not being overly concerned about that, too."

Krait shrugged, "I'm used to strange types in these alleys, but I gotta ask this: are you in some kind of trouble? Running from someone, or something? I'm not gonna fire you, kid, but if I don't know, then I can't help you, and I might give something away to the wrong person."

Harry shook her head, "It's nothing like that, Mr. Krait. I'm not caught up in anything funny, and I'm not going to bring trouble to your shop. I just prefer to keep a low profile. So if anyone asks about the potions, could you just tell them you have a brewer who doesn't like to be associated with his work? Heck, you can take credit for the potions yourself if you like. That might even be easier. I don't care, as long as I get paid for them."

Krait grunted, "You're something else, kid. No pride in your work, that's for sure."

Harry privately disagreed. Pride was not about the world knowing what she could do. As long as she knew, there was pride and satisfaction in doing the work alone. After all, she took pride in the secret homework she did for Flint, didn't she? It was so much harder than the first-year work, and she did it all with competence, while no one but Flint knew. She also was proud of getting into—and staying at—Hogwarts, despite being ineligible due to her blood status. Just because she didn't tell anyone, didn't mean she wasn't proud of it.

Harry suddenly had a strange thought, and glanced up at Krait with a frown, "In all these weeks, you really never went and asked Mr. Tate about me, even though you know he recommended me? Weren't you curious?"

Krait stared down at her blankly, "If I want to know something, I ask the person I'm curious about. I don't waste my time rooting around behind people's backs. None of my business, anyway, I suspect."

"Thanks," Harry said, and picked up a couple of empty crates for the next day, "See you tomorrow, Mr. Krait."

"Sure, kid."

Harry left the shop and made her way slowly up Knockturn Alley. She had a couple more stops to make on Diagon before she could go back home, and she was debating dropping off the crates at the Leaky Cauldron first when she accidentally knocked into a passing pedestrian. She was about to apologize for not seeing them when she felt it—a slight release of pressure from the left inside pocket of her robes.

The pocket she kept her money pouch in.

Cursing, Harry fumbled with the crates in her hands and tried in vain to hold them steady in one hand while reaching out for the person she'd bumped into with the other. It was fruitless. The person was agile and twisted away from her with the ease of skill and experience in evasion. She caught a glimpse of wide blue eyes and a taunting grin below a dark brown cap before the person—no, boy—raced off on light feet, her money bag no doubt securely tucked away in his fist.

Harry set her jaw and moved as fast as she dared back along the alley. She paused for barely a moment to set the empty crates down none-too-gently in a shadowed nook before picking up the pace and racing in the direction she'd seen the boy take off in. The crates might be gone by the time she got back, but the money in that pouch was worth five times what the crates and all the bottles were. One of the stops she'd been planning on making in Diagon was an antique bookstore, where she'd reserved a copy of a manuscript on blending magic. The shopkeeper requested payment in gold, so she was carrying much more money than she would usually risk.

Most of her savings, including the money she would need for she and Archie's little project, was tucked away safe in her room, but Harry was not going to let the amount of gold in that pouch get away without a fight. It was the principle of the thing, after all.

She ran swiftly to where Knockturn met Kyprioth Court and skidded on the cobblestones around the corner. Kyprioth Court wasn't as crowded as Knockturn, and by craning her head a bit Harry caught sight of a slight figure in a dark brown cap jogging casually toward the far end of the alley. The boy, who she could now see was dressed in shorts and an oversized t-shirt, had slowed down considerably, apparently confident that his target wouldn't be fool enough to pursue him through the Lower Alleys.

Shows what he knows, Harry thought grimly. She would have been smirking as she closed in on the boy if she wasn't so out of breath. Seriously, she needed to work out more.

She was only a few feet behind the boy when by some terrible chance he glanced behind him. His eyes widened at the sight of her bearing down on him and he let out a startled yelp before taking off once more. The boy in the cap darted left, down an alley Harry had never taken, and swerved in and out of foot traffic to try and put some distance between them. Harry doggedly kept after the kid. He was fast—faster than she was, and he obviously knew the alleys better as well. He led her through twists and turns, over fences and under clothes lines, and Harry was thoroughly winded after just a few minutes of the brutally quick pace the boy set. Not to mention thoroughly lost.

She did have the advantage of being the follower, though. The boy had to look out for obstacles and waste precious seconds deciding on what paths to take, while she just had to mindlessly pursue him. Also, what Harry lacked in agility and speed she made up for in sheer determination.

Still, the kid was quick. He scampered and clambered over any and all obstacles in his way, jumping around barrels and litterbins with barely a pause in his stride. Harry could see him pulling further and further ahead of her, and knew that soon he would be out of her reach.

If only she could use magic over the summer holidays. Harry could feel her magic building inside of her, eager to come to her aid as her emotions surged forward, but she tamped down on the urge. She would get in trouble—though with Hogwarts or AIM she wasn't entirely sure—if anyone saw her, and in any event she had no idea what kind of a spell she could use. She didn't want to hurt the kid, as she might if she levitated something in his way or tried stunning him. She just wanted her money back.

Just as she was cursing her own shortsightedness at not having exercised her body while she was training up her mind all last year, Harry caught sight of a huge cart of cauldrons backing slowly into the alley ahead of them. It was too high to jump over and hung too close to the ground to try sliding beneath. Harry felt a rush of elation at the sight of it—here was her chance! The boy would have to stop.

Yet he didn't. Harry frowned. He wasn't even slowing down. Harry realized with an ugly dread that the boy didn't see the cart he was speeding toward. He was staring at the ground—no, at his shoe—trying to shake loose a piece of rope that had gotten tangled around one of his feet while he ran.

Harry called out a warning, but it only made the boy look back at her with confusion, and he was running so fast that even if he turned back around and realized the danger there would be no time for him to stop.

Her magic welled up inside of her again, and this time, Harry didn't push it back down. She reached out with a hand—no time for her wand—and released it toward the boy ahead, whose wide blue eyes widened further at the sight of her reaching for him so intently. Her magic caught up to him faster than she ever could have. Mere moments before he would have—should have—careened headlong into the cart of heavy cauldrons, he froze, suddenly suspended in mid-air as his momentum was arrested by raw magic. Harry ran the last few feet to where the boy was hanging, looking like some kind of strangely realistic statue hovering about a foot off the ground.

Harry grinned at the boy, whose face was now almost at her eye-level, and clamped a hand down gently but firmly on the boy's arm while at the same time asking her magic to let the boy go.

"Got you," she said breathlessly, "Good run, though."

The boy, who couldn't have been older than nine, scowled up at her after a few frustrated tugs got him no further away from her hold, "Lemme go."

"Sure thing," Harry said, "Just give me my money pouch back."

"I don't know what you're talking about," the boy said, wrinkling his nose up and averting his gaze.

"Then why were you running from me?" Harry asked, "Come on, just give it back and you can go."

The boy opened his mouth to reply but was cut off as a middle-aged wizard came jogging around the cauldron cart, a look of concern on his face.

"You two all right there?" he asked, glancing between Harry and the boy anxiously, "I thought for sure the lad was gonna hit my cart. Sorry about that, but I really didn't see anyone coming when I started backing into the street."

Harry smiled at him, "It's all right, neither of us got hit."

"Make him lemme go!" the boy piped up, looking pleadingly at the older man.

The cauldron merchant frowned and tugged at what little hair he had on his head unsurely, "Here now, what's this? Are you detaining this boy for something?"

Harry nodded, a bit apologetically, "Only for a moment. He was just about to return something of mine."

"He's a liar," the boy scowled, "I haven't got nothing of his."

The man looked a bit at a loss for what to do, "Well, ah, that is—are you sure he has something of yours? You couldn't be mistaken perhaps?"

He looked quite hopeful, but Harry shook her head slowly, "I don't think so. I'm missing a moneybag. It's dark red, and there are exactly seventeen galleons and four knuts inside. My initials are embroidered on the outside—HP. Here," Harry dug in her pocket with her free hand and pulled out a letter, "This is a notice from one of the shops in Diagon Alley. See? It has my name on it, Harry Potter, which matches the initials that are on the money bag if this boy has it."

The cart owner glanced over the piece of parchment, a pale, uneasy look on his face, "I see. Well, I suppose it's simple enough to resolve. Do you have such a moneybag, young one?"

The boy glared defiantly up at them, "So what if I did? Maybe I found it."

Harry pulled the boy around and used her other hand to dip into his shirt pockets. She pulled out the moneybag within, which was clearly red and inscribed just as she had said, and raised an eyebrow wryly, "Lucky we ran into each other then, so you can see it safely where it belongs."

She released the boy, and he quickly backed away from her. Unfortunately, the cauldron cart was still behind him, blocking his escape that direction, and he seemed hesitant to try and dart past her and the merchant to the other end of the alley.

The cauldron man turned a face filled with trepidation toward her, "Well, that's all settled then, don't you think, young sir? No need to involve the Aurors really, since everything worked out."

The boy blanched at the mention of the Aurors. Harry blinked, taken aback, "The Aurors? Why would I—oh." She nearly rolled her eyes. Sure, technically the boy had committed a crime, but who called the dark wizard catchers for a case of petty theft? Besides, her dad was an Auror, and bully if she was going to try explaining what she'd been doing in Knockturn Alley with that much money in the first place. "No, I don't care about that. I just wanted my bag back. Sorry to trouble you, sir," she told the cauldron merchant, "And next time steal from someone who looks too fat to run after you," she suggested sarcastically to the boy.

The kid, realizing he wasn't going to get into any real trouble, tipped his cap at her cheekily and scampered around her with a spry sort of grace, running off into the early evening without a glance back.

The cauldron merchant smiled with obvious relief at her, "That's a merciful thing you did, young man."

Harry blinked up at him, "You would have done the same, wouldn't you?"

The man looked taken aback, "I would have, yes, but you're not—"

He broke off and coughed in an embarrassed kind of a way. Harry wondered what he'd been going to say, but politely continued the conversation as if he hadn't aborted his sentence, "Well, it was nice to meet you. Good evening."

"Oh, good day," the man returned, lifting a hand in a vague kind of wave, then glancing down at his hand as if wondering why he'd done such a thing.

"Thanks," Harry waved back bemusedly as she walked away, then paused and turned around, "Um, do you by chance know how to get back to Knockturn Alley? Or at least to Kyprioth Court?"

The man smiled indulgently, "Yes, of course."

He gave her directions, which were so complicated that Harry had him repeat them twice to make sure she would remember them all. Apparently she'd run further into the Lower Alleys than she'd thought.

She thanked him once again and set off back toward Kyprioth Court. She was already going to be home much later than she'd anticipated, but maybe if she hurried she would make it back for dinner. Not that her parents checked up on her or anything. While she usually attended meals, if she missed one they'd probably assume she was working on a potion that couldn't be interrupted.

Harry was just a couple of streets from Kyprioth Court when she passed a window with a bright red sign that caught her attention. She slowed, hardly daring to believe her luck.

FOR RENT

One Bedroom Apartment

9 Galleons / Week

Utilities and Floo Connection Included

Inquire at Number 5

She grinned. It was perfect. In the wizarding sector, so no worries about being asked for muggle identification, cheap, not too big or too flashy. The street it was on was called Dogwood Lane. It was narrow, but well-kept, with small flower boxes on every windowsill and sturdy shutters in the colour of the corresponding door. The apartment that was for rent looked to be on the second storey, and there were pale pink curtains hanging in the window behind the for rent sign. The number next to the window was 8, and the apartment below it on the ground floor was number 7. Number 5 was on the first floor across the street, so Harry crossed and knocked gently on the door that went to apartments 5 and 6 and waited.

The curtains in the window closest to the door fluttered and parted, revealing the face of a thin woman with soft brown hair. The woman waved at her before leaving the window. A few moments later the yellow door opened and the woman from the window smiled down at her.

"Hello, dear, what can I do for you? Or were you knocking for number 6?" the woman asked kindly.

"Actually, I was hoping to inquire about the apartment across the street," Harry said, "Number 8. Is it still for rent?"

"It is," the woman said, surprised, "Come in, child."

Harry stepped through the yellow door into an entryway that had a staircase going up and a door on the right hand side. The woman led her through the door and invited her to sit while she fetched the apartment owner.

"I'm Mrs. Botting, by the way," she said over her shoulder.

Harry waited for a few minutes and then a white-haired old lady came slowly tottering into the room, leaning heavily on a wooden cane. Harry jumped up and helped her sit.

"Thank you very much young man," the woman said, her voice squeaking with age, "Now, I hear from the dear Mrs. Botting that you've come to ask about Number 8, is that right?"

"Yes, ma'am," Harry said, "Are you still looking to rent it out?"

"Oh, yes," the old woman sighed, "I just couldn't bear to let the old place go completely, you see. So many memories. But I had a nasty fall last month, and if Mr. Botting hadn't stopped by to check on me that afternoon…well, I'm just too old to be living alone anymore I guess."

"Are you all right now?" Harry asked.

"Fine, just fine," she said, "Maywell saw to that."

Not knowing what she was talking about, Harry just nodded in what she hoped was an understanding way.

"The Bottings are being so kind to me," the old woman said, "Just so kind. Letting me stay here, they are, though they've no extra room to speak of as it is. Are your parents looking for an apartment to rent? It will be so lovely to have a way to repay the Bottings for their kindness. I've no mind to be a burden to anyone, and every little bit helps around here."

Harry nodded, "Yes, ma'am. It's not my parents though. I was actually looking to rent an apartment myself, if that's all right with you."

"Oh, well," the woman frowned, "Are you living alone? Dangerous business, I should know. Can't you find a place at a shelter? The Rogue would take you in, you know, no matter who your parents were."

"I'll be all right, ma'am," Harry said, "Can I rent the apartment right away?"

"Yes, yes," the woman said, "If you're sure about it you can move in as soon as you like."

"Thank you," Harry said, "I promise I won't be a troublesome neighbour. You'll probably never even see me, since I plan on using the Floo connection to get in and out when I can."

"I'm sure you'll be a lovely neighbour," the elder said, nodding her head judiciously as she did so, "Now then, as you probably read I'm hoping for 9 Galleons a week, but you can pay by the month or bi-weekly or whatever works for your situation."

Harry smiled, "If it's all the same, I'd rather pay the first year up front in cash, so that I don't have to worry about getting the payments on time."

The old lady's brows rose, but she didn't ask how Harry was going to get the money. Harry had the impression she was used to seeing self-reliant young people around the alleys, if the way she barely protested at a kid renting an apartment on their own was any indication.

"That's fine as well, of course," she said after a moment.

"Great," Harry smiled, "I'll bring payment the day after tomorrow, if I can. Also, could I ask a neighbourly favour of you?"

The old woman blinked her wrinkled eyelids, but nodded slowly, "Yes, what is it?"

"I had originally budgeted more than 9 Galleons a week for an apartment," Harry said, "So I was wondering if I paid 11 Galleons a week, could you possibly keep my personal habits to yourself, should anyone ask?"

"Personal habits?" the woman repeated, nonplussed.

"Yes, you know, comings and goings, anything peculiar you might hear—or not hear—from the house, things like that," Harry explained innocently, "You can tell them Harry Potter rented the apartment if someone like from the Ministry or anything should ever ask of course, but I'd appreciate it if you kept any other kind of information to yourself."

The woman raised both her brows sceptically, "For 11 Galleons a week I'll tell the Ministry whatever you want—not that the likes of them ever come down here. You're a right strange little thing, aren't you?"

"So I've heard," Harry said, "Thank you so much, ma'am."

"Not at all, young Mr. Potter," the woman said, "And please, just call me Mrs. Whitlock."

Harry smiled easily, "As you like, Mrs. Whitlock. It was lovely to meet you."

She stood to leave, but Mrs. Botting came in at that moment with a tea tray and set it down on the coffee table, smiling expectantly at her

"Won't you stay for dinner, my dear?" she asked, handing Harry, who had sat back down out of politeness, a cup of sweet smelling tea.

"Oh, I don't know," Harry said hesitantly, "I should probably go home and get something to eat there."

"Nonsense," Mrs. Whitlock pursed her lips dismissively, "What's the use going home to have dinner alone when you can stay right here and get to know your new neighbours?"

Harry blinked, not sure what to say to that. It wasn't as if she could tell the women that her mother and father had a dinner of their own for her, because that would take credence from the idea that she was renting an apartment to live in on her own, despite only being almost-twelve. She prevaricated for a second, but couldn't think of a good excuse not to stay, and they had been very kind to invite her to their table in the first place. Her parents would probably assume she was working, so as long as she was home before dark she would probably be fine.

Harry accepted their invitation, and twenty minutes later was sitting around a small but abundantly laid table in the Bottings' kitchen. She met Mr. Botting as well as the two children of the house, Jim and Clara Botting, who were seven and five respectively. The meal was pleasant, and the Bottings were all very welcoming to her as a prospective new neighbour, though Harry warned them several times that they likely wouldn't see very much of her.

When she finally left the Botting residence at Number 5 on Dogwood Lane, it was a good thirty minutes past dusk. Harry sighed. There was no way she was making it home before dinner. She also suddenly remembered that she'd left Krait's crates just sitting in a nook off of Knockturn Alley when she started off on this prolonged detour of hers, and thought that it would be a miracle if they were still there. Great.

Harry walked quickly through the darkened alleys. This was not the shadowy dark caused by the buildings' overhangs, but rather the complete darkness of a summer night that was broken only by the rare shaft of moonlight. Luckily, the signposts on every street corner were charmed to be lit up, so she found her way with little trouble.

Approaching Kyprioth Court, Harry felt the first prickling of unease. She had never been in the Lower Alleys so late before, so at first nothing had felt strange or off about the deserted nature of the streets she walked. When she noticed that the street up ahead was lit by something other than moonlight, however, something red and flickering, she started to think perhaps there was something ominous about how empty and silent the alleys were.

Except that they weren't silent. There were faint sounds on the wind, coming from up ahead of her. Part of her was thinking she should turn back, avoid the eerie red glow coming from ahead, but the other part reminded her that she didn't know any other way to Knockturn Alley than through Kyprioth Court. So she continued forward, though at a slower and more cautious pace.

As she grew closer, sounds became clearer. There was shouting, and beneath the shouting small explosions, like rock imploding and gravel spraying. The orange-red glow flickered against her eyes, but offsetting that were sharp, erratic flashes of multicoloured lights that refracted and cast quick-moving shadows across the alley wall. These flashes were easily recognizable to anyone who had ever seen serious magic used—they were the heralds of magical duels—several, judging by the frequency and variety of the flashes alone. The persistent red glow, though, was something Harry had never seen before. And yet, once Harry reached the mouth of the alley and caught sight of its source, the dark truth hit her with the gut wrenching force of something a deep, unacknowledged part of her had known instinctively all along. Like how an infant knew his mother's face or a dog knew the fear of thunder.

Fire. Something was on fire. No, she sagged against the rough alley wall with the realization, the Dancing Dragon was on fire. She opened her mouth to call for help, but snapped it shut again as the full extent of the scene before her impacted like a sledgehammer against her brain.

Kyprioth Court was littered with rubble, and between the rubble—bodies. Some standing, some fallen, most male, all covered in a gritty layer of dust and debris. Harry had seen fights before—schoolyard skirmishes and the occasional tavern brawl that she had sworn to Sirius not to tell her mother about—but this was nothing like that. It looked like what she might have imagined a muggle gang fight to be like, had she given enough credence to the propaganda spread by the SOW Party about the violent nature of muggles to try imagining one. There seemed to be two distinct factions warring against one another, but the dueling was so fluid and indistinct that she couldn't be sure. It didn't look like a free-for-all, though. There were definitely groups of people fighting together, so there had to be some kind of organization and reason to the mad scene. Harry just didn't know what it was.

The fighting was centred in the half-circle of street before the Dancing Dragon. After squinting against the blaze, Harry was able to discern that it was the upper floor that was burning. The entire right side of the second story was up in flames, but in addition to the continuous fighting going on in the street outside of the inn, there were several witches and wizards with water much stronger than what a mere Aguamenti would produce gushing out of their wands. The fire didn't seem to be spreading, but the effect of the impromptu fire fighters was the production of great gusts of steam as the water met the burning building. It drifted down the court, hot and heavy, casting a hazy film over everything it touched.

The fight itself could only be described as barely restrained chaos. Fighters on both sides were dodging and weaving around one another in what might have been a beautifully choreographed dance, had there not been so many things going clearly wrong. Instead of the eye-catching spectacle of flashy moves and successive near-misses one might find in a staged fight, the exchanges between fighters were as fast as they were brutal. Light and sound battered the night. The twinkle of reflective steel and the sudden spurt of blood unaccompanied by a corresponding flash of magic told her that at least some of the participants were free dueling. Once she was aware of it, the occasional clashing of mixed weaponry could be picked out above the shouting and the dull thudding of missed spells against the surrounding buildings.

Her mind was cataloguing all of this rapidly, but her consciousness was frozen with abject horror. She hadn't been prepared when she'd first heard the sounds of trouble, however uneasy she had instinctively felt, for who could ever be prepared for such a thing? Not twenty feet away from her people were fighting—and dying, she thought numbly, if the amount of blood now running into the gutters on the sides of the alley was any indication. She didn't know what she'd stumbled into, and as her presence of mind recovered from the original shock and reasserted itself she realized she didn't want to know. She stumbled back from the mouth of the side alley she'd been watching from with the intent of finding another way home. Any other way.

But her sudden movement must have been somehow noticeable against the still and silent backdrop that was the area immediately outside of the conflict zone, for no sooner had she staggered a few steps back from the grizzly scene than one of the fighters broke away from the battle and headed straight for her alley.

She would never know what the man in the blue vest had wanted with her. Did he think she was an enemy fighter, sneaking up on his flank? Did he realize that a third, oblivious party had inadvertently stumbled upon the field, and come over to warn her off? Had he even seen her in the first place? Or had he been trying to do something else, like send a message or run away from the battle completely? She would never know, for he had barely reached the mouth of the alley she was in, the same alley she had so recklessly followed a young pickpocket down just hours before, when he was struck in the back with what she later learned was a large throwing knife. At the time all Harry knew was that one moment the man was running toward her and the next he was falling forward, and there was something protruding from beneath his shoulder blade, and his body was landing awkwardly in a shallow puddle of alley muck. The fall dislodged the knife in the man's back and his pretty blue vest was stained so red with what seemed to Harry to be impossible amounts of blood, impossibly fast.

He died, there in the alley, before her eyes. Far enough that the pool of seeping fluid couldn't quite reach her shoes, but close enough that the look of surprised denial on his face would haunt her dreams for countless nights to come.

She shook her head back and forth slowly, too caught up in the horror she was witnessing to even scream. All she could think was, why was he so surprised? Didn't he know what was happening? Shouldn't he have expected—or at least suspected—that such a thing might happen on a night like this? In a fight like this?

Maybe death was always a surprise, Harry thought, but she didn't want to know that about the world either.

It was time to leave, Harry knew. Time to run and possibly to hide and definitely not the time to stand there gaping at something she couldn't change. And she couldn't change it. She could heal bruises, cuts and scrapes, sure, broken bones even, but stab wounds? Ones that, from the way the man in the blue vest had gurgled and choked before stilling, had pierced a lung? No, she couldn't fix that, and she had to stop thinking about it or the stinging in her nose and eyes would signify something more than the effect of breathing and squinting in smoky air. It would mean tears. Breakdown. Collapse.

No, no. Harry took a deep breath, ignoring the smell of burning wood that assaulted her senses as she did so, and swallowed hard. She would get away. She would get home. And then she would let the brittle façade crack.

Harry took another deep, calming breath—and promptly vomited against the alley wall. That time she had smelled more than smoky wood. That breath was an attack of sweet copper perfume and her stomach rebelled vehemently. All of Mrs. Botting's wonderful cooking came spilling onto the ground, wasted and smelling a lot worse than it had when she last experienced it. Harry gagged for a moment, but managed to haul herself away from both noxious odours by struggling backwards, further away from the fight, the dead man in the blue vest, and the blatant evidence of a weak stomach.

She didn't back away fast enough. She wasn't far enough when the second man came into the alley. He moved quickly to the fallen man and stooped down over him. His objective became clear when, with a slight grunt of effort, he pulled the knife the rest of the way free from the man's back and stood once more. He went to reach for his shirt—to clean the blade, she realized with a sick jolt, to clean his blade—but noticed her standing not-far-enough away and darted forward faster than she could convince her shell-shocked limbs to evade him.

There was an instant of confused movement as he grabbed her, and then she was freezing with fear at the touch of a wet blade against her neck. It was accompanied by the tip of a wand pressed to her lower ribs, and Harry could only think that she had never known terror until that moment. It was an ugly, consuming thing, which drove all thoughts from her head except those that might somehow help her to survive. Don't move. Don't cry out. Wait for the opportunity to run. Wait. Wait. Her magic swelled up inside of her and she felt it searching for an outlet, but she had no will to direct it with. Her mind was blank. No intention meant no form for her magic, so she just stood there, frozen in the arms of danger, waiting for something to shake her free.

The man chuckled low in her ear, "Nice try, little rat, but no one escapes tonight. Thought you could run, did you? Scared once you saw the true might of the rightful King, were you? Too bad, little rat, and too late."

"Please, I'm not—" Harry whimpered at her own inadequacy. Not what? A rat? She didn't even know what was going on, "I'm not whatever you think I am. I don't know what's going on, or who you are, or anything about a rightful King. I just want to get home."

The man spat carelessly on the ground beside them and scoffed, "Don't matter. If you aren't with Claw, you're against him."

His grip on the knife changed ever so slightly and Harry felt the air grow thin. This was it. She was going to die in a dirty alley, not even worth a Killing Curse. She tensed automatically though she knew the muscles in her neck would be as butter before the knife. She felt the edge of the blade begin to dig in, and then there was a blinding flash of light and the pressure was gone. She fell to her knees as whatever had been supporting her was suddenly removed. Was that the end? Just a flash of light and then everything falls away?

No, that wasn't right. Harry blinked rapidly to regain her stolen vision. The spots caused by the flash cleared and she could see the alley once again, from the mucky ground she was sitting on to the prone form of her attacker. Her eyes widened at the sight. He was collapsed at the base of one side of the alley, bent double in a way that suggested he'd impacted heavily with the wall before falling to the dirt. Standing over him, face grim and eyes aglow in the dim red light, was Leo.

Harry shook her head to jump-start her brain once more. Leo was in the alley, just standing there in his usual sleeveless black shirt and slim-fitting trousers, as if anything about this night was usual. Leo had saved her from that man with the knife, the man who had killed Mr. Bluevest. Leo had shot the spell that made the world turn white for an instant, and Leo had blasted the man with the knife away from her while he was distracted. What was Leo doing there?

She didn't realize she'd voiced the question aloud until he answered.

"Me? Harry, what are you doing here?" Leo snapped, bending over to grasp her arm and haul her to her feet briskly, "Do you have any idea how dangerous it is to be wandering around tonight? Sweet Mother, I thought he'd got you the way you collapsed like that. What were you thinking?"

Harry swallowed painfully—her throat was bleeding from a long but thankfully shallow cut where the knife had almost…she shook her head, "I was just trying to get home."

"Trying to—now?" Leo wrapped both arms around her fiercely, his wand clenched in one hand and a long knife in the other. He transferred sweat and blood from his hands and arms to her robes, but Harry didn't care, "Don't ever scare me like that again, Harry. Not ever."

He released her, and Harry nodded obediently, too shook up to really think or react the way she normally would to things.

"You've got to get out of here," Leo said quickly, "The fight isn't through, and there's the Dragon to deal with as well. I can't go with you, but you need to get somewhere safe. Go to—" he cursed softly, "No, that's no good, not at this time of night. Okay, Harry, listen carefully. Are you listening?"

Harry gazed up into Leo's face and nodded, though she still felt dazed and lost.

"Good. You're going to go to the end of this alley, away from the fighting. You're going to turn right. Then you run straight down that street until you get to the fountain with the statue of Arthur Pendragon standing in it, got that?"

Harry nodded again, "King Arthur statue. Run."

"Yes," Leo said, "At the statue, turn left and on the right hand side of the street you'll see a big lit up sign for Maywell Clinic. It's always open, so just go inside and tell the lady at the front desk you're there to see Mrs. Hurst."

"Your mother," Harry said, blinking slowly.

"Yes, you'll be safe there. Run there as fast as you can and don't leave until I come and get you," Leo said.

"Safe?" repeated Harry.

"Yes, Harry, safe," Leo said, "I have to go now. Run fast."

Before Harry could say, 'what about you?' Leo was gone again, moving like a shadow back toward Kyprioth Court. She steeled herself against the new emotion battling for dominance in her confused psyche: worry for Leo. Harry turned determinedly away from the flickering lights coming from the fight in the court and began moving. It was slow at first as her muscles seemed to be frozen and her joints clumsy, but soon she was jogging, running, sprinting away, right then straight then left at the fountain. She didn't slow at the sight of the brightly lit sign for Maywell Clinic, and instead burst straight through the front doors and staggered to a halt in the well-lit lobby. The woman at the desk half-stood at her entrance, eyes scanning over her sharply and zeroing in on the blood soaking her robe collar from where it ran down her throat.

"I need to see Mrs. Hurst," Harry said quickly, her voice raspy from the exertion, and possibly from the pain around her throat as well.

"Oh, child, what's happened to you?" the lady fussed as she rounded the front desk and started toward her, "Come, sit down and let's stop up that bleeding."

"Please," Harry said tiredly, "I just need to see Mrs. Hurst."

The woman shook her head disapprovingly, "You need to see a Healer, young man, before you pass out from blood loss."

"Isn't Mrs. Hurst a Healer?" Harry asked, "Please, ma'am, couldn't you just take me to her?"

"Well, it isn't really procedure to just…" The desk woman trailed off, taking in the sight of Harry's muck-ridden clothes, bloody neck, and desperate expression, "Oh, very well then. Come with me, lad."

Harry followed her behind the counter to a long hallway dotted with numerous doors. The woman knocked on one perfunctorily and ushered Harry inside.

"Healer Hurst will be with you in a moment."

Harry sank down gratefully onto the padded wooden chair in the small patient room and closed her eyes. She had done it. She was safe. Harry felt very lightheaded now that she was sitting down, so she bent over to put her head between her legs, trying to stave off the vertigo. She heard the door open a few minutes later, but didn't look up until a woman's voice said, "Oh, dear, what has my Lionel sent me this time?"

Harry raised her head and the woman's eyes widened. She whisked out her wand and Harry couldn't help but flinch when it pointed at her. The woman, who had to be Mrs. Hurst, stepped toward her, though her eyes were soft, "No, child, I'll not be hurting you. I'm going to help."

Harry nodded, feeling foolish. She knew that, it was just an automatic reaction she had apparently picked up within the last hour. Harry kept very still as Mrs. Hurst went to work, though she tensed a few times when the kindly woman's wand gave an unexpected flick or twist. After a while, Harry was able to relax a bit, and her anxiety over the wand pointed at her was greatly lessened by the fact that her neck was healed and the blood siphoned away almost immediately. The woman healed several scrapes Harry hadn't known she'd picked up, either stumbling around in the alley or chasing the pickpocket earlier in the day. The woman also repaired her robes in the places they had ripped and cast a strong cleaning charm over the rest of her. When she was finished, Mrs. Hurst stepped back and met Harry's blank look with a very fixed one.

"Now, I don't pretend to believe my son when he tells me he never gets up to anything dangerous," she said, "And so I don't usually ask questions when Leo sends some poor soul along to be patched up in my clinic, but when I see a lass your age in here with a sloppy knife wound and hands too soft to belong to any Rogue rat I just can't keep my peace. What in the Great Mother's name are you doing here, child?"

Harry just stared at her, "You…you know I'm a girl?"

The woman looked taken aback, "Well of course I do. I'm a Healer, child. I also know you're not yet twelve years old, you've broken your wrist within the last year, and I've a strong suspicion you're a vegetarian, in which case I'd advise you to eat more protein because it's going to stunt your growth otherwise."

Harry's jaw dropped open a little bit. This woman was good. "I see," Harry managed eventually, "Well, you're the first one to recognize me as female on sight in a long while, ma'am, even as a Healer."

Mrs. Hurst smiled, "Perhaps you simply don't have very observant acquaintances."

Harry smiled wanly back, "Perhaps you're right. Either way, thank you for Healing me, ma'am, and to answer your earlier question…I'm not really sure what I'm doing here. This whole day has been so…fast. I just want to go home."

Mrs. Hurst gazed down at her sympathetically, "Well, you're as Healed in body as a body can be. You're free to go home whenever you like."

Harry shook her head, "Leo told me to stay here until he came and got me. He said I'd be safe here."

"Safe from what, child?" Mrs. Hurst took out her wand again and Harry barely flinched at all. She conjured a second chair and sat down across from Harry with a concerned expression, "Perhaps you'd better tell me everything. Start at the beginning."

So Harry did. She told Mrs. Hurst about her job working for Krait at the Serpent's Storeroom, and about being picked while she was walking back toward the Leaky Cauldron. She then had to explain quickly why she'd been so foolish as to carry that much gold around Knockturn. Mrs. Hurst smiled in veiled disbelief when Harry told her about chasing, and eventually catching, the young pickpocket because of the opportune timing of a cauldron cart. Harry told her about stopping to look at an apartment, though she glossed over the reasons she was interested in it, and related how she'd been asked to stay for dinner by the neighbours. When Harry got to the part about coming across the fight on Kyprioth Court, she paused, overcome by the hugeness of it all.

"The Dancing Dragon…it was on fire," Harry said, frowning. Mrs. Hurst drew a sharp breath and clenched her wand without seeming to notice. "I think they had it contained, but it was so awful. The fire was making everything smoky and red, and there were people fighting everywhere in the court. I didn't know what was happening, and I was scared. I was going to leave, to run somewhere else, but then a man came and died right in front of me." Harry looked up at Mrs. Hurst imploringly, "I didn't mean to let him die, I swear. I just couldn't…all I know is cuts and bruises. I can't heal deep muscle tissue fast enough to be of use in an emergency yet, and I don't know how to fix a lung once it's punctured. Please, ma'am, you have to believe me, I couldn't—I didn't—"

"Hush, child," Mrs. Hurst leaned forward and scooped Harry's whole body up into her arms. Harry clung to the older woman's Healer robes and started to cry. The tears leaked out everywhere, no matter how she tried to stem them, and Harry started mumbling apologies between her sobs. "No, child, don't fret about it. You just let it out, now, that's it," Mrs. Hurst stroked Harry's hair softly and Harry cried harder, thinking that her own mum would be doing this if Harry hadn't been keeping so many secrets from her, "It's not your fault, child, so don't you take that darkness into your soul. His life was in the gods' hands, not yours. Not yours."

Harry sniffed loudly and slowed down her breathing to try and control the spasming of her diaphragm. She leaned back from Mrs. Hurst's hold and wiped her eyes on her newly cleaned robe sleeve. "Thank you," she said, sniffing one last time, "I didn't mean to fall apart on you like that."

"It seems to me you're over-due," Mrs. Hurst said kindly, "Are you all right, now? I can make you a cup of tea, if you like."

"No, thank you," Harry said, "I'd rather just tell you the rest of it, so you know."

She related the rest of the tale as quickly and accurately as she could. She hoped Leo wouldn't mind her spilling her guts to his mother about what had went on that night, but she figured he wouldn't have sent her to his mother's clinic if he didn't expect Mrs. Hurst to find out about the fight.

The fight she still wasn't sure how Leo had gotten mixed up in, now that she thought about it. Really, what were the odds that Leo had been in the exact right place to save her when she hadn't seen him all day?

Mrs. Hurst just sighed when she was done telling her story, "What a mess you've gotten yourself into, child."

"Do you know what the fight was about?" Harry asked curiously.

"Anyone who keeps up with the Court business could hazard a guess," Mrs. Hurst said, "Fights like this don't happen much—they aren't supposed to, as long as everyone follows the code and settles disputes directly in single combat. If the fight was as bad as you say, with the fire in the Dragon on top of it…well, there's only one person I know of in the Court who would dare such a thing right now."

"Claw," Harry breathed, suddenly recalling the words that man had spoken to her, "The man with the knife, he mentioned Claw's name."

"That would be a good assumption," Mrs. Hurst said distastefully, "That man will never be worthy of my son's crown. A bad thief and a worse coward. Stupid, too. I wouldn't be surprised if he'd let his plans slip into some of Leo's ears. That would certainly explain what my son has been so busy doing all day. No doubt preparing for it."

"Is that what the fight was over?" Harry asked, fearing for her friend's safety, "The position of the Rogue?"

"Nothing else is worth attacking the Dancing Dragon itself," Mrs. Hurst said darkly, "Though it's a fool's errand. Even if Claw somehow bested my boy, no thief would answer to him after he broke the code like that."

"Why would he even try, then?" Harry asked, frowning.

"He doesn't understand the Court of the Rogue," Mrs. Hurst said, "Claw's an outsider, come into the Rogue less than a year ago, and from the very start he was dripping poison in folks' ears, turning them over slowly but surely to his own circle. We all thought he was building a base of support for when he challenged Leo to a duel for the crown. It looks now like he was just building an army of thugs to take the Court like a barbarian tyrant would."

Harry bit her lip, thinking things over, "Is that why he sent that false recipe to Mr. Krait? To try and get rid of one of Leo's supporters before he attacked?"

"Too right, young lass," Mrs. Hurst said, brows raised, "That's a sharp mind you've got there. Eddy wasn't the only one to get targeted though. Aled's house was broken into last week and everything ransacked. He only wasn't home because he'd stayed over at the Dragon to help old Solom out that night. Some thugs got to Marek not two nights ago, pulled him into an alley and beat him something fierce. I patched him up myself, but he was to be on bed rest for the rest of the week. I imagine he'll be upset to have missed the fighting, the big idiot."

Harry considered this silently, "Is Rispah all right, at least?"

"Fine," Mrs. Hurst said, sounding a bit miffed, "Claw doesn't waste his time with women. Yet another reason I hope my Leo trounces him tonight."

"Aren't you worried about Leo?" Harry asked, trying not to sound critical, "He's not even of age yet, and there were so many people fighting…"

Mrs. Hurst patted Harry's hand gently, "My son has been giving me grey hair since he learned to run before I knew he could walk. Always the trickster, never where he should have been, Leo drove my husband and I to distraction trying to keep up with him, and that was before he ever started leaving the house. I learned long ago to just support him where I can and pray for him where I can't. Leo is a rare soul. He goes after what he wants and he's rather good at getting it. He's also quite talented. No man like Claw is going to win out against Lionel Hurst."

Harry marveled at the woman's complete faith in her son. She didn't think she'd ever had that much faith in any one person. People were just so…fallible. Perhaps one had to be a mother to completely understand it.

Mrs. Hurst finally got around to making tea, and the two of them sat and talked about various things to pass the time. Harry's schooling came up at some point and she automatically fed Mrs. Hurst the line about her attending AIM and wanting to be a Healer. Mrs. Hurst just looked at her with frank disbelief.

"What?" Harry asked defensively.

"You're a pretty good liar," Mrs. Hurst said calmly, sipping at her tea, "Calm-faced and unhesitant. Either that or you've told that story of yours so many times that it's become routine. Still, that's all it is. A story."

Harry took a careful breath, not daring to look up from her teacup, "You think so? I suppose any stranger's life might sound like a story if you don't know them very well."

Mrs. Hurst laughed, "Oh, child, stop your pretending. I'm not asking for the truth, mind, but lies irritate my magic. I can always tell—and good thing, too, with that son of mine. The boy lies when the truth would sound better, sometimes just to see if I'm listening, I think. But apart from that, a few things don't match up very well. If you'd lived in America for nine months, your accent should have gotten a bit weak, but you talk like someone who's never left the country. Also, you claim to want to be a Healer, but you've been talking here with me for a good forty minutes and not once have you asked me a single question about Healing."

Harry blinked, then winced internally. By Merlin, the woman was right. Now that she thought about it, Archie did talk a bit differently ever since he came back from school. His accent wasn't that noticeably different, but he used American slang every now and then, and enunciated better, probably because he was used to compensating for Americans who didn't have an ear for the British accent. Also, Archie would have jumped at the opportunity to question an actual Healer about his or her profession. He always, always took the time to ask questions when they visited Sirius at the hospital.

Harry wasn't sure what to say, "I'm sorry," she tried, "Honestly, you're right. I am lying, but I'm not trying to trick you or anything. I lie to everyone, and I know that sounds horrible, but I just…it's important to me, and…I'm not explaining this very well. I can't tell you the truth about me, though I really am Harry Potter."

"Harry Potter?" Mrs. Hurst gave a little start of surprise and her eyes widened slightly.

"Oh, did I not introduce myself?" Harry smiled sheepishly, "How rude of me, yes, I'm Harry, ma'am—well, Harriett, but nobody calls me that."

"Goodness, that certainly explains a lot," Mrs. Hurst murmured distractedly, "I know who you are—perhaps more than you'd even guess. If you're Harry, my son has been talking about you almost non-stop for weeks. Every day it's 'I'm going to meet Harry' or 'Sorry I'm late, mum, Harry and I went for ice cream.' I admit I'd thought you were a boy the way he talked about you, but now…" Mrs. Hurst looked over Harry with a new gleam in her eyes. Harry felt inexplicably nervous. "Well, this certainly changes things."

"Does it?" Harry asked nervously, "Really, my being a girl doesn't matter that much."

"Whatever you say, dear," Mrs. Hurst smiled knowingly, "Now then, what was I saying? Oh yes, did Leo tell you about what I do for a living?"

"He said you work here, at this clinic," Harry said, nonplussed.

"Indeed I do," Mrs. Hurst said, "In fact, I own this clinic. I founded it a year after Leo was born. Malcolm had just gotten his Mastery, and the Guild pays a very generous stipend to its researchers. Also, the Hursts left Malcolm with more money than either of us knew what to do with, so I decided to open a clinic here in the Lower Alleys, exactly where the little apartment I grew up in used to stand before a Ministry raid on the building caused it to become structurally unsound and it collapsed. This clinic is officially a charity outpost of St. Mungo's, though the Hospital actually only pays sixty percent of the clinic's expenses. The Rogue funds thirty percent of the expenses, and my husband and I take care of the last ten."

"How did you get St. Mungo's to agree to open a clinic in the Lower Alleys?" Harry asked curiously, "Even if they only pay sixty percent, that's still a pretty big venture to take on all of a sudden."

"Before I opened this clinic, I worked for St. Mungo's. I used to run the children's ward, as a matter of fact, and I still volunteer there twice a week. Interesting people, the volunteers in that ward. One in particular always gives me a laugh—a Mr. Sirius Black, perhaps you know him?" Mrs. Hurst laughed at the look of utter panic on Harry's face, "Oh, yes, your 'uncle' talks about you a lot, young lady."

"Is that so?" Harry asked weakly.

"Yes, indeed," Mrs. Hurst said, "Enough that it's apparent to me that you do 'lie to everyone,' as your uncle, too, seems to think you've been off at AIM for the last year. No, don't fret, I'm not going to say anything to him. I won't even tell him I've seen you, since I very much doubt your family knows where you are right now. I imagine your life is very complicated, though, isn't it? Just know what if you ever need to confide in someone, I've an open ear and a closed mouth."

Harry nodded silently, though of course she would never take the kind woman up on her offer. It was too much of a risk, no matter how trustworthy Leo's mother seemed.

"Anyway, we were talking about how I got the clinic opened. It helped that I was influential among the staff, and of course it didn't hurt that I was married to one of their highest grossing researchers in experimental potions," Mrs. Hurst said fondly, "That's how we met, you know. He would provide new, better potions for the children in the ward and I would shout at him for using innocent children as test subjects, and then we decided to move in together."

Harry felt her mouth hitch into a slight grin at Mrs. Hurst's description of her relationship with Master Hurst, but didn't interrupt.

"The Hospital held both of us in such high esteem that when I proposed the idea they didn't immediately reject it," she went on, "I argued that a free clinic in the Lower Alleys was a good move logistically, because most folk from the Lower Alleys don't have easy access to a floo, and by the time they can get to St. Mungo's their injury is likely worsened considerably. Also, most of us in the Lower Alley don't hold much stock in the Ministry, and that can include the sort of identification requirements St. Mungo's has for all of its patients. I said they would be treating even more people more effectively with a clinic like this, and of course they told me I was a naïve fool who wanted to waste hospital resources on the undeserving."

Harry gasped, "They really said that? Of all the snobbish things to—" she broke off, too upset to even finish her sentence, but added bitterly, "Soon they'll only be serving purebloods, or only people who have passed their NEWTs."

Mrs. Hurst chuckled without much humour, "Yes, well it's lucky I had my Malcolm with me, because he speaks bigoted arsehole rather well, having been sired by one. He told the board that opening a clinic was a good political move, since it would make them seem sympathetic to the 'plight of the unfortunate', and also that it made sense economically, because a new clinic meant plenty of excuses to hold elaborate fundraisers. They agreed almost immediately after that. Still, the point is that we got the clinic in the end."

Harry nodded seriously, "Sometimes the end justifies the means. Sometimes you have to play by their rules for a while, or at least pretend to, even though some might say you're being hypocritical or a coward by giving in to the system instead of trying to change everything right away. Sometimes the only way to get what you want, to help other people by getting someplace that can really make a difference, is to keep your head down and your mouth shut about things you don't agree with, just for a little while. Just until you have the power to really change things instead of just complain about them. Right?"

Mrs. Hurst fixed hazel eyes on Harry's earnest face, "I think, sometimes, you're right, Harry. In circumstances where going along with the crowd in order to accomplish a long-term goal that will undermine it doesn't hurt anyone, it's not a bad strategy, and in some cases it might be the only way."

"Yeah," Harry said softly, "The only way."

Not ten minutes later, the door to the patient room was flung open by the woman from the front desk.

"Healer Hurst, come quickly," the woman said urgently, "There are at least a dozen young people in the waiting room, bleeding and shouting and carrying on. Your son is out there, too," Harry breathed a silent sigh of relief for Leo's sake, "No doubt somehow responsible for whatever the blazes is going on in these alleys tonight."

The desk lady left once more, still muttering agitatedly, and Mrs. Hurst stood and set aside her teacup. "We'd better go see who needs patching up, don't you think?" she said to Harry.

"Um, Mrs. Hurst," she said cautiously, "Those things I told you—"

"Healer-patient confidentiality," Mrs. Hurst said, winking.

Harry smiled back gratefully and followed her out the door.

The waiting room was in chaos. Men and women with varying degrees of health stood, sat, or leaned on one another. They were all dirty and all smiling broadly. Leo stood in the midst of them all, a grin of equal brilliance on his own dirt-smeared face. He was shouting over everyone, directing them to one side of the room or the other. Harry got the feeling he was trying to get those with the worst injuries in one area so they could be treated faster, but everyone was too excited to pay attention, and instead shouted congratulations at Leo and slapped him on the back, cheerfully ignoring his suggestions.

Mrs. Hurst took one look at the mess, shook her head in amused disgust and whistled so sharply the closest people winced. "You lot, pay attention!" she shouted as everyone turned toward her in surprise, "Anyone bleeding see me immediately. Anyone who got hit on the head at any point tonight, see Janice. If you can't remember if you've been hit on the head or not, see Janice. If you've a broken bone, see Carol. If you're just here to wait and celebrate go sit in those chairs and the Mother help you if you disturb the actual patients. Go now!"

People scurried, scampered, and generally bent over backwards to appease the formidable Healer. Two other Healers, presumably Janice and Carol, stepped forward from the chaos and started collecting patients. Harry stood to the side and watched as the worst hurt were treated quickly and efficiently by the three Healers. Leo broke from his friends and came to stand by her with a relieved look on his face.

"Harry, thank the trickster you made it," Leo said, looking her over, "All in one piece?"

Harry nodded, looking him over in turn, "I'm fine, but you're bleeding."

Leo looked down at himself in surprise, as though he hadn't noticed the blood dripping down his wrist and hand from a puncture wound just below his elbow, "Huh. Guess I am. Still, there are others with worse, and my dear old mum has enough to work on. I'll get it Healed later."

Harry shook her head and reached out to pull Leo's left arm toward her. It was shining with sweat in the places it wasn't streaked with grime, so the first thing Harry did was pull out her wand and cast a basic cleansing charm that all first-year Healers learned over the area close to the wound. Leo looked on with bemusement as she closed her eyes and focused on what she wanted her magic to do. Archie had taught her all of the fancy theory behind it, but Harry still found it much easier to simply focus her magic into Healing the muscle and skin the way she wanted it to.

She forged the magical connection to the injured area easily enough, but when she sank into the connection with her consciousness and started to direct her magic toward the area, Leo's magic, which had already surrounded the wound protectively, rose up and gave what felt like a magical hiss at her. Harry paused, taken aback by the aggressiveness of Leo's magic. She pushed forward once more, slowly, and projected Healing intent toward the magic. She felt it hesitate, before moving back ever so slightly from the wound. Harry asked her magic to move in immediately and began the tedious process of re-directing blood flow until she could get her magic to knit the tissue back together seamlessly and rebuild the lost and damaged skin cells. Her magic flowed out of her and into Leo's arm with a pointed impatience that very clearly communicated the idea that she should have been using it earlier. Harry ignored her magic, since she already felt three times the fool for freezing up in the middle of danger like she had.

When the wound was Healed, Harry pulled the connection back and wiped a hand up under her bangs to get rid of the few beads of perspiration that built up when she used her magic for Healing. It didn't tire her much, but Healing was very intense. It was satisfying in an odd sort of way, but Harry didn't think she'd ever enjoy it enough to do it for a living.

Leo flexed his arm for a moment, then smiled brightly down at her, "Full of surprises as ever, I see. Thanks, Harry." He reached out to ruffle Harry's hair, but she ducked away, scowling.

"Don't mention it," Harry said, then, feeling stupid, added, "So, you guys won, right?"

Leo laughed, hazel eyes dancing, "Yes, Harry, I guess we did."

"Oh," Harry said, "Good."

Leo laughed some more, "Harry, you—"

"MAREK SWIFT! WHAT. ARE. YOU. DOING?!"

Leo and Harry both turned to watch as Mrs. Hurst apparently caught sight of Marek in her line and railed into him.

"Umm," Marek looked like a child caught with a fist full of biscuits, "Bleeding?"

Indeed he was, Harry thought. Marek had several shallow gashes on his arms and legs that were bleeding sluggishly.

"You are supposed to be on bed rest!" Mrs. Hurst scowled, "Not running around getting stabbed left and hexed right."

Marek smiled helplessly, "Well, Leo needed me, Mrs. Hurst. I had to, um, help him fight Claw."

Mrs. Hurst pointed her wand at Marek and Harry noticed with amusement that he cowered dramatically, "Don't you bring my Leo into this. I told you not to do anything strenuous for at least a week."

Marek shrugged his big shoulders, grinning, "It weren't that strenuous, ma'am."

Several people laughed along with Marek and Mrs. Hurst just shook her head and started Healing Marek's wounds.

Harry felt that she was no longer needed there, and she had calmed down considerably since she came sprinting into the clinic a couple of hours earlier. So she went to Mrs. Hurst and asked if there was a floo connection in the clinic. Luckily, there was one, so Harry wouldn't have to brave the dark streets again that night. She promised herself she would look for the crates she'd abandoned tomorrow, when the sun was up again.

She went to tell Leo she was going, but he was surrounded by his closest confidantes, including Marek, Aled, Solom, Rispah, and to Harry's surprise Mr. Krait. She didn't want to tear him away from his friends in the midst of what was very clearly a victory celebration, and she didn't feel that she could join in the celebration for several reasons. One was that she simply wasn't a part of the Rogue. This was their victory, not hers. Also, no matter how victorious they were, Harry was all too painfully aware that they, too, had lost people. She had watched one, the man in the blue vest, die in front of her, and she would be a fool if she assumed he was the only casualty of the battle. Harry understood the need to celebrate life before mourning death, but she had come too close to death herself to revel in it.

Instead, she called a quick goodbye to Leo over the crowd. He smiled and waved at her, shouting something indistinct over the noise of everyone packed together in the clinic waiting room. Harry wasn't sure he'd even really heard her, but she had to be getting home anyway. It was lucky she knew the password for her parents' floo, or there was no way she'd be able to get in at this time of night, after the wards were up.

And so Harry had flooed home, using the password to bypass the night wards, and ended up…here.

Trying to convince her father she wasn't a burglar before he hexed her and called in his Auror buddies to arrest her.

Harry took in the distrustful expression on James' face and knew she had to talk fast. "Dad, I promise it's me. Remember on Uncle Sirius' birthday when we had a pool party in his basement? And Sirius brought all of his silly snakes onto his raft, and then tipped them into the pool when he and you tackled Uncle Remus off of his raft. It was lucky they could swim, really, or mother would have broken her promise about not disagreeing with Sirius on his birthday."

Harry watched her father frown and step backwards slowly, "Harry? Step forward until I can see your face. Slowly, and don't reach for anything."

Harry moved forward as slowly as she could, lifting her face up so that the light of the Lumos would catch it when she was close enough. She knew the moment James recognized her, because his face muscles slackened with relief, but he didn't lower his wand still.

"I'm sorry, Harry, but just to make sure—what did I tell you to never forget in the last letter your mother and I sent you before you came home from school?" James asked.

Harry froze. She had read through the letters Archie both received from and wrote to her parents when she got home that summer, but she had read them all at once, and she couldn't remember which one of them had said what, as she might if she had read them one at a time over the course of a year.

"I…I don't remember, Dad," Harry said shakily. James immediately looked on guard again and took an aggressive step forward, "I'm sorry, Dad, please ask me something else. I can't remember those letters right now, they all blend together. Please, ask something else."

James frowned into her face, but said, "Then tell me this. Who are we planning on marrying you to if the new marriage legislation gets pushed through?"

Harry blinked, well that was easy—wait. Too easy. It was a trick question.

"No one," she said, "Everyone will think I'm marrying Archie, because we'll get engaged to protect me, but in reality the engagement will have a clause of unsuitability which will allow us to dissolve it when we turn seventeen."

James nodded, "Yes, that's right." He lifted his wand so that the light encompassed both of them, "Harry, what are you doing out so late? We thought you were down in the lab, and assumed you'd go to bed when you were finished with whatever project you were working on." James frowned down at her, "Do you have any idea how terrifying it is to realize you have no idea where your only child has been all night?" Harry winced as James started toward her, but he only embraced her, exhaling tiredly into her hair, "Never did I imagine you would pull something like this. Your cousin Archie, maybe, your Uncle Sirius, definitely, but you? You're supposed to be the smart one. The level headed one who doesn't do stupid things like stay out till midnight without telling anyone. What if something had happened to you? We wouldn't even know where to look, and it would be much too late to help by the time we noticed you were even gone."

"I'm sorry," Harry said, "Believe me, I didn't mean to stay out so late. You know me, Dad, I would never be so unthinkingly foolish. I just…things came up and it wasn't really my fault."

That sounded weak even to her, and James gave her an unimpressed look, "I'm sorry too, Harry, because this kind of thing just isn't okay. I never, and I do mean seriously never, thought I'd say this, but…you're grounded."

Harry gaped and stared at her father, who was looking puzzled at the taste of his own words, "Grounded?"

"Yes," James nodded slowly, "Yes, Harry. You are grounded. You will not leave this house for a week. Not to Diagon Alley. Not to your friends' homes. Not even to Grimmauld Place. You will stay here and every night at nine pm you will be responsible for setting the wards. With any luck that will help you remember when exactly your curfew is."

Harry blinked in utter incomprehension. Grounded? She had never, as far as she could remember, been formally disciplined in such a way. In any way. She couldn't recall the last time her parents had taken her to task for something. Every now and then they offered advice, cautionary suggestions, or intelligent input on her plans, and she respected their counsel and took it under consideration. They gave her chores, of course, and asked for her respect and obedience in minor matters that were of little consequence to her, but punishments? It was like James was speaking a foreign language.

"Harry?" James prompted.

"Oh, yes," Harry shook her head, "Okay, Dad. Um, so I'm really grounded?"

James grimaced a bit, "Yes. I'll tell your mother in the morning."

"Don't tell Uncle Sirius," Harry said, still a little dazed at the very idea of being grounded, "He'll think you're starting a dangerous precedent."

James' face softened and he even smiled a bit, "You'll have to come up with convincing excuses then, if he asks you to go somewhere."

Harry was about to respond when the dinging alarm on the floo went off as the fire turned green once more. James snapped his head around and barked out the acceptance password and a head appeared in their fireplace.

"Auror Potter?" a man with dark skin and a deep voice called.

"Yes, Auror Shacklebolt?" James bent down to answer the man, "What is it?"

"We're using your on-call shift tonight," Shacklebolt said quickly. Harry nodded to herself, understanding now why her father had been so quick to respond to her flooing in. He must have been awake already and felt the wards fluctuate. "There's been reports of a fire in the Lower Alleys, and we've already got both squads out dealing with a domestic dispute that turned violent and injured several muggles living in the apartment above the magical couple."

James fingered his bangs distractedly, "Okay, Shacklebolt, I'll be right through."

The Auror's head nodded, then disappeared.

James turned to Harry and said, "I've got to go, Harry, but please think about how dangerous it is for you to be out so late. You're only a child still, however grown-up you feel with a wand in your hand. Please don't let this happen again."

"Okay, Dad," Harry said, "I'm sorry. Be safe tonight."

"Will do," James said. He reached out to ruffle Harry's hair and she let him, though she really didn't appreciate when people did that. Yet another reason she mourned her long hair. No one ruffles long hair. "Night, little Fawn."

He left, and Harry walked wearily upstairs to her bedroom. At the sight of her bed she nearly groaned out loud. It was as if her body had been refusing to admit how tired it was, but gave way under the sudden temptation of four fluffy pillows and a heavenly down comforter. Her limbs carried her forward and onto the soft mattress in a trance, and she didn't even take off her shoes before allowing her head to hit the pillow. She could scarcely believe the day she had had. She closed her eyes with relief, not knowing that she would snap them open once more in just a few short hours after a paralyzing nightmare visited her dreams. A nightmare about fire and death, blue vests and red ink. For now, however, she drifted eagerly into oblivion, and her last thought before sleep was a fervent wish that the rest of the summer went by as uneventfully as humanly possible.

Harry got her wish. Between being grounded and starting to prepare for the coming school year, the next few weeks passed in a blur of normality. Her twelfth birthday came and went with little ceremony, though she and Archie did have a cake that shouted rude insults every time you cut into it, courtesy of James and Sirius. She received a few presents, mostly academic in nature, including a new pureblood etiquette book from Pansy and a school planner that automatically colour coded assignments from one Hermione Granger, which she stored with 'her' school supplies so that Archie could take it with him to AIM in September.

She had to owl-deliver her potions to Mr. Krait for the week she was grounded, which was a tedious and annoying process involving much smaller packages and numerous owl-induced wounds on her hands from dealing with unfamiliar birds, and she apologized profusely to Leo in case he had looked for her those days, but he waved it off. The Court of the Rogue was picking up the pieces after Claw's attack, and rebuilding the Dragon took up a lot of Leo's time in the weeks following the fire in any case.

Harry used the week she was grounded industriously, and soon she'd finished the first-year owl school curriculum and taken the final exam. It occurred to Harry that the people at Sphinx Correspondence School of Magic were inordinately trusting, if they let her take the exams at home without a sworn proctor or at least a parental signature, but perhaps the parchment was charmed not to allow cheating. It didn't make much difference to Harry, who had learned the material twice now, and she finished her first year as Harry Potter nearly a month ahead of schedule.

With all of her schoolwork out of the way, she had more time to devote to Polyjuice Potion research. Harry had found a very interesting spell that was traditionally used by magical couples who were looking to have children and wanted to see how their genes mixed.

The spell was in the book on blending she'd gotten from the shop on Diagon Alley, and as such it essentially blended two people's physical characteristics. It required the same input that the Polyjuice Potion did, but instead of adding one hair, you added two. Technically, one could add whatever part of a person they could get their hands on, but everyone in the potion community agreed hairs were the easiest and most ethical thing to take—if ethical was indeed a word that could be applied to the impersonation of another wizard. After all, a hair didn't generally cause pain in appropriation, unlike fingernails or blood, both of which also carried magical signatures in them. After scanning the magical signatures via hair, the spell required an input command to determine the sex of the 'child.' Then the spell took both hairs and transformed them into one. It blended the hairs together, and the idea was that the parents could then use the blended hair in a Polyjuice Potion and transform some random kid into their theoretical kid so they could get a good look at him or her. The book suggested using a muggle child and obliviating him afterwards, but the book had been written in the medieval period, so Harry ignored much of the author's opinionating.

The best part was that the discovery of this spell meant most of Harry's work was done for her. Clearly the spell didn't blend just the hairs, but the magical signatures attached to the hairs. This meant that Harry didn't have to worry about trying to figure out what characteristics a person who looked halfway between her and Archie would have. More importantly, however, it meant she didn't have to try and simulate the impossible task of creating a unique magical signature that coded for the physical characteristics she needed. The spell took care of that by blending the signatures instead of trying to create a whole new one, and it also consolidated the two signatures into a Polyjuice-friendly package. One she got the hang of the spell, all Harry would have to do was find an ingredient to make the potion semi-permanent.

Smiling down at her extensive notes on the spell she was about to attempt, Harry ran through the instructions once more, then went to find Archie. He would definitely want to see this.

She bumped into her mother upon leaving the Lab, and the beautiful redhead smiled with pleased surprise at the sight of her.

"Harry, you're surfacing rather early today, aren't you?" Lily asked teasingly.

Harry smiled in acknowledgement—it was only four o'clock in the afternoon, and even on the weekends it was true that Harry was rarely seen before dinnertime at six. "I'm going to find Archie. Have you seen him?"

Lily pursed her lips delicately in consideration, "I think he and Sirius were going to the Hogsmeade branch of Zonko's today to check on the Marauder sales. They had to run a few errands first, though, and they only left about an hour ago, so you could probably catch up with them if you flooed directly to the Three Broomsticks."

Harry hesitated, but really, what else did she have to do? It would be somewhat suspicious if she told Lily she couldn't talk to Archie about what she needed him for in public or around Sirius. Also, it wasn't likely that Madam Rosmerta would recognize her from the one time Snape had brought her through the Three Broomsticks' floo, so there was no reason she couldn't go to Zonko's to see her cousin and uncle. She really should take more of an interest in the Marauder line anyway. Archie loved pranks, after all, and it would help her credibility as him if she was at least up to date about her family's latest joke products. "Okay," Harry said decisively, "I'll go meet them there. Thanks, mum."

"Sure, darling," Lily said, adding, "Oh, could you pick me up something from Honeydukes while you're in Hogsmeade?"

"Of course," Harry said, "More ice mice?"

Lily smiled a bit helplessly, "I don't know what's gotten into me lately, but the last couple of weeks I've just been craving the stuff. You don't mind? I just need a few more boxes and then I'm sure I won't want any more…"

Harry nodded agreeably, well aware that Lily had been saying that she only wanted a 'few more boxes' of ice mice for a good three weeks. Poor James was heading to Honeydukes every other day it seemed, so Harry would try to get a bunch of the squeaky little sweets this time to hold Lily over until she got through this strange craving of hers.

She grabbed her trusty red-velvet moneybag, and with a speed only magic could engineer, Harry stepped out of the fireplace and into Hogsmeade barely five minutes later.

The street was packed with shoppers that Saturday afternoon, but Harry ducked and weaved through the crowd with ease. She'd been traipsing through the crowds on Diagon Alley for so long now that the masses of people didn't even faze her. She reached Honeydukes in no time and began looking around for the ice mice. It seemed that the owners had re-arranged the shop since she'd last been in, so it took her a few minutes to find her mother's new favourite sweet. The ice mice were now by the window, and in between loading box after box of the sweet into her basket and ignoring the curious looks she was getting from the other customers—none of whom seemed to have ever encountered a person with a healthy taste for ice mice before—Harry happened to glance through the glass at the crowded street. Her eyes were immediately drawn to a wizard who seemed to be parting the crowds with sheer willpower, and Harry resisted the urge to shrink away from the window in sudden alarm.

It was Professor Snape. He was striding purposefully down the street, in the direction of what Harry thought might be the apothecary. He stood at least a head over most of the other wizards on the street, but it was his aloof and unapproachable expression that set him apart from everyone else. She stared at him with no small amount of frustration. If she were really who she pretended to be, would she be standing here, denied the right to cross the street and strike up a conversation with her mentor? Better yet, if Hogwarts still allowed half-bloods and Harry could simply be herself, would she perhaps be striding alongside Snape at this very moment, helping him with his summer errands as she soaked up potions expertise and sought advice on her Polyjuice experimentations?

No, Harry shook her head, it was a silly thought. If Snape knew who she really was, he would likely be even less keen on accepting her as his student than he had been in the beginning. He loathed her father more than he did Sirius, after all, and though Harry was hazy on the details, she knew it had something to do with her mother, who had been childhood friends with Snape before going off to AIM. Harry didn't really want to know more than that, though she strongly suspected the hatred had begun when they were all eleven. James met Lily at King's Cross station when she went to see Snape off to Hogwarts, and immediately declared his passionate love for the pretty red-haired child and proposed marriage, completely ignoring a young Severus Snape's possible prior claim to Lily's affections. Or something. Harry shuddered. It was quite simply too gross to contemplate.

In any case, being herself would probably never have helped in her goal of earning the Professor's academic esteem, and if she had been allowed into Hogwarts in the first place she probably wouldn't be studying Polyjuice Potion at all. Her thoughts were nothing but ungrounded fancy, so she turned from the window and purchased her basket full of ice mice without further consideration of might-have-beens. Harry did check to make sure Snape was still inside the Apothecary before she darted over to Zonko's, however. She really wasn't prepared to have all of her plans explode in her face because of one ill-fated sighting of her notorious green eyes in Rigel Black's familiar face by one of the few men probably shrewd enough to put it all together in an instant given the right information.

Harry entered Zonko's quickly, and immediately spotted her uncle Sirius near the Marauder display cases, surrounded by children of all ages who were eager to meet one of the famed prank legends. Archie stood off to the side, watching with exasperated fondness as his dad played the crowds, hamming it up and sending all the children into delighted fits of laughter. Not that it wasn't completely condescending of her to refer to the kids gathered around her uncle as children, being herself only recently turned twelve, but obsessive public displays of adoration and those who either committed or basked in them had always seemed to Harry to be a bit childish. It wasn't just that she herself hated attention—or perhaps it was. Maybe her own dislike of the limelight had made her look just the tiniest bit down upon anyone who truly enjoyed fame or infamy, as Sirius and James often did for their pranking expertise.

Archie, at least, seemed to share her opinion, as he shook his head with an expression that revealed complete acceptance without any understanding and moved away to look about the shop while Sirius entertained his fans. Harry went over to intercept him.

She tapped him on the shoulder and Archie spun around with an expression that was impatient before he caught sight of her.

"Harry!" Archie blinked, then smiled broadly, "What are you doing in here? My birthday was last week, you know, so it's a little late to be shopping for me."

"Surprise," Harry said mildly, "I wanted to talk to you about something, but you weren't home, so Lily sent me to find you."

Archie lifted an unconvinced brow, "Aunt Lily was out of ice mice again, wasn't she?" His eyes flicked meaningfully toward the Honeydukes bag in her hand, and Harry shrugged helplessly.

"My mother is now a slave to her own strange cravings," Harry said, "Although I really did want to talk to you."

"What about?" Archie asked curiously.

"Our little project," Harry said as softly as she could to still be heard over the din, "I've had a major breakthrough. I think the next stage should be ready before we go back to school."

"Really?" Archie asked, sounding impressed, "You can finish everything in three weeks?"

"As long as what you and I are going to do when we get home works out," Harry said, "Yes."

Archie grinned, "Right on. So as long as you're here, we need to take care of an aspect of your education you've been seriously neglecting."

Harry sighed a bit, "I suppose we do. So tell me what the cutting edge of the pranking business is, Arch."

"I'll do you one better," Archie said, "I'm going to buy all the basics while we're here and explain them, then when you get to school you'll know what to do—and you'll have to do something this year, Harry. The first year I can say I'm settling in, but this year you have to cause some mayhem in my name or my dad will think I'm abandoning the family traditions."

Harry winced. She still felt pretty bad for inadvertently messing up Archie and Sirius' relationship. "Okay," Harry said, "I know what most of this stuff is already—I might not participate, but I have been a member of this family for a decade or so. Just go over the new stuff with me and pick out the ones I'll need."

Archie happily agreed. Twenty minutes later Harry and Archie were laden with everything from all-purpose pranking tape to ever-changing fabric dye. They'd even picked up a few of the Marauders' newest product, which had been officially dubbed the Barrier Button. The only thing Harry firmly declined was dung bombs. She still couldn't stand the things.

"But all of this stuff is just the accessories that make pulling off a prank easier," Archie had cautioned her before they proceeded to the checkout stand, "A good prank isn't tossing a stink pellet at someone or turning their food blue. The best pranks are original, creative, and remarkable, and that comes from the prankster. It's about finding obscure spells that no one imagined could be used in comical situations, or about using mundane objects in a way that is so hilarious people tell their children about it. If you aren't going to really try, don't bother pranking anyone, okay? I mean it, Harry. I'd rather be known as a stick in the mud than a copycat prankster without class or finesse."

Harry scowled slightly, "Yeah, I'll try not to embarrass you with my inexpertise in this area, cousin."

"Much obliged," Archie grinned, "Now let's get this stuff paid for so we can drag Dad away from his adoring fans. I think his head is blown quite big enough for one day."

That evening, Harry asked her parents if she could sleep over at Archie's house and the two of them holed up in Archie's bedroom where Harry explained the finer points of the spell.

"So we have to do it twice, right?" Archie said, "Once for a boy and once for a girl, if we're sticking to the plan where neither of us actually change our gender."

Harry nodded firmly. Definitely they would be sticking to that plan. "Ready?" she asked, face alight with excitement. They were just so close.

Archie nodded, "Let's do it."

They each plucked a hair from their heads and placed them into the correct positions in the runic circle Harry had drawn in temporary chalk on Archie's bedroom floorboards. All she knew about runes was what she'd picked up from doing Flint's OWL-level Ancient Runes homework for a year, but the book on the blending spell had very helpfully included a diagram of the required circle, so Harry had simply copied it out onto the floor. Her understanding of the runes was good enough to be able to tell that they at least weren't summoning demons or making blood sacrifices, so Harry wasn't terribly worried about using a runic configuration she didn't fully understand.

Once the hairs were in place, Harry sealed the circle and began the chain of wand movements she'd memorized that would channel the spell properly through her wand. More importantly, at least for Harry who wasn't exactly familiar with the theory behind the magic she was attempting, she concentrated her will very strongly on the desired outcome of the spell. She willed—read 'asked nicely'—her magic to act as the spell required and blend the magical signatures of the two hairs in the circle. When the long chain of wand movements was complete, Harry waved her wand in a pattern that mimicked the rune for 'man,' which would indicate a preference for a male result, and intoned the words of the spell carefully and clearly.

"Miscetis Essentiae."

Harry stiffened as the spell began to work. She could feel the magic course through her, like no spell she'd ever attempted. Instead of a small stream of magic being drawn from her outer core, it was as if the spell had forced a floodgate to open at the very heart of her inner core. The magic came pouring out of her. It flooded the runic circle she was standing over until the chalk lines lit up with an eerie glow, as if the magic within its boundaries was so strong it had to be manifested in a physical outlet. And still the spell demanded more. Harry could actually feel her magical core draining steadily, and when the feeling did not stop after a moment or two, Harry became slightly alarmed. The spell had her in its grip at that point, however, so there was nothing she could do except grit her teeth and keep her will focused on the proper outcome, so that at least the magic would not be wasted.

The runes began changing before Harry's eyes as magic continued to fill the circle. They shifted and transformed, faster and faster until they blurred, and Harry's limited knowledge of the art couldn't make heads or tails of the process. Was this supposed to happen? Harry had no idea, but it was both mesmerizing and terrifying, like watching a great majestic dragon being just barely contained by its keepers. It was awe-inspiring, but there was an element of danger always present, because if at any time the magic found a weakness in either the circle or Harry herself, she knew instinctively that it would break free of its constraints and roam free, wild and at the current levels devastating. Harry held firm, but in the back of her mind was the idea that runic magics were definitely not things to be messed with.

It was her good fortune that the runic circle she'd copied had been a good one and held the magic firmly in the desired form until the spell's processes were complete. The runes settled after a final burst of light, and where there had been two hairs in the circle there was now one hair, innocent and completely unextraordinary despite the sheer amount of magic that had gone into the spell. The final phase of the spell dissolved the runic sphere completely, as if it had never been there. Harry blinked, thinking that this must be why the book made no mention of what kinds of material to draw the circle with—clearly the medium didn't matter, as it was consumed by the spell in any case.

Archie reached forward to pick up the hair carefully, saying, "It's almost anti-climactic, looking at this tiny strand of hair after all that."

Harry smiled tiredly in response. Her limbs felt heavy and weak, while at the same time her head felt lighter than the air around her. Was this magical over-exertion? It was terribly disorienting, she thought idly. "I don't feel very well," Harry said out loud.

Archie peered at her with concern, "Did the spell do something strange to you?"

Harry shook her head, then stilled abruptly when the action made her dizzy, "No, it just took a lot of magic from me, I think."

Archie nodded, "I could feel it even from over where I was watching. Do you need a Pepper-Up Potion? I think Dad has one in the downstairs bathroom."

Harry was going to decline, but a good look at her core with her magical senses had her reconsidering. What was once a ball of fire surrounded by writhing snake-like tendrils was now unrecognizable. There were a few stray coils of magic hanging like loose skin around her inner core. Usually her true core was a tightly-compressed ball of fire and superheated gas, not unlike a miniature sun, but now it looked like a weakly spinning sphere of magical glitter. Just the barest specks of magical power swirled around and around in a lazy way, and the snakes that were supposed to hide the true core from view were just resting, as if exhausted, in suspension above her pitifully drained core. Already, she could feel her core working quickly to replenish itself. She felt the generation of more magic like hot internal combustion in her chest, but even as fast as it was rejuvenating itself, it had never been quite so depleted.

"Yeah, I think I'd better take one," Harry said, a little uneasy at how low her magic levels had gotten without her control. Even in the midst of the Sleeping Sickness, Harry didn't remember ever being this pressed for magic. Still, it looked like the spell had worked.

Archie ran and grabbed the Pepper-Up Potion for Harry, who felt immediately better, if not fully recovered, after taking it.

"So do you think it worked?" Archie asked.

Harry grinned a bit, "Only one way to find out. Want to test it now?"

Archie nodded eagerly and Harry hauled herself up to root around in the overnight bag she'd brought with her. She pulled out the small vial of Polyjuice potion she'd taken from one of the many control batches she'd been making over the summer and held it out to Archie. He put the hair in and watched with badly concealed impatience as the mixture turned a deep blue-grey. A mixture, she presumed, of the electric-blue Archie's hair usually turned the potion and the deep charcoal grey her own hair normally effected.

"Bottoms up," Archie said, and he tipped the dose into his mouth as quickly as possible.

Harry watched carefully as Archie transformed, but he didn't seem to be in any more discomfort than what was usually experienced with Polyjuice. As usual, Archie's face began to slowly look more like Harry's did, but unlike in the past, it reached a certain point and then…stopped. Harry cocked her head consideringly.

Archie's hair hadn't changed at all, except for perhaps becoming messier. The colour would stay the same and the theoretical magical signature didn't code for hairstyle, so Archie had kept his short-but-shaggy haircut. His eyes were also the same colour, which gave Harry the hope that the girl version of their fused physical characteristics would have grey eyes as well. She was really getting tired of the contacts. His face had become just the tiniest bit more delicate than it already was. His chin was a tad bit more rounded, and his nose was a hair smaller, his eyes just a bit bigger. His eyebrows were a little thinner and his top lip curved just a tiny bit more than usual. Archie's eyelashes were perhaps noticeably thicker, but Harry hadn't ever paid enough attention to her cousin's eyelashes to be able to say for sure.

All in all, Archie looked like himself, only…different. It was hardly noticeable, Harry thought, though as she looked at him she was having trouble remembering just what exactly was so different about his old face. She started to smile slowly.

"This…is going to work," she said, taking the full effect in by stepping back a step, "Yes. Archie, you look like yourself."

"Isn't that…bad?" Archie asked, walking over to his bathroom to take a look in the mirror.

"No, it's good," Harry said, "Because this means that we look enough alike already that changing half-way into one another doesn't dramatically alter the way we appear. It means that after we take the potion, no one will be able to say with surety that we've somehow changed our appearances."

"Does this mean we can nix the whole 'potion regimen' idea?" Archie asked, "Because honestly the idea of slowly over the course of forever changing our appearance seems overly complicated. For one, it would be difficult to conceal all those different potions, not to mention hard to keep it all straight without you there to differentiate the doses. For another—what's the need? We haven't seen our friends since early July, and two months is probably enough time to dull their memories of us—or at least enough time that they will assign any lingering confusion about our appearances to the time we've been away. Also, if we take the potion before we see our friends but after we leave our parents, our family won't see us till winter break. They'll be more likely to notice the difference, but we can blame it on puberty. A lot can change in five months."

Harry stopped to consider this for a moment. "I suppose…that makes sense. I'll have to run the spell again for a girl to make sure the changes aren't too extreme for me either. Actually, I'll have to run the spell three more times once to test the girl version of our hybrid and then once more for each of us with the modified Polyjuice recipe." Harry frowned, "That might take a while, depending on how long it takes my magic to recover from the spell casting, but if everything goes smoothly…I guess it would work if we took the potions as you said, just before we see our friends but after we say goodbye to our parents."

Archie grinned, "This is going to be so cool. Like being in costume all the time, only no one else knows! Will we have to keep taking the potion as we get older?"

Harry nodded, "Yes, we will. Well, we don't have to, but it will look strange if we never change at all after this year. So each summer we'll re-do the test to reflect our ageing, okay?"

"Sounds great," Archie said, "And you've got the modifications for the potion all worked out?"

"I think so," Harry said "Though of course it's only theory until I test it."

"That's just so comforting," Archie muttered half heartedly, "Still, I'm really impressed we've even gotten this far. The only bad part about this is that no one will ever know how awesome we are."

Harry smiled ruefully, "And that's the best case scenario."

Harry had one more thing to do before school started. It was this that found her several times a week in the Potter Library, researching something she'd never really paid much attention to before, despite training in the Healing arts.

Nutrition and Fitness.

If the night of the fire had taught Harry nothing else, it was of her fragility. Never in her life had she been so aware of her own physical weakness, helplessness, and mortality all at once. It had scared her, demoralized her, and then it had inspired her. She took it as a lesson well learned, and before the school year started she was determined to get started on a program that would help her slowly start overcoming the limitations of both her female form and her comfortable upbringing. Harry vowed to train until she was fit enough to chase and catch a pickpocket, and to learn to defend herself with and without a wand, so that she would never be put in a situation where she didn't know how to keep herself safe. What if Leo hadn't come? Worse, what if someone else had been depending on her that night, and freezing up under attack had put more than just her in immediate peril? Harry couldn't afford to let something like that happen again, and since disasters were notoriously hard to predict and therefore avoid, the only solution was to make herself into someone who could handle herself in the midst of danger.

So her new side project was to become capable in the most basic meaning of the word, and the start of her plans for getting into shape revolved around what Mrs. Hurst had said to her.

Apparently, she needed to eat more protein, because being a lazy vegetarian was stunting her growth. Harry would be the first to admit that she wasn't a very good vegetarian. She avoided meat more because she didn't really care for it than for any misplaced sympathies for her fellow barnyard animals. She also didn't exactly take great pains to make up for the lack of meat in her diet, as true vegetarians were supposed to, so Harry couldn't say she was terribly surprised her slight stature was due in part to her diet. Hadn't she thought when she started Hogwarts that keeping a vegetarian diet would be a great surface reasoning for anyone wondering down the road why she was smaller than the other boys in her class? Unfortunately, however, the 'excuse' turned out to be a little too close to the truth and she actually was going to make herself smaller than the others in her class—the other girls, that is.

Perhaps it was time for the truth to become a pretense, Harry thought wryly, that would be a nice change. And yet, it was probably the best plan. She would begin eating meat once more in secret, despite not having much taste for the stuff, but to everyone else she would remain a vegetarian, to explain her slight stature in case she ended up her mother's height, which was a rather modest 5 foot 6 inches.

In addition to the changes in her diet, Harry had been researching various exercise regimens. Mostly, this consisted of going through her mother's Witch Weekly magazines until she found the weekly workout and trying to find one that didn't sound ridiculous. She didn't exactly see herself jazzercising her abs into shape in the middle of the Slytherin common room. Even Pansy would be too embarrassed to speak to her. Eventually, Harry decided she needed to talk to a professional.

With this in mind, Harry flooed to her uncle Remus' two-bedroom condo in London one afternoon in mid-August to get some expert advice.

"Uncle Remus?" she called quietly into the small house, "Are you home?"

A moment later a faint voice came up from the direction of the basement stairs. While none of the surrounding condos had basements, Remus' condition required him by law to keep a secure holding cell in his home. He didn't ever actually use the 'cell' in the basement, preferring to spend his full moons with Sirius and James at Grimmauld Place under the influence of the Wolfsbane Potion, so he had transformed his basement into a gym instead.

"Harry?" Remus called back, and though his tone was questioning, Harry knew he knew who she was. Very little confused a werewolf's senses, and their hearing was particularly keen, "Be right up!"

"Don't," Harry said, "I'm coming down."

She descended the stairs and passed through the barred gate that separated the stairs from the rest of the basement, creating the 'cell' when the gate was secured and warded. The basement was victim to a very obvious expansion charm, and was several times wider than the condo itself. It hosted various sets of weights and several different machines that must have been muggle in origin, as Harry had never seen their like outside of Remus' basement. Machines you ran on, machines with cords tied to weights that you pulled or pushed on in various positions, and a good third of the gym was dedicated to a mat-padded sparring floor. Harry knew most of the machines were gifts from Sirius, who as a pureblood wizard with naturally slim genetics found his friend's gym hobby to be terribly amusing, but they all looked well worn, so clearly Remus made good use of them no matter how ingenuine the intent behind them was.

Remus set down the weight he was squatting with and grinned a bit lopsidedly at her. "What's up, Harry?" he panted, wiping his face with a nearby towel, "It's a rare day for you to go out of your way to find someone."

Harry blinked, a bit taken aback by that statement. Was she really so distant from her family?

"I actually came here to ask you for a favour," Harry said, a bit apologetically, "I feel kind of bad about it now, though. Do I really never come to see you?"

Remus shrugged easily, "I didn't mean it like that. There's no need for us to seek one another out, since we see each other nearly every night for dinner at the very least. I wasn't rebuking, just commenting. What can I do for you, Harry?"

Harry glanced around the gym, "I've been thinking lately that I'm not very fit. Since you're the only person I know who exercises seriously, I figured you'd have some ideas of where to start."

Remus raised his eyebrows, "You want to get in shape? Isn't Quidditch enough? I know you enjoy it, and it would be easier to stick to sports than to try and plan a weight-regimen for someone your age. It's important not to damage the bones or muscles in the back by adding too much weight too soon at your age."

"Quidditch is good," Harry said, "And while I do want to be physically stronger, I was actually thinking something along the lines of self-defence training. That's good exercise, isn't it?"

"It is," Remus said slowly, "And good to know in general for a…well, girl." He smiled apologetically, but Harry nodded in understanding. "What brought this on, though?" her uncle asked, "Did something happen?"

Harry shook her head, hoping Remus wasn't paying enough attention to her heart rate to catch the lie, "I just read something about how girls were at an increased risk for predators of all kinds starting at around twelve or thirteen. So I thought it would be a good thing to learn now, rather than not learn it and wish I had later. Also, I really do need to start exercising."

Remus considered her quietly for a moment. He seemed to be sizing her up, weighing her request against his better judgment, and Harry felt herself grow unexpectedly uneasy at his contemplation. She had honestly never considered that he might refuse, for all that she had phrased the request politely. After all, why wouldn't he want to teach her self-defence? It was a good idea, and Remus liked spending time with her…didn't he? Now she was thinking perhaps she had gotten a little too used to her family's infinite generosity and care. Maybe she was taking more things for granted than she realized.

Finally, Remus said, "If I agree to teach you, Harry, I want you to understand what you'll be getting into. I'm not saying this to discourage you, but I've never been under the impression that you…" he trailed off, clearly uncertain of what he wanted to say, "What I mean is that you've always been very focused on some things and very apathetic about most other things. Learning a self-defence style takes a lot of dedicated effort, and I'm just wondering if you've got the…focus to commit the time and energy necessary."

Harry took a moment to respond, "I understand what you're saying, Uncle Remus, and I agree with a lot of it. I admit I have a tendency to devote my energy with extreme prejudice to the things that interest me most. What I would say, however, is that fitness and in particular self-defence has recently become something that interests me greatly. I honestly think that your teachings would not be wasted on me now, thought they might have been if you'd tried teaching me as recently as a few weeks ago."

Remus had that concerned look again, but he didn't pry further. Instead, he said, "If that's what you think, then I will teach you. It's important to realize that this cannot be done in the little time we have before you go back to America, however. For now what I will do is design a regimen for you to follow once you are back at school, and when you come home in December we can evaluate your progress, okay?"

Harry nodded seriously. Remus was speaking to her as a student, not as a niece, and she instinctively reacted with respect, "Yes, sir."

Remus nodded in acceptance of the new dynamic, "We will begin immediately. I will start by teaching you a series of stretches and strengthening exercises. Learning to throw a punch won't help you if there's nothing behind it. I'll figure out what style, if any, I'll try to teach you tonight, so tomorrow morning report back here at six am and I'll let you know what I've decided while you join me on my morning run."

"Yes, sir," Harry said, feeling a bit overwhelmed. She had been right to come to Remus with this, she thought, but she was a little afraid of how quickly he was taking to his role as fitness coach.

"What are you waiting for, then?" Remus asked, "Go home and change into something you can sweat in."

Harry went.

She spent all afternoon under Remus' expert tutelage. Many would assume because of Remus' shabby and often-tired appearance that he did not take very good care of himself. Those that knew him, however, knew the truth. Remus had spent his life fighting the wolf within him, and that battle was waged on multiple plains. Remus was extremely well versed in multiple academic subjects, because studying hard in his youth helped him become mentally disciplined enough to hold the wolf at bay with his mind. His body, too, had to be conditioned to withstand the strain of both the monthly transformations and the wolf itself, which constantly sought control over the wizard's physical body as well as over his mind during the full moon. There was a reason werewolves often died young and tired. The wolf ate away at them one full moon at a time until there was nothing left. All the Wolfsbane potion in the world would not help if Remus did not have the will and the strength to fight the wolf at every turn. He was strong in mind, body, and spirit, but this was no accident—Remus had made it so.

He showed her how to limber and stretch both to reduce the chances of injury and to increase flexibility, of which Harry quickly discovered she had none. When he found she could barely press the weighted bar on the dumbbells, Remus set her a series of arm and wrist strengthening exercises that she was to do every morning, noon, and night with a set of balls that looked like Medi-minis, only heavier. They seemed to grow heavier still as she went through her lifting, curling, and clenching exercises, but Remus assured Harry that it was merely an illusion of her own weakness. She was greatly reassured by this.

Remus made a rather good teacher, Harry found. He explained things before he expected her to do them, and he corrected her firmly but with boundless patience. He also didn't just stand there watching her work. He did all of the stretches and exercises himself, which Harry found helped her keep her pace and motivation up. When Harry's arms were shaking from the number of push-ups, pull-ups, and other various arm-torturing exercises she was instructed to perform, Remus let her go home for dinner with the promise that he would have some light leg weights for her to wear on their run the next day.

She groaned at the pain involved from merely lifting a hand to the floo pot in Remus' living room. Still, Harry could not regret her decision to do this. All she had to do was think back to the night she stood frozen and helpless in the arms of death, and her determination sparked violently anew. She would see this torture through, and she would never be a victim again.

The rest of the summer went by fast in a blur of activity. Before she knew it she had gotten school supplies, switched them in secret with Archie, said goodbye to her friends in the Rogue, Polyjuiced into her cousin for what would be (hopefully) the last time, and arrived at King's Cross Station with Sirius for the start of her next year at Hogwarts.

She said goodbye to Sirius with as much good cheer as she knew Archie would have, if he were here and not back at the Potter residence, waiting to go to the airport for his flight to America.

"Be careful this year," Sirius said before she got onto the train, "No curing mysterious sicknesses or incurring life debts from dubious politicians. Just have fun, okay? And for Merlin's sake, go out for Quidditch."

Harry glanced awkwardly away, "It's just not the same without Harry there. We were always a team."

"The best Chaser-Beater team since the Prewett twins, I'd say," Sirius winked at her, "But try out anyway. Who knows, maybe you'll find someone just as challenging to play with as Harry."

"Okay, Dad," Harry said, mustering up a big smile, "Love you."

"See you in December, sport," Sirius said, pulling her into a strong hug.

"See you," she smiled, stepping back. She waved and headed off toward the train, pausing to look one last time over her shoulder and smile reassuringly at Sirius before she shut the door behind her.

She ducked into a boy's bathroom and closed a cubicle door behind her firmly. In her pocket, next to Archie's miniaturized trunk, was a vial of modified Polyjuice potion that Harry's fingers were itching to uncork.

It had taken her several days of straight research (in between breaks for Remus' merciless training exercises) to find an ingredient to add to the Polyjuice recipe that would make it permanent but also reversible. It turned out that the key wasn't in adding an ingredient to the actual recipe, but to the cauldron while the potion was being prepared. At first Harry didn't see the difference, because if you added something to the cauldron while you were making a potion, then surely you were adding it to the potion, but in the case of certain additives, you could add without adding, if that made sense.

Amber was the key. She had never used stones in potion making before, which was perhaps why it had taken her so long to come up with the solution, but once she started looking into it, she found that amber was a stone of permanence. The ancient Egyptian wizards used to place amber stones inside caskets, because the magical energies the stone gave off preserved the body and ensured that it would forever remain whole. Gems, like many things in the world, were excellent magical lodestones. They absorbed natural magical energies from the earth, but because each type of stone had different properties, each stone shaped the wild magic a different way once it was absorbed.

It was similar to the way a witch or wizard's magical core shaped magic in different ways depending on the wizard's personality, physical condition, disposition, etc. Each type of stone imbued the wild magic it absorbed over time with different tendencies as it shaped the magic—passively, of course. Stones were not like wizards, who could overcome their natural tendencies toward shaping magic with simple intent and willpower. The magic in an amber stone would be similar to the magic in all other amber stones, because the nature of the stones was similar, and that was the entire determining factor in how the magic from the stone was shaped.

When a stone was added to the cauldron while a potion was brewing in it, the magic interacting in the cauldron drew out the magic stored in the stone. It was much like what she'd done with the modified Weightless Draught, in that it was a matter of adding shaped magic instead of imbuing the potion with only raw magic, only the shaped magic came from the stone, not from her. She couldn't have accomplished the same effect with her own magic because unlike with the imbued Wingardium Leviosa spell, she didn't know how to shape it into the sort of magic that would cause permanence on the scale she needed. The stone, which was dipped in a protective potion to protect its physical form, didn't interact with the potion in any way except to release its magic into it. The type of magic released depended on the stone. Amber was not actually made of minerals from the ground, as other gemstones were, but was in fact tree sap which had fossilized over millions of years. Its magic, when included in a ritual, could lend anything from power to protection to the wizard invoking it, depending on the controlling runes involved. In a potion, however, it almost always increased the length of time the potion was effective—exponentially.

If her calculations were correct, the Polyjuice she had brewed on one pea-sized stone of amber should hold the ingredients which effected the reverse transformation in stasis for a little less than a year, thereby keeping the drinker in the transformed state for at least that long. Which was perfect, because she and Archie were going to re-do the blending spell every year and re-take the potion anyway. The only downside was that, because the potion could only be reversed by waiting for it to wear off, they would be unable to resume their original appearances immediately if the need arose. Not that she thought such a need was likely.

Probably the reason no one had done serious studies in the use of amber in Polyjuice was because so little increased the active time by so much that it was impractical for anyone who didn't want to remain transformed for months at a time. Really, who would want to be someone else for that long? The need was for a Polyjuice that worked for three, maybe four hours at a time, not three or four months.

Unless of course you were prepared to lie both explicitly and implicitly to everyone you knew for several years, in which case amber was the perfect solution to the Polyjuice problem.

She fingered the vial nervously. She had waited a good fifteen minutes for the Polyjuice she took to look like Archie for Sirius' benefit to wear off, and now she was ready to take the modified version. Once she drank it, there would be no going back for an entire year. With one last, deep breath as Harry Potter, she dropped in the blended hair she'd prepared and knocked the dose back in one gulp. Rigel Black, Hogwarts second-year, stepped out of the cubicle a few moments later, grimacing at the too-familiar taste in her mouth and moving toward the mirror to inspect her new image.

She really hadn't changed that much. Her face was perhaps a little sharper, less delicate in the minutest details. Her eyes were unequivocally grey now, the exact shade that Archie's were, though perhaps a shade lighter than the contacts she wore last year had been. They now had that indescribable sheen to them that always set the Blacks apart, though they weren't quite the silver that the Malfoys were known for. Her bottom lip was a bit thinner. Her hair, to her secret pleasure, looked significantly more manageable than she remembered it being, despite the fact that it was now grown out a bit from the close-cropped curls she'd had at the beginning of the previous year. She also felt slightly taller, but that was probably wishful thinking.

All in all, Rigel thought she looked noticeably different, but not unrecognizable. More importantly, she now looked exactly like Archie did, while still remaining a girl beneath her clothes. That meant she didn't have to worry about many of the things she'd worried about last year. She could try out for Quidditch and not worry that if she made it Sirius would want a picture of his son in his Slytherin robes. She could see people who knew her as Harry and still pretend to be Archie—as long as she didn't have to pretend for long. Most important of all, Rigel Black was now a distinctly different person, at least in appearance, from Harry Potter, and the differences would only increase as she grew older. In a couple of years it would be impossible for anyone to trace Rigel Black back to her without information that only she and Archie knew.

Rigel left the bathroom to find her friends. The train had long since started moving, so she was fairly sure she would find them all settled into the same compartment. She found them without much effort and slid open the compartment door after knocking politely.

She was met with various expressions of exasperated relief from Draco, Pansy, Millicent, and Theo, while Blaise just smirked superiorly and said, "See? I told you Rigel must be on the train. He was probably chatting with those Gryffindor cohorts of his."

Draco scowled in mild annoyance, "You went and saw those lion-hearted idiots before you came to see us?"

Rigel smiled uncomfortably, "Well, I'm here now. Good to see you all."

"And you as well, Rigel," Pansy said, "Come and sit. Tell us about your summer. You look different, did you do something new with your hair today?"

Rigel took the window seat beside Pansy and across from Draco, "If wetting it before combing counts as different, yes. As for my summer, nothing much to tell. Draco's birthday party was really the highlight of my break."

Draco grinned in a way that Rigel knew meant he'd forgiven her for being late and worrying him, "As it should be. So, excited for the new year?"

Rigel shrugged, "I suppose, though it won't really be much different from last year."

"Except for the part where we aren't the fresh meat anymore," Millicent said.

"And the part where everyone falls prey to a mysterious illness that our friend Rigel just as mysteriously cures," Theo added. He raised his brows at the mild glares and eye-rolls he got from the rest of the compartment, "I'm just saying."

"You're all forgetting the most important part of this year," Draco said grandly. The look on his face was the one he wore when he was about to say something outrageously self-important just to get a rise out of everyone else. Rigel was of the opinion that Draco thought being a Malfoy was in itself a sort of inside joke that he could play on the uninitiated. The Slytherins all knew better than to take him seriously by now, but anyone else became affronted and/or insulted by Draco's over-the-top narcissism. Their offence only seemed to fuel him.

"What's that, Draco?" Pansy asked solemnly.

"Last year Terence Higgs graduated," Draco said brightly, "Which means that this year I'm going to be starting Seeker. I expect you all to cheer with gusto."

"Don't you have to try out again?" Millicent pointed out.

"The tryouts are a formality," Draco said, "The only position that really needs filling this year is Beater. Derrick is banned from extracurriculars because his grades fell below the cutoff last semester."

"Peregrine Derrick?" Pansy asked, "I wasn't under the impression that he was particularly thick."

"He's not," Draco said, "A lot of the starters fell behind in their school work last semester, though. Flint was scheduling practices almost impossibly often, though somehow the captain still had the best grades on the team. He's inhuman."

"Beater?" Rigel said, "Will there be a lot of people trying for the position?"

Draco fixed her with hopeful eyes, "Interested? You should try out. It would be great to have you on the team, and you're an excellent flyer when you don't have a broken wrist to hide."

Rigel smiled slightly, "Maybe I will."

"All right, I'm going to stop you two before the Quidditch talk goes any further," Millicent said, "I am not about to sit here and talk sports for the next three hours."

"Seconded," Blaise said lazily, "Let's talk about something more interesting."

"Like what?" Theo said, "Politics?"

There were murmurs of interested agreement at the suggestion, and Harry smiled wryly to herself as even Draco gave an amiable assent to the change of subject. Only Slytherin produced twelve-year-olds who thought politics more interesting than Quidditch.

Then again, for the children of those witches and wizards who lived and breathed according to politics, it was a lot less like theoretical ethics and a lot more like gossip.

"Anyone else feel like there was something really big supposed to be going on this summer that…didn't?" Theo began tentatively.

The others exchanged looks of dark agreement.

"It was some sort of legislation," Millicent said, "I know that much from listening to my parents talk while they think I'm absorbed in my reading. It was supposed to be pushed through this summer, but instead it was taken off the agenda."

"Not completely, though," Pansy added, "It was tabled for revision, at least that's the official story. Unofficially I believe the party reconsidered the timing of the proposed legislation and opted to wait for fairer weather in which to introduce it."

"But what was the legislation?" Theo asked, concerned, "It must have been the SOW Party's if they decided to wait—it's no secret that Dumbledore's credibility and base of support swelled after the curing of the sickness, so I'm not surprised the Party would hesitate before making any major moves against Dumbledore's faction, but what was it going to be?"

"It's big," Millicent said, "Very big. And highly anti-muggle-blood, I believe."

"Aldon said something last semester…" Pansy trailed off, looking hesitant, "I thought he was teasing me, but this summer I caught my mother going through the books of Gold and Silver, making a list of names. Male names."

Draco frowned, but Theo just shrugged, "What's so shocking about that? I mean, all the society mothers make lists like that for their daughters at some point. I'd be more surprised if your mother didn't have one already."

Pansy bit her lip, "I would agree, except that I saw a few of the names before she folded the list away. They didn't belong to purebloods."

Blaise finally spoke up, "All of you are correct for the most part. There is very controversial legislation being cooked up by the SOW Party, and they were indeed planning to introduce it this summer. It also has a lot to do with why your mother was looking up half-blood lineages, Pansy. Part of the legislation is a Marriage Law that severely disadvantages those of muggle blood. There is more to it than that, of course, and there are revisions and additions being made to it even now, but that is the heart of the situation."

"How do you know this, Blaise?" Millicent demanded, "Even your mother wouldn't spill Party secrets to the uninitiated."

"One hears things," Blaise said vaguely, "But I'm not the only one. Rigel doesn't look surprised at all by this, does he? Grimly resigned, perhaps, but certainly not surprised."

The others turned to look at her, and Rigel winced internally at the slightly betrayed look Pansy in particular was giving her.

"You knew of this, Rigel? You knew there was going to be new marriage legislation and you didn't say anything?" the blonde girl asked, the hurt thinly masked by stiff effort.

Rigel nodded slowly, "I was aware of the possibility of such a law, yes, but I didn't tell you for several reasons. One is that I didn't expect the law to pass, particularly after the SOW Party's plans concerning the Sleeping Sickness did not exactly pan out the way they expected. Another is that the law will mean only what you want it to, for purebloods like—us." She had almost said 'like you,' but luckily caught herself in time, "There is nothing for you to worry about, Pansy. Your mother was likely just exploring all options, but the law would not require purebloods to marry halfbloods by any stretch. It is quite the opposite."

Blaise raised his eyebrows consideringly, "You are even more informed than I'd realized. I was able to glean only the bare bones of the legislation, but you speak as though you've read through a copy of it at your leisure."

Rigel shrugged uncomfortably, "This legislation will have far worse consequences for my family than it will for any of yours. I'm not saying this to make you guys uncomfortable or anything, but it's the truth. Some of the people I hold closest to me have muggle blood. Because of this, my family had a more vested interest in the proposed legislation than perhaps yours did. I didn't want to bring it up when it might make you all feel sorry for me or resent me for complaining when you yourselves had nothing to do with it."

Draco finally spoke up, "I understand that, Rigel, and I don't think any of us blame you for not wanting to talk about it, especially when it was only a possibility, not a certainty, but there is something I don't understand. You said the SOW Party had plans concerning the Sleeping Sickness. What did you mean by that?"

Rigel gazed sadly at her friend, "You already know what I mean, don't you? I could see it in your eyes when people were falling ill. You had a vague idea that the sickness wasn't accidental, didn't you?"

Draco looked away, an uncomfortable frown on his face, "I can't believe that my father, all of our fathers and mothers, would knowingly endanger their Heirs for strategic gain. Even if that's what makes sense politically, I know that my parents would never do that to me."

Pansy spoke up tentatively, "But we never were in danger, Draco. I know, I know how close it was for you, but the only reason you became so ill was because they unexpectedly switched the ingredients in the sustainment potions to something you were allergic to. Your parents would never have foreseen that, if they did in fact know about the sickness." She looked a little disturbed, "Somehow it makes too much sense. Like I always knew but never wanted to admit it to myself. Rigel, I think you're right. The SOW Party did have something to do with the sickness."

"Of course," Millicent said slowly, "Yes, because if kids fall sick, Dumbledore loses credibility, and Dumbledore's faction is what stands in the way of anti-muggle legislation. If the sickness was as benign as it was intended to be, then no harm comes to us, but the sickness can't be logically traced back to the SOW Party, because all of our parents are big supporters of it and people will assume exactly what Draco did—that parents would never endanger their Heirs. It all fits."

"Except it wasn't as benign as it was supposed to be," Draco said angrily, "You're telling me that I almost died for a piece of legislation to be passed. A piece of legislation that sounds like it has nothing to even do with us. It's just some law about halfbloods getting married, and for that we lived in constant fear for months at Hogwarts. Just pawns in some political manoeuvre that obviously wasn't well-planned out if it went so horribly wrong that the Heir to the Party's biggest supporter nearly died."

He was breathing heavily, scowling so hard none of them could meet his eyes.

Rigel spoke softly, "Someone made a mistake, Draco, but it wasn't any of us, and it wasn't really your parents, either. They weren't there, so I'm sure they didn't understand how it was when the sickness hit. I'm sure it made a lot of good sense to the Party leaders when it was proposed, if indeed any of them actually knew about it, which we're not sure they did."

"Don't act like it isn't obvious now that it's said," Draco scoffed, "You all read the interview my father gave the day I fell ill. He wasn't worried at all about me, just worried about putting the right spin on the situation."

Rigel bit her lip, wondering how long Draco had kept quiet in loyal denial about these thoughts.

"Exactly, Draco," Pansy said, "He wasn't worried because he knew the sickness wasn't going to harm you, not because he didn't care. When he realized the danger to you, didn't he and your mother come to Hogwarts immediately? Didn't they stay there for days under Quarantine?"

"They were really scared for you, Draco," Rigel added truthfully, "Your father nearly killed me when he realized who had been brewing the potions that caused your allergy. He didn't sleep, and he barely ate a thing. He moved mountains to get Snape home ahead of schedule just on the off chance that the Professor might be able to save you. Don't blame your father for this, Dray. It truly was an accident."

"And you didn't die," Theo put in, "Rigel saved you. I guess that means that you're the reason this legislation was tabled, doesn't it, Rigel? Since you cured the sickness and then turned around to give the credit to Dumbledore, thereby restoring his political clout."

Rigel fidgeted under the others' scrutiny, "I suppose in a round-about way that's true."

Pansy just shook her head, "So you've known at least since you cured the sickness that it was a political move. I did wonder why you made it sound like Snape and Dumbledore had done all the work when anyone asked." She considered Rigel seriously, "We might make a decent politician of you, yet."

"Except he's playing for the wrong side," Millicent pointed out, "I mean, shouldn't we be upset that Rigel foiled the Party's plans? He basically made it so that we all fell sick for nothing."

Draco and Pansy glared at Millicent, but the dark-haired girl just shrugged, "I'm not saying I'm not grateful to Rigel for saving Draco, I'm just pointing out the political technicalities of the suggestion."

"Because the sickness went so wrong, not even the Party can truly blame Rigel for curing it and setting back their plans," Blaise said thoughtfully, "It would be far worse if the Malfoy scion had died, even if it did get the legislation passed. The Party would lose a lot of support if the reason for the sickness got out, as it surely would if the Malfoys turned on the Party in their justified grief and anger."

"Well, as mercilessly as Blaise just phrased that, it sounds about right," Theo said, "And I for one can't blame Rigel for working against the Party's political agenda if the legislation means bad news for his family. I mean, even the biggest Party supporters understand that family comes before politics and even House loyalties."

The others agreed with various degrees of vehemence, and after that the conversation drifted to other things. All of them were aware of the tentative balance they had achieved, though. They had never brought it up, but Rigel knew her friends had always wondered just who she was loyal to, despite having said repeatedly that she had no interest in politics. As it was now abundantly clear that Rigel both understood and even actively influenced politics when it became necessary, it was much harder for them to act as though she was no different than the rest of them. Thankfully, they were too polite to voice any disdain or disgruntlement concerning Rigel's conflicting loyalties. She wasn't sure, however, how long such a situation could last in the face of the ever-thickening political soup that was seeping into their lives as they grew older.

When their true loyalties were eventually called upon, could any of them really remain her friends?

That was a thought for the future, however, so she ignored it. She didn't want to worry about politics just then. Instead, Rigel made a promise to herself that she would not get caught up in anything serious or complicated that year. She wanted to focus on enjoying the friendships she'd formed but neglected the previous year, and on furthering her studies and extracurriculars. This year she wouldn't distance herself from her housemates. She would get to know them in truth, rather than in passing. Rigel told herself she wasn't going to care about anything that happened outside of Hogwarts until June. She would concentrate on her studies and her friends, and actually enjoy herself.

After all, what was the point of risking her very soul for her dream if she didn't even stop to appreciate the fruits of her labour? She was at Hogwarts, for Merlin's sake. She, a halfblood, was attending Hogwarts and studying under Professor Snape, the greatest Potion Master that ever lived. Politics could wait. She had good friends and a great opportunity to learn, and she was not going to waste either one.

Their group got off of the train and, instead of following Hagrid, set off toward the carriages for the first time. Rigel had caught glimpses of the carriages the previous year, as they were the same ones used to ferry the third years to Hogsmeade, and so could be seen coming and going from the grounds every other month or so. There was something different about them, though, and Rigel couldn't put her finger on what it was until she realized with a horrified jolt that the last time she'd seen these carriages they had been pulling themselves.

Now, however, great black horses with soulless white eyes and wide, leathery wings stood restlessly before the carriages. The horses were thin to the point of unnaturalness, and their heads were shaped more like a small dragon's, long and pointy, than any horse she'd ever seen.

"What are those?" Rigel blurted, stunned into voicing her thoughts abruptly. She got a feeling of unease about the creatures, which only intensified when one of them turned its glittery, white eyes on her and seemed to sniff the air in her direction with interest. She was pretty sure she caught a glimpse of fang, as well.

"What are what?" Pansy said absently, scanning the queue around them and smiling politely at people she knew.

"Those horses pulling the carriages," Rigel said, "They weren't there last year, were they?"

Pansy looked toward the carriages, then back toward Rigel, then back to the carriages, before shaking her head, "There's nothing pulling the carriages, Rigel."

Rigel blinked, then frowned, "You can't see them?"

"Of course she can't," Theo spoke up from behind Rigel, "None of them can, Rigel."

Rigel turned to Theo, who looked upon the skeletal horses with an expression of great distaste. "What do you mean?" she asked, "You can see them, can't you?"

"Yes," Theo said shortly, "I can."

"What are you two talking about?" Draco scowled, looking between them and the carriages with frustrated confusion, "They're horseless carriages."

"No, they aren't," a voice spoke from behind them. It was Aldon Rosier, and his expression was unusually serious, "Those beasts are called thestrals, Black. You aren't imagining them, most people just can't see them."

Edmund Rookwood, who was standing behind Rosier beside a blank-faced Alesana Selwyn, nodded his head in agreement, adding, "A fact they should be thankful for."

Rigel narrowed her eyes, "But why—"

"Come on, Aldon," Rookwood interrupted her, "Let's get inside."

The three of them went to climb into a carriage, and Rigel, suddenly possessed with a fierce curiosity, started after them.

"See you at the feast," she said quickly to her friends, before jogging over to jump into the carriage with Rosier, Rookwood, and Selwyn.

The upperclassmen looked at her with raised eyebrows and expectant expressions. Rigel flushed slightly at her own rudeness, but she had to know.

"Why can only Theo and I see the—the thestrals?" she asked.

Selwyn frowned and opened her mouth, but Rookwood put a hand on her shoulder repressively. "There's no use trying to protect the boy if he can already see them," Rookwood pointed out in his deep, mountain-voice.

"Then why didn't you just tell me?" Rigel asked, trying not to sound petulant.

"Pansy didn't need to hear," Rosier said, gazing at Rigel with an emotion that was hard to unravel. It was something like interest, but tempered with a solemn sort of pity, "She worries about her friends too much. It would only upset her."

Rigel was becoming more and more uneasy the longer they hinted and prevaricated, "Are you going to tell me why, or just make vague generalities until I look it up myself?"

"It's death, okay?" Selwyn snapped, her kohl-rimmed eyes roiling with suppressed emotion, "You can't see a thestral unless you've witnessed death."

"And accepted it," Rookwood said. His voice was sad, but his sharp, half-lidded gaze was directed at Selwyn, not at Rigel. The dark-haired beauty didn't seem to notice as she turned her face to the window and stared, unseeing, across the dark grounds. Rigel felt that she had upset the older girl, but also felt that it would make things worse to try and apologize when she had no idea what Selwyn had gone through to make her sensitive to death.

Rigel herself was taken aback by the idea of a creature that one could only see after being basically traumatized in some way, but she was suddenly grateful that most of her friends couldn't see the thestrals as well. It made her sad for Theo, who was obviously bitter about whatever death he'd seen. She recalled that his mother had died when he was younger, and hoped fervently that that hadn't been the death he experienced. Rigel then remembered that while she had not been there for Aunt Diana's last moments, Archie had, and wondered if he would be able to see the thestrals, too.

"Black," Rosier's voice called her back to the present. She turned to look at him, and was surprised to see the fifth-year almost…hesitate, "Would it be correct to assume that you were unable to see the thestrals last year?"

Rigel nodded, suddenly reminded of her own brush with death over the summer. A man, running through an alley. Blue vest. Blood, so much blood, and a knife that gleamed in the light of a blazing—no. She shook her head slightly, banishing the images. Yes, she had seen a man die. She understood that, accepted it even, but she didn't have to relive it. She had moved past the terror and numb horror of that night. She was training with Remus, and even more on her own, growing faster and stronger so that nothing like that would happen before her eyes again. Never again would she be a witness to death without actively seeking to prevent it.

"Our condolences, Black," Rookwood said softly, finally looking away from Selwyn, who was ignoring the conversation.

"Thanks," Rigel said absently, "What? Oh, no, it wasn't anyone I knew personally. I mean, I just happened to…see it." Blood. Smoke. Fire. Wand. Knife. Rigel blinked hard to dismiss the images that for some reason just would not leave her mind. She obviously hadn't tucked them away securely enough in her mindscape if they flashed across her eyes without her summoning them.

Rosier's gaze sharpened and the interest seemed to win out over what Rigel now recognized as sympathy—or perhaps it really was just pity. "You just happened to see the death of a complete stranger? Do you volunteer at St. Mungo's with your father?"

"No," Rigel said, "It was just an accident. I was out running errands and it just sort of…happened." She was quiet for a moment, then said, "So, can you all…sorry, that was insensitive."

"I cannot," Rosier said, "Though Edmund and Alice can."

Rigel wondered who Rosier was talking about until she realized that Alice was a nickname for Alesana. The tension in the carriage seemed to go up another notch and Rigel shifted uncomfortably.

"Let's talk about something else," Rookwood said firmly. Rosier shrugged, and Rigel nodded her agreement.

"Actually, I was going to speak with the two of you about something anyway," Rigel said.

"What about?" Rosier asked with polite interest.

"Pansy's birthday," Rigel said, "Last year we weren't good enough friends to celebrate it, but it's September sixth, isn't it?"

"It is," Rosier said, narrowing his eyes ever so slightly, "What are you planning?"

Rigel grinned slightly, "I'll tell you, but I need your help."

"Doing what?" Rookwood asked.

"Distracting Pansy," Rigel said.

"A surprise," Rosier said, his honey-gold eyes glinting, "Count us in, Black."

Soon the carriage came to a stop and she disembarked, keeping her eyes away from the grim, black thestrals as she went to join her friends, who were climbing out of the carriage behind hers.

They all filed into the Great Hall and took their seats. Last year's sixth years were now in the coveted seats at the end of the table closest to the doors. The seventh years traditionally got to sit furthest from the teachers' table with the sixth years next to them, then fifth, and so on. Rigel and her friends were in the lowest occupied portion of the table, but of course one-seventh of the table on the end closest to the Head Table was empty now, reserved for the new Slytherins that would be sorted before the night was out.

They waited quite a while for the first-years, and Rigel supposed it took much longer to take the boats across the lake than to ride in the carriages. Eventually, however, McGonagall went to fetch the new first-years and the Sorting Hat was revealed.

Rigel could have sworn she saw the hat smirk before it began its song.

"Every year begins this way

With faces old and new

And first-years filing in the hall

And standing in a queue

Most of you look scared to death

As you await your turn

I promise it won't hurt much but

There's something you will learn

You see it is my job to tell you

Where you ought to be

And look inside your mind and judge

Your heart on what I see

Now here's the part where I explain

What different Houses mean

This knowledge gives you some idea

Toward which House you should lean

But sometimes hats get bored you know

And sometimes they get tired

Of singing self-same songs to you

And so I got inspired

To really shake things up a bit

And have a little fun

And tell you all a story of

A song that wasn't sung

For once there was a wizard kid

Who walked through that same door

He listened as I told him of

The mighty founding four

He got it in his head that one

House stood above the rest

And when he put me on his head

He thought that he knew best

And though I told him otherwise

He stubbornly resisted

And did not go where he belonged

Despite what I'd insisted

And though this boy obtained his wish

His needs were never met

He spent his school life looking back

On that day with regret

If only he had listened when

He heard his destiny

He spent his years in shackles when

He could have been set free

This year you won't find differences

Of Houses in my song

You'll come to me unbiased

And you'll go where you belong

So please forget the things you've heard

Or what your friends might do

The most important thing is finding

What is right for you."

There was a moment or two of incredulous silence before applause slowly started up from the students around the hall. Even a few of the professors looked entirely bemused by the hat's song, but the sorting proceeded nonetheless.

Rigel thought it was a bit optimistic for the hat to think that not going over the stereotypes just before the sorting began was going to help much, especially considering that all of the students were purebloods, and had no doubt been hearing of the four Hogwarts Houses for years. Still, she supposed a talking hat was entitled to its eccentricities, and it did have a good point. There was a lot of bias embodied in the House system—not just in what each House represented, but in who went to each House. Weasleys went to Gryffindor, Macmillans went to Hufflepuff, Malfoys went to Slytherin, and the Turpins went to Ravenclaw. It was one of those universal truths that only changed when people like Sirius Black rocked the boat. Then again, Rigel thought, as a Slytherin who was also technically a Potter, it's not as though she had room to talk about upsetting natural orders.

The newest Slytherins sat stiffly to Rigel's left. She glanced over during Dumbledore's speech to take in the new faces and saw a couple of first-year boys with dark hair sending quick looks up the Slytherin table. The boys were remarkably similar looking, though Rigel didn't recall them having the same last name. They'd look over at the upperclassmen, then look quickly away again, heads bent together, whispering quietly, then look at a different section of upperclassmen. Rigel raised a brow at the two of them when they happened to look her way, but instead of flinching or blushing at being caught they both grinned at her with identical mischievous winks. Rigel felt a shiver run down her spine and fervently began hoping those two never met the Weasley twins.

The feast itself was glorious. Rigel stuck to meatless dishes for posterity—she was planning on sneaking into the kitchens in the early mornings to get her major proteins in. Everything was moving along smoothly until Adrian Pucey cursed loudly from a little further up the table. It wasn't loud enough to carry to the other tables, and certainly not the Head table, but it was noticeable enough above the chatter that every Slytherin within ten seats of Pucey turned to stare at him. No one could accuse Slytherins of being overly concerned about other people's sensibilities, but rarely would one be so crass as to curse out loud over a dinner table for no apparent reason.

Pucey didn't even seem to notice the attention he was garnering. He had his neck bent looking at something in his lap, and he seemed from where Rigel was sitting to have both hands in his lap as well, as though he were struggling with something. Many of the girls gave disapproving murmurs and averted their eyes, but Rigel seriously doubted Pucey was doing whatever they thought he was in the Great Hall. Most seemed content to watch Pucey mutter and curse to himself, though Lucian Bole, who was sitting next to him, finally hauled Adrian's shoulder back so he could see just what exactly his friend was doing. A second later, Bole reared back, knocking against the person on his other side and nearly spilling his pumpkin juice everywhere. His eyes were wide and his lips were pressed tight together with muted shock.

"Shit, Lucian!" Pucey threw his friend a glare, "You startled it! Oh, crud."

A flash of panic flew across Pucey's face before he froze and looked up. His gaze moved from one Slytherin to the next and he swallowed heavily, "Um, nobody move, okay?"

The other Slytherins within hearing became instantly motionless.

"What have you done, Pucey?" a boy Rigel recognized as Miles Bletchley narrowed his eyes at Pucey from his seat across the table.

"It's a snake," Bole snapped, glaring at Pucey, "Adrian's got a snake and he's lost it."

"Adrian, what the hell?" A fourth-year girl with long, blonde hair said. Everyone was speaking as softly as they could and trying not to glance at the Head table. They might think Pucey was an idiot, but no one was going to get him in trouble on purpose.

"Just don't move, okay?" Pucey said, "Spread the word to everyone at the table to stay very still. It's under the table, and we don't want to startle it."

Surreptitiously, each Slytherin student turned to his or her neighbour and explained the situation. Rigel passed it along to Draco, though both of them had been paying attention from the start, and Draco explained it quietly to the first year on the other side of him. The eleven-year-old girl had a pair of long, dark pigtails that quivered slightly when she stilled.

"Is it poisonous?" the first year whispered back.

That, Rigel thought, was a very good question. Just then, Pansy, who was sitting on Rigel's right side, closer to Pucey, stiffened in her seat. She let out the barest hint of a squeak, then said, in a very calm and quiet voice, "It's on my foot."

Pucey looked over from where he was sitting, "You feel it, Pansy?"

Pansy nodded slowly, "It's moving across my shoe now, headed toward you, Rigel."

Rigel nodded her acceptance. She was used to snakes, thanks to Sirius' little collection of them at Archie's house, so she was prepared when she felt the first flicks of a questing tongue against her ankle, which was bared by the way her robes rode up a bit when she sat.

"Yes, I can feel it now," Rigel said evenly. She kept her face blank and slowly slid her hand under the table.

"Don't, Rigel," Draco frowned, but didn't make any sudden moves, "You don't know if it will bite or not."

By the worried and uneasy look on Pucey's face, Rigel would say the odds of avoiding being bitten weren't good—at least for anyone else.

She felt the snake wrap itself around her ankle and then slide higher. Rigel put her palm beside her knee and waited. Sure enough, she soon felt a small tongue flicking against her palm, testing her scent. Rigel slid down in her seat slowly, very slowly, and bent sideways at the waist so that she could stick her head under the tablecloth. It was dark, but with the sounds of the feast muffled slightly she could now clearly hear the hissing coming from the snake, which was coiled quite firmly around her right leg now.

"Too many ssoftlingss," the snake complained, "Too many ssmellss…hungry…tired…sso cold…"

"Come here," Rigel hissed as quietly as she could, though of course Parseltongue was already a very quiet language.

The snake stilled, then shifted higher on her leg, "Sspeaker?"

"Yess," Rigel said, "Come here, pleasse. I will feed you, and then you can ssleep."

"Food?" The snake wound its head around Rigel's hand and loosened its hold on her calf a bit, "Promisse me, sspeaker. Promisse me food."

"I sswear it," Rigel said, "But you musst come now, and wind about my wrisst. If you bite me or the other humanss, you will get no micce."

"Agreed, sspeaker," the snake wound its way quickly from her leg to her wrist. Rigel used her other hand to cover the snake with her robe sleeve before re-emerging from the table slowly. She brought her right hand, with the small, black snake hidden around her wrist, into her lap, using her left hand to pick up her goblet and take a sip as though nothing had happened.

"Rigel, where's the snake?" Draco asked quietly.

Rigel glanced pointedly at her lap, and Draco inhaled sharply.

"You are such an idiot," her friend muttered, "What if it poisons you?"

"You're just upset because Black handled it while you were too scared to," Daphne Greengrass said snidely from diagonally across the table.

"I am not afraid of snakes," Draco said, "I just don't like surprises."

Rigel ignored them. "Tell Pucey I'll give it back in the common room," she told Pansy. Pansy nodded tightly and turned to relay the message down the table.

Rigel was the recipient of many apprehensive glances for the duration of the feast. Dumbledore introduced the new Defence Against the Dark Arts Professor, who was smiling awfully brightly considering the track record of his predecessors. She was trying to ignore the snake's disgruntled complaints about sitting still and staying hidden, as well as its demands for her to speak with it. Instead she ran a soothing hand down the snake's coils every now and then and when the feast was over she slipped away as quickly as she could and headed to the kitchens to beg a mouse from Binny.

The cheerful elf was very accommodating, even giving Rigel a bag of stunned mice for the road. Rigel promised to stop by and see the elf before breakfast the next day, and then left to head back toward the common room.

She arrived just as the first-years were being led through the portrait hole by Selwyn, who was head girl that year. Rigel followed the new Slytherins into the common room and was momentarily surprised to see all the Slytherins still sitting or standing about the large, low-ceilinged space. Then she remembered that Snape would be coming in to give his start of term speech, and that the only reason he hadn't the previous year was because something had 'come up.'

Rigel spotted Pucey arguing quietly with a few other upperclassmen near one of the fireplaces and went over to them.

"—Can't believe you would be so idiotic, Adrian," Bole was saying quietly, "Bringing that to the table—what were you going to do with it?"

"Nothing," Adrian defended, "I just didn't want to leave him with the baggage. He was a gift from my uncle, and I'm supposed to take care of him."

"We're not even supposed to have snakes," Bletchley snapped.

"I didn't think anyone would find out," Adrian said, "I was just gonna keep him in the dorms, but as soon as we got into the Great Hall he started freaking out on me. Wouldn't stay in my pocket."

"You'd better hope Snape didn't see anything from the Head table," Bole said lowly, "If Black hadn't taken care of it—"

"Eh-hem," Rigel coughed pointedly and tilted her head to the side in a way that she knew made her look especially innocent.

"Black!" Pucey rubbed the back of his head awkwardly, "Listen, I'm really sorry about—"

"I have your snake," Rigel said, holding out her right wrist and peeling back her sleeve, "He's had a mouse just now, and he's warmed up a bit, but I think he's very tired, so it would probably be a good idea to put him up in your room for now, and feed him one of these mice," Harry pulled out the bag and handed it to him, "When he wakes up."

"Uh, thanks," Pucey said, accepting the snake from Rigel's wrist gently, and tucking the mice away into his robes, "I'd best do it before Snape gets here, then."

Rigel nodded, and turned away to find the other second years. They asked her a lot of questions, but Rigel gave the standard answer that her father kept snakes as pets, so she had a lot of experience with them.

Ten minutes later, Snape made his entrance. Rigel was momentarily frozen as her mind raced back to that night just one year ago, when she had first laid eyes on the greatest Potion Master of their time. She had thought him the truest embodiment of genius and authority. Now…well, he was certainly a genius, and he still exuded the kind of authority that seasoned Aurors could only dream of, but Rigel felt as though she didn't look at him with nearly the same amount of starry-eyed idolization as she had last year.

She had worked with Snape now. Learned from him. She had seen him darkly amused whenever Ron Weasley answered a question incorrectly. She had seen the lines of tension in his forehead after brewing for hours on end to stock the Hospital Wing during the Sleeping Sickness. She had seen his triumphant smirk when Slytherin won a Quidditch game, and his stiff relief when Draco awoke from his coma. Snape was everything she'd ever imagined him to be—snarky, competent, brilliant and cold—but he was so much more human than she'd anticipated, as foolish as that sounded.

Snape gave his customary speech, and told Selwyn to show the first-years their dormitories. Then he turned to the rest of them and scowled darkly, adding, "I don't know what was going on at the dinner table during the feast tonight, and I don't want to know. Suffice to say that none of you are as subtle as you think yourselves, and I trust it does not happen again."

The Slytherins all murmured various versions of, "Yes, sir." After that, they were free to go to their dorm rooms. Rigel followed the other second-years down their hallway, but was taken aback to see Blaise continue right past the dorm he'd lived in last year and turn into hers. She exchanged a bewildered look with Draco, but when they reached the door to their room it became rather obvious. Where once it had read: Arcturus Black, Draco Malfoy, and Theodore Nott, Blaise Zabini was now tacked on underneath.

When they entered the dorm room, several changes were immediately apparent. It was significantly bigger, for one thing, and on the left side of the dorm there was an extra bed between Rigel's and Theo's, with Zabini's trunk sitting at the foot. An extra wardrobe had appeared along the wardrobe wall, and an extra desk was sitting to the right side of the room as well.

Theo turned to smile incredulously at Blaise, "You're in here with us, now? Why didn't you say anything?"

"Surprise," Blaise said mildly, "Yes, I requested the switch at the end of last year. Sorry about the inconvenience, though I did argue that if Snape agreed to my request he should add a second bathroom to this dorm, since the girls and now Crabbe and Goyle only have to share in twos."

Sure enough, when Rigel looked over there were two doors where previously there had only been one bathroom door. Rigel shrugged and headed over to her trunk to find her toothbrush, "I don't mind."

"I definitely don't," Theo said, grinning, "It's so boring in here with just those two. Rigel's almost never here except to sleep, and Draco just studies or writes letters to his parents when he's in here."

Blaise glanced at Rigel with an expression she couldn't decipher, then turned to Draco and said, "And you? Are you all right with the change?"

"I wouldn't wish Crabbe and Goyle on anyone," Draco said, "Welcome to our dorm."

"Thank you," Blaise's smile was very wolf-like, but perhaps he couldn't help it.

Rigel cleaned her teeth and kicked off her shoes before climbing into bed. She didn't bother with the hangings, as it would be better logistically if she had a clear view of the room in case something happened in the middle of the night. She had been thinking more and more in terms of strategic safety since the night of the fire, and was now in the habit of sleeping with her wand under her pillow, rather than on her bedside table or even in her trunk.

A few minutes later, Draco called irritably, "Aren't you going to douse that light, Blaise?"

Blaise answered back slowly, "I am, I was just waiting for Rigel to change so he doesn't have to in the dark."

"Oh, Rigel sleeps in his robes," Theo said from his bed, "You can just douse it."

"In his clothes?" Blaise's voice was clearly incredulous, "Why?"

"Well," Theo said slowly, "I guess I've never thought about it. He's always done that, since the first night last year."

"Still here," Rigel said mildly, mentally groaning. Of course Blaise would think it strange. When she first got here, Draco and Theo hadn't been well enough acquainted with her to comment on all the strange things she did, like sleep in her clothes or change in the bathroom after her shower, and once they'd become friends they were used to it. Blaise, however, now had the unfortunate position of being both new to her habits and good enough friends with her to question them. Joy.

"Well, why do you sleep in your clothes?" Draco asked suddenly, "I can't believe we never asked you this before."

"Nott asked me if I owned nightclothes once, I think," Rigel said thoughtfully, "But after that you just let it drop."

"Oh," Draco said, "No—wait, you still haven't answered the question!"

Rigel shifted uncomfortably, "It's in case there's an emergency in the middle of the night. I'd feel more prepared to deal with it if I had my robes on and wasn't hampered by bedclothes." Originally, that was even sort of true, though she had been expecting her dorm mates to prank her for being the son of a blood traitor. Now, she trusted her dorm mates, and was more concerned with intruders. Then, of course, there was the fact that she felt significantly more vulnerable as a female in her nightclothes than she did in her form-hiding robes.

"Wow, Rigel," Theo said, "You're really paranoid."

"As he should be," Draco said, "Considering how much trouble he attracts. He did have someone trying to attack him all of first semester last year."

"Yet he began sleeping in his clothes before all the trouble even started," Blaise said, "Interesting."

"Not really," Rigel said shortly, "Could you put out the light, now? We should get some sleep."

Blaise chuckled softly, but he put out the light nonetheless.

The next morning, Rigel woke much earlier than her roommates. She quietly grabbed the drawstring pouch she kept her workout clothes in from her trunk and crept out of the dark room and into the quiet common room. Part of the exercise regimen Remus had her on involved a long run every morning before breakfast, and Rigel fully intended to keep up with his prescriptions while at school.

She changed in a bathroom on the ground floor, near the Great Hall, and strapped on her leg weights. Her workout clothes were more comfortable than her robes, and lighter, too, but still baggy enough that her burgeoning figure—which was admittedly non-existent at this point, but might be of worry in a year or so—remained indiscernible. Rigel stowed her bag, which now held her school robes, in an alcove by the front entrance to grab when she finished, and slipped out of the castle doors.

The lake was choppy from the brisk morning wind, and the sound of the small waves beating against the shore helped to block out everything around her as she began her run. She decided to try running all the way around the lake once, and then see how tired she was. Running, Rigel found, was a lot like meditating. It cleared the mind and made your breathing sound much louder than normal. It was also good for thinking, and one of the things Remus had warned her of was that it was nearly impossible to defend yourself without knowing yourself. If you couldn't understand yourself, how could you understand your enemy? He made it very clear that her greatest flaw at the moment was her tendency to bury things.

If something bothered her on a conscious level, she didn't think about it. She pretended nothing upset her, and by doing this never came to terms with events in her life that should have changed her. Instead, she accepted things that happened to her, let them sink into her mind, then helped them sink further, until they lay so hidden beneath the surface of her consciousness that they didn't bother her.

Rigel accepted that Remus was right in this case, but didn't really see what was wrong with that. After all, once you acknowledge that something happened, you can forget about it and move on with—no. She was doing it again. Remus had warned her how hard it was to change yourself. He had predicted that her mental patterns would reassert themselves wherever possible. She was not supposed to give in to that. She was supposed to let her life experiences change her, instead of treating them like an interesting fact she'd read about, or a story she'd heard about someone else.

She ran faster, frustrated with her lack of progress mentally. Remus said he would teach her basic self-defence without a wand, but that he wouldn't teach her proper dueling until she had the correct mind frame to handle the instruction.

Rigel supposed it was a bit like what Professor Snape had pointed out when he diagnosed the problem with her magic last year. When she first performed accidental magic, she had either been frightened, or she had received negative feedback about it, and as a result Rigel had developed hyper-control of her unconscious magical output, to the point that later on she couldn't even use her magic consciously without great effort. Rigel had eventually come to a compromise with her magic. She asked it nicely to do what she wanted, and it didn't try to escape her control at inopportune times via the outlet of her phoenix wand, which seemed to side with her magic more often than it did with her prior to the unspoken agreement. Still, Rigel couldn't control her magic like her peers did. They demanded their magic obey them, and if their willpower was strong enough for the spell they were attempting, it worked. Rigel had to coax her magic to work with her, and while the system worked well, she was yet unable to relax her unconscious controls on her magic.

She didn't leak magic like most wizards did, according to Snape and Riddle. She also couldn't imbue potions unconsciously. Snape accepted it as simply a fact about her level of magical control, but deep down, in a part of her mind Rigel didn't like to focus on, she knew it for what it was. A symbol of her fear. She was afraid, on a subconscious level, to release her tight hold over her magic. On the surface, they were in sync, but underneath Rigel still couldn't trust her magic not to…what? Hurt anyone? As Archie had pointed out, her magic had never actually hurt anyone. It had blown things up, whirled them around in the air, even disintegrated things when she got really upset as a child, but through all that it had never injured someone she cared about.

Perhaps it was the fact that the potential for destruction was there that made her tamp down on her magic. It was the idea that one day it could hurt someone that she didn't trust. No, Rigel shook her head as her feet pounded on the grass, that wasn't true. It wasn't her magic that Rigel didn't trust.

It was herself.

The magic only responded to Rigel's will, although sometimes that will hadn't reached the point of intent yet. What she feared was that the more she relaxed her control, the more sensitive that response would become. What if, once she freed it, the magic started responding to her vague inclinations? To her whims? What if one day it acted in response to a thought? All it would take is one unkind, frustrated thought, and someone around her would get hurt. And it would be her fault, not the magic's, for having that thought. She would never consciously will harm to another person—she didn't think—but what if for one instant she had a weak desire and her magic chose to act upon it? She couldn't take that risk. Not when the year before her magic had already shown itself to be capable of acting without her express intent. How many things had it blown up in Quirrell's classroom, just because his constant picking annoyed her?

So she acknowledged that she had too tight of a hold over her magic, but she wasn't going to do anything to change it.

Only, wasn't that the same thing Remus had warned her about? Mentally she was in a similar habit. She started ignoring things she didn't want to think about young. Like when her father had rolled his eyes at her Potions magazines and bought her a broomstick. Then again when he presented her with the Snitch and frowned when she pointed to the Bludgers. Like when her mother uncomfortably changed the subject when Rigel asked her what she knew about Severus Snape. Little disappointments and uncomfortable truths all got stored away safely in a place where she didn't have to think about them. After all, she didn't want to be frustrated with her mother, or feel like a letdown to her father. Since she didn't want to feel that way, why should she? Emotions were natural responses to environmental stimuli, and if she didn't want to feel a certain way, she simply had to ignore the experiences that might prompt a certain emotional response.

It was easy, and it was familiar, but according to Remus it was going to hold her back. Because ignoring events, he said, didn't help you come to terms with them. You had to accept that the event happened, yes, but that wasn't enough. You then had to allow that event to change you to shape you into something new, though for better or for worse was up to you.

Rigel understood, sort of. The night of the fire, for instance, had been the kind of event that deeply affected a person. She had first broken down a bit, but then after crying on Mrs. Hurst she'd accepted it. Next, Rigel had used the event as fuel and impetus for changing herself for the better. She had started learning to protect herself and others around her. Then, once the experience's usefulness to her was past, she ignored it. Apparently, however, ignoring was not enough. And using it as a springboard for personal change was not enough. Rigel was missing something, some step in the process, but she couldn't figure out what it was.

She finished her lap and doubled over, panting, by the shore. She was dripping with sweat, and her legs were shaking quite a bit. She knew that Remus could have run around that lake four times without stopping, but she felt accomplished with her paltry one lap all the same. After a few more minutes' rest, she began the strengthening and flexibility exercises that she was still convinced were some sort of torture regimen.

There were the usual push-ups and sit-ups, and then there were all sorts of convoluted stretches that she hoped no one ever saw her doing. After that she had to start on her weights. She removed the weighted balls from her pockets, where Remus-the-sadist had bade her to keep them while she ran, as if the leg weights weren't enough, and began lifting, curling, squeezing, and otherwise punishing her arm muscles for being weak and girly.

When she had practised her basic punches and kicks until she thought Remus could not possibly fault her for stopping, Rigel jogged back up to the castle and retrieved her bag from the alcove before making a bee-line down to the kitchens.

When she entered, the house elves seemed to be just starting their preparations for breakfast, and Rigel realized she must have woken earlier than she thought. She really ought to get a watch or something. Archie's was fine and well for special occasions, but as a 'pureblood' Heir, she should have one all the time.

"Binny!" she called over the noise of plates and silverware being set out.

A house elf with a necklace of champagne corks and a pretty pink tea cozy separated herself from the throng.

"Young sir," Binny curtsied and then bounced happily on her toes, smiling up at Rigel, "You came!"

"I promised, didn't I?" Rigel smiled back, "So do you have time to talk?"

"Well, Binny is working…" Binny hesitated, "Is you needing something that Binny can be doing while we is chatting?"

"Um, sure," Rigel thought quickly, "Could you sit with me while cutting up some meat for me to eat?"

Binny's eyes widened, "You is eating meat now?"

"I'm going to try to eat more meat this year, but I don't want to eat it at the table," Rigel said carefully, "So I was wondering if you could keep sending vegetarian stuff upstairs, but if I could come down here in the mornings to get some meat as well?"

The house elf nodded seriously, "Binny can do that. What kind of meat is you liking?"

"I'm not sure," Harry wrinkled her nose, "Maybe chicken?"

Binny gave her a very unimpressed look, "I is making you lots of meat, and you is trying them all."

Rigel grimaced, but agreed. Binny bustled about picking up different pre-cooked meats and things, then perched herself with a cutting board and several bowls of seasoning.

"So how was your summer, Binny?" Rigel asked, "I mean, what do you guys do all summer?"

Binny glanced amusedly at Rigel over the large knife she was wielding, "I is working over the summer, of course."

"At Hogwarts?" Rigel asked curiously, "I'd have thought there wasn't much to do."

"There isn't being much," Binny agreed, "The oldest elves is staying at Hogwarts, but the rest of us is finding work elsewhere. Binny is working at the unicorn stables on Madame Touraine's estate."

"Really?" Rigel asked curiously, "Is that in France?"

"Yes," Binny nodded enthusiastically, "It is beautiful there. I is liking the unicorns very much. If we is finishing work quickly, Madame Touraine is letting the elves play with the baby unicorns until they is going to sleep." Binny gave a dreamy sigh, "I is liking work at the stables almost as much as I is liking Hogwarts."

"Do you speak French, then?" Rigel asked.

"Oh yes," Binny nodded quickly, "French is being very fun to speak."

Rigel smiled, "What other languages can you speak?"

"All kinds," Binny shrugged, "A house elf is never knowing who is needing them to work."

"That's so cool," Rigel said, a bit wistfully, "Was it hard to learn?"

"Not so very hard," Binny said earnestly, "It is being easier than flying."

"What?" Rigel said, smiling in amusement.

"It is being a house elf saying," Binny said, "When things is seeming hard, we is thinking they is not as hard as flying, and they is seeming better."

Rigel laughed, "If only everyone saw life that way."

"Maybe I is teaching you?" Binny suggested slyly.

"To be more optimistic?" Rigel blinked, "I guess it couldn't hurt."

Binny giggled and shook her head, "No, no. French. Maybe I is teaching you French, if you is so interested in languages."

Rigel was about to decline politely, figuring she had enough on her plate, but then she paused. It would lend credibility to the back-up story that she was a poor pureblood from the continent if she knew a European language or two.

"Won't it interfere with your free time?" Rigel said tentatively.

Binny beamed, "Yes, exactly."

Right. House elf. Rigel smiled a bit ruefully. She was definitely going to find Binny a selfish hobby one of these days. "Well, if you're sure you want to," Rigel said, "I would love to learn French. How about…hmm, no we won't have enough time in the mornings, and you have to work anyway…evening is no good, either. I've got too much work to do, and I might be brewing with Snape…say, Binny, do you work during lunch?"

"Binny is making lunch," Binny said.

"I mean, after it's made. Do you work during lunch?" Rigel asked.

"No, Binny is eating during lunch," Binny said with a smile, "And young sir is eating, too."

"Why don't we eat together?" Rigel asked, "I'll get a book on French from the library, and learn it in my free time. Then over lunch you and I can chat in French."

"And Binny can mercilessly correct young sir's pronunciation!" Binny squealed happily, then leaned forward and said, in a very serious tone of voice, "It is being the only way to really learn."

Rigel raised her eyebrows, "Whatever you say, Professor Binny."

Binny looked momentarily horrified by the address, before she collapsed into giggles once more, "Five points to Slytherin! Oh, this is being fun."

Rigel stayed for a while longer. She tried the various meats that Binny presented her with, finally deciding that chicken was the closest to fish, and therefore the one she liked best. She could stomach a little steak and pork, but she would definitely be sticking to birds and other white meats if she could. She said goodbye to Binny when it seemed that breakfast was almost ready and headed back to the common room to shower and change into a clean set of school robes.

When she entered her dorm room, it was to the sound of raised voices. Well, one raised voice.

"What do you mean you don't know?" That was definitely Draco, "You were awake first."

"And he was long gone by the time I was," Blaise's voice sounded bored and annoyed, "He's probably in the library."

"It's the first day of school! We have nothing to be in the library for," Draco said.

"Who are you looking for?" Rigel finally spoke up. Blaise and Draco turned to the door and while Draco brightened visibly, Blaise rolled his eyes.

"Who do you think?" Blaise muttered.

"Where were you this morning?" Draco asked.

"It still is morning," Rigel said mildly, going around Draco and fishing in her trunk for a clean robe and pair of boxer shorts, "I've got to shower, so you guys should go ahead."

"Why do you have to shower?" Draco called after her, "And what on earth are you wearing?"

Rigel smiled briefly over her shoulder, "See you at breakfast, Draco."

Her first day of classes went fairly smoothly, until they got to double Defence Against the Dark Arts with the Hufflepuffs.

It was pretty clear, to Rigel at least, that Dumbledore had fired Quirrell at the end of last year because of his involvement with the Sleeping Sickness. Rigel herself had overheard Snape confronting Quirrell about being the one to expose the population of the castle to the sickness, and if Snape was as loyal to Dumbledore as he seemed, then there was no doubt the Headmaster knew exactly who was responsible for that fiasco and had fired him posthaste. She supposed he didn't have enough proof to file criminal charges, but a Headmaster didn't need a specific reason to fire his teacher—there weren't exactly unions in the wizarding world. It was good that he'd taken what action he could to remove a threat to the school.

On the other hand…looking at Gilderoy Lockhart posturing at the front of their DADA classroom, Rigel was a little less convinced that Dumbledore knew what he was doing.

"Welcome, welcome all of you," Lockhart said, beaming down at them all from the raised platform he'd installed in front of the blackboard, "When your Headmaster showed up personally at my mansion in the south of Wales and begged me to instruct you all in the ancient art of self-defence against the dark forces, I was a little hesitant."

Draco and Pansy looked at each other, looked at Lockhart, and then looked back at one another and raised simultaneous eyebrows.

"I mean, it isn't really in my nature to hesitate," Lockhart went on grandly, "But was I ready to take on the immense responsibility associated with the moulding of young, impressionable minds of innocents like yourselves? After a bit of soul-searching at my vacation home in Peru, however, I came to the conclusion that yes, yes I am. For the next year you will embark on a journey of knowledge, the likes of which I seriously doubt your past professors could even dream of. You will learn things you've never known, and do things you've never done, but don't be afraid. I will be with you every step of the way."

"Is he serious?" Draco muttered, "What a joke."

"Learn things we've never known?" Pansy scoffed quietly, "As if there was anything else possible to learn."

"Now I'm sure all of you have read my books by now, and think you know the real me," Lockhart went on, "But in this room you will see the truth behind the legend—the mountain beneath the mist, if you will. For in this room we shall face the things which test the mettle of even the bravest and most fiercest of men—even me. We will face them down together, however, and when I am through with you the world of the dark arts won't stand a chance. Who is ready to fight the forces of darkness?!"

He raised his fist dramatically and tossed his cloak behind him to strike a pose.

Several of the second-year girls, to the rest of the class' shame, answered back, "We are!"

Draco's face was so incredulous that if he hadn't been a Malfoy he would have face-palmed.

"Now let's see who is, in fact, here and ready to learn," Lockhart said jovially, pulling out a roll of parchment from the desk. He unrolled it and cleared his throat. "Hannah Abbott?"

Hannah raised her hand and said, quietly, "Here." Rigel noticed Blaise, who was sitting in front of she, Draco, and Pansy, cock his head to the side slightly, as though he were some kind of canine, responding to an octave of sound no one else could hear.

"Ah yes, young Hannah, such a pleasure to see you here today," Lockhart said. Hannah blinked, probably unsure how to respond to a professor using her first name, but Lockhart didn't appear to need a response. "Arcturus Black?"

Rigel raised her hand just high enough to be seen above her head, "Here. I prefer Rigel, however, if you're going to go by first names, Professor."

"Rigel Black, Rigel Black, now where have I heard that name before?" Lockhart said with a tone of mock concentration, "A-ha! Yes, I recall hearing something about you last spring. You did a small service for the school or some such thing, isn't that right? I think it even made the papers, though of course that was when I won my fifth Witch Weekly's Award for the Most Charming Smile, and in light of that everything else sort of fades into the background, doesn't it? In any case, I suppose you got a little taste of fame back then, did you? Well let me be the first to caution you about fame, Rigel. It is a fickle, fickle friend. Remember that, and come to me if you are ever in need of that sort of advice."

Rigel raised both eyebrows, but kept silent for fear of setting Lockhart off again. He really was quite a character.

"Now then, where is Susan Bones?"

The roll call went on. Lockhart seemed to have something to say to every. Single. Student. By the time he told them all to open their copies of 'Magical Me' so that they could 'begin a lively debate on which of my many accomplishments was the most daring and difficult,' the bell had rung.

"Is it really time to go already?" Lockhart said, glancing at the clock with exaggerated surprise, "I guess we were having too much fun to notice. Never fear, my precocious pupils, there will be plenty to learn on Wednesday. Toodles!"

He did a little finger wave, which too many of the girls in their class returned, then dismissed them. Rigel shook her head rather ruefully. It looked like DADA was going to be yet another thing she'd have to study in her ever-diminishing free time.

After DADA, Rigel went to Snape's office to see if he would open up her personal lab once more for the school year.

He wasn't in his office when she looked, so instead she went to check the Labs. The wards to Lab One were down, and light was coming through the door, so Rigel knocked quietly and peeked her head inside. The differences between now and the last time she had been to that Lab were extreme. Snape was brewing at only one station, instead of six or seven, and he looked like he'd gotten at least six hours of sleep the night before, which, as she had come to learn, was pretty good for Snape. His face was relaxed as he worked, and he didn't snap at her or sigh with exhaustion when she walked in. All in all, things were looking much better than last semester.

"Mr. Black, good," Snape said as he stirred the cauldron a final time and turned to address her, "We need to iron out the details of your accelerated schedule for the year. You are still determined to complete the OWL curriculum and reach NEWT study by the end of this year?"

Rigel nodded. That would mean she finished NEWT Potion work by the end of her third year, meaning she had four additional years of tutelage under Snape before she graduated.

"In that case, I have a syllabus that should last you through December in my office. I will give it to you at dinner this evening. I will also be re-opening your lab for you tomorrow morning, but I expect you to clean it thoroughly and inventory your supplies before you brew anything." Snape fixed her with a stern look, "If at any time you feel that you cannot both get all of your work done and complete the accelerated syllabus, your regular school work comes first. I do not want to explain to my co-workers that you are failing out of school in an effort to learn everything there is to know about potions in seven years. There will be plenty of time, so take it at a pace you can handle."

Rigel nodded and agreed, but the look Snape gave her said clearly what they both understood. She would pretend to give her normal second-year classes her priority, but she would get the extra potions work done, or collapse trying. Not that she was terribly worried. Adults always seemed to think things took longer than they did. Each teacher assigned about an essay every two weeks, and each essay only took a couple of hours to complete. At most homework took five hours a week, and most days they got time at the end of class to work on their assignments quietly. Then there was a bit of time between classes, meal time, time before class if you woke up early enough, and at least six solid hours every evening of free time around dinner and before curfew. If anything, Rigel imagined everyone who didn't have her workload must be terribly bored all day. She had plenty of time for her homework, Flint's homework, extra brewing, studying Healing, Occlumency, and now French, her new exercise regimen, and hanging out with her friends.

Rigel liked being busy, at least when there wasn't an emergency at hand, and she honestly didn't think she'd have any trouble keeping up with everything that year.

The week went on and Rigel settled easily into the swing of things. Classes weren't all that difficult, unless one counted the difficulty Draco had holding his tongue during Lockhart's classes, or the difficulty Pansy had getting Rigel to pay attention during History of Magic, which she preferred to spend buried in a Healing textbook.

At breakfast on Friday morning, their section of the table was bombarded with owls. It was Pansy's birthday, and it seemed as though everyone she knew had sent her a card or token. She smiled delightedly as she collected them all, and accepted her Housemates' well-wishes with graceful aplomb. Pansy wasn't the only one getting mail that morning, however. Draco received a thick letter of his own, which he tucked away without opening at the table, and when the flock of owls surrounding Pansy had cleared, Rigel found both a letter from Sirius and a large, paper-covered package from the apothecary in Hogsmeade.

She was still brewing for Krait, though most of what she made was Blood-Replenishers for Mr. Burke, only now she did everything by owls. It was a good thing school owls were both free and unmarked, as it meant she could send the potions, heavily padded of course, in as many bundles as she had to without letting Krait know where the owls were coming from. Rigel couldn't use the ingredients in the Hogwarts storerooms for her own personal gain, of course, so she had to order the ones she needed from Hogsmeade and charge them to Archie's account. He had given her permission to take what she needed from his school account, and reimburse him later.

Pansy finished neatly stacking her birthday cards and turned to Draco and Rigel primly, "Well, it looks like I've gotten a present from everyone. Oh, wait, my two best friends haven't actually given me anything. How upsetting."

Draco sighed, and said, "Not as upsetting as learning that your best friend has no faith in you."

"And to think that the Parkinsons are known for their patience," Rigel said archly, "I guess I owe you a galleon, Draco. I was sure Pan would last until lunch."

Pansy huffed, "You two are impossible. I take it that means you'll give me my present later today?"

"I guess you'll find out if and when we give it to you," Draco said, grinning, "Until then, you live in the agony of ignorance."

"Well at least I'll be aware of being ignorant, which is after all a far better position than the unknowingly unknowing, as Socrates would say," Pansy said, "So, what news from home, Rigel?"

Rigel looked down at the letter from Sirius and scanned it, "Nothing much, just the usual. Sirius talks about his work in the children's ward. Uncle Remus says hello, too, as do Aunt Lily and Uncle James. Everyone's doing great, I guess, though my Aunt Lily is apparently still consuming ice mice in unnerving quantities."

"You know all that would mean more if we'd ever actually met your family," Draco pointed out, "As it is, you could be making all this up for all we know."

Rigel looked at Pansy, who nodded her agreement a bit apologetically. "Oh," Rigel said, "I didn't realize you felt that way. Well, why don't I introduce you over the Christmas break? I'll tell Dad to meet me at the platform this time, and everyone can meet each other. If it's all right, I'll invite Remus along, too."

"Of course it is," Pansy said quickly, "We'd love to meet them both, and the Potters, too, some time."

"Great," Rigel said, smiling, "Owl your parents about it, will you? I think Sirius would be more comfortable with me going over to your homes if he could actually talk to your parents civilly without school rivalries in the way."

"I'll ask my father about it immediately, though I already know my mother will agree," Pansy said.

"Same goes for my parents," Draco said, "We'll let you know for sure, though, before break."

They finished breakfast and the day continued normally. During lunch, Rigel and Draco slipped away. Rosier and Rookwood distracted Pansy during lunch so that she didn't notice their absence as much, and Rigel and Draco went to Hagrid's hut to see that everything was ready for Pansy's surprise.

All through Herbology, Draco kept shooting excited glances at Pansy and tapping his foot restlessly. Pansy shot him several questioning glances, to which Draco just beamed back with a knowing gleam in his eye. Rigel finally elbowed him pointedly in the side once Sprout dismissed them.

"Ow, what?" Draco whispered.

"Not exactly subtle, Draco," Rigel whispered back.

"So?" Draco sniffed, "No sense in being subtle when she already knows something's happening. As long as she doesn't know what, it will still be a surprise. Besides, subtleties are so easily ignored. I hate being ignored."

Rigel had to laugh at that, and when Pansy asked them what was so funny they just smiled innocently in her direction.

She narrowed her eyes, "Don't think I didn't notice you two missing from lunch. I know you're planning something."

"Then you won't mind playing along," Draco said brightly, "Come put this blindfold on."

"What?" Pansy backed away quickly, "No way."

"You actually don't have a choice," Rigel said sadly, "Hold her arms, Draco."

"Wait, stop!" Pansy tried to make a break for the door, but Draco caught her quickly.

Pansy let out a breathless laugh and shook her head as Rigel approached with a strip of dark green cloth in her hands, "Don't you dare, Rigel Black."

"Well I guess we don't have to give you your present," Rigel said, a look of pondering on her face, "What do you think, Draco, should we just take it back?"

"No!" Pansy seemed to struggle internally for a moment before sighing, "Okay, fine. But don't mess up my hair, and if you play a prank on me or let me trip, I will get even and then some."

Rigel and Draco exchanged amused glances. Pansy wouldn't know how to 'get even' any more than she'd know how to fly an airplane. More likely one of Pansy's many upperclassman friends would make their lives hell if they ever hurt her. Pansy inspired great loyalty in the people who knew her, seemingly effortlessly. Not that either Draco or Rigel ever would do anything to knowingly hurt her.

They led her from the greenhouses, across the grounds, past Hagrid's hut, and to the edge of the forbidden forest.

"I smell pine," Pansy said, "Are we in the forest?"

"No, Pans, just at the edge," Draco said reassuringly.

"Wait here," Rigel said. Draco held Pansy's elbow so she had something to ground her while Rigel set off at a quick walk a little ways into the forest.

Hagrid was waiting in a near-by clearing, "Hello there, Mr. Black. All set, then?"

"Yes," Rigel said, "Pansy is by the edge of the forest with Draco. I just wanted to make sure we were ready before bringing her in."

"All set," Hagrid said cheerfully, gesturing to his charges, "These fellas are ready when you are."

"Great," Rigel grinned at the animals pawing the ground around the clearing, "I really appreciate you helping us with this, sir. I'll have the potion for Fang's digestive system for you on Monday."

"Well that's right kind of you," Hagrid said, "But I woulda helped anyway, you know. They're sweet creatures, and they deserve to be appreciated."

"They will be," Rigel said, grinning, "I'll be right back."

"Hold on," Hagrid said, striding forward, "Take a few of these." He pressed a handful of sugar cubes into Rigel's palms, "Put them in Miss Parkinson's pockets."

Rigel nodded, "Okay. Thanks."

She hustled back to where Draco was entertaining Pansy by describing their surroundings in unconvincing detail.

"And of course with the sky being green, the grass has gone into a jealous fit—Rigel! Ready?" Draco grinned, bouncing on his toes.

"Yes," Rigel said. She slipped the sugar cubes into Pansy's pockets quickly.

"What are—"

"Don't worry about it," Rigel said, taking Pansy's other elbow, "Step lightly."

They guided her slowly through the sparse trees and into the clearing where Hagrid was beaming nervously and giving she and Draco two big thumbs up. Draco grinned infectiously at Rigel, who smiled back.

"Ready for your surprise, Pans?" Draco asked with barely contained glee.

"Yes," Pansy said, nodding decisively, "Also, more than ready to take the blindfold off."

Rigel reached behind Pansy's head, saying, "Keep your eyes closed." She untied the green cloth and motioned Hagrid to move quietly forward with his smallest charge. She waited until it was right in front of Pansy, then said, "Okay, open!"

Pansy opened her eyes and froze, inhaling sharply. There before her, shining like gold in the afternoon light, was a baby unicorn. "It's…oh! He's beautiful."

Rigel wondered how she knew the unicorn foal was a boy, but Hagrid simply nodded his head and patted the young unicorn's flanks fondly, "This one's about fourteen months. He won't get his horn for another few months, and they don't turn pure white until around two years old, though of course their hooves will always stay this golden colour. His name is Calanon."

Pansy reached out a tentative hand and waited for the foal to sniff her. Calanon gazed up at her with a look that was two parts calm intelligence and one part childish inquisitiveness. The unicorn foal stepped forward, but instead of sniffing Pansy's hand, it ducked its head and nudged gently at Pansy's pocket. Pansy looked down, clearly bemused, and Calanon whickered softly, nudging her robe pocket again. She reached a hand down and into her pocket, then laughed as she pulled out several cubes of sugar.

"Is this what you were looking for?" Pansy held them out and offered them to the young foal. The unicorn tossed his head with excitement and went to take the cubes, but a sharp whinny from one of the older unicorns made Calanon freeze. The baby unicorn looked almost sheepish. It stepped back and very distinctly bowed its head to Pansy carefully, as if thanking her for the cubes, before coming back and delicately nibbling them out of her hand. Pansy laughed delightedly, "You're welcome. Is that your mum back there?"

Hagrid positively beamed at Pansy, "Good eye, young miss. Have you had experience with unicorns before? Only you seem to really understand them. Anyway, that beauty is indeed Calanon's dam. Her name is Fainauriel."

Pansy threaded one hand through the golden unicorn's soft coat and stepped toward the other unicorns. There were six adults, all pure white with hooves of gold and eyes of softest silver. With the promise of another sugar cube, Pansy coaxed Calanon over to his mother and the rest of the herd, so she could admire them all at once.

Rigel and Draco watched from a distance as Pansy greeted each unicorn and spoke quietly to them, praising and crooning sweet words of esteem into their ears. The unicorns seemed to love Pansy, circling her and brushing against her as they passed. The little one seemed rather put out when Pansy informed him she was out of sugar, but Hagrid pressed another handful into her palms and Pansy happily treated all of them, giggling when Calanon nipped playfully at her fingers and butted her cheek with his nose in a parody of a chaste kiss.

Draco and Rigel had been warned by Hagrid when they were planning this that the adult unicorns wouldn't like being touched or even approached by male humans, thus the reason for them hanging back. Rigel supposed that as she was technically a maid she could approach the herd, but she felt no real desire to. This was Pansy's present, and besides, Rigel felt somehow tainted by her recent experience with the thestrals that pulled the school carriages. Surely someone who could see the heralds of death shouldn't also attempt to cavort with unicorns. She felt as though, maiden or not, she was no longer as innocent as Pansy was, if indeed she ever had been. Innocence, she imagined, was a state of being, not necessarily a chronological precursor to adulthood. It involved a certain level of trust and faith in the world, something that Rigel had never had in abundance, even before learning that an accident of birth could and would prevent her from achieving her dreams unless drastic action was taken. Still, it was rather appealing from afar. Pansy looked so happy with the unicorns, utterly at peace with her place in the world. If Rigel reached out with her magical senses, she could actually feel Pansy's magic humming with contentedness.

It occurred to her suddenly that the pool of mercury she had seen in Pansy's mindscape during the sickness was the same exact shade of silver as a unicorn's eyes.

Draco took a moment to look over at Rigel and whisper, "We did well, didn't we?"

"Yeah," Rigel said softly, "I think we did."

Chapter 4

Every September Dumbledore dragged Severus Snape away from his immensely busy schedule in order to attend the annual Head of House meeting. It was long and tedious, largely due to the fact that each Head of House had a slightly different opinion on every single issue, and it was a rare third Friday in September when Severus Snape learned something from the Head of House meeting he either cared about or didn't already know. As such, it seemed to him to be a phenomenal waste of an evening. The only reason he went was to prevent Albus from exacting some form of petty revenge, the results of which would undoubtedly be tacky and/or headache inducing.

In 1986, when Severus last missed a staff meeting, the Headmaster cheerfully asked the house elves to paint the Potion Master's cauldrons pink. Without telling him. Even better was the Headmaster's idea to then construct a selective illusion of plain grey pewter over the cauldrons, keyed to Severus' magical signature. Only Albus, Severus later reflected, would throw around such enormously difficult magics on a mere prank. Imagine his surprise when, upon entering his classroom on Monday morning and taking a cauldron out of his cupboard to demonstrate a new potion for his NEWT students, his entire class burst into laughter. The gleeful noise was unprecedented in his classroom, and though Severus had quickly unraveled the illusion and spelled off the abhorrent colour, the story had spread like wildfire by lunchtime, and Severus had never missed a staff meeting since.

Whatever else could be said for the Headmaster's sick sense of humour, his methods were certainly effective.

So here Severus sat, silent and unimpressed by his colleagues' inconsequential natterings, nursing a cup of strong tea and waiting for the Headmaster to arrive so that they could get this farce of a meeting started. He would never admit that he found his fellow Heads of House mildly less irritating than the rest of the Headmaster's merry men, though he had a sneaking suspicion that the other three considered themselves close personal friends. If he did not disabuse them of this notion, well, that was his business.

Albus arrived, finally, and they began the meeting with the usual start of term announcements, followed by the opening of the floor. Minerva, as usual, seized it with a vigour belying her years.

"We really must decide what we're doing about Marcus Flint," the Head of Gryffindor said briskly, "He got away with obvious and flagrant plagiarism all last year, and I admit we got a little sidetracked by the sickness, but we've let it go on too long."

"I must say, it doesn't seem to have changed at all this year," Pomona put in, "So we can at least be sure whoever is doing Flint's assignments didn't graduate last year."

"But we still don't know who is doing them," Filius said, "And without either that or some other significant proof, we can't punish Mr. Flint."

"Exactly," Severus spoke up on Flint's behalf, "Additionally, I must question whether in this case Mr. Flint truly needs to be punished at all."

Minerva sighed loudly, "Here we go again. Pray, tell us, Severus, exactly why one of your snakes should yet again receive preferential treatment."

You're one to talk, Severus thought rather snidely, thinking of all those miserable lions got away with, but he merely said, "Tell me, Minerva, why do we assign children homework? Is it to punish them?"

"Certainly not," Filius piped up, "It's to help them learn, and also to gauge their rate of learning and understanding."

"So we are in agreement that homework is for the student's benefit, not our own?" Severus asked rhetorically, ignoring Minerva's scowl, "In that case, it seems to me that Mr. Flint has recognized the purpose of homework and made a rather sound judgment call concerning the use of his time. If he already knows the material, what is the purpose of forcing him to regurgitate it to his professors, when it is a waste of both his time and ours in having to grade one more essay?"

"It is not for the student to decide what he does or does not need to do—" Minerva started, but Severus broke across her.

"Then perhaps we should let the test results, impartial as even you will admit, decide for us," Severus pulled out a roll of parchment he brought for this very eventuality and passed it around, "Marcus Flint received straight Os on his OWLs this year, and I do not believe I exaggerate when I say he would have done just as well had he had the chance to take them last year."

"Oh, my," Pomona raised both eyebrows at the roll of parchment, "He did indeed. And in so many subjects, too. Arithmancy, Runes, and Care of Magical Creatures. I don't recall him being in that last one, though…"

"He wasn't," Severus said, smirking just a smidge, "He sat the exam without taking a single class. As I understand it, he studied for a few months with Alesana Selwyn, a well-known creature enthusiast, before registering for the exam. Clearly, he finds classes here at Hogwarts both slow-paced and unnecessary to his studies."

Minerva pursed her lips, but even she could not fail to be impressed, "He is bright, there's no doubt about it, but the fact still remains that he is both flouting academic expectations placed on him by his professors and forcing another student to do his work. No matter how brilliant he may be, it is no excuse for laziness and bullying."

"Except we don't have proof of the laziness or bullying," Pomona frowned, "Because he turns in all his assignments, and we've yet to hear a whisper of complaint from another student. What can we do except watch and wait?"

"Have we really no inkling of who the other student might be?" Filius asked tentatively, "We know it wasn't one of last year's seventh years, because the work is the same voice this year, which makes it all the more likely that it's either a sixth or seventh year now. It might be a fifth year, but I don't see Flint getting a fourth year or younger to do his OWL-level homework last year."

Minerva coughed awkwardly, and spoke up, "I may have a name…it seems incredibly unlikely, but the similarities between the work are…notable."

Severus could tell from the look on her face that she was speaking of one of her little lions. It galled her something bitter to ever admit that one of her charges might be less than noble.

"Who, Minerva?" Filius asked, "I've not seen any similarities in the writing style among my other upper-years."

"It's not the style that is similar," Minerva said carefully, "It is the content. I'm speaking of Percy Weasley. His essays are written in an entirely different tone and voice than Flint's are, but he talks about very similar things. He has similar takes on the subjects and he approaches them from the same angle more often than not. Mr. Weasley also often brings questions to class, which I've noticed tend to relate to things written in Mr. Flint's essays. All in all…it is a disturbing trend."

"Perhaps, but Percy Weasley?" Pomona repeated incredulously, "He would no more condone cheating than hand in his prefect badge. He would be the last person to do Marcus Flint any favours, excepting perhaps Oliver Wood, and the first person to report an attempt at bullying or blackmail, even on himself."

"I would have thought so, too, but…" Minerva shrugged helplessly, "Well, can the rest of you keep an eye on those two students' work? Perhaps I was mistaken, but if not…"

"Mr. Weasley would be punished as well, you realize?" Filius put in sadly, "He contributed to the cheating, whether under duress or not."

"I am aware," Minerva said stiffly, "Nonetheless, justice must be done."

Severus was tempted to roll his eyes at the sheer dramatization going on in the room. He was only thankful the Headmaster had not spoken up yet, as there was only so much sap and drivel he could handle in one conversation, "Personally, I still do not see any harm being done." The other Heads of Houses shot him exasperated looks, but Severus went on, "Mr. Weasley's grades have not slipped even a point over the last year. If he is the one doing extra work, it would appear to be only to his benefit. He studies twice as much, does well, Flint doesn't waste his time, still does well, and everyone wins. I have yet to see a downside to this situation, despite the technical rule infringement involved."

Not to mention the fact that Severus seriously doubted it was Weasley's work. Though there might be a connection to the Gryffindor prefect…it was as if his mind had all the pieces, but couldn't quite grasp their relation. Ah, well. It would come to him.

"That's rather rich coming from you, Severus," Pomona pointed out with good humour. It was true Severus was usually quite the stickler for the rules, but in this case it was in the best interest of one of his students if he expressed leniency, so he did. It was really as simple as that.

"Nevertheless, Severus does make an interesting point," Albus finally put in, "It seems to me that there is not yet any proof of wrongdoing, though there is smoke enough to start gathering fire hoses, as the muggles would say." Severus very much doubted the muggles ever said anything of the sort. "In any case, keep an eye on the situation and we shall see if something more definite comes of it. That is all we can do for now."

Minerva looked torn, but she willingly let the conversation flow to other matters. The rest of the items on everyone's agenda had little or nothing to do with Severus, and so he largely ignored the proceedings until the topic of Slytherin's number one trouble magnet, Rigel Black, was brought up by Albus himself.

"I'm sure I don't need to remind you all of the unfortunate events of last spring. As the four of you know, Quirrell was eventually identified as the party of immediate guilt concerning the introduction of the sickness to our school, and has forthwith been let go because of it," Albus said, "What is still of pressing concern, however, is not the instrument of the sickness, but that of its cure. Rigel Black. A surprising young man, as I'm sure we can all agree. Why, just this time last year we were discussing his apparent lack of magical ability to speak of, and now we find ourselves stunned by its depth and scope. Thoughts?"

"I suppose you are referring to his seemingly unique ability to enter into a person's mind by means of their magical core?" Minerva clarified, "Well, I don't know much about it, but I can say that after the first couple of months his academic performance turned around dramatically. You got him a new wand, did you not, Severus?"

Severus inclined his head, "Indeed, he was using an unmatched wand, and on top of that suppressing his magic to an unbelievable degree. Headmaster, I'm sure you've noticed the boy has no discernable magical aura."

Albus nodded thoughtfully, "I noticed in the Hospital Wing when young Mr. Black woke Mr. Malfoy from his coma. Very odd in a child, though not entirely unheard of."

"Indeed," Severus said, "But Mr. Black's magical suppression was not entirely the result of psychological trauma. In fact, it seems to be mostly conscious, though there is an unavoidable unconscious element which prevents him from using his full potential even now that he directs his magic consciously. He has extraordinarily good control over his magic, which is both what prevented him from using magic early on when he was not committed to exercising it, and what I believe affords him a unique creativity in the usage of his magic."

"Yes, well put, Severus," Albus said, "Young Mr. Black, simply speaking, has such control over his magic that he is able at times to work outside of the normal bounds of formed magic. By this I mean that it may be possible for him to exercise his magic in a way that he has not been taught a spell or form for, much like the accidental magic of childhood, except willfully harnessed. There have been cases of this in the past, the most notable of which in the last fifty years or so was Tom Riddle, and generally such control over magic is a sign of a powerful burgeoning wizard. It is hard to gauge Mr. Black's potential, however, as the majority of his magic is, indeed, suppressed. He has no aura to read, and even the levels of his magical core are hard to estimate due to its elemental nature."

"Fire?" Filius guessed, "It's always the hardest to tell with fire-types, because a lot of their magical energy is hidden in potential, waiting to combust and create energy at a moment's notice. Endurance is really the only way to judge a fire-core."

"Of which he has plenty," Severus said, not bothering to hide the pride in his voice, "Black's levels are well above normal, if the amount of magic he can continuously imbue in high-level potions is any indication."

"Do you think he's going to be Lord-level?" Pomona asked thoughtfully, "Sirius Black was certainly nothing to sneeze at, though I don't remember Diana Black having an extraordinary level of talent. She was hardworking and driven, but not naturally gifted as it seems Rigel is."

"Unlikely," Minerva said, "There is one Lord-level born in a century, statistically speaking, though I'm sure he will be a credit to the school by the time he graduates."

Long before that, if Severus Snape had anything to say about it.

"Regardless, we must keep a close eye on Mr. Black as well," Albus said, "He has already shown himself to have hidden depths and talents, and there is nothing more dangerous than an untrained talent. If he shows any more unusual gifts, we will be sure to get him the training he needs to harness them beneficially."

The meeting concluded shortly afterwards, and Snape adjourned to his quarters. Though his body moved at a slow pace, his mind spun fast with deliberation. Flint, Weasley, Black, magic, power, knowledge. There was some sort of connection he was missing, but at the sight of the summer homework he had yet to grade stacked on his desk, Severus put those thoughts away and turned to more practical matters. The school year had only begun, after all. There would be time for unraveling puzzles later.

Lionel Hurst had never been called a gossip. Neither had he, to his not inconsiderable knowledge, been termed a busybody, a newsmonger, or even a rubberneck. It was true that his mother often accused him of dropping eaves, and occasionally he had been known to snoop if the situation warranted it, but a gossip? Certainly not. For gossiping implied a penchant for passing on what one knows, and Leo would certainly never be accused of that. His lips were practically sewn together, in fact, but his ears…well, that was a different story. If Leo was the head of the most extensive network of informants and spies in the country, including those numbskull Aurors with their fancy 'monitoring' spells, well, it was because Leo listened. His ears were everywhere; they missed nothing of import in any part of the wizarding community. If a fly dropped dead in Newport of mysterious causes, Leo heard a fourth-hand account of the incident two hours later.

The point was, Leo was always listening, and if someone else happened to be talking—well, gossiping—at the same time, well, that didn't really make him a gossip, did it? Just an opportunist. With his compunctions thus mollified, Leo settled more comfortably in his chair at Miss Betsy's Beauty Boutique and opened his ears a little wider. A couple of witches under the dryers across the room were having a very interesting conversation, and Leo did not want to miss a bit of it.

"—being very closed mouth about it," the witch with about eight pounds of curlers on her head was saying to her friend, "I mean, you'd think since we're the ones living just downstairs that we'd deserve to know just who they'd rented it out to. Could be some kind of hoodlum. Or worse, a Ministry spy!"

Leo peered over the top of the Witch Weekly magazine he was holding to remain inconspicuous. The witch-in-curlers' friend didn't look convinced, but she did look intrigued.

"A Ministry spy? Oh, Gale, what will you come up with next?" she said, flapping her hands with their still-wet Wonder Shine on the nails at her friend. The nail-polish changed colour abruptly, becoming a bright sky blue. "Oh, no! Now look what I've done. Go back!" She flapped her hands again, and the polish turned a sunny yellow. "For Merlin's sake, I'll have to cycle through all the colours again." So saying she continued to flap her hands rapidly until the nail polish changed to green, purple, red, and finally to a pearly pink she was apparently satisfied with.

"You never know, Patricia," Gale insisted, eyes wide with more than that sticky Magic Mascara stuff, "It pays to be careful, especially in times like these. Why, he could be a dark wizard!"

Patricia pursed her lips and gave her friend a very exasperated look, "Didn't little Clara Botting say it was a boy living in number eight? How could a boy be a dark wizard or a Ministry spy? He's probably an orphan whelp, or his parents run off and left him. Nothing new around here."

Leo's ears twitched and he frowned at the article a few inches in front of his nose. The words 'Seven Spells to Charm your Prince Charming (Without Him Suspecting a Thing)' jumped across the page, but Leo wasn't really seeing them. An orphan kid living alone in the Lower Alleys? He'd better send someone to check on the lad. Maybe they could find him a place in the Court as a runner, or perhaps Solom could use an assistant. No child should have to fend for himself—not while he was the Rogue.

"Well, yes," Gale admitted, "Though that was near the only thing she did say. Her mother came over and scolded her something fierce for talking about 'that dear Harry boy' behind his back. I wish I knew what those Bottings have got to be so tight-lipped about. I mean, I've lived at number seven, Dogwood Lane for near on ten years now. I've a right to know when some strange lad moves into my own unit, and old Mrs. Whitlock should have told me she'd rented the place out anyhow."

"I tell you, Gale, nobody has basic manners anymore," Patricia said sadly, "Oi! Betsy! This dryer is much too hot!"

Miss Betsy came running over and waved her wand over the dryer in question a few times. The dryer itself didn't actually do anything, as far as Leo knew. It was just an aesthetic way to contain the warming and de-hydrating charms. Still, the old betties liked the ritual and pageantry of a muggle spa, so they kept the pretense. When Miss Betsy had left once more, the two middle-aged witches resumed their conversation.

"I just don't see why you can't go upstairs and see the new tenant for yourself," Patricia said, "I mean you've complained about it, you've asked the Bottings about it, so why don't you do something about it?"

"Don't you think I've tried?" Gale snapped. She rolled her eyes, "The boy never answers the door. He never goes in or out, though of course Mrs. Whitlock did have a floo connection, so who knows what hours he keeps. Still, you'd think he could take the time to introduce himself."

"Well, what sort of visitors does he get? You could ask one of them about the boy," Patricia suggested.

"He doesn't get any," Gale shook her head, "The boy must live like a ghost, whoever he is. Never has the lights on at night, either. Frank and I think perhaps he's a mite strapped for cash, and doesn't want to use the utilities too much. It would certainly make sense. The lad's as quiet as a mouse. Never plays the wizarding wireless—and believe me, we'd know considering how thin the walls are. Probably doesn't even own shoes, since we never hear him walking about. That or he's a cat animagus."

The two witches twittered at one another for a good minute over the joke, and Leo only restrained himself from rolling his eyes because they were visible over the edge of the magazine.

"Surely you must know something about the boy," Patricia said slyly, "I know you, Gale, if there's a plump little tidbit within arm's reach, you've got your teeth in it, sucking out the juice."

Leo privately reflected that that was a perfectly gross way to phrase things.

"Well, little Clara did say one other thing before her ma pulled her off by the ear," Gale said, drawing it out with relish.

"Don't make me beg," Patricia huffed, "Go on then, what was it?"

"She said," Gale leaned in close and Leo had to cast a quick sound amplification spell to catch the rest of it, "That the neighbour boy had the prettiest green eyes she ever did see."

Patricia groaned out loud, "You tiresome hag, you really had me going. Green eyes indeed, I thought you were gonna say he was a runaway prince or something. Why do you always get my blood nice and stirred and then leave me with something so ordinary?"

"Oh, you're just too much fun to tease, Trish," Gale chortled at her friend from behind her own neon tips.

Their conversation moved on to other things, but Leo was caught up in his own thoughts and couldn't be bothered to pay attention to them any longer. A green-eyed boy named Harry? It couldn't be the same Harry, of course, but on the other hand…what were the odds? Perhaps he'd have to pay Dogwood Lane a little visit. Though why Harry would say she had gone to America if she was really staying in the Lower Alleys, Leo couldn't fathom. Not that he could ever fathom that lass. She was something else, his Harry.

His musings were interrupted when Witch Weekly was ripped from his grasp rather rudely. He looked up into familiar hazel eyes and couldn't keep the grimace of resignation off his face. He might have known. Who else could catch him unawares?

"Leo, my lad, what a surprise," Eleni Hurst smiled down at him in a way that Leo thought was notably a bit evil, "Finally come to get your hair cut? Wonderful."

Leo gulped, "Mum, what on earth are you doing here?"

His mother raised an eyebrow, and glanced about the salon, obviously unimpressed with his venue of choice for the afternoon.

Leo tried again, "You know this is a beautification parlour, don't you, Mum? What would you want in such a place when you're so naturally beautiful already?"

Eleni Hurst chuckled dryly, "Too forced, Leo, entirely too forced. You're not getting out of this one with that silver tongue of yours."

Two hours and one entirely overpriced haircut later, Leo ran—yes, he would admit it to himself, ran—from his mother's clutches and wandered down Dogwood Lane. He contemplated the front door for numbers seven and eight for a moment, but really, what kind of a Rogue would he be if he knocked?

Leo cut around to the backside of the buildings on Dogwood and counted the windows until he reached the one he was looking for.

I'll just take a quick peek, Leo thought as he performed the selective sticking spell he'd learned by the time he was eight on his fingertips and toes. If no one is home, they won't be there to mind my peeking. If it's some other Harry who lives here, I'll offer him a place in the Rogue, and if it is my Harry, well, I'll be due for some explanations.

Win-win-win, he thought happily as he pried open a window with the ease of long practice. He dropped silently to the dusty floor—whoever Harry is, he or she really needed to learn the Evanesco charm—and straightened up to look around at…nothing. There was nothing there. Leo frowned, and crept silently into the next room over. It, too, was entirely empty, except for a few counters built into the wall indicating the room was supposed to be a kitchen. He looked through the entire apartment, and didn't find a single trace of life. No furniture, no pictures on the wall, nothing. Just a jar of floo-powder on the fireplace mantel in the living room.

"Well, that's not suspicious," Leo said to himself, mildly amused. Either someone was playing an elaborate joke on the lady who lived in number seven, or there was something peculiar going on.

Leo ran a hand through his hair and blew out a quiet breath, thinking hard. Maybe his Harry had rented the place, and then…gone back to school in America. That made no sense. Who would bother to rent out a place they weren't going to live in? Maybe she'd lived there all along, and had really been flooing here all those times he walked her to the Leaky Cauldron. Maybe she wasn't Harry Potter at all. Maybe she wasn't even a girl! After all, he'd only taken her word for it…no, no, his mother knew she was a girl right away, so that, at least, was true. Still, if she'd lived there before, she would have either left the furniture in anticipation of her next summer break, or she would have stopped renting the apartment if she'd moved out.

Plus, Gale from the beauty parlour had made it sound like this Harry was a relatively new neighbour, and she'd also said she'd never seen him before. That would only make sense if Harry had rented the apartment at the end of the summer, and gone back to school before moving in.

But why would Harry do that? Leo shook his head, his Harry had parents, and a place to live, and went to school in America. It just didn't add up. He realized he was jumping to conclusions. There might be other, real boys named Harry with green eyes about the Alleys, though why they would rent an apartment and not live in it he couldn't guess at either. On the other hand…Harry had been working at the Storeroom all summer, saving up for something big. Was this it? What if she hadn't been planning to live in it at all? What if the apartment was a fall back, some kind of safe house where she could go if something went wrong? Leo had always gotten the feeling that Harry was involved in something heavy, and Krait agreed. Was she anticipating some kind of trouble, and needed to have a place ready to hide?

He didn't know, but he did know that he would have to keep an eye on Dogwood Lane. And probably he should keep an ear at that school in America, as well. If he got wind that Harry did a runner, at least he'd know where to find her, and maybe help, if she'd let him.

Leo left the apartment as silently as he'd come, all traces of footprints in the dust wiped clean with another handy spell he'd picked up when he was just a lad. He had an owl to send to one of his acquaintances in the 'states, and maybe then he'd stop by the Gobstones tables in the park. One could always find good gossip—err, news—around a Gobstones table.

Most of September passed before Rigel felt she had quite settled into things. When the third Saturday at Hogwarts had come around, Rigel couldn't believe so much time had gone by. Part of it was that Rigel had been so distracted trying to fit everything into her new routine that she hadn't noticed the passing of the days, and part of it was that in the three weeks they'd been back at school, Rigel had yet to learn much of anything. Their professors were mostly doing a comprehensive review of last year's classes, since so many of the students had fallen ill during the spring semester. Everyone had passed their finals, but it was immediately apparent that most of the students' knowledge was spotty at best, even those who were not actually sick, but merely distracted by their classmates' illness. So Rigel sat through endless lessons on things she already knew, so bored that she began taking her Healing textbooks to all of her classes, not just History of Magic, in an effort to learn something while her school mates caught up on what they'd failed to learn the previous year.

Her friends couldn't understand why she had such an easy time of it. Most of them had only been sick for a few days, or perhaps a couple of weeks, but there were obvious gaps in their knowledge. The tense and confusing atmosphere last spring just hadn't been conducive to really paying attention to their studies. Rigel, on the other hand, had spent all summer going over the first year material for her owl-correspondence course, and was nearly bored to tears waiting for the day her professors finally began introducing new material once more.

Then, of course, there was Defence Against the Dark Arts. Although Lockhart certainly did present them with new material, it wasn't exactly the sort of information Rigel could see coming up on their OWLs.

"I swear to Salazar, if that moron gives us one more pop-quiz on his favourite colour…" Draco glared mutinously at the Head Table, where Lockhart appeared to be either regaling a reluctant Professor Sprout with his slaying of the Bandon Banshee or showing off an incredibly bad singing voice.

Pansy patted Draco's arm consolingly and passed him the strawberry tarts, "It's only for a year. Maybe less."

"Even that's too long," Draco said, though his annoyed tone was a little undermined by the way he was piling strawberry tarts onto his plate, "Think of all the damage he could do to our minds in a year. Not to mention our psychological stability. I've never felt like braining myself, but fifty minutes in his presence and…ugh. Where did Dumbledore even find this guy?"

Pansy pretended to think, "He was probably flipping through his copy of Witch Weekly and thought, well, there's a handsome fellow. With a smile like that he's sure to inspire the students! Let's give him a call."

"Really?" Crabbe gazed at Pansy in a blank sort of way.

"No, Vince, not really," Pansy said with a sigh, "Probably he was the only one to apply. My father tells me it's exceedingly difficult to convince anyone to take the post at this point, what with the curse and all."

"Why is it cursed, anyway?" Theo asked, frowning.

"I heard Slytherin cursed it when he left the school," Tracey Davis commented from across the table.

Millicent shook her head, "It's only been cursed the last forty or fifty years. It was something Dumbledore did, I think. He ticked off someone with a lot of power, and they cursed the position."

"Why that position, though?" Theo pressed.

"I would guess that whoever cursed it first applied for it," Pansy said thoughtfully. "The Headmaster probably denied their application, or greatly offended them some other way."

"Why would he turn away a wizard powerful enough to cast such a long-lasting curse?" Draco asked, "He already sounds exponentially better than Lockhart, who we've yet to see actually do magic."

"He must have been Dark," Blaise said knowingly, pushing a lone pea around his plate, "That would have been reason enough for Dumbledore to deny his application."

"Snape's Dark," Theo pointed out.

"Sshh!" Davis glared at Theo, shooting Rigel a pointed look.

"Oh, yes, because no one would ever have guessed that without Theo pointing it out," Draco rolled his eyes, "Don't be daft, Davis. Rigel knows Snape's Dark."

Rigel nodded easily. It was pretty apparent to Rigel, who had seen Snape's magical core and felt the characteristically aggressive edge to his magic personally. Then of course there was the fact that his affinity had been common knowledge since her father was at Hogwarts.

Dark and Light politics were a tricky thing in the wizarding world. It was the nature vs. nurture argument played out on a dangerous scale. To a certain extent, family had a lot to do with the way your magic leaned. Many people were born with a predisposure to Light or Dark magic, either passed down in their blood or just because of the way their soul was made up naturally. Then, of course, there was the fact that the environment a child spent the first few years of their life heavily influenced their tendencies by subtly conditioning the child to the feel of either Light or Dark magic. Unconsciously, a child began forming their magic in a similar way to what they were used to experiencing. In addition, raw magic itself had the tendency to take on the properties of that which it came into contact with for a long period of time, like it did when absorbed by a stone. A child's untrained power usually responded the same way, leaning Dark or Light depending on both its natural inclinations and its environment.

Then, of course, there was Neutral magic. As many people as there were that leaned either Dark or Light, there were an equal number who didn't use magic one way or the other. A large number of the Neutral magic users were muggleborn, leading credence to the idea that Dark and Light leanings derived more from environment than from natural inclination, but there were Dark muggleborns and Light muggleborns, too, so the idea of an inherent tendency toward one or the other couldn't be discounted.

"Knowing isn't the same thing as knowing," Davis was saying angrily, "If you keep giving him definite names, he'll report us all to his Auror father."

Rigel raised an eyebrow, but it was Blaise who spoke up scathingly.

"First of all, you have just by your own words admitted to being a part of the 'us' you're so afraid Rigel is going to report," Blaise said, nailing the girl with a look of uncompromising disapproval, "Second, if we're going to talk about people reporting on other people to their fathers then we should include everyone guilty of such an action. Looking around at those of us with the wherewithal to even send letters—" here he glanced with amusement at Crabbe and Goyle, "—Rigel is probably the only one I would guess hasn't been actively informing on the rest of our year to his family." Rigel was slightly startled to see every single second-year Slytherin glance away at that. She'd known Draco reported on her—had tacitly approved, even—but all of them were sending information home about one another? Interesting. And Blaise was not finished yet, "Third, Rigel's father hasn't been an Auror for several years—he works at St. Mungo's now. Fourth, Rigel moved through our magical cores last spring when he was curing us of the sickness. If he doesn't know exactly which of us is Dark and which Light by now, he doesn't deserve to own a wand. And finally," Blaise said, looking rather satisfied by the way Davis' face turned an unbecoming puce in response to his words, "As Rigel is sitting here, and not at the Gryffindor or Hufflepuff tables, I very much doubt he cares at all what our personal leanings are, as even if he is somehow uneducated in the mechanics of the debate he at the very least obviously lacks any prejudice of the sort you were so quick to go into fearful hysterics over."

Their section of the table lapsed into awed silence as Blaise concluded his impromptu speech. Davis was staring at the table and frowning rather petulantly, though she did not speak up to contradict Blaise's points.

Rigel cleared her throat a bit awkwardly, and said, "Although Blaise put that very nicely, I will say this now so that there is no confusion." The eyes of her classmates locked onto her with varying expressions of expectant concentration. Taking in their intensely interested faces, Rigel realized they must have been wondering about this very thing for a while. How long had they been holding back from questioning her about her position on Dark-Light politics? Since the train ride, when she had placed herself firmly in the anti-SOW camp? Earlier than that, even? "I am thoroughly educated on the matter of Light and Dark inclinations, and, as Blaise rightly indicated, could frankly not care any less which camp my friends fall into. As far as I am concerned, it is a personal decision that is both none of my business and beyond my jurisdiction as a fellow magical being to either influence or place an ideological value on. That said, just as it isn't my business, it isn't anyone else's either, so I won't share what I know about your leanings with anyone, just as I will not discuss others' leanings with you."

"You and Blaise talk like Professor Snape," Goyle said, blinking.

"We speak like academics," Blaise said, eyes flashing with veiled mirth, "Because we are both well read, are we not, Rigel?"

Rigel tilted her head in agreement. She knew she often sounded like one of the potions journals she liked to read, but it was better to sound too old than too young, in her opinion.

"Getting back to the point, though," Theo said tentatively, "You're really okay with us being Dark? I mean not that it would matter if you weren't okay with it. Um, but you really are?"

"Yes, Theo," Rigel said, "Magic is magic, as far as I'm concerned. It's where magic mixes with politics that things get murky."

"In that case, from now on magic will be magic and politics will be something else, yes?" Pansy looked around at them all, "I think it will be much more comfortable if we can separate the two, in any case."

"I agree," Draco said, surprising Rigel and most of the others as well. "What? It's a sad fact that in recent years the two have become too mixed. When magical leanings determine what politics you support, and your family's politics determine your magical leanings, well, then we've lost sight of the point, haven't we?"

Rigel thought that was a rather good way of putting things.

She had learned a lot about Light vs. Dark magic in her research into formed magic over the summer. Some of the texts she found were naturally biased, but between the extremes found in the Black Family Library and the other extremes littered about the Potter Library, she thought she had a balanced grasp of the conflict.

It was a common, though incorrect, belief that there were 'Light spells' and 'Dark spells' and that a wizard had carte blanche in deciding which spells to use. This led directly to the moral implication that if one was a 'good' wizard, one would choose not to use 'Dark' spells.

The truth was a little more complicated. In reality, Light and Dark referred not to the spells one used, but the way one's magic was shaped. It was not the wizard who chose the spells they used, but the way they shaped their magic that determined which spells they were capable of using.

All magic was not the same kind of magic. That much was clear to anyone who compared the magic of wizards to the magic of house elves, for example. But it went further than that. Wizard's magic wasn't all the same either, and just as there were things that elves could do that wizards could not, there were some kinds of magic that Light wizards could do, which Dark wizards could not, and vice versa. The spells and rituals that only worked if you shaped your magic in the way referred to as 'Dark' were naturally called Dark spells and Dark rituals. The same was true of Light magic. It was simply magic that could only be done by shaping your magic in the form that Light wizards inherently used. The 'Light' and 'Dark' misnomers were derived from the simple fact that Dark wizards' formed magic had a more powerful edge to it. Dark magic typically was faster, stronger, and, yes, more dangerous in general than Light magic. It had an…aggressiveness to it that was necessary for performing curses like the Unforgivables. Because the most destructive curses could only be cast by those who wielded magic in the Dark way, Dark magic had a bad reputation.

In the same way, there were some spells that one could only perform by using magic in the Light way. Light magic was slower, but very precise. Light magic could create things of detail and delicacy. It wasn't that Dark magic was less complicated—some of the advanced Dark rituals were extremely complex, taking months to bring to fruition—but it was less straightforward. The way Dark wizards formed their magic left a wild quality to it that made it sometimes unpredictable, and not so suitable for Light spells, which required exact parameters and a strict form. With Light magic, a wizard could charm a toothpick to paint a mural of the Sistine Chapel on a butterfly's back. Many upper level Healing spells, which required an exact outcome to ensure patient safety, were also only usable for Light-oriented wizards. If a Dark wizard attempted the spell, at best it failed and at worst it seriously compromised patient safety.

Of course, Dark magic had its own, very strong and very fast, way of Healing, just as Light magic had very precise ways of maiming a person for life. In all honesty, it would be more accurate to refer to one kind of magic as blue and the other as red. Blue can't be used to make orange and Red can't be used to make green, but they both can be used to make purple.

In the end, magical leanings were about family tradition and personal preference, and morality had very little logically to do with it. Unfortunately, Dark magic's often violent-seeming nature caused wizards of Dark leaning to be treated with suspicion. The theory was something like this: Only someone who owns a gun can shoot a gun, and though it may be true that not all people with guns would shoot them, the best policy is to…register…the people with guns, so that if someone does get shot they know who to blame.

When politics joined the debate, of course, things became even more complicated. Nothing was inevitable. The Bones' were traditionally Neutral in their magic usage, but almost always chose to put their lot in with Light-sided politics. Sirius came from a long line of Dark wizards, grew up in a Dark environment, and even used his magic in the Dark way, yet he, too, chose Light politics, though it was more of a way to distance himself from his family and to benefit those he cared for than for an ideological principle concerning magical leanings. Sometimes a wizard from a Light family chose to vote Dark or simply ended up Dark magically speaking by chance, and vice versa, though such a thing was usually looked upon as a betrayal by the more traditional families.

In the end, Rigel firmly believed that good and evil existed, but she didn't think they were embodied in Light and Dark magic. It was people who shot people, not guns. It was evil wizards who caused destruction and violence, not Dark wizards or even Dark magic.

"So what are you, then?" Theo asked curiously.

"Light, obviously," Davis sneered, "Look at the people he grew up around. His father is Light, and those Potters are practically incandescent."

Rigel frowned, wondering where Davis had gotten the idea that Sirius was Light. His magic had developed in a Dark environment, and the tendency for Dark was deeply rooted in his blood in any case. That was exactly the kind of confusing of politics with actual magical affinity that people should be more careful about.

"It's none of our business," Pansy said primly, though she couldn't quite hide her own curiosity.

"I mean, it sort of is…" Theo said tentatively, "He knows all of ours, after all. Turnabout and all that."

Rigel considered this. It was true she knew of their affinities. As might be expected, considering their families, all of their year had a Dark affinity, except Pansy, who was Light, and perhaps Blaise, whose magic Rigel hadn't gotten a very good read on. Of course, Rigel could have guessed that after their first week in Transfiguration if she'd known what she knew now.

Basic Transfigurations, like most general magic, were classified as Neutral. The term 'neutral' was misleading, because what was meant was that anyone could do basic magic, those with a Light edge, a Dark edge, or those with no lean to their magic. In reality, there were high-level Neutral spells that were truly Neutral in that one had to have perfectly balanced magic to accomplish them—neither Dark nor Light magic would work with those types of spells. But in any case, Transfigurations were very distinct when performed by Light, Dark, or Neutral magic. When Draco transfigured a match into a needle, his match practically exploded into a needle. The change was forceful and instantaneous. Pansy's match, on the other hand, changed slowly but seamlessly into a needle with delicate precision.

Rigel's Transfigurations were just erratic, like everything else about her magic. It wasn't like before her magic had started working with her—the spells always worked nowadays, but sometimes they worked instantaneously, and other times the magic took its sweet time about it. Still other times it changed one part of something first and then the other part a moment or two later, and a couple of times Rigel could have sworn the magic had changed the object she was working on to something else entirely before Transfiguring it correctly. It happened so fast, however, that Rigel couldn't be sure.

"I suppose I'm Neutral," Rigel said after a long moment of contemplation. In truth, she didn't know what her magic was. It seemed fickle, sometimes manifesting with a Dark edge, other times so refined it had to be Light, so Neutral was probably the safest guess since she didn't know for sure. At times she wondered what was wrong with her magic, but those thoughts weren't terribly constructive, so she tended not to worry about it.

"Really?" Draco looked a bit sceptical, but took another bite of strawberry tart without questioning her further.

As they headed back to the dorms, Draco spoke up hopefully, "So, Quidditch tryouts are tonight. Are you coming, Rigel?"

Rigel prevaricated automatically, "I don't know. I mean, you said Flint's really only looking for a Beater, right? Usually I play Chaser…"

As expected, Draco turned cajoling eyes on her, "Come on, Rigel, try something new! I bet you'd be a fair Beater. You're pretty good with hitting those little practice Snitches with me, and a Bludger is a much bigger target."

"Heavier, too, though," Rigel commented, rather enjoying dragging it out a bit, "And to hit an independently moving target is probably harder than hitting a dead ball with a predictable trajectory."

"Oh, just do it, Rigel," Pansy said. Her expression was utterly resigned, "There's no harm in trying out, and Draco would never forgive you if you didn't. I guess this is what I get for befriending boys."

Rigel smiled slightly, "I suppose I could try out. Maybe you should, too, Pansy. If you can't beat them…"

"Run the other way?" Pansy suggested wryly, "Thanks but no thanks; the spectator's box is the closest I've ever wanted to be to a Quidditch game, and even that is a strain on my sensibilities."

Draco and Rigel exchanged looks of mock disappointment, before breaking into amused grins. Pansy shoved them both playfully and they spent the rest of the trip to the common room trying not to laugh—they couldn't be seen chatting gaily in the dungeon halls, after all. What would the Gryffindors think?

That afternoon they headed out to the Quidditch pitch for tryouts, and if Rigel had thought last year's trial was intimidating, it was nothing on what Flint had cooked up for this year.

First, before ever trying out for individual positions, each contender had to complete a general flying test in the form of an obstacle course. Rigel didn't know which Master Spell-crafter Flint had blackmailed into setting up the field for the Slytherin Quidditch team, but more than half the applicants dropped out upon the mere sight of what awaited those determined enough to try the course.

The goal was to make it three laps around the pitch as quickly as possible, but Rigel felt that if seven players managed to make it around three times at all it would be a miracle of magic and sheer dumb luck. They were limited by means of a hyper-extended Ceiling Charm to a vertical span of about thirty feet above ground level around the whole track. No one knew this, of course, until the first unfortunate fourth year shot right into it while trying to fly over the first obstacle—a giant metal blade that swung like a pendulum across the track. The kid smacked against the invisible ceiling barrier with a sickening thud and spiraled weakly to the turf (which was luckily just thirty feet below him and reinforced with a Cushioning Charm for just such an eventuality), nursing a concussion.

Needless to say, the second kid in line experienced a sudden drop in gumption and graciously insisted someone else could go next.

After the razor-pendulum was a series of hoops that they had to fly through to get credit for the lap. Some of the hoops were placed awkwardly horizontal, so that one had to come at them from the top or bottom and risk plowing into the ground or the barrier if they attempted the manoeuvre too fast. After the hoops was a stretch of field that had been placed under what looked like a localized Weather Charm, specifically a rather nasty Storm Spell. That entire section of the course was waterlogged, with aggressive winds and pelting rain to test the flyer's ability to handle extreme Quidditch conditions. Rigel caught a glimpse of lightning crackling in the heavy black clouds from where she stood next to Draco in the line up and quickly averted her eyes. That was going to be ugly.

Immediately after the rainy segment, they would be faced with three cannons. One of the cannons—and they wouldn't know which one until they got there—would fire a ball the size of a cantaloupe into the air in front of them. If the ball was yellow, they were to catch it like a Quaffle. If it was blue, they were to bat it away with their fists, and if it was red they were to avoid getting hit by it at all. This was a test of both hand-eye coordination and split-second decision-making. Of course it went unsaid that at that point their fingers would be slick with water and probably freezing after flying through the rain, adding another layer of difficulty to the task.

Then there was a stretch of pitch that looked like one thirty-foot-tall chunk of transparent Swiss cheese. From what Rigel could tell, it was some kind of three-dimensional maze, requiring the flyers to make their way into tight cylindrical holes and find the path to the other side without doubling back too much. It would test manoeuvrability and also endurance under anxiety and pain, for, as Flint cheerfully informed them, the entire construct was lightly charged with a Static Spell. If they brushed up against the sides of the maze while manoeuvring through it, they'd receive a sharp sting for the mistake.

Rigel supposed it would also test a candidate's short-term memory, if they managed to make it back around for a second go at the maze.

Once through that, it was a straight shot to the finish/start line. The catch? That section of the track was where the Bludgers were. Flint had rounded up an even six of the mindless things for the occasion, and they bounced around like deranged pin balls between the edges of the course, the ground, and the Ceiling Charm. The goal in that segment was fairly simple—don't get pulverized.

After that they just had to do it all again. Twice.

"Well, if the Gryffindors aren't impressed by this, they mustn't have eyes in their heads," Pansy commented from where she was keeping them company in line, "It's not too late to come sit up in the stands with us sane folk," she added to Rigel, eyeing the swinging scythe with wary distaste.

"Thanks, Pan, but I'm afraid from now on you'll have to be sane enough for the three of us," Rigel said, clenching and unclenching her fingers around the smooth handle of Archie's Comet 260. It was almost identical to her own Comet, and she had worked out the kinks in a quick warm-up with Draco, so she wasn't too concerned about the difference.

Pansy took her leave of them with a last admonition to be careful and not get themselves killed, to which Draco cheerfully replied that some things were worth dying for. Their blonde friend just shook her head and wished them luck before sauntering off toward the stands.

Not long after the fifth contender had been disqualified for either skipping a hoop or being blown off their wind by the Storm Spell, Flint sidled up to them and raised an inquiring eyebrow.

"So?" the captain said, a smug tug playing at the corner of his lips, "What do you guys think?"

"Impressive," Rigel said easily.

"The spellwork, not the competition," Draco added without missing a beat.

Flint chuckled appreciatively, "Well, thanks."

Rigel blinked, "You did all this yourself?" Flint sent her a knowing look and Rigel flushed with embarrassment. For some reason she always forgot how utterly brilliant Flint was. Whether it was the way he comported himself or his general laid-back, gruff approach to life, she was always tempted to underestimate him—and she was the one who should know better than anyone how smart he was. She was only doing his homework because he had no need to, after all. "Right. It is really well done, Flint."

"Also, a bit vindictive," Draco commented as they watched a weedy-looking sixth year's broom catch fire from an unlucky graze with a bolt of lightning.

"Madam Pomfrey's been notified to expect patients. At least no one can say they didn't know what they were getting into," Flint said, not a shred of remorse on his face as yet another hopeful was disqualified, "Oh, he made it to the cannon volley. Too bad he can't tell red from yellow."

Sure enough, the little third year had made to catch the ball automatically before realizing it was red—but by then it was too late to avoid the projectile, and it smacked into his shoulder despite the third year's attempt at dodging.

"What happens if no one makes it through?" Rigel asked curiously.

"Don't speak too soon," Flint said, lifting his chin toward the next contender.

It was Adrian Pucey, she saw, and he was through the first obstacle so fast she nearly missed it. Pucey flew through the hoops nearly as quickly, rolling and twisting the broom around to get through the more awkward hoops as fast as possible. The Storm Charm didn't seem to faze him, except to make him bend lower onto his broom and swerve slightly to the side to avoid a strong upper-cutting wind that whipped up in front of him. When the cannon fired a blue ball, Pucey batted it away unerringly, and then he was making his way through the maze, much slower than he had been flying, but still at a remarkably steady pace. He was zapped a couple of times when he had to double back from a dead end, but soon he was out the other side and hurtling with heart-stopping recklessness through the final leg of the course. One of the six Bludgers came awfully close to breaking the nose of his broom off, but Pucey pulled up sharply at the last moment and darted across the finish line before the Bludgers could make a return pass.

A cheer went up from the line of waiting Slytherins, and a smattering of applause from the sparsely populated stands was heard as well as Pucey headed into his second lap. This one caused him a bit more trouble, as he had hit the swinging blade with bad timing and had to put on the brakes to prevent being sliced in half before continuing. Well, probably the blade was blunted so that no one actually got cut to ribbons, but the effect was still terror inducing.

"Now that is a Quidditch player," Flint said with no small amount of pride. "Six minutes and sixteen seconds!" he called out to the rest of them, "That's the time to beat if you want a guaranteed spot on the team!"

The waiting hopefuls cheered eagerly, pressing forward to get closer to the front of the line.

Draco scoffed, "Like anyone will beat Pucey's time. He's the best flyer for sheer manoeuvrability on the team, next to you, Flint."

"I know," Flint said, "I just want to see if they'll psych themselves out or not."

Rigel grimaced at the riled up competitors suddenly keen to take on the course as soon as possible. Flint's mind games were definitely in her top three scariest things ever witnessed, right up there with Walburga Black's horridly scowling portrait and Mr. Riddle's smile. A flash of blue, like a tailored vest, flashed across her mind's eye for a brief moment as the thought of fear churned the memories in her mind like a stick poking through muddy water, but she blinked it away. She had no time to get distracted by the past.

When it was Draco's turn, Rigel gave him a reassuring smile and watched him like a hawk as soon as his attention was on the course. She had faith in Draco, she truly did, but if it looked for even a second like he really was going to be sliced into ribbons by the possibly blunted razor blade…well, she and her magic would not be standing by quietly.

In the end, her caution was unnecessary. Draco had been a member of the Slytherin team for an entire year, even if it was on reserve, and it definitely showed. He flew so smoothly that if you watched only him and not his surroundings you could almost forget the obstacles were even there. He brushed through the hoops with practised precision, and though the thick rain made his bangs drip directly into his face, he still managed to catch the yellow ball launched at him with relative ease. The maze took him a moment or two to puzzle through, but the second and third laps went much faster once he had the rhythm of the course down.

Her friend finished in just under seven minutes, and he landed with a wide grin, cheeks flushed with exertion and pupils wide with excitement.

"That was great, Dray," Rigel said honestly, "You're definitely moving on."

Draco flicked a bit of water from his sleeves at her playfully, "You'd better be there with me, Rye, so don't mess up."

"Rye?" Rigel repeated with amusement.

Draco looked briefly away, then back defiantly, "Pansy and I have nicknames. Why not you?"

Since saying 'because Rigel isn't my name in the first place' wasn't an option, Rigel just shrugged and let it go.

"Then, here goes nothing," Rigel said. She mounted her broom and rose about five feet off the ground to hover, waiting for the signal. When the whistle blew, she shot off toward the giant swinging pendulum of death. It was a lot more ominous up close, but when compared to the speed of a broomstick, it also appeared to move a lot slower than it did from a standstill. Rigel had no trouble manoeuvring toward the side the blade wasn't, and immediately focused on not missing any of the hoops that were coming up next. She'd been watching people attempt the course for a good half hour, so she took the path that both Pucey and Draco had taken, as it seemed to be the most efficient overall. It was a little bit cheating, but mostly she thought it was just paying attention and being clever.

She had braced herself against the wind and rain, but was entirely unprepared for the cold. She and Archie had never played Quidditch in the middle of a storm before (Lily would have had their brooms snapped in half for even thinking about it, and really, why would they even want to?). The water was one thing, encumbering her as an extra ten pounds of weight absorbed into her robes, and a nightmare for visibility. Not for the first time, she thanked the Polyjuice potion that she wasn't still wearing contacts, which surely would have been washed away when the rain started getting pushed horizontally at her by the impossible winds. The cold, though, was something else entirely. It froze her muscles and made her want to seize up with discomfort for precious seconds after getting through the rain to the other side. In those seconds the blue ball seemed to come out of nowhere; though Rigel instinctively batted it away from her face when she finally registered it approaching, if it had been any other colour she would have been disqualified.

Grimacing, she made a mental note to be more prepared coming out of the storm on the next lap. The maze she had watched several others make it through already, so she simply followed the path she'd memorized and tried not to touch the edges. One carelessly draped sleeve, however, demonstrated to Rigel exactly how painful a 'mild' shock could be when conducted through water-soaked robes and skin. Seriously disoriented by the shock, Rigel just managed to duck a Bludger that came careening toward her before she'd even gotten the tail end of her broom out of the maze's exit.

Deciding she didn't want to spend any more time in that section than she had to, Rigel shot forward as quickly as she could while maintaining an irregular flight pattern to throw off the Bludgers' Homing Charm, which acted like a navigational auto-lock on the closest moving non-Bludger within the Charm's range.

She raced across the finish line, hurtled once more toward the menacing pendulum, and began the whole ridiculous process over again. It went better the second time around, and she was feeling pretty confident by the third time she encountered the obstacles. As she made her way through the course for the final lap, it occurred to her, not for the first time, that many of the things wizards got themselves involved in were sheer farce if looked at from a certain angle. Ah well, such was the influence of magic, she supposed, which was a force of farce if ever there was one.

Rigel finished with a respectable time of eight minutes and nine seconds. Not as good as anyone who had been on the team the year before, but definitely in the top twelve.

Flint then divided them into who was trying out for what positions and called out the top finishers for each position. Last year's Keeper was called, as well as the potential Keeper who had the fastest time. He kept Draco and a fifth year who had a time thirty seconds faster than Rigel's to try for Seeker. The two Chasers besides Flint from last year were kept on the pitch, as well as the three fastest finishers among the hopefuls. For Beaters, since Derrick wasn't able to try out, Flint kept Bole, the other veteran Beater, and three of the newbies with the fastest times—including Rigel, who had placed right in the middle of her two competitors, all three of whom had placed a good minute below Bole.

The Beaters and Seekers stepped off the field to watch the Chasers and Keepers try out first. Their tryout was fairly straightforward, just a mock Quaffle game, with one Keeper at each goal set and the six Chasers facing off against one another to see who scored the most goals.

"Great flying, Rigel!" Draco said when the Chaser-Keeper scrimmage had begun.

"Not as good as yours," Rigel said, grinning back a bit, "You flew like you didn't even notice the obstacles."

"What obstacles?" Draco laughed, "Oh, those old things? Flint has us train with obstacle spells all the time. Didn't you ever wonder why I'd come back from practice soaking wet, even though it was sunny outside?"

Rigel had honestly never even noticed the discrepancy. She didn't know if it was because she didn't pay enough attention to the weather, or, she winced inwardly, if she didn't pay enough attention to her friends. Out loud, she said, "I thought it best not to ask."

"Well, Flint likes to keep us on our toes," Draco shrugged, apparently not noticing how his words were seriously freaking out the kids standing nearest them, "One time he made us practise with deafening spells over our ears, so we had to hone our situational awareness with sight only, and once he cast Hampering Charms on our brooms to make them move slower, but then charmed the Bludgers a little bit faster, so that we'd learn to react faster to make up for the lack of mobility. Most of us ended up in the Hospital Wing, but it was an enriching experience."

Rigel glanced bemusedly at Draco. Her friend had never once described an experience as 'enriching' if it caused him physical discomfort. Looking at the kid on Draco's other side, who was noticeably green in the face, Rigel understood that Draco was telling her this for the benefit of those around them. She thought it was a bit risky, since he might have psyched her out as well as their competition, but maybe Draco didn't care if he upset her as well, or maybe he had faith in the strength of her stomach.

Deciding to pitch in, Rigel affected an interested but nervously incredulous tone of voice and asked, "So Weather Charms are common, too?"

"Oh, yeah," Draco said with an innocent smile that should have sent alarm bells through the head of anyone who knew the blond aristocrat, "We've practised in all sorts of conditions. You'd think the icy rain and snow would be the worst, but sometimes we practise in fog so thick you can't see the end of your broomstick, much less a Bludger coming straight at you. Then there are the days Flint cranks up the localized heating charms in the stadium to desert levels, and won't let us rehydrate until we get to 100 points. The worst, though, was definitely the plague of locusts."

"P-plague of what?" The girl who was trying against Draco for Seeker finally snapped and rounded on the blond boy, "You can't be serious!"

Draco blinked, as if extremely taken aback that someone would doubt such a thing, "The plague of locusts. Once Flint transfigured all the dead leaves on the pitch into a swarm of locusts, which then attacked at random to see how good we were at ignoring annoying distractions. Let me tell you, those suckers bite like nobody's business."

Rigel was now hard pressed to keep an amused smile off her face, and from the corner of her eye she could see Bole smirking openly as the rest of the Beater and Seeker hopefuls gave up their pretense of not listening and gaped with horror.

"What kind of crazy sadist is Flint?"

"I saw Higgs with bites all over his neck last year!" a beady-eyed boy trying for Beater exclaimed, "I thought they were from his girlfriend at the time, but now…that's sick."

Rigel coughed quickly into her hand to disguise the snort that escaped her. Honestly, how did people believe this stuff? Most of it was probably true to a certain extent, but locusts most certainly didn't bite—they didn't even have teeth. Just a hard outer shell that was mostly useful for thickening up Debilitating Draughts. At most one might be able to pinch with its mouth, but there's no way it would penetrate the skin, and Rigel doubted it would look anything like a teenager's hickey.

Still, the other three candidates who weren't already on the team seemed very in awe of this information.

"I thought this obstacle course thing was just intimidation tactics, to test the nerves, you know?" the other potential Beater, a beefy boy in a silver scarf that in Rigel's opinion was highly impractical for flying in, said with a frown, "But if this is the kind of thing we can expect all the time…the prestige of playing on the House team just isn't worth it." Without another word, the boy walked off the pitch and didn't look back.

Rigel sent Draco a surreptitiously impressed look, and Draco just smirked at her. Now it was essentially she and the beady-eyed boy competing for the second Beater's spot, since Bole was practically guaranteed a place back on the team.

Soon enough the Chasers were decided, and the Keeper position as well. Consistent with what Draco had surmised, the old members kept their spots, and the hopefuls were sent off with disappointed expressions. There was one exception—the girl who tried out for Keeper against Bletchley was kept on as a reserve, since she did manage to stop all but one of the goals shot against her by the seasoned Chasers.

Flint called out the Beaters, of which he was obviously amused to note there were now only three, and explained to them what their tryout would consist of.

"Originally," Flint informed them, "I was going to give you each a Bludger and then see how many times you could hit it accurately through one of the goal posts in ten minutes."

Rigel felt quite suddenly relieved that he had phrased it in such a way that it was clear such a feat was no longer expected of them. The Quaffle goals were an extremely precise target to hit a Bludger at. Usually with Bludgers, you just had to hit it in the general direction of an opposing player—it didn't have to connect, it just had to pose enough of a threat that the opposing player stopped whatever they were currently doing, like chasing the Snitch or blocking the goalposts, in order to dodge it. This was good, because Bludgers rarely stayed on the trajectory you hit them on. They were spelled to veer and swerve, and that was without the influence of the Homing Charms pulling them toward the nearest source of movement. To try and hit one through an inflexible and just-barely-big-enough Quaffle hoop would be nearly impossible.

"Then I thought, what's the point in that? In a real game, the targets aren't going to stay stationary," Flint went on blithely, "And there's no sense of risk when aiming at a dead hoop. So I came up with a way to really test your skills."

Rigel didn't think she was the only one who gulped.

"But before I explain, let me call the Seekers over here," Flint whistled and gestured with two fingers at Draco and the girl he was trying against. They came trotting over immediately, and upon their arrival Flint presented each with a flimsy plastic hoop roughly the size of a single goal hoop. Rigel's stomach began to sink as she looked from the hoops, to Flint's gleaming eyes, to the innocently excited faces of the potential Seekers.

"I can see by the rapid loss of colour in your face that you've figured it out, Mr. Black," Flint chuckled darkly, "Well don't spoil the fun before I build up to it. So anyway, I thought moving targets were just essential to a proper Beater tryout, and to make it more realistic, the targets would have to be in close proximity to something that was emphatically not a target. Like, say, a fellow teammate."

The beady-eyed boy stuttered and gaped inarticulately, while the girl trying for Seeker looked like she was biting her tongue to prevent herself from protesting vehemently as she realized what was going on.

"Then of course there's this part of me that just hates wasted time," Flint said contemplatively, "And that's the part of me that came up with a brilliant idea to kill two Seekers—er, I mean, birds—with one Bludger and incorporate the Seekers' tryouts into this situation as well. For anyone who needs it spelled out, this is how it's going to go down. Malfoy and Caviet will each have one of these hoops affixed with a sticking charm to the bottom of their brooms. Just to prove to anyone who thinks otherwise that I never put my team through something I'm not willing to do myself, I, too, will have a hoop affixed to my broom for this tryout. As you may have noticed, that means there are three hoops, and three Beaters trying out. Incidentally, good job thinning the herd, Malfoy. Now I won't have to choose a random spectator to make it an even four."

Draco preened a bit under the praise, though he was still giving the plastic hoop in his hand apprehensive glances.

"Now, each of you will get one Bludger—they'll be colour coded, so don't try hitting someone else's unless it attacks you directly—and you'll have fifteen minutes to see how many times you can get it through your hoop. The hoops will also be colour coded, and Pucey will be my eyes in the sky to keep score. The two Beaters with the most 'goals' win, but be aware that hitting the person or broom of the one carrying your hoop will result in serious deductions," Flint said sternly.

"Um, Mr. Flint?" the beady-eyed boy spoke up nervously, "Why are the Seekers carrying the hoops? I mean, it'll be harder for them to manoeuvre with them on, so how will they catch the Snitch?"

"They won't," Flint shrugged, "No Snitches in this game. I already know Malfoy can catch the Snitch when he tries hard enough, and I've seen enough of Caviet's flying to assume she's got talent as well. This tryout's not about talent, though—I can beat that into you once you're on the team. It's about guts. The Seekers will be judged on how well they hold up under the pressure of being a constant moving target. Their role in this requires gumption to stick it out, and also trust in their fellow players. One badly timed Bludger and you could knock them out of the air, but that's no different from how a real match will be, so it's best to get used to it now."

Rigel thought that was a little bit not at all true. No Beater would aim a Bludger at a player who was right next to his own player. You went for the lone flyers. The Seekers or Keepers, the other Beaters and occasionally the stray Chaser. And that was when you aimed at anyone at all. Bludgers didn't need a Beater's help in targeting other players—they did that on their own. Most of a Beater's job was to keep the Bludgers away from their own players. Catching the other team unawares was usually just a bonus.

Flint stuck the hoops onto the bottom of his, Draco's, and the Caviet girl's brooms. He then charmed the one on his broom red, Draco's blue, and Caviet's green.

"Bole, you're red. Black—blue. Tuiggins, you're green," Flint said. It did not escape Rigel's notice that Flint was paired with the most experienced Beater, and was therefore the least likely to get hit. Caviet seemed to be a bit leery of the pairings, too, and she eyed Tuiggins' nervously tapping fingers with uneasy concern.

Pucey brought over three Bludgers, one charmed red, one green, and one blue, and when Flint set them free the three Beaters took to the skies after their Bludgers as quickly as possible. The Seekers and Flint took off carefully with their coloured hoops. It was immediately apparent that they'd have to fly awkwardly with their legs tucked up and out of the way if they didn't want to get an ankle broken by any shots that actually went through the hoops. Still, they seemed to be managing all right, and Rigel had no more time to spare them as she tore through the air after the brutal blue comet streaking across the sky above her.

When she finally caught up to the Bludger, she just followed it for a moment, flummoxed. What was she to do now? She couldn't catch it and wait for the perfect shot like it was a Quaffle, but she couldn't hit it blindly toward Draco's hoop either, as it was both too far away and at a bad angle for a shot. She considered hitting it softly in Draco's direction until it was close enough to get a better shot, but without enough momentum the Bludger was as likely to go where she hit it as it was to go anywhere else. One did not simply nudge a Bludger in the direction one wanted it to take, after all.

As she kept pace with the blue Bludger for a few moments more, she saw Tuiggins get off a pretty solid hit on his green Bludger towards Caviet. Unfortunately, it was too high, and Caviet was forced to duck and roll swiftly to avoid getting hit in the chest with the glowing green ball. Rigel shook her head at the foolishness. The only way that would have worked is if Caviet had pulled up enough to make the ball go through—

Oh. Rigel blinked at the realization. Well, exactly.

Hadn't Flint just said it wasn't about skill? It was about guts—for both the Beaters and the Seekers. Rigel turned her broom sideways so she could both follow the Bludger on its random path and catch sight of Draco once more. He was watching her, seeming content to wait for her to make a move. Rigel whistled sharply just as Flint had done down on the pitch and swung an arm in a motion to indicate he should come closer. Draco seemed to get the idea quickly enough, and he zoomed toward her quickly.

If she couldn't get the Bludger to the hoop, they'd bring the hoop to the Bludger. Wasn't the whole point that the hoop was mobile? Admittedly, an opposing player would never cooperate during a game, but Flint hadn't said they couldn't work together, and in Slytherin House that was as good as saying you could.

Soon Draco pulled up beside her, though his movements were wide and exaggerated due to the hoop. "What are we doing?" he shouted over the wind.

"Winning!" Rigel yelled back, "If you give me a straight shot to the hoop at less than thirty feet, I can make it."

Draco grimaced, but nodded, "No problem. Fly ahead of it and give it a target. It will head right for you, and I'll keep the hoop directly behind its path."

Rigel nodded, and leaned forward on her broom. She shot forward, coming level with, then moving past, the blue Bludger. She could tell when the Homing Charm on the 'front' of the Bludger locked onto her. The Bludger started shifting ever so slightly in response to tiny variations in her movements. She increased her speed enough to get a good distance ahead of the Bludger, but not outstrip it completely, and when she felt she had enough room, she shouted, "Now, Draco!"

She pulled the broom up so sharply it flipped neatly in place and readied her bat in the split second it took her to turn on the spot. The Bludger was closing in five seconds, and she had a clear line of sight to where Draco hovered just 25 feet behind it. It wasn't very far of a distance, and an inexperienced Beater might be tempted to hit the Bludger with less than full force, in case it missed, so as not to endanger their teammate more than necessary.

Rigel, however, was not so naïve. If she hit the Bludger with less than 100%, it dramatically increased the likelihood of the Bludger breaking the trajectory and aiming for Draco instead. The Homing Charm could be overcome by brute force, so the only way to make it fly true was to commit totally to the hit, but that also meant that if her aim was off, Draco wouldn't have time to move out of the way before it hit him.

All of that rushed through her head in five seconds, and before she could lose her nerve she set her sights on the blue hoop and let her bat swing forward with all her might. The crack of the bat against the metal Bludger was always somewhat sickening at close range, but as a Beater one got used to it quickly. The Bludger changed direction with violent energy and careened back toward Draco with all the suddenness of a Bombardment Hex.

Rigel held her breath as she watched the Bludger's path. It looked for all intents like it was headed straight for Draco's face. She knew, in the logical portion of her mind, that it wasn't going to hit Draco in the face. They were right above the part of the obstacle course where the Weather Charms had been cast, and because of this there was a serious downward wind created by the vacuum of the spell as it sucked air currents into the charmed space to use in the storm. The wind would pull the Bludger down a good three and a half feet at approximately ten feet away from Draco's position if Rigel had put the correct rotation on the Bludger as she hit it, but a very alarmed part of her just realized that no one had told Draco that.

Just as she was cursing herself for not warning him about the illusory trajectory, she realized that her friend was not diving out of the way as any sane person would have done in that situation. Draco was still hovering there, in the exact same place he'd been when she took aim, and the expression on his face was expectant, not worried. Draco, who had no idea she'd ever even played Beater before, and had only ever seen her hit tiny little practice Snitches with the bat, was not a bit concerned that the Bludger flying at his face was about to break his nose.

He trusted her.

The realization was like a blow to the solar plexus, and Rigel was grateful the Bludger wasn't heading for her, because with the way she jerked with the sudden knowledge of Draco's completely unwarranted faith in her, it would have missed entirely. In the end, Draco was steadfast enough for the both of them, and the Bludger did indeed drop at the last moment to swoop neatly through the plastic hoop and continue on its drunkenly careening way toward the other side of the pitch.

Draco whooped and cheered before flying toward her and wrapping one arm roughly around her shoulder in an awkward air-hug, "That was awesome! Let's do it again. I bet we can get three more in the next ten minutes or so if we're fast enough."

Rigel just stared at him, not daring to open her mouth for fear of what would come tumbling out. Seeing him stare down a Bludger on nothing more than the faith he had in her abilities, Rigel just couldn't believe someone like him was friends with someone like her. Draco, with his wildly swept about hair and wide-eyed expression of intense enjoyment, was freedom incarnate. That he could just give in completely and trust in someone like that—in her, of all people—rubbed something raw within her gut. She, who had lied to him since the moment they met, she who couldn't even tell him her real name, she, who was using this game as a way to subdue her family's suspicions and as a single, selfish pleasure in her life of sacrificed indulgences, while Draco flew with the freedom of someone who would never pretend to be something he wasn't, no matter how much easier things might be for him if he did. She could never be worthy of such a gift, and the worst part was that she couldn't even tell Draco how remarkable his trust in her was, because the comparison would only raise more questions that she would never be able to answer.

"Rigel? Rigel! Time limit? Hello!?"

Rigel snapped out of her thoughts and cursed herself. Her mind always spaced out at the worst possible moments.

"Okay, let's do this," she called, "Same pattern. When I call for you to freeze, do exactly what you did before."

"No problem," Draco said, grinning, "Let's show them what we're made of."

It seemed that the rest of the tryout was going to be a sweep. In the next five minutes, Rigel and Draco scored twice more with their Bludger, and Tuiggins didn't seem to have gotten even one. He was chasing a nervous Caviet in circles as he tried to work up the nerve to aim at her again and she tried to stay still long enough to be sure the Bludger was going to hit her before diving once again out of the way. Flint and Bole were…

Wait. What were they doing? Flint was hovering nonchalantly on the East side of the pitch, and Bole was on the complete opposite West side, corralling his Bludger. Corralling was when the Beater needed to control the Bludger but wasn't yet ready to hit it. Instead, the Beater teased the Bludger by flying in front of it, as Rigel had done earlier, to make it follow the trajectory they chose without getting rid of it yet. There was a famous game from the 1960's in which one team's Beaters had decided to do nothing but corral the Bludgers the whole match, taking them out of the equation completely and letting their Chasers, who were world-renowned at the time, work uninterrupted and win the match.

Rigel wondered what Bole was doing with his Bludger, though. He wasn't herding it back toward Flint—instead, he seemed to be flying toward where she and Draco were trying to line up another shot on the edges of the Northwest stands. In fact…oh, crud.

"Draco, look out!" she changed direction before their shot was lined up and absently batted the blue Bludger away from them as she shot toward Draco's position. The blue Bludger wasn't the one they had to worry about, because Bole had just whacked the red Bludger right at them—or more specifically, right at Draco, who, with the unwieldy hoop attached to his broom, probably wouldn't be able to manoeuvre fast enough to avoid the barreling ball.

Draco's eyes flew to the ball, and when he realized how close it was a grimly resigned look overcame his features. No matter where he moved, the Bludger was close enough to follow at this point. Unless—

"Fly toward me!" Rigel yelled, bent double over her broom to get there in time. She wouldn't have made it if Draco stayed where he was, but when he flew toward her as quickly as he could with that stupid hoop, it brought the Bludger toward her as well. It was close—too close—but Rigel managed to bring the bat between the red Bludger and Draco's left shoulder as he darted past her. It was barely a hit, and only moved the Bludger back ten feet or so, but that was more than enough time for Rigel to bring her arm back and hit it more squarely when it came round again.

She hit it, not at Bole, but towards Flint, whose idea she was sure that had been. She could practically feel him smirking from across the field, and was almost disappointed the captain dodged the Bludger so easily. Then again, he didn't have it shot at him practically point blank, like Draco had. Bole gave them an indifferent shrug as they glared at him in annoyance, though he did send Draco a slightly apologetic smile on his way back toward Flint.

"That's time!" Flint roared, holding up his watch. He descended to land at the Eastern goal posts and the rest of them followed suit.

Tuiggins looked keenly disappointed, while Caviet seemed somewhat relieved to be on the ground once more.

"Well, overall I'd say it was pretty pathetic," Flint said, un-attaching the hoop from his broom and tossing it to the ground with casual disgust, "Tuiggins, you didn't score a single goal. Black, you scored three, but only because your partner aided you actively. In a real game, that's not going to cut it. Caviet, you have the nerves of a frightened rabbit, and the only reason I'm not banning you from tryouts in the future is because Tuiggins can't aim for shit, and frankly I'm not surprised you didn't trust him enough to sit still. The only one who showed any real guts was Draco."

"What about Bole?" Tuiggins spoke up, frowning.

"What about him?" Flint drawled, "He's been on the team for years, and doesn't have to prove anything to me. So, obviously Draco is going to be starting Seeker, and Black will fill the Beater position. Any questions? No? Good, get off my pitch then."

Draco grinned delightedly and punched Rigel in the arm, "You did it! Ha, and you didn't even want to try out."

Rigel smiled back bemusedly, "You did it too, Mr. Starting Seeker. Let's go tell Pansy."

They jogged over to the stands the spectators were sitting in, and Pansy hurried down to meet them.

"So?" she asked excitedly, "You must have made it, no one else even made any goals."

"We're both on the team," Draco said proudly, "Which means now you definitely have to come to all our games."

Pansy sighed, but they could see her pride for them behind the surface gesture, "This is what I get for being friends with you two hopeless boys. With Rigel on the team, too, it'll be nothing but Quidditch all day long."

"You'll learn to love it," Draco said reassuringly.

"And if you don't, you'll have manifold opportunities to practise exhibiting patience and false interest over the next six years," Rigel added thoughtfully.

"And at least you'll know what you're talking about when you finally get a boyfriend and he's interested in the sport," Draco said with a rather poor impression of a rakish grin.

"Win-win," Pansy said with extremely false enthusiasm, "And just what do you mean 'finally?' I'm barely thirteen, and I don't see you with a girlfriend hanging off your arm."

"Well, that's because I'm too young to be tied down," Draco said airily, using the put-upon snobbish voice he affected when he was joking around, "And anyway, for a girl it's more pathetic to be alone."

"That explains it," Rigel said, "I thought Draco was looking a bit pathetic lately."

Draco did a good impression of pouting while Pansy and Rigel laughed their way back to the castle.

"What should we do with the rest of the evening?" Draco asked once they'd stepped into the castle entrance hall.

"I think Pansy should decide," Rigel said, "We did make her sit through those tryouts for hours."

"And took a few years off my life, too," Pansy said primly, "Reckless boys. As it happens, Rookwood intimated that he wanted to speak with you at some point, Rigel, so I think we should go see what he's up to tonight."

Rigel glanced curiously at Pansy, "Me? Whatever for?"

"Who knows?" Draco said, "But it's bound to be interesting if Rookwood, and therefore Rosier, are involved."

Rigel thought 'interesting' was a good word for encounters of the Rosier-Rookwood kind, but couldn't say she was very much looking forward to it. Somehow, things always got more complicated with the upperclassmen around.

They met Rookwood in the Slytherin common room an hour or so before dinner, and, as expected, found Rosier there with him.

"Well, well, the up and coming 'silver three' made the time to see us after all," Rosier said, golden eyes glinting with amusement, "I guess that means we're still interesting, Rookwood."

"As if that was ever in question," Pansy said easily, "And whatever do you mean 'the silver three,' Aldon?"

"Didn't you know?" Rosier said, clearly enjoying dangling the knowledge over them, "People are starting to notice you three. The Malfoy scion, the only daughter of Rose Parkinson, and the heir to the ancient House of Black, three noticeably talented Slytherins with money and familial power to spare, all in the same year and best friends to boot. There's really no question that you three are going places—the only question is how far?"

"You forgot witty and good looking," Draco said loftily, a smile playing about his mouth.

"I didn't forget," Rosier said delightedly, "I just didn't want to bore you with things you already knew."

"In any case, please sit," Rookwood said, gesturing to the three empty chairs across from the couch he and Rosier shared, "Thank you for coming."

"What did you want to speak with me about?" Rigel asked, figuring it was best not to waste too much time.

"A mutual friend of ours has recently come into the keeping of a particularly moody vipera berus," Rookwood said, "He received it as a gift, and therefore has really no idea how to take care of the creature. He came to me for help, since I work with all kinds of animals on my family's wildlife preserve. I have an abundance of theoretical knowledge, but little practical experience with snakes, so I thought to inquire whether you had any tips for inexperienced handlers."

Rigel blinked. That was…unexpected. "Why didn't Pucey just buy a book on keeping snakes?"

Rookwood raised an eyebrow, "I gather he thought it would seem…suspicious, for a Slytherin student to be seen looking for information on keeping snakes. As you know, strictly speaking pets excluding owls, cats, rats, and toads are forbidden at Hogwarts."

"Father's tried to get them to change the rules, but the board insists that snakes are more dangerous than cats and toads and such," Draco said, shaking his head regretfully.

"Indeed," Rosier said, "So you see Adrian's plight? Luckily we have amongst our number someone with a snake-enthusiast for a father. So, Black, any tips?"

Rigel's brain stalled for a moment. What could she say? She didn't do much besides occasionally pet the snakes in Sirius' courtyard, and only knew what they ate because Archie complained about the dead mice in the freezer all the time. "I'm really not sure," she said apologetically, "My dad takes care of them for the most part. I just spend time with them when they get bored."

"But that's just it," Rookwood said, leaning forward intently, "You seem to have a way with the creatures. How else would you know when they're bored? You told Adrian that his snake was tired and hungry, as though such a thing were obvious. Also, last semester you somehow obtained boomslang venom for Alice, and boomslang snakes are notoriously choosy about who they allow near them."

Rigel thought the boomslang she'd met in the forest didn't seem too choosy when confronted with the possibility of a free meal, and said, "I just bribe them, mostly. If you show them a mouse, they'll cooperate pretty easily. Snakes in general seem to be practical animals, too smart to turn down free food."

Rookwood looked half-disappointed, half-unsurprised, "You don't have to lie, Black. If you don't want to tell me how you do it, then don't, but there's no need to insult my intelligence. I let it go with the boomslang venom, because I was still half-convinced it was something Alice put you up to, but although Aldon enjoys his little games of deception, for me it gets a bit old being flat out lied to."

Rigel winced, but could not deny the claim.

"Hey, watch what you accuse our friend of," Draco growled, "Rigel's entitled to his secrets, same as any of us. Don't act like it's your business, and don't ask questions you know he can't give you a straight answer to."

"There's no crime in being curious," Rosier said in an airily waspish way, "And you can't deny Black's habit for prevaricating and misdirection annoys even you, his friends, at times."

Pansy looked between her old and new friends, completely unsure whose side to take, and said, "Let's all calm down for a moment. I'm sure this is a misunderstanding."

But it wasn't. Rigel closed her eyes briefly, thinking she should have anticipated things coming to a head like this eventually. Surely someone would notice all the lying and avoiding she did and call her on it. It just turned out they'd been noticing for a while and refrained from bringing it up out of politeness. What could she say? She didn't want to start spilling her secrets every time someone made her feel guilty about lying, but she also didn't realize it was becoming both so blatant and so insidious—were other people getting slowly fed up with it as well? If she could expect more confrontations in the future, perhaps she should give in just a little. After all, if she gave them enough truth to satisfy, then they wouldn't think to look deeper, right? The classic bend to keep from breaking approach with a little misdirection thrown in for good measure.

Rigel spoke slowly, as though incredibly unsure, though in truth she had already made her decision. Even though what she was about to reveal could be dangerous, it was also one of the more…innocent of her secrets. It wasn't illegal, after all, but it was looked down upon enough that her hiding it for that reason alone was plausible. It was, in short, the perfect secret to reveal to appease the upperclassmen.

"You're right," she said, looking around at them, "All of you are, in a way. I do keep secrets, and they also really aren't any of your business. Still…I guess I don't need to keep this one any longer, as long as you guys can be discreet about it." She saw that she had their full attention, so she affected a look of sheepish embarrassment, "My dad doesn't even know about it, because, well, it's not really something you bring up in casual conversation, and it's also a bit…Dark."

Draco raised an eyebrow, and the corners of Rosier's mouth drew down slightly. Pansy just blinked at her, and Rookwood looked completely impassive.

"Not that there's anything wrong with Dark," Rigel added, "I just figured it wasn't something my family would really understand. Anyway, in truth I don't really have any specialized knowledge of snakes. I only understand them because I can… well… understand them."

There was a beat of silence, then Draco said, "What?"

Rigel took a careful breath, "I can talk to snakes, and understand them when they speak." Seeing that none of the other four knew quite what to say in response to that, she rambled on, "It's how I knew Pucey's snake was hungry—it told me. It's also how I got the venom—I just asked. So, I'm sorry I didn't tell you before, but traditionally it's seen as an unsavoury sort of talent, and it's not that I'm ashamed of it, but you know how much I dislike attention, and a snake speaker tends to get a lot of attention once it's known."

Draco swallowed hard, "I can't believe…you…didn't tell us! Wow! Rigel, what in Salazar's name were you thinking, keeping a talent like that locked up? Do you know how popular that's going to make you in Slytherin once everyone—oh…Right, so, we can't tell anyone, can we?"

Rigel grimaced apologetically, "I'd prefer it if you didn't," she said faintly, "You're not mad at me?"

"Well I'm disappointed you felt like you had to hide that part of yourself from us," Draco said seriously, and Rigel saw Pansy nod in mute agreement, "But like you said, it was your secret to tell. What made you decide to tell us now?"

"I've been thinking lately I should trust my friends a little more," Rigel said, smiling, "And you've just proven to me why I should. Thank you."

"You don't have to thank us for keeping your secrets, Rigel," Pansy said softly, "We'd do it anyway. And you don't have to apologize for being yourself. We like you the way you are, whoever you turn out to be."

Rigel felt a warm feeling flush through her, starting in her gut and rushing up to her head, where it pooled and made her dizzy with happiness, "You guys are the best friends I could ever ask for. I don't deserve you."

"Of course you don't," Pansy said lightly, bumping Rigel with her shoulder, "But we're friends with you anyway, because that's how wonderful we are."

Draco nodded regally, and the three of them laughed in perfect understanding.

"Not that this isn't touching," Rosier said, voice laced with honeyed amusement. The three second years turned to look at their upperclassmen with identical expressions of chagrined surprise, having all forgotten the other two were still there in their moment of friendship affirmation. "But just to be clear, you're a Parselmouth, Black?"

Rigel nodded slowly.

"Well, that explains a lot," Rookwood said.

"I no longer wonder that you were placed in Slytherin," Rosier agreed, "But rather wonder how your father got out of it. Don't traits like that usually run in families?"

"It's very recessive in my family," Rigel said, "In fact, I think it came from a different family, one we married into at some point, and was passed down accidentally until it activated in me by chance."

"I suppose it's possible," Rookwood said, "Usually familial magic ensures talents and abilities are passed in the direct line only, but there are always exceptions. It could even have come from your mother's line."

"Well, however you got it, it's amazing. To think, I know a Parselmouth personally," Draco looked at her pleadingly, "Are you sure I can't tell my father?"

Rigel shook her head, "I won't tell you what to do, and I did give you permission to write your father about me last year, so it's in your rights to do so, but I'd really appreciate it if you could keep this to yourself for a while at least. I want to have an uneventful school year, you know? And all the stir something like that would cause…"

Pansy nodded slowly, "Rigel's right. Parselmouths are rare, and powerful Parselmouths are even more so—most of Slytherin's line was inbred to the point of Squib-hood, after all, and the surviving descendants disappeared into obscurity dozens of decades ago. You must be descendent from one of the lines older even than Slytherin, where the line branched before Slytherin became known for the trait—after all, he wasn't the first Parselmouth, just the most well known, so you could have gotten it from anywhere, really. The point is, a Parselmouth appearing out of nowhere after all this time…it will be unsettling for a lot of people."

"Especially concerning the current politics," Draco said, looking serious once more, "Blood tension is at an all-time high, and a powerful Dark trait appearing now of all times in the Heir of a famously old pureblood family would definitely set some teeth on edge. You would be at best a poster boy for pureblood power, at worst a threat to the Light faction and their arguments that pureblooded inbreeding leads to talentless, magically impotent basket cases."

Everyone turned to stare at Draco for a moment.

"What? I read it in one of the pamphlets my father is always burning in the fireplace," Draco said defensively.

"So, anyway," Rigel said, "Now you four know why I'm 'good' with snakes. I'm afraid I can't help you with many practical tips for handling them, Rookwood, though I wasn't kidding when I said a bribe works wonders."

"That's all right," Rookwood waved her off, "I've learned something much more interesting."

"And since we can see how…delicate the current climate is, we, too, will keep this talent between ourselves for the time being—though Rookwood will probably tell dear Alice," Rosier said, smirking, "The only people those two can't keep a secret from is each other."

Rigel smiled, "Thank you. I'm sorry I lied to you all, though I probably will do so again in the future."

"We understand why you did, in this case," Pansy said, patting her arm gently.

"And it makes it more interesting to be your friend if you don't spill all your guts at once," Draco said teasingly, "Otherwise we might get bored."

"In that vein, I've been meaning to ask—could you guys lie to me a little more often?" Rigel asked sweetly, "Only I've been so uninterested by you guys lately—ow!"

Draco had thrown his chair pillow at her.

"I think that's our cue, Edmund," Rosier said, rising gracefully, "Thank you for your…enlightening conversation. See you around, little snakes."

The next afternoon Rigel was just finishing up a particularly grueling Arithmancy essay for Flint when it occurred to her that she had spent hardly any time with her Gryffindor friends since the start of term. Since she needed to ask Percy something about linked transfigurations for the last of Flint's essays anyway, she stopped by a bathroom to get rid of her disguise (Madam Pince's ire had not lessoned one iota with the new semester), and headed off in a beeline to the portrait guarding the lion's den.

Neville answered her knock on the portrait. The young Gryff looked a bit wan for some reason, but when he saw who was in the corridor, he grinned a bit. "You would show up now of all times, Rigel."

Rigel raised an eyebrow, "I can come back later, if you'd prefer."

"No, no," Neville said, "You may as well come in, just…ah…take off your tie, will you? And, um, you're not here to see Ron, are you?"

Rigel blinked down at her green and silver tie, but removed it obediently and stowed it in her bag, "I actually wanted to talk to Percy, but it would have been nice to hang out with you and Ron for a while. We haven't seen each other outside of classes much."

Neville sighed, "Well, Percy's with Ron, unfortunately, and Ron's in the Hospital Wing."

Rigel frowned, "Is Ron okay?"

"He's fine," Neville said, "It's his sister, Ginny. As best Madam Pomfrey can tell, she fainted sometime between breakfast and lunch. They found her in the Charms corridor and brought her to the infirmary, but she still hasn't woken up."

Rigel frowned a little deeper, "Is it…?"

Neville knew exactly what she was asking, "Not the Sleeping Sickness, no. But Ron and his brothers are still really worried. She's the youngest of the family, you know, and their only sister."

"I'm sorry to hear about Ron's sister," Rigel said, "But why do I need to take my tie off?"

Neville bit his lip worriedly, "Don't be mad, but some of the other Gryffindors think it was a Slytherin who hexed Ginny. They said first years don't just faint for no reason, so she must have been either really shocked or frightened, or else someone put her under a sleeping spell."

"Even if someone did, it could have been anyone," Rigel said, "She was found in the Charms corridor, not the dungeons. Maybe a ghost surprised her, or she simply didn't eat enough for breakfast."

"I know," Neville said, shrugging, "But you know how House sentiment is. They see it as an attack on the House of lions, and the prime suspect is the House of snakes. So, like I said, you can come in but don't advertise your House too much, okay?"

Rigel shook her head, "That's all right, Neville. I think I'll go to the Hospital Wing to make sure the Weasleys are doing okay. Want to come?"

"I've just come from there ten minutes ago," Neville said, "It was getting a bit…well, you'll see, I suppose. Thanks though. See you around, Rigel."

Rigel retraced her steps down to the Hospital Wing, a place she was sure she never wanted to see again, and told herself she would just stop in to pay her respects quickly and then go struggle through the transfiguration essay on her own. After all, there was no reason for her to stay long—she didn't even know Ginny Weasley, and she didn't want to bother Percy with academia while he was worried over his sister. The same went for catching up with Ron; it could wait until his concerns over his family were assuaged.

She entered to find the ward much livelier than it had been the last time she was there, and traced the source of the atmosphere to Fred and George, who had somehow managed to conjure an entire bandstand without getting kicked out by Madam Pomfrey for it. In fact, Rigel didn't see the formidable nurse anywhere in the ward. Fred had his hands on a some sort of flute—a recorder, she thought it might be called, and George was plunking away on a miniature piano while every now and then banging on a kick drum with his feet. Ron was tentatively holding a pair of maracas, looking as though he had no idea what to do with them, and Percy was standing with his arms crossed, disapproval on his face and a tambourine that was clearly meant for him abandoned on the bedside table. On the bed itself was a young girl with long red hair and an abundance of freckles that must have been their sister, Ginny.

"What are you doing?" Rigel asked when it became clear they hadn't noticed her come in.

Ron turned and dropped the maracas onto the foot of the bed hastily, as though he couldn't believe he'd been caught holding them. Percy sighed, and began to explain, but Fred cut across him after leaping up from where he'd been perched on the bed's bottom railing to ruffle Rigel's hair and sling a friendly arm around her shoulder.

"So good of you to ask, pup, but I should think it rather obvious," Fred said reprovingly.

At her blank look, George took pity on her and supplied, "We're waking up Ginny, of course."

Rigel nodded as though that made sense, "And is it working?"

"No, it is not," Percy said, scowling, "All they're doing is giving me a headache."

"You had a headache this morning," Fred said dismissively, "You don't need our help to give you one. Besides, if you've got a medical issue, tell the nurse."

"And how am I to do that when you two have run her off?" Percy asked exasperatedly.

"Run her off? We did no such thing, did we, George?" George said innocently.

Fred thought about it, "I'm afraid he might be referring to that little story we told her about a third year Hufflepuff falling down the West stairs, Fred."

"Well, that could have been true," George said reasonably, "Third years are notoriously clumsy."

Rigel had to suppress a smile at how true that was. George must have seen it, though, for he said, "Ah, it appears someone is recalling an incident that was perhaps less indicative of our own grace as third-years than we'd appreciate."

"Oi, show some respect!" Fred said, affronted, "Where do you get off laughing at us like that? This is a place of healing."

Percy sighed, "Like you two know anything about respect. Not to mention the fact that no one's getting any healing done with the nurse gone off on a wild goose chase to the West stairs."

"Well if you aren't going to mention it…don't," Fred suggested.

"You know, I hate to admit it…but Percy's got a point," Ron said, wincing a bit at the betrayed looks Fred and George proceeded to give him, "I'm just saying, Pomfrey might have had a better shot at waking Ginny up than all this would."

He gestured to the musical instruments, and Fred got out his wand with an affronted sniff, "Well if you're not going to be appreciative…" he flicked his wand at the recorder, which promptly vanished. Three seconds later, the other musical instruments vanished as well seemingly of their own accord.

"How did you do that?" Rigel blurted out, "That was a linked transfiguration! I've been trying to figure out the theory behind it since lunch."

Fred exchanged a look with George that had them both nodding to something no one else understood before turning back to her, "Theory? What theory? You just do it."

Rigel gaped at the redhead for a moment. Was this how other people felt when she 'just did' things? How annoying. "So you can't explain it to me?"

"George could," Fred said with a yawn, "He likes to figure things out. Once he does, I just have to tune my magical output to his and then copy it to get the same result."

Rigel just stared…there were no words for how unbelievably brilliant, not to mention useful, that ability must be…

"Yeah, yeah, twins are special, whatever," Ron said, rolling his eyes in the face of his brothers' genius, "What I want to know is why you care about linking transfigurations? That's sixth year material."

"Oh, is it?" Rigel said innocently.

"You should know it is," Percy said, frowning, "That's why you're learning it, right? Because it's the same thing I'm learning now?"

Rigel inwardly flinched. She'd forgotten Percy was there, and what she'd told him about why their transfiguration studies coincided so perfectly, "Heh, yeah, it's just embarrassing, you know? Working ahead…I guess I shouldn't be so ashamed to be studious."

She was met with four considering looks, and mentally reminded herself not to try and fool the Weasley children when she could help it. They were all extremely sharp in their individual ways, and she had a feeling their friendship didn't exempt her from their shrewd scrutiny.

"So, is your sister going to be okay, then?" Rigel asked, feeling like a coward for using their sick sister to deflect the conversation, but frankly intimidated by so many serious blue-eyed stares aimed her way.

Ron frowned, glancing back at the sleeping girl's face, "Pomfrey says it's not the sickness, but it's not a natural sleep either, or Fred and George's racket would have woken her by now."

Rigel looked more carefully at Ginny Weasley. She was paler than her brothers, and since she had the delicate muscle tone of a girl who regularly exercised, Rigel assumed the pallor was a symptom, not a natural characteristic. Her breathing was even, but her eyelids fluttered rapidly, as though in the midst of some serious REM sleep. If it wasn't sleep, though…

"She seems to be exhibiting all the signs of intense mental activity," Rigel said, "Does she meditate often? She might have just gone too deep in a trance, which would mean she'd wake up on her own time when her body got too hungry or tired to maintain the meditative state."

"Pomfrey asked something similar," Ron said, "But as far as we know, Ginny's never expressed any interest in mental arts of any sort. She's not exactly a sitting still kind of a girl."

Rigel frowned, "Oh. Still, I'm sure she'll wake up soon, Ron. Don't worry."

That sounded weak even to her, but what else could she say?

"Yeah, or you could wake her up," Ron said slowly. Fred and George frowned identically at him, but he rushed on, "I'm just saying, Rigel can get inside people's heads, you know? Maybe he can get her out sooner, if it's really just a matter of time."

"I don't think that's a good idea," Percy said, "I'm sure Rigel would mean well, but it's a dangerous thing to be going into other people's minds."

Rigel nodded apologetically, "I wouldn't feel comfortable experimenting with mind diving on your sister. I only did it with the sickness because the alternative was so dire."

"What's so dire about Malfoy being sick?" Ron muttered darkly, "Pompous git."

Rigel bit her lip and said, carefully, "Draco is my friend, Ron, and he was dying."

"Ugh, I know, okay?" Ron blew out a breath fraught with annoyance, "He's still a Malfoy, though. You know, if he wasn't your friend I'd accuse him of making Ginny like this."

Rigel was taken aback. She hadn't realized Ron and Draco hated each other so much, "I was with Draco and Pansy most of the morning, Ron. I really don't think he did anything to Ginny."

"Yeah, probably not," Ron said reluctantly, "But nothing else makes sense."

Rigel privately didn't think that theory made sense either, but didn't say so.

"You know, Malfoy senior got in a row with our dad in Flourish and Blotts just before end of break," Ron said suddenly, gazing down at Ginny again, "Dad broke the guy's nose. It was over something Lucius Malfoy said to Ginny, actually, so it's not so much of a stretch to think…well, someone had to do this to her, didn't they? She's never just fainted before, and she sure as magic didn't ever go into a coma for no reason at home."

"We'll know when she wakes up, Ron," Percy said gently, "Ginny will know what happened to her."

"I guess," Ron said morosely.

There were a few minutes of awkward silence after that, until Rigel couldn't really take it anymore, "If she doesn't wake up by tonight, why don't I ask Madam Pomfrey and Professor Snape to supervise me and try to wake her up?"

George smiled at her warmly and Fred ruffled her hair again.

"I suppose if the Professors were supervising…thank you, Rigel," Percy said, "Do you still need help with linking transfigurations tonight?"

"Oh, that's okay," Rigel said, "I'll learn about them some other time." Flint could deal with a grade lower than an 'O' on this one.

"Well in that case, come with us, pup," Fred said, rubbing his hands together in a thoroughly unreassuring way, "We've got a lot of work to do if Ginny's going to be waking up tonight."

"Work?" Rigel repeated uneasily.

"Well of course," George said, grinning, "We've got to welcome our sister back to the world of the waking with style, right brother?"

"Indeed, brother," Fred said, "I'd say it calls for something really grand to cheer poor Ginny up for missing a whole day of relaxing."

"Nothing worse than waking up to a Monday," George agreed solemnly.

"Oh, no, you two are going to prank someone again, aren't you?" Percy shook his finger at them, "I've half a mind to tell McGonagall before you do something to embarrass the rest of us unfortunate enough to share your last name."

"Ah, but a burgeoning barrister like yourself would never accuse someone before proof beyond a reasonable doubt was established," Fred said gravely.

"Innocent until proven guilty, Perce," George added, "Even you can't argue with that. Now come on, pup, and let's get out of here before he finds some way to argue with that."

Rigel barely had time to wave to Ron and Percy as she was ushered unceremoniously out of the Hospital Wing and whisked off into a seldom-used corridor with the twins. "I actually have a bit more studying I was going to do this afternoon…" she trailed off when they rounded on her with serious expressions.

"Oh, you're not getting out of this," George said with sharp cheerfulness, "We've not seen you all semester. Do you know how frustrating it is to put off pulling any really good pranks because our touchstone is too busy learning sixth year transfiguration material to come up to the tower and say 'hi' to us?"

"It's quite frustrating, in case you were wondering," Fred added idly. Rigel winced, and opened her mouth to apologize, but Fred went on blithely, "Don't apologize, pup—you do that too much anyway—and don't go acting like we kicked you. We're not angry, cause we know how you are."

Rigel wasn't sure exactly what that meant, but it didn't stop her feeling somehow guilty for it.

"But we are going to insist you help us out with this prank," George said, smiling down at her from his superior height, "And in return, I'll teach you linked transfigurations."

Rigel smiled back and gave in, "Okay, what are we doing?"

"Well, funny you should ask…"

They spent the next few hours planning out the prank they were going to pull the next day if Ginny woke up. As far as pranks went, it was surprisingly…nice. Rigel was actually looking forward to the end result.

They wandered back to the Hospital Wing after finishing a 'working' dinner in the kitchens, where Binny was happy to help convince the other elves not to clear away their hard work the next day. After assuring them the results would disappear on their own around lunch, the elves more or less happily agreed to leave the prank alone.

When they arrived in the white-washed room, Madam Pomfrey was back (and fixing the twins with a very displeased look that communicated exactly how she felt about being sent off to the West stairs for an imaginary third-year Hufflepuff earlier), and Professor Snape was standing beside Ginny's bed, a look of concentration on his face that told Rigel he was probably attempting Legilimency. Rigel was impressed that he had mastered the mental arts to the extent that he could remain standing while essentially unconscious.

As they approached where Ron and Percy were standing off to the side, watching, Professor Snape's features were abruptly animated once more as his consciousness came back to reality.

"It is no use," Snape said to Pomfrey, shaking his head, "There is something clouding her mind from Legilimency. It is definitely not the sickness. That barrier was solid, but this is more like a dark mist, twisting mental probes away with alarming elasticity. I would say it was the work of an accomplished Occlumens, if you had not already insisted that Ginevra Weasley is undisciplined in the mental arts."

"Will it lift naturally, Severus?" Pomfrey asked with puckered brows.

Snape frowned as well, "Without more information, it is impossible to know."

Judging by the troubled expression lurking in the Potion Master's dark eyes, Rigel gathered he rather doubted it would.

"Please, sir," Rigel spoke up, "Could I be of any help to Ginny?"

Snape and Pomfrey turned measuring looks on her.

"I suppose it's possible that your particular talent may at the least provide insight to the situation," Snape said slowly, "However, the state of Miss Weasley's mind is currently unknown. This is not the sickness we are dealing with, and as such there may be something considerably less benign lurking about in the girl's mental landscape. I do not like the idea of your going into her mind alone and unprepared."

Rigel nodded, "I understand, sir, but if there's a good chance that she is endangered by what caused her collapse, it's important to figure out what it is so that Madam Pomfrey can try and treat it, or else contact some kind of curse breaker or something."

The nurse pursed her lips, "Mr. Black is correct, Severus. What I need is information, and there are very few things that can cause permanent damage to a person's consciousness without having direct access to their own mental plane. As such, there does not seem to be much danger to Mr. Black, who will only be projecting his consciousness into Miss Weasley's mindscape. If he feels himself in danger, he can, of course, simply let the connection snap; his consciousness should automatically retreat to his own mind."

Snape looked like he'd tasted a milkweed stalk to check its viability and found it soured. "Very well," he said eventually, "I will allow this, but I would like you to allow me to establish a connection to your core, Mr. Black. If I feel a sufficient amount of time has passed on the physical plane, I will send a pulse down the pathways to alert you that you are to return posthaste."

Rigel agreed, "Wait just a moment, then, sir."

She took a seat on the bed next to Ginny's, and sank easily into her mental landscape. The familiar mountain brought a nostalgic smile to her face as she hurried into the decoy lab and down through the trap door. She loved coming here. There was something freeing in the air, and she thought it had to do with being able to be completely herself while in the comfort of her own mind. Although…she stopped for a moment to concentrate on turning her avatar's eyes from green to grey. Even though her physical body was now semi-permanently polyjuiced to have Archie's eyes, her mental self still retained her green eyes and long black hair. She did feel a little taller, though, so at least her estimation of herself was ageing properly—imagine, being mentally an eleven-year-old forever.

She whispered the password to her Space Room and took a moment to simply bask in the warmth of her magical core before taking the now-familiar plunge into the sun. When she reached the other side of her magical core, where it manifested in the physical world as a ball of concentrated magic around her midriff, she used the part of her awareness that controlled her physical body to say, "Ready now."

A moment later, a rather agile thorn of magic came shooting toward her magical core from the direction she sensed her Professor's core to be. She moved out of the way and sent a coil of her own fiery magic to meet it and help establish the connection. She could feel a pulse of magic come questioningly down the connection, so she sent an affirmative pulse back. Then she stretched her senses toward the magical cores she didn't recognize by feel. She knew Ron's, and peripherally Madam Pomfrey's, and passed over the two almost-identical cores as well, assuming those to be the twins'. Of the other two, she stretched toward the smaller and denser of the two cores and established a connection to it.

It felt young and rather warm, so she knew before she sent her consciousness along the connection that Ginny Weasley must be a fire-type as well. Sure enough, at first glance Ginny's core looked like a ball of simmering gold. It bubbled and rippled as though an open flame was heating it constantly from beneath, and when she offered it her hand and asked for entrance, the molten, lava-like liquid fire reached out to encase her hand like a warm glove. It was a comforting sort of core, she decided, but also looked a bit…volatile.

She soon had her entire form encased in hot gold, and after wading blindly forward for a moment, she felt a searing heat wash over her, as though she had just stepped fully into a tempered flame. Then her head popped out the other side to see… nothing. Absolutely nothing. As far as her eyes could see, there was only air. The ball of fiery metal she was encased in floated in a seemingly endless landscape of sky-blue nothingness. She hesitated before stepping away from the core, not sure what a fall to her death would actually do in another person's mental landscape, but as soon as she let go of the core, gravity took a holiday.

She was floating, she noted with no small amount of interest. No, she was flying. At the barest thought, she was skimming through the air, up, down, any way she could imagine. It was the strangest thing she'd ever experienced in someone else's mind. There was that one boy who used clouds like hard surfaces in his mind, but just flying through the air? Most people maintained a basic adherence to the natural order of the universe, even in their heads, but Ginny Weasley didn't seem to care about physics. Or perhaps she just really liked flying.

It was fun getting the hang of movement via mental hovering, but after a moment she recalled herself. She was here to gather information, and the preferred information source seemed to be completely missing from the picture.

Where was Ginny?

There wasn't really a horizon to look out towards, because there was no ground for the sky to 'meet.' It was just blank, blue expanse in every direction. Not sure what else to do, she called, "Anyone here?"

After waiting the requisite beat in case of an answer, she sighed. Plan B, then.

She set off in a random direction, deciding to treat the molten magical core as North and simply travel directly away from it. After floating for a while, all the time glancing over her shoulder to check that the only landmark was still in sight, she began to feel uneasy. Her shoulder blades were beginning to itch, as though someone were staring particularly hard at her back. She slowed down her flying, and glanced around again, but still nothing was in sight.

"Hello?" she tried again, "Ginny Weasley?"

Nothing, but the feeling of being watched increased sharply, and she gave up the pretense of floating along to address the unseen watcher, "I know you're there."

"You can see me?" a quiet voice said from just behind her, "He said you wouldn't be able to."

Harry whirled around to stare at the patch of air the voice had come from. She couldn't see anything, but at least she knew she wasn't alone, "Is that you, Ginny?"

"How do you know my name?" the voice asked again. It was definitely the voice of a young girl.

"Your brothers told me," Harry said, "They sent me to find you."

All of a sudden, a girl who looked very much like the Ginny Weasley she had recently seen in the Hospital Wing materialized in front of her. Her red hair was pulled back from her face in a ponytail, but a few tendrils escaped to frame the annoyed expression on her face.

"My brothers? So after ignoring me for the last month, now they acknowledge my existence?" the girl, who must have been Ginny's mental avatar, snorted, "Typical. So they sent you to 'find' me? Who are you? And how did you even get in here?"

Harry blinked at the aggressive tone, "I'm Rigel Black. I came in via your magical core, because your physical body fell unconscious in the Charms corridor. Do you know how it happened?"

"The Charms corridor?" Ginny muttered, frowning, "I haven't been anywhere near—hang on. Rigel Black? The one who cured the Sleeping Sickness? My brother Ron wrote about you in one of his letters. And Fred and George mentioned you this summer, too. I think even Percy likes you, actually, but…" Ginny looked her over with obvious confusion, "I thought you were a boy."

Harry tried to look as embarrassed as she was sure a real boy would have, "My mental avatar just has long hair, though if we meet in the physical world you'll see me with short hair."

"Oh," Ginny said, "Weird. Anyway, you've found me. Now what?"

"Um," Harry faltered. What indeed? "Well, I'm supposed to figure out what happened to you, so Madam Pomfrey or Professor Snape can wake you up."

Ginny shuddered, "Whatever you do, don't let Snape in here! He hates my family. Probably Fred and George's fault, though I don't remember him being too fond of Charlie, now that I think about it."

"He's not so bad…" Harry trailed off under Ginny's unimpressed look, "In any case, do you remember what happened to make you fall unconscious? Were you meditating, or did another student curse you with anything?"

Ginny's face suddenly became carefully blank, "Nothing happened. I mean, yeah, I guess I was meditating. I still am, actually, but I'll wake up soon if everyone's really so worried. I mean, sheesh, it's been like half an hour."

Harry shook her head, "It's been more like half a day, at the least." At the girl's shocked look, Harry smiled sympathetically, "It can be a bit difficult to judge time in the mental realm. It helps to set an alarm in the physical world to jar you out of it after a few hours just in case, though if you didn't even wake up when they moved you…you must have been very deep in meditation. Your brothers were making all kinds of noise to try and wake you."

"So in other words, Fred and George were making a ruckus, Ron was watching, and Percy, as usual, was completely ineffectual at trying to stop them," Ginny said flatly.

"Something like that," Harry said absently, "It's strange, though, that you'd be so difficult to wake up, especially if you're not very experienced at Occlumency yet. It is usually difficult to retain the meditative concentration at first."

"Who says I'm inexperienced?" Ginny said a bit defensively.

"Well, I just assumed, I suppose. For one thing, you seemed unfamiliar with the difference in how time is experienced on the mental plane, and for another…" Harry glanced around the air meaningfully, "Forgive me, but you don't seem to have spent time doing much with your mental landscape."

Ginny huffed, "This is only the first layer. It's, like, an illusion. That's why you couldn't see me until I let you. My consciousness was manifesting on the layer beneath this one, which lets me see into the first level without intruders seeing me back."

The way she said 'intruders' made Harry wince and hastily apologize, "I only broke in because your brothers were so concerned. None of us realized you had fallen unconscious on purpose, and with the Sleeping Sickness just last term…we didn't want to take any chances."

Ginny softened a bit, "Those idiots. They never pay me any attention, but as soon as I get so much as a scraped knee, it's like the world is ending. Still, I guess I should say thanks for going to so much trouble for a complete stranger, Black."

"Please call me Rigel," Harry said, "Seems silly to stand on ceremony in your own mind. Can you wake on your own, then? Silly question, I guess. If you have the shields to deflect Snape already, you must be more experienced than I assumed."

Ginny nodded carefully, "It will take me a couple of minutes, though. I have some…things to tie up here before I leave."

Harry nodded, "Okay, I'll be going then. I look forward to meeting you officially, and don't be too hard on your brothers when you wake up, okay? Especially Ron. He was really worried someone had hexed you or something."

Ginny sighed, "Yeah, Ron's a total git, but he's way less crazy than the rest of my family. Oh, here." The red-haired girl concentrated for a moment, and at once all the space between where they were hovering and where the floating mass of boiling gold was disappeared.

Harry smiled, chagrined, "So all the time I spent moving away from the core was an illusion, too? That's pretty impressive." Also, weird. How was Ginny at once so good with Occlumency and also so inexperienced with its basics? Maybe she was self-taught. Merlin knew Harry understood how difficult getting complete understanding without a teacher was. After all, she knew all sorts of things about fifth year transfigurations, but almost nothing about third year transfiguration.

Ginny smirked, "Thank you. Now get out of my mind."

Harry raised an eyebrow with amusement, but willingly plunged a hand back into Ginny's magical core. As she did so, Ginny stiffened, "What are you—get out! You're making him mad, get out."

Startled, Harry was completely unprepared for the violent push Ginny gave her that sent her stumbling through the molten core much faster than she'd ever phased through a core before. She gasped ineffectually as she broke free of the sticky substance, unable to catch her breath because she was mentally winded, not physically.

What in Merlin's name was that all about? That was the second time Ginny had mentioned a 'he' while she'd been in her mind, and it was the first time anyone had reacted negatively to the feeling of Harry passing through their magical cores. In fact, she couldn't recall anyone even mentioning a sensation accompanying the action. Strange.

She pondered this as she retreated back along the connection to her core, sending a pulse down the link to Snape's core as she did so to tell him she was finished. Maybe 'he' was an alternate personality of Ginny's? She'd read about split-personality disorders, and theoretically it would make sense for a person whose consciousness was split to manifest separate avatars in the mental plane, didn't it? Or maybe it was possible to create a separate consciousness within the mental sphere that had nothing to do with split personalities. If Harry's magic had its own personality, wouldn't it be possible to create a consciousness entirely of magic? Musing along these lines, Harry made her way back through her mind and eventually back out into reality.

Upon opening her eyes, she was immediately bombarded with questions from the Weasleys and Madam Pomfrey. Snape was silent, but the look in his eyes demanded answers just as plainly as speech.

Rigel started to explain, but was interrupted by an irritable, "Shut up, you lot! Oh, not you, Madam Pomfrey. Just these idiots. Honestly, what a way to wake up."

"Ginny!" Ron exclaimed, obviously relieved at the sight of his sister slowly sitting up. Well, attempting to sit up until Fred and George glomped her.

"Sister!" they cried, dramatically crushing her in a hug between them.

"Yes, yes, I'm perfectly fine, now get the heck off me," Ginny said, though her voice was a bit muffled.

Madam Pomfrey stepped forward and insisted on doing a full check up on the girl before pronouncing her as healthy as could be expected after not having eaten all day.

"I told you I was fine, ma'am," Ginny said, "I was practising my meditation and went a little too deep, that's all."

"Since when do you meditate?" Ron asked, nose wrinkling sceptically.

"Do I tell you everything? No? Then don't act like you know my life," Ginny said sharply. "After you wrote home about the Sleeping Sickness, what did you expect me to do? Wait around for my mind to get invaded by icky black tar? No thanks. I've been working hard to protect my mind. Besides, I could have taken up pole dancing for all you four would know, the way you've been avoiding me all semester."

Her brothers looked alternately embarrassed and sheepish.

"Sorry?" Fred offered, "But we'll make it up to you tomo—" he broke off at the suddenly suspicious look on Snape's face, "Some day."

After that, Ginny was forced to stay in the ward overnight 'just in case' and Rigel left to go prepare her part of the prank the twins were planning. It wasn't anything hard, but it was certainly time-consuming, and the odds of getting caught…well, it was a good thing she had her father's cloak, not to mention the Marauder's Map. If she managed to get caught with those two advantages, she probably deserved to, didn't she?

Chapter 5

Her alarm went off at exactly four am, vibrating gently under her pillow to let her know it was time to wake up.

At least, that's what it was supposed to do.

Instead, her wand wriggled its way out from the pillow and promptly jabbed her between her fifth and sixth ribs several times before attempting to bury itself into her ear. Luckily, it was too thick to do so. Unluckily, the uncomfortable feeling—was the tip of her wand wet?—made her yelp with surprise and roll straight onto the floor with a distinctive thump as a result of unconsciously trying to squirm away from it.

She froze, listening for sounds of her roommates stirring. Theo snorted into his pillow, but otherwise didn't move. Draco's hand, which was hanging off the bed, twitched a few times, but he, too, remained fast asleep. From the last bed…oh, no. Was that rustling?

"Rigel?" Blaise's voice whispered across the silent room.

She sighed, it would have to be Blaise who awoke.

"Sorry," she whispered back, "Just fell out of bed. You can go back to sleep."

"Are you not going back to sleep yourself?"

Rigel bit her lip to keep from sighing again, "I can never sleep after I've woken up already. I'll just go read in the common room. Night."

So saying, she crept out of the room in the slightly wrinkled robes she had slept in. She was about to slip out of the door when Blaise appeared beside her.

"Hard to read without a book," he commented.

"You're right," Rigel said, getting annoyed, "I'm not going to read. I'll probably go and have a clandestine meeting with my secret girlfriend from another House instead."

"Just as long as she's not blonde with pigtails," Blaise said lazily.

"Why would—never mind," Rigel muttered, "Goodnight, Blaise."

She opened the door to the hall as quietly as she could, but before she could close it behind her, Blaise stepped out behind her, clad in a forest green dressing gown that probably would have been semi-presentable if his bare feet hadn't been peeking out from underneath the hem.

"Where are you really going?" Blaise asked as they walked out into the common room.

"I'm probably going to keep lying to you if you keep asking," Rigel said, too tired to be delicate about it.

"So it's somewhere you're not supposed to be going," Blaise said, "Smart of you to wait until now, then, when even if you're caught you could feasibly just have woken up really early, and so wouldn't technically be breaking curfew."

In reality, Rigel had been planning on using the Map and cloak that were currently keeping warm in her robe pocket to avoid detection, but she supposed the early hour would be just as good. After all, even Filch stopped patrolling after one am. That was, in fact, why the twins had decided on four am as a good time to set up the prank. Filch wouldn't resume his duties until almost lunch time, which was the only way he was able to afford staying up so late every night at his age.

Still, she couldn't tell Blaise this, so she just shrugged, "If I'm not supposed to be going somewhere, do you really think it's a good idea to tag along?"

Blaise thought about this for a moment, "You don't strike me as someone foolish enough to get caught, and in any case, I think it would be more interesting to follow you than to go back to sleep."

Rigel stopped at the false-wall entrance to the common room and said, "I'm going to help some friends of mine with a prank. That's it. It's going to take at least two hours, and it will be a very tedious and boring process, not to mention if you watch me set the whole thing up you won't get to enjoy it as much with everyone else. Still want to come?"

Blaise looked taken aback at her frank answer.

"What?" Rigel said with amusement, "Did you think I was going to go for a moonlit ride on the back of a thestral? Sorry to disappoint."

Blaise smiled slyly at her, "Ah, but one thing I never am around you is disappointed. Very well, Rigel. Let's go attend to this…prank."

Rigel considered him carefully, "First, please assure me you aren't coming along so that you can turn me or my accomplices, whose names I will not give you, in to Filch."

"If my word means anything to you, consider yourself assured," Blaise said, smiling. "Shall we?"

Rigel led the way out of the common room and through the dungeon corridors. She didn't really want to bring Blaise along, but…it's not like she could actually stop him from coming. For one thing, he was physically stronger than her, and for another, though he might not turn her in, he could easily use the threat of reporting her as leverage to force her to let him come. Really, it was easier and less time-consuming to invite him along, and the odds of him reporting a fellow Slytherin, much less a roommate, were virtually zero.

They walked until they reached the second floor, where Rigel used the directions the twins had given her to find the storage closet they'd left their supplies in. It seemed the twins had already gotten started on their parts, because of the three metal wind chimes Fred was supposed to stash there, there was only one left. She took out the wind chime carefully after casting a silencing charm on it.

"What's that for?" Blaise asked bemusedly.

"You'll see," Rigel said, grinning. She closed the door and started back down toward the first floor. Fred and George hadn't gotten to the second floor yet, but she supposed they were starting from the top. They were responsible for the second through seventh floors, while Rigel would deal with the first floor, the basement, and the dungeons.

When they reached the first floor, Rigel approached the first sconce and held the wind chime up in front of her. She glanced between it and the torch-holder, concentrating hard. Along every corridor in Hogwarts, there were torches, held in place against the stone by sconces. On every sconce, there was a decorative rendition of the Hogwarts crest that dangled like a talisman. After another long look at the wind chime to make sure she'd gotten the correct form in her mind, she pointed her wand at the dangling crest and asked her magic to perform the transfiguration George had spent the better part of three hours teaching her to do.

The next moment, the sconce supported a small metal wind chime, no bigger than a water goblet, which was hastily silenced as soon as it began to flutter in the slight draught of the corridor.

Satisfied, Rigel turned down the hall and walked to the next sconce, Blaise trailing behind her. After the third transfiguration, Blaise asked, incredulously, "Are you going to do this for every torch bracket in the whole castle?"

Rigel shook her head, "Just the first floor, the basement, and the dungeons. My friends will do the other six levels."

"So you weren't kidding when you said it would be tedious," Blaise said, "Need any help? My transfigurations aren't bad."

"Can you link them?" Rigel asked.

"Can I what them?"

"You can do the silencing charms, if you want," Rigel said, "Not too strong, since they need to wear off before breakfast."

Blaise shook his head wryly, "And you think you're uninteresting? Hardly. All right, I'll silence the chimes as you transfigure them. I don't know if I can do over a hundred silencing charms in a row, though."

"You can stop if you get tired," Rigel said, thinking absently that it was a lot of chimes they were supposed to transfigure. She wondered how Fred and George would manage, but then realized they would probably be fine, being both fourth years and from what she could tell from the brief glance she'd had of their magical cores the night before, pretty powerful themselves.

She and Blaise worked their way from the first floor to the dungeons over the next couple of hours. Even Blaise had to admit the corridors looked pretty cool with all the wind chimes hanging from the torches.

"It'll be a pain to clean up, though," Blaise said, "Here's hoping we don't get caught."

"That's what the linking transfigurations are for," Rigel said, "When a transfiguration is linked to another, whether a regular transformation or a conjuration, then as soon as one of the linked objects is vanished or reverted, the rest follow suit."

"That's…useful," Blaise finally said. "When do we learn those?"

"In a couple of years, probably," Rigel said vaguely, "So as soon as I transfigure one of my chimes back, the rest will revert as well. Same for my accomplices. It was the only way we could get the house elves to leave the chimes until lunch."

"I see," Blaise said thoughtfully, "And if it doesn't cause caretaker Filch extra work, he's less likely to devote an abnormal amount of effort to rooting out the perpetrators."

"I hadn't thought of that," Rigel said, though Fred and George probably had. They seemed to think of everything.

She and Blaise didn't do the whole of the dungeons, obviously. Instead, they finished the most frequently traveled routes and hurried back to the Slytherin common room to get changed for the day. Rigel came out of the bathroom from showering and changing as Draco and Theo were finishing getting ready for the day as well. They headed to breakfast with the other second years just as the silencing charms on the chimes in the dungeons were beginning to wear off.

As they walked, one by one the chimes dangling from the torch brackets were set into motion by the displaced air. Soft, tinkling sound echoed through the corridors, bouncing off the walls and mingling beautifully with the sound of the next chime, and the next, and the next.

Pansy gasped and pressed her hands together, beaming, "Oh, what a clever idea! Putting chimes in the dungeons is sure to liven them up a little."

As they ascended the stairs to the Entrance Hall, however, it became apparent to the rest that the chimes went much further than the dungeons. Everyone was talking about it as they took their places at the tables.

"Joanna from Ravenclaw says they're even in the four main towers," one fifth year was telling his friend, "The only place they haven't been found is inside the classrooms themselves and in the Owlery—good thing, too, as I don't expect the birds would appreciate the sound like we do."

"Imagine how much effort it must have been," Theo commented, "It can't have been one person who did all this overnight."

"They wouldn't have even had the night," Blaise said, an amused gleam in his eyes that Rigel hoped no one else caught on to, "After all, the prefects and teachers patrol until one or two am, not to mention Filch's rounds."

"It would have taken half a dozen people at least to transfigure them all before anyone woke up this morning," Pansy said thoughtfully, "I wonder who would do such a thing?"

"Someone with too much free time," Draco said dryly, "Still, it's made the morning much more interesting than it would have been otherwise."

"Do you think the teachers will take them down?" Theo asked, "They don't seem too upset about it."

Indeed, the teachers appeared to be animatedly discussing the prank (well, most of the teachers), but none of them looked particularly angry.

"The chimes aren't that loud," Millicent pointed out, "And as long as they aren't in the classrooms themselves, they can barely be considered disruptive. I bet they'll leave them for the house elves to put away."

"But if the house elves were going to get rid of them, wouldn't they have already done so?" Pansy said, "They're very efficient, usually."

"Maybe they were bribed," Blaise said innocently.

"Bribe a house elf?" Theo snorted, "With what, more work?"

"Do you think it was your friends the Weasley twins, Rigel?" Pansy asked.

Rigel was saved from having to answer by a letter being dropped onto her plate. It was from Archie. It wasn't coded as sensitive, so she slit it open at the table and began to read.

Dear Rigel,

How's term going so far? I hope you're not learning as much as I am, because I feel a bit overwhelmed by how quickly our professors here are pushing us into the deep end. Last week we learned how to repair shattered joints, and the method is a bit tricky, so I've enclosed a copy of my notes to help you, as the textbook is fair useless on this one.

Hermione was surprised by how different I looked after a summer away, but none of my other friends seemed to notice. Mione's always been very observant, though. Do you have any friends like that? Ones you just can't get anything by? They're great to have on your side, but don't ever try to pretend you did your homework if you didn't—it won't work!

I received some very interesting news about my mum this morning, so I thought I'd shoot you a letter right away. Be on the lookout for news from Sirius, because I think they were going to tell you next. I hope you're as surprised as I was, and to ensure that you are, I'm not giving you any hints.

Also, I think someone I met at work this summer misses me, because I heard there was someone asking about me around school, and I'm told the man definitely had an English accent, though it was apparently quite uncouth. No one's approached me directly, though, so I guess my new friend is shy.

Anyway, I hope you're doing well. I heard from Uncle Sirius you tried out for the Quidditch team—do let me know how that works out. You'll also find my new syllabus for the year in the envelope, so send me yours right away so we can compare.

All the best,

Harry

Rigel picked up the envelope to look for the extra pages, but it was empty. Frowning, she glanced around to see if it had fallen out somewhere, and found Draco looking over the handwritten notes curiously while Pansy tried discreetly to get him to put them back.

"Um, Draco?" Rigel looked at the notes in his hand pointedly, "Can I have those back?"

Draco looked up, not one iota of guilt on his face, "Yeah, in a second. This is interesting. Did your cousin send it?"

"Yes," Rigel said, "Those are her notes on one of the Healing lessons she found particularly difficult."

"Yes," Draco mused, "It looks like a process for repairing joints that have been severely traumatized. Why'd she send it to you?"

"I'm interested in Healing," Rigel said casually, "I learn what I can on my own, and Harry is kind enough to send me her syllabus and some of the more difficult notes so that I can keep up with her curriculum when I have time."

Draco stared at her and even Pansy seemed a bit surprised.

"Just how much school work do you do, Rye?" Draco shook his head sadly, "It's like you're allergic to free time, so you fill it with all these things you don't have to do. Learning Healing. Studying Occlumency and extra Potions lessons and reading up on fifth and sixth year material—don't think I haven't noticed. Then there's the brewing you do for no apparent reason in the evenings, and you get up at the crack of dawn every morning for some reason I haven't been able to fathom yet, wearing absolutely hideous clothes, and—and—don't you ever just take a break?"

"That's why I joined the Quidditch team," Rigel said sweetly, "I'm sure that will be very relaxing."

Draco groaned, "I forgot you'll even have Quidditch practices to deal with now. You're going to run yourself into the ground!"

Rigel shook her head, "You make it sound like I'm doing everything separately. I can multi-task a lot of it. I do most of my regular schoolwork during class when everyone else is practising the spells. I read up on material I'm interested in, like Healing, advanced Transfigurations, Occlumency and the like during my boring classes, like History, and during my breaks. That covers the middle part of my day, and in the evenings I brew, which is a good opportunity to study because of the down time required as a lot of potions simmer, and in the mornings I work out. I get my eight hours of sleep, and all my meals, and I'll be even more physically active when Quidditch starts. Overall, I'd say my lifestyle is pretty healthy."

Pansy pursed her lips, "That's just it, though, Rigel. You've been skipping lunch several days a week lately. And how can you be getting enough sleep if you both stay up late and get up early?"

"I'm not skipping lunch," Rigel said, thinking of pleasant hours spent learning French from Binny. She was really making good progress on her conversational understanding of the language, though she couldn't spell it to save her life, "I always grab lunch from the kitchens those days while I'm studying. I just don't have time to come to the Great Hall. And I don't stay up that late."

"That's where you go every morning?" Draco asked, frowning, "Running? Well, that explains the clothes…and the smell when you come back, actually."

"Excuse me for sweating," Rigel rolled her eyes, "I need the exercise."

"Not with Quidditch starting up," Draco said.

"It's not the same type of exercise," Rigel argued, "Quidditch is good cardio, but I'm working on strength training, too."

"We just don't want you to over work yourself," Pansy said softly, "You have to admit you have a tendency toward doing so, if the result seems to outweigh fatigue in your mind."

Rigel smiled, "I have such good friends. Tell you what, as soon as you think I'm excessively tired, sick, or in some other way overdoing it, let me know and I'll listen, okay? As long as I'm healthy, though, I'll just continue with what I'm doing."

They didn't look happy about it, but there wasn't really anything for them to say after that. Rigel was grateful for their silence. She didn't need to be watched over like she was self-destructive, and the closer they watched her the more likely it was that they would pick up on something she didn't want them to. Yes, her life was busy, but she was handling it just fine. Besides, most of the things she did were completely necessary in a way that Draco and Pansy, who didn't know she and Archie's situation, couldn't possibly understand. So, really, what did they know?

As September bled into October, nothing really changed, unless one counted the autumn leaves, but considering how many leaves there were on the Hogwarts grounds, Rigel couldn't imagine anyone wanting to actually count them.

She went through her classes like clockwork, completing assignments and learning magic at an almost abysmally slow pace. Luckily, Rigel had extracurricular studies to keep her mind occupied. As for her body, it was occupied as well—in Quidditch practices. Flint, it turned out, was not at all exaggerated by his reputation. In fact, he seemed to be quite a bit more harshly critical and ruthlessly ambitious in his expectations than the rumours had made him out to be. At least, that's how it seemed from Rigel's point of view, which was, admittedly, often clouded by fog, dirt, rain, muck produced by the combination of dirt and rain, and occasionally an actual blindfold when Flint was experiencing one of his particularly creative phases.

Still, getting to fly all the time, no matter how absurd and demeaning the conditions, certainly kept her happy, so with mind, body, and soul thus satiated, Rigel began October with a transcendent sort of peace.

It was at that point, of course, that something had to go wrong.

She had been conscripted into another of the Weasley twins' brilliant pranks, and although she did enjoy hanging out with the duo, and she did want to start establishing Rigel Black's reputation as a prankster, this particular prank was much more tedious than most.

It was based on a muggle Christmas tradition, and basically it was a prank that slowly but inexorably drew everyone in the castle into its game. At first, no one even knew it was a prank. The twins had transfigured a spool of thread into a wooden puppet with a pointed wizard hat and a wide grin on its blank wooden face. The puppet had then been placed quite randomly in an alcove just off the Great Hall, positioned so that the puppet's head, with its shock of red hair jutting out from under its hat, was just visible peeking out into the corridor. Only a couple of people noticed the poor, forgotten puppet that day, and the next day the puppet was moved to another innocuous location—perched on the railway to the Astronomy tower stairs.

It took nearly a full week for people to start noticing the puppet more. Each day the puppet was somewhere different, and as people mentioned the peculiarity to their friends and compared notes they realized that someone was doing it on purpose.

After that, it became a game to see who could find the puppet first when it was moved the next morning. People began carrying around cameras and film-developing potion, so that if they came across the puppet they could capture evidence. The more serious competitors all included some sort of time stamp—a watch or the tempus spell visible in the picture—and someone, probably Fred or George, had started a bulletin board in the Great Hall where students could post their pictures each day and figure out who'd won.

The Headmaster seemed to delight in the game, and a couple of the photos showed a pajama-clad Dumbledore happily shaking the puppet's wooden hand at some absurdly early hour of the morning. Because of this, or perhaps because none of the teachers really cared that much, the bulletin board became a permanent fixture over the next few weeks, and impromptu prizes were arranged by the more indulgent school prefects for whoever found the puppet first each day.

What was for the rest of the school a mildly interesting entertainment or a fun and engaging diversion was for Rigel a complete drain on her time in the mornings. The twins had all but handed the prank over to her after giving her the initial model for the puppet, saying that it was a good chance for her to spread her prank-making wings.

She was not, of course, retrieving the puppet each day and moving it before anyone else woke up. That was a good way to get caught—after all, Filch, the professors, or even one of the more enthusiastic students would have only had to wait around at night where the puppet was for her to come get it. Instead, the original puppet was given to the house elves to hide away once Rigel had gotten its appearance memorized, and Woody—as he was affectionately, if rather unimaginatively, called by the student population—was now nothing more than a conditional transfiguration.

Conditional transfigurations were pretty much exactly what they sounded like. The transfiguration was dependent upon one or more conditions pre-determined by the caster at the time the spell was cast. A condition could be anything. It could be as simple as a time limit after which the transfiguration automatically reversed or as complicated as a series of very specific actions that must be completed before the transfiguration reversed. Percy had told Rigel that McGonagall had claimed one could perform a conditional transfiguration so complicated that transfigured objects behaved more like animated objects, responding to any number of external stimuli depending upon the conditions set.

Rigel wasn't doing anything like that, of course, but the prank wasn't exactly a boat ride across the Black Lake either. Woody was set every morning at 4:30 am, and 24 hours later the transfiguration was conditioned to wear off. Then, whatever mundane object had been used in the transfiguration would be abandoned where it fell. For this reason, Rigel had to be extremely careful not to let any of the objects used to base the transfiguration off of reveal anything about herself. She didn't choose anything lying around the Slytherin common room, and she also was very careful to avoid shedding hairs around the scene of the 'crime' in case some wise guy picked one up and tested it with Polyjuice potion. She also had to make sure she was ready every morning at 4:30 to transfigure something else into Woody the minute the old transfiguration wore off.

Luckily, her roommates were used to her getting up early, and she could perform the transfiguration on her way outside to work out, so she had a semi-plausible alibi as long as she wasn't caught somewhere too outlandish.

On the second Thursday in October, Rigel had just about used up her ideas for places to put the puppet. She couldn't re-use old hiding places, obviously, and it had to be somewhere that wasn't obvious, but which could be found with a little effort. That morning she decided that since the day before she'd put Woody in the boys' locker room down at the Quidditch pitch, she should put it somewhere girls frequented, to make it fair. Unfortunately, if she were caught sneaking in or out of a girl's bathroom as Rigel, there would be questions that no amount of prevarication could answer.

So that day Rigel had on the blonde wig that she had once rescued from the lost and found, as well as the glasses she often wore in her 'Gryffindor' disguise at the Library. She had changed into a Hufflepuff tie and kept her head down as she hurried down the third floor corridor toward the girls' lavatory. In truth, she didn't feel very guilty about sneaking into the girls' bathroom, mostly because she was, in fact, a girl, and therefore wasn't doing anything nefarious. She did, however, realize what it would look like if anyone recognized her, and it was this knowledge that added a slight pink tint to her cheeks as she slipped into the bathroom.

There was no one inside, of course, because it was so early in the day, so Rigel made quick work of transfiguring a spare roll of toilet paper into Woody. She positioned the puppet so that he was sitting cross-legged on one of the lowered toilet seats, with one hand up under his chin, as though the puppet were thinking very hard about something.

Smiling with soft amusement, she slipped out of the bathroom once more and nearly jumped out of her skin when a jovial voice said, "Why hello there!"

Rigel whirled around, one hand clutching at her heart with exaggerated surprise, and said, "Oh! Professor Lockhart. Good morning."

Lockhart beamed cheerfully down at her. He was already dressed for the day in a deep orange overcoat with silver pumpkins on the trimming and a hint of lace peeking out from the collar of the shirt beneath. "Fancy meeting a student up and about so early," he said grandly, "Of course, when I was a youth I was always among the first to start the day, but children nowadays…well…you can't blame them. They just don't know how serious a world it really is. But it is so wonderful to see a young person like yourself already prepared to face the day."

"Thank you," Rigel said uncertainly.

"So where are you off to, young miss?" Lockhart asked curiously.

For a moment, her mind blanked completely. What could she say? She couldn't say she was going to work out, because that was something Rigel Black did every day, not some no-name Hufflepuff girl who didn't exist. As Lockhart began to frown, she realized she'd taken too long thinking about it and blurted out, "Using the bathroom."

Lockhart's eyebrows rose, "Yes, well, I assumed so considering…" he glanced delicately at the bathroom door behind her, "Awful long way to walk from the Hufflepuff dorms just to use the bathroom, though. In fact…it's a bit…strange. Isn't it?"

"Oh, um," Rigel fumbled, and cursed herself for being so stupid. If she got caught by Lockhart of all people she would never forgive herself. It was just so early, and although her body was used to working this early in the morning, her mind was still half asleep, "I didn't come up here just to use the lavatory, of course, I just meant…that was my immediate intention in being here…" she trailed off, having successfully made herself sound even more idiotic than before.

Even Lockhart seemed to notice. He peered at her shrewdly, then glanced back at the bathroom, then checked the time in his watch and gasped in an exaggerated manner that made Rigel a bit queasy about what it meant for her.

"A-ha! But of course, I suspected something like this," Lockhart smiled cheekily down at her with a twinkle to his eye, "A student wandering around at just a few minutes after 4:30 in the morning? Don't think I haven't heard Filch complaining about how the puppet disappears every day at this time," he wagged a finger at her playfully and she internally groaned. Lockhart stepped behind her and made a show of knocking on the door to the girl's bathroom loudly, calling, "Anyone in there? No? Let's go check it out, then, shall we?" He clamped a hand on her shoulder and was about to steer her into the bathroom when a second voice made the both of them freeze. Lockhart with surprise, and Rigel with horror. Oh, no. Not him. And yet, it was.

"Pray tell, Professor Lockhart, just what you intend to do after manhandling that student into the female lavatory?" Professor Snape's voice was nearly a growl, low and dangerous, and Rigel was close enough to hear Lockhart gulp with trepidation before turning around to face the Potions Master.

"I say, Severus, this really isn't…that is, the situation isn't how it might appear…" Lockhart looked at quite a loss for words, the hand he still had on Rigel's shoulder starting to shake nervously.

Suddenly realizing what Snape must think to see Lockhart pushing a young girl into the girl's bathroom at 4:30 am with no one around, Rigel had the completely inappropriate impulse to laugh. It was just so absurd, not least because she was a girl pretending to be a boy pretending to be a girl, and she was sure that boy or girl Lockhart really hadn't meant anything like that. He was an idiot, but probably not a paedophile. She bit her tongue to keep from smiling, and concentrated on looking at the floor. With any luck, Lockhart and Snape would focus on each other and not on her.

Snape sneered at Lockhart, "Do explain, then, what business a teacher could have with a student in an out of the way lavatory at this hour of the morning."

Lockhart laughed weakly, "Well, you see, I was just…the puppet, I mean, going to check if…yes, well…"

Snape, somehow, made enough sense of Lockhart's mutterings to glean a basic understanding of the situation. He whipped out his wand and cast, "Homenum revelio," at the girls' restroom. When nothing happened, he stowed his wand away and strode briskly into the bathroom, somehow not looking at all foolish doing so. A moment later, he had come back out, and he spared Rigel a quick glance before saying to Lockhart, "Congratulations, Gilderoy. It seems once again your gift for sniffing out mysteries has reared its head; you've caught the student responsible for the ongoing puppet prank."

In a flash, Lockhart was back to his usual self, "I did have a feeling, and like I always say, it pays to follow your gut. Still, it was rather clever to get so far without being caught, Miss…, forgive me, Miss, but I don't seem to recall your name. Still learning all the students, you know."

"Am I going to get into trouble, Professors?" Rigel asked softly, pitching her voice a little higher than normal and not looking up from the stones, "Only, I wasn't hurting anyone. It's just a bit of fun, and it's not really against school rules to practise transfiguration outside of the classroom, as long as one doesn't perform the magic in the corridors."

Lockhart chortled, "Oh-ho! She's got a point, Severus, you must admit. I suppose since no harm was done, there's no reason to—"

"Thank you, Gilderoy," Severus said sharply, "I will oversee the situation from here. You, come with me." Rigel did not have to look up to know that he was referring to her. Snape strode off toward the stairs and Lockhart gave her a commiserating pat on the back before she slowly set off after the Potions Master.

Snape continued to walk briskly until they reached his office in the dungeons, at which point he took out his wand to remove the wards and then gestured impatiently for her to precede him. Rigel meekly slipped into the office. She kept her blonde head down, trying to project an appearance of timidity and contrition.

Snape shut the door with a firm click and stalked over to sit behind his desk. At the sight of her standing there, one toe fidgeting against the flagstones, he scoffed impatiently, "Enough, Mr. Black. Take that ridiculous thing off and explain yourself this instant."

Rigel couldn't hide the shock on her face as she whipped her head up to stare at him. "How did you know?" she blurted, "You barely looked at me."

"I did not need to look at you," Snape said dismissively, "Have you forgotten Mr. Malfoy's birthday party already? You are the only student at this school with no discernable magical aura. Not to mention my familiarity with your Occlumency shields, and the fact that unlike Professor Lockhart I do know every student in this school and was able to recognize the duplicity by simple process of elimination."

Rigel winced. She hadn't thought of that, though she should have. She reached up and slid the wig off of her hair slowly, blatantly stalling for time as she put it away in her bag. Snape sent a very pointed look at the yellow and black striped tie around her neck, and Rigel quickly took the Hufflepuff tie off as well, trying not to feel amused at the put out expression of distaste on his face.

"I suppose you'd like an explanation now," Rigel said hesitantly.

"I would," Snape said flatly, "Starting with where you got that ridiculous disguise and ending with why you were about to willingly enter a female lavatory with a member of the male staff."

Rigel thought 'willingly' was a bit of a stretch, but decided to just get the explanation over with instead of commenting, "The disguise was originally for my use in the Library." At Snape's raised eyebrow, she clarified, "It would seem that Madam Pince harbours some ill will toward me because of my father's…colourful history with the Hogwarts Library. Something about catching an entire section of the place on fire."

For a moment, Snape almost looked amused, in a darkly satisfied sort of way, and Rigel got the uneasy feeling that he'd been involved in the Library incident.

"Because of that, she banned me from the Library the first week I started here," Rigel went on, sighing, "It's really been a pain, considering how often I use the Library, but with my disguises I can at least go and read books there, though I still can't check any books out. Anyway, that's what the disguise is supposed to be for. This morning, I didn't go to the Library, though," Rigel examined the desk carefully as she admitted to the rest of it, "I was using the disguise so that my going into the girls' bathroom wouldn't seem so suspicious, although now that I've been caught it seems more suspicious that I wore a disguise, I suppose."

Snape gave a sardonic lift of the brow that Rigel thought was roughly equivalent to an unspoken, You think?

"I wasn't doing anything…nefarious," Rigel felt compelled to add, "I would never try anything so unsavoury, Professor. I had to put the puppet somewhere girls went, though, since yesterday it was in the boys' locker room."

Professor Snape didn't say anything, merely looked at her with a shuttered expression.

"I'm sorry," Rigel offered, "I know I probably embarrassed Slytherin House, even if Professor Lockhart had no idea who I was. I am also sorry for going into the girls' bathroom, but I did check if anyone was in there first, and I didn't think it would be an issue so early in the morning."

"And the puppet?" Snape prompted, "What have you to say about that, Mr. Black?"

"Well, I know it's a bit silly," Rigel said carefully, "But it doesn't in itself break any rules, does it?"

Snape scowled at her, "Just a bit of fun, was it? You think you can become a Potions Master before you're thirty by wasting your time with nonsense like this? You said you were focused, Mr. Black. You swore to me there was nothing you wanted more than this."

"There isn't! I am," Rigel said vehemently, "It's just a prank. It means nothing, and it hardly takes up any of my time. Are my studies lacking? Did you have any inkling that I might be distracted before you caught me with this?"

"That is not the point," Snape said, frowning, "This isn't the Rigel Black I know. Where is the boy that doesn't care for frivolities that distract him from his studies? I know you are not the mastermind behind this scheme, but why would you even agree to participate in it? Do not think that going along with others is enough to make them true friends—"

"It's nothing like that," Rigel said quickly, "I have too many friends as it is. I don't want any more."

"Then why did you get involved with this farce? What could you possibly gain from engaging in such a pointless, wasteful application of your talents for the sole purpose of cruel entertainment at others' expense? I thought you were better than that, Rigel Black."

"I am," Rigel said, frustrated with the way Snape was painting things, "I'd never do anything mean to anyone. The puppet is completely harmless—it's not even a prank, really. It's not a big deal."

"But you've just said yourself it doesn't mean anything to you," Snape said exasperatedly, "Why, then, would you do it? You have defended your actions but have yet to give a plausible motive for them. Am I to assume you perform random acts of tom foolery for no reason?"

Rigel shook her head, "It doesn't mean anything to me, sir, but it means something to…others."

Snape favoured her with a pointed look, "While I do not question your character, Mr. Black, you have never struck me as a particularly altruistic person—at least not one who would go out of his way for the sole purpose of cheering up his peers when they have no need for such a diversion."

"It's not them, exactly," Rigel said, internally squirming. How could she explain in a way that didn't sound pathetic? "Professor, you have to understand, I…my family is really big on pranks. I know I don't have to tell you that," she hurried on, seeing his face darken, "It's just that you're right, okay? I'm not all that interested in them, but…I sort of have to be. If I don't, my dad will worry about me. Well, not worry about me, exactly, but I've always been different than my family expected or maybe hoped. It's already a lot for my dad that I enjoy potions and book learning so much, and I don't want to…"

"Disappoint him," Snape finished, sounding as though he had finally obtained something that had long eluded him, only to find he didn't care for the feel of it in his grasp. Rigel snuck a look at him, but his face was blank and unreadable, "Tell me, Mr. Black, is your father aware of exactly how closely you are studying potions under my tutelage? Does he have any idea that I am training you, specifically, outside of the regular student curriculum?"

Rigel felt her stomach sink pitifully, "Not exactly, sir. No, actually, not at all."

Snape gazed at her wordlessly, which somehow felt worse than if he'd shouted. "Are you ashamed, perhaps, to be working with me? Are you somehow embarrassed to be given this opportunity that other young potioneers would go down on bended knee for?"

"No," Rigel protested, "I'm grateful, you have no idea—you can't imagine how—I just can't tell them. Not my family, they wouldn't understand. It would only cause problems and…and I cause them enough problems as it is."

"So what is your plan, exactly?" Snape asked coolly, "Do you intend to hide the extent of your studies from them forever?"

Yes, Rigel thought stubbornly, I do. She didn't say so, but Snape must have seen the answer shining below the surface of her expression.

"Foolish boy," Snape snapped, "You cannot pretend to idiocy all your life."

"I'm not," Rigel said, "I'm just not saying how I'm learning, exactly." She winced, realizing what that sounded like, "It's not that I don't want to give you credit—I do. I will, just not until I graduate and get my Mastery. If they knew what I was doing before then, even without your name thrown into it, I wouldn't be able to realize my goals."

Snape scoffed, "Even I do not think your father so childish as to deny his own son happiness out of spite. Such a thing is beneath Gryffindors, after all."

Rigel shook her head slowly, "You don't have all the facts, and I cannot provide them to you, but believe me when I say that if my family found out the truth before I graduated, they would pull me out of Hogwarts so fast it would be as though Rigel Black never existed."

Snape sat back in his chair hard, a look of thinly veiled shock on his face at that pronouncement, "It is obvious that you believe this, so perhaps there is some amount of truth to what you say," he said slowly, "This development is disturbing, though it does explain certain things about you I had dismissed as idiosyncrasies. Nevertheless, I do not see how this double-sided game you are playing can continue for much longer. At the end of this year you will be expected to consider electives for your OWL classes, and as such to have some idea as to a future career path. What does your father expect you to do with your life if not potions?"

"I have intimated a desire to become a Healer," Rigel said carefully, trying to mesh her own and Archie's ambitions in a way that didn't leave too many holes in their story, "A lot of Healing has to do with potions, so skill with and interest in the subject lends itself easily to the field. In fact, at times I have considered actually becoming a Healer after I get my Potions Mastery. It would be a way to do a great amount of good with my training, at least."

Snape considered this for a moment, "Even if you became a Healer after first becoming a Potions Master, you would still need to begin training in the subject now. It would mean extra work, but if your plans are truly as you say, perhaps it would be best if I were to arrange something with Madam Pomfrey after your regular lessons. She can begin teaching you the basics, if nothing else."

"My cousin Harry attends school in America," Rigel said, slightly surprised that Snape was willing to arrange extra lessons for her simply because she said she might want to become a Healer one day, "She is actually studying Healing there, precisely because she knows I need to learn it both to convince our family it is my primary area of focus, and in the event that I do decide on becoming a Healer."

Snape's eyebrows rose even higher, "You have already begun studying Healing? That is a dangerous discipline to attempt to self-learn. How far have you progressed?"

Rigel shrugged, "I'm about at the same level as Harry is. We keep pace with one another's curricula pretty easily—"

"One another's?" Snape broke in, frowning.

Rigel clamped her mouth shut. She shouldn't have said that…or wait…maybe that would make the most sense in the end? When they switched back how better to explain how she had Archie's knowledge and he had hers than to simply say that they'd taught one another everything they learned? It was even true, only in reverse of what people would think. Still, how could she tell Snape that without making it seem as though she was sharing the knowledge he had entrusted to only her with someone he'd never met? Because of course she wasn't, but in the end Harriett Potter's knowledge would seem to come from nowhere unless Rigel Black had shared it with her. Her parents could believe she'd self studied all her knowledge, but to other potioneers it would be obvious she had been trained somehow—after all, some of the things she would know simply weren't written down. They were passed in trust from master to apprentice, and wasn't that the cincher? Trust. Snape had trusted her with his teachings, and she was metaphorically (and in his eyes literally) betraying his knowledge to another.

Perhaps it wasn't so dramatic. He hadn't really imparted any significant secrets yet, had he? Maybe he wouldn't be irate over the technicalities of the situation.

Realizing she'd once again been silent too long in contemplation, Rigel said, "Yes. It would have been natural for me to go to AIM to learn Healing, but luckily my father insisted I attend Hogwarts, so I was able to come here to study potions without it being obvious I'd chosen one over the other. My cousin, on the other hand, wanted to come to Hogwarts as well, as she had a very similar interest in potions, but couldn't, of course, so since she was going to AIM anyway, she started in the Healing tract to help me out. The potions tract at AIM isn't all that impressive, so since the Healing tract is quite good, she's learning something useful in any case."

Snape was rubbing his temples now, "You have once again managed to somehow completely complicate what should have been straightforward. Am I to understand that you are here to learn potions, but your family thinks you are here against your will because they think you'd rather be in America learning Healing, and that your cousin actually is in America against her will, and so decided to learn Healing for you by proxy to help your possibly-fake future career path along, and in return you…what? Tutor her in the things you learn at Hogwarts?"

"Ah, yes?" Rigel said, now a bit confused herself, "That sounds right. Only, I suppose I should ask if it would be okay with you if I taught her some…er, a lot, of what you teach me about potions? Only she's a big fan of yours, and will probably decide to take the Potions Mastery exam herself at some point."

This, it appeared, was too much for Snape's rational mind to comprehend. He positively gaped at her with bemusement, "Harriett Potter, child of James Potter, is a…fan…of my work?"

Rigel hid a smile, "Yes, sir. She was ever so disappointed to be going to AIM, which in her words has not seen the light of a potions periodical in nearly a decade."

Snape snorted seemingly involuntarily, but quickly pulled himself together, "You have given me a lot to process, as usual, Mr. Black. For now, you will be receiving a detention on Friday for entering the women's lavatory. I will speak to Madam Pince personally and ensure that you never have need of so ridiculous a disguise again. Then I will see Madam Pomfrey and attempt to work out a couple of days a week for her to at the very least supervise you so that you do not inadvertently kill yourself trying to learn Healing on your own."

"Thank you, sir," Rigel said, really meaning it for all that he'd done for her.

"Next, I want your word that whatever I teach you goes no further than Miss Potter," Snape said, his neutral tone belying the weight of the words he was speaking, "If you vouch for her skill, then I am sure she is not completely incompetent, though at some point you will arrange a meeting so that I may assess that for myself, and you and I will be having a much more in depth conversation about what exactly you and your cousin are doing with your lives. For now, however, we are due for breakfast. Do you have any immediate questions?"

"Who is my detention with on Friday?" Rigel asked.

Snape sighed, an annoyed but resigned sound, "Me. We might as well make use of the time, and I have a vague suspicion that you wouldn't respond to normal disciplinary actions even if I were to set you to clean cauldrons all night."

"I like cleaning cauldrons," Rigel said.

"And I have reached the point where nothing surprises me about you anymore," Snape said tiredly, "Go to breakfast, Mr. Black, and if I ever catch you entering a women's bathroom again, with or without a teacher, I will excommunicate you from Slytherin House faster than you can say Salazar."

After that, Rigel was more careful in any pranks she got involved in with the twins, and Professor Snape seemed to have decided to look the other way where her extracurricular antics were involved. He did convince Madam Pomfrey to meet with Rigel once every two weeks to assess her progress and correct any mistakes she was making, but for the most part her Healing studies continued under her own steam.

The best thing that came out of her conversation with Snape was the access she now had to the Library. Madam Pince hadn't said a word when Rigel went as herself the first time, and after a couple of weeks she didn't even give Rigel the evil eye when she checked out a book. It probably helped that she always returned them timely and with no visible signs of wear.

The day before Halloween, however, she was vastly disappointed in the Library. She had an essay to do for Flint's NEWT Runes class, and it was reaching the point where she could no longer get by with mere theory on the essays. It wasn't that the Library didn't have the information she needed to complete the essay, rather, it was that Rigel couldn't make any useful sense of the information. She didn't have enough of a foundation to go any further in the theoretical study of Runes without backtracking and learning everything from the beginning. Unfortunately, she also didn't have time to do that before the next essay was due.

Since books weren't helping her, she needed to find a person who could. Percy took Runes, but she doubted he'd be able to swallow her wanting to add sixth year Runes to their transfiguration studies. Flint would probably know everything she needed, but somehow she didn't see him helping her complete his own homework assignment, even if it would make things easier.

Alesana Selwyn also knew Runes, or at least how to read them, which probably implied some knowledge of their application, but Rigel got the feeling Selwyn was still a bit touchy about the thestral thing from the beginning of the school year. She also wasn't eager to owe Selwyn any favours—who knew what she'd ask in return?

That left a total of zero people she knew who were taking Runes. Great.

Rigel shelved the useless books on Runic theory carefully and headed back toward the common room. Surely there was someone in Slytherin House who knew a thing or two about Runes…and didn't mind talking to younger students…and wasn't terribly suspicious. Rigel sighed. Anyone not smart enough to be suspicious wouldn't be smart enough to answer her questions. Still, it was more productive than staring blankly at a book of gibberish.

She had barely gotten through the common room wall when she was waylaid by a nervous looking Millicent.

"Hi, Rigel," she said, holding a notebook on one hand and tapping the fingers of her other hand against her leg.

"Hello, Millicent," Rigel said, "What are you up to?"

"Potions homework," Millicent said immediately, "And it's really hard."

"Oh," Rigel said, blinking, "I'm sorry to hear that."

Millicent hesitated, peering at Rigel as though searching for some clue. Rigel stared blankly back at her, not sure what she wanted, so Millicent just sighed and said, "Will you help me with my potions homework, Rigel?"

"Oh," Rigel said, smiling slightly, "Sure."

"Well—" the other girl paused, "Wait, just like that? You'll really help?"

Rigel raised an eyebrow, "Of course I will. Why wouldn't I? We're friends."

Millicent shrugged, "Well, yes, but you never have before."

Rigel frowned, "You never asked me before."

Millicent stared at her for a second, then said, slowly, "That's true, but the rest of us do almost all of our homework together. Since you never joined, I figured you weren't interested in peer tutoring, at least not giving it out."

"I didn't know," Rigel said, wondering how long that had been going on. Draco and Pansy almost never asked for her help with anything, so she'd assumed they were either too proud to ask or were too smart to need help. She didn't do her homework around her friends for obvious reasons—if they kept careful enough tabs on her homework load, it would be obvious she was either doing more than twice as much as the rest of them, half of which was on topics they wouldn't cover for years, or else lying when she said she had more homework to do after she'd finished all of her 'official' homework. Maybe she'd been missing out on more than just homework help, though.

"Well, you're always really busy, I guess," Millicent said uneasily, "Anyway, you can come now, right?"

Rigel mentally shrugged. She wasn't making any headway with Flint's essay anyway, so why not? "Sure, now is good for me."

"Great, thanks," Millicent led her over to a secluded corner of the common room where the second year Slytherins did indeed seem to be gathered around a table, comparing various homework notes. She never would have noticed them if she was just casually walking through the common room, but when Millicent pulled two empty chairs for them the others looked up. When they saw Rigel, several of her year mates did a double take.

"Rigel!" Theo exclaimed, "What are you doing here?"

Pansy nudged him admonishingly with her shoulder, "Don't say it like that. Hello, Rigel. How's your afternoon coming along?"

"Well enough, Pansy, thank you," Rigel said, sitting down next to Millicent, "Good to see you, too, Theo."

"I guess I owe Millie a sickle," Theo said, ignoring her muttered 'don't call me that' in favour of grinning unrepentantly, "I bet her you'd be too busy to come over."

Rigel wasn't sure how to respond to that. Did she really come off so aloof to her classmates?

"And you owe me two sickles," Blaise added with a satisfied smile, "Because I bet you that as soon as someone actually made him aware of our little group, he'd be perfectly amiable to joining in."

"How could he not know?" Theo rolled his eyes, "We've only been sitting here practically every school night for the last month and a half."

"Rigel doesn't notice anything," Blaise said, as though it were common knowledge, "Do you, Rigel?"

Rigel shrugged, wanting to say, I notice how often you stare at Hannah Abbott, but knowing better than to be so rude. Instead she took a seat and pulled Millicent's homework assignment toward her.

"Swelling Solution?" Rigel guessed, glancing over the ingredient list.

"Just the theory," Millicent said, "We don't have to brew it until after Halloween, but one of the homework questions asks how many times you stir counter-clockwise after adding the bat spleen. One book says three and the other says four, but our textbook just says, 'stir counter-clockwise twice-proportionately to the solute.' What does that even mean?"

Rigel tilted her head to the side to consider the question, "Well, off the top of my head I'd say it's supposed to be four stirs counter-clockwise after the bat spleen for the textbook recipe, but Professor Snape will definitely want to know why, so I guess you'd better explain the reasoning behind the number of stirs if you want full marks."

"Okay, but why did the other book say three stirs?" Millicent asked.

"Well it could either have been written by an idiot, or the recipe just makes less of the potion. Not all potion recipes are standard. Does the recipe given in that book call for a different amount of solute?" Rigel asked.

Millicent scrunched up her nose, "What's a solute?"

"It's just a word for the stuff that dissolves into the liquid part of the potion," Rigel said, "You have to crush puffer-fish eyes and dried nettles into powder for this one, right? That's probably the solute they're talking about."

Millicent ran a finger down the ingredient list in one of the books, "Oh. Yes, it says one and a half measures of the powdered stuff, and our book calls for two measures. Oh, I see. So you stir twice as many times as the number of measures you put in. That's what it means by proportionate." She scowled a bit grumpily at the book as she wrote down the answer in the neat, flowing handwriting that all pureblooded heirs seemed to possess, "Why didn't they just say that?"

Rigel smiled, "Some would say it's a way to keep idiots from playing around with potions if they don't understand them, but they forget they're writing a textbook for school kids, and the ones who don't understand the text have to try and make the potions anyway, so really they're just causing more problems by being unclear."

Millicent shook her head, "You should write a translation of the textbook for normal, not obsessed with all things dried and pickled, people. You'd probably make a killing."

Rigel laughed softly, "If you say so. Was there anything else you needed help with?"

"Well, five minutes ago I would have said yes, but you actually just answered a lot of my questions by explaining the proportionality thing," Millicent said, looking down at her sheet, "I think I can do the rest myself, now, but thanks for your help."

"Anytime," Rigel said easily.

"Do you really mean that?" Millicent asked bluntly, "Or are you just being polite?"

Rigel raised her eyebrows, "I mean it. Do I really seem like the kind of person who wouldn't help out his friends?"

Millicent shrugged, and Theo put in hesitantly from across the table, "It's just that you're so closed-mouthed about everything. It seems like you don't like sharing your knowledge very much."

Rigel shook her head, "It's not that. I just don't want to come off like I'm flaunting it, you know, showing off or something. I'd feel really rude going around spouting off things I know all the time, even if I was well-meaning."

Theo shook his head wryly, "And here we were thinking it would be rude to ask you to help."

"We're not trying to use you for your talent, of course," Millicent said hurriedly, "If there was something I could teach you in return, I would, but…"

"But you always know everything already," Draco cut in with a smirk from behind his Herbology textbook, "And anything you don't know, you probably aren't interested in, or you would know it."

Rigel nearly laughed. "That's what you think? There are tons of things I wish I knew. Things that you guys take for granted, probably. My dad isn't big on pureblood traditions, so I don't know anything about wizarding history farther back than the last couple of decades, for instance. I don't know etiquette, or how to play any musical instruments, while Pansy over here can play three. And look at my handwriting—it's pathetic compared to Millicent's."

"But that's all boring stuff," Theo said. "You never need help with the kind of things we need help with—school work and such."

"To you it's boring," Rigel shrugged, "Do you know what I'd give to have grown up learning Latin like you did, Theo? That's really useful."

"It's not that great," Theo shrugged modestly.

"In any case, I need help with my studies all the time," Rigel told them.

"Anything we can help with?" Pansy asked curiously, and perhaps a bit hopefully.

"Well," Rigel said slowly, "Do any of you study Runes? I got really interested in them over the summer, but the books in the Library are too advanced for me to start with, and I didn't think to buy the third year beginner's textbook."

One by one, everyone in the group turned to look at Blaise. The dark-skinned boy smiled slyly, as if to say, Who, me?

"You know Runes, Blaise?" Rigel asked curiously.

"Since I was very young," Blaise shrugged gracefully, "My mother is a Runes Mistress, and she taught me well before I started Hogwarts. It's not unlike your study of potions, in fact; because there is no magic involved in just learning the theory and the more basic formulas, it was easy enough to learn before getting a wand."

"That's amazing," Rigel said honestly, "Do you mind if I ask you a few questions about them? I can wait until you're done with your homework, of course."

Blaise shrugged once more, "I was finished a while ago. I just hung around to see how the bet turned out. Sure, I'll help. In return you will teach me linked transfigurations, deal?"

Rigel nodded, "No problem. I'll teach it to you now, if you want, since I don't know how long my questions are going to take."

"I want to learn them, too," Draco decided suddenly, closing his Herbology book with a snap, "Sounds useful."

The second years passed the rest of the afternoon and early evening just like that, trading knowledge and the occasional joke comfortably in the Slytherin common room. They all went to bed early that day, knowing that the following evening they'd be up late celebrating Samhain at the Halloween feast with the rest of the school. As she fell asleep that night, Rigel sent up a tiny, half-hearted prayer that this year's feast would not be nearly so eventful as the previous year's. Just don't let anyone try to poison me this time, she asked. Anything but an assassination attempt she could probably handle.

Right?

Chapter 6

[Draco POV]:

The Halloween feast was as glorious as last year's, even without the added excitement of fireworks exploding from the Hufflepuff pumpkins. The sweets were scrumptious, the decorations were brilliant, and everyone agreed it was the most fun they'd had all year. Everyone except, of course, for Rigel, who was exceedingly late…again.

Draco glanced at the doors to the Great Hall for the tenth time in the last half hour, and this time Pansy finally said something.

"I don't know why you're acting surprised and worried, Draco," his friend said from across the table, "He's always late to things like this."

He couldn't disagree with that. If it was a class or an event that Rigel had a responsibility to attend—like Quidditch practice—he was always perfectly punctual, but for everything else…it was as though Rigel forgot about them completely, and just showed up when he happened to be in the area anyway and remembered. Of course, Rigel always gave a perfectly reasonable explanation for why he wasn't somewhere earlier, but if anything the patient, reasonable way he explained himself only frustrated Draco more.

It would be one thing if Rigel was a complete scatterbrain, and genuinely apologetic or upset about showing up either late or not at all to events that everyone else attended as a matter of course—feasts, House meetings, Draco's birthday party, and lately even lunch. But Rigel wasn't flustered or sorry when he showed up. He just shrugged and gave some lame but supremely understandable explanation and then changed the subject. It was annoying how little he cared about things most twelve year olds cared about, and though his apathy was no longer intimidating or strange, it was still, if Draco was completely honest with himself, a little hurtful. Shouldn't friends want to spend all their time together?

Brushing that thought aside dismissively, Draco went back to picking at his pumpkin pie, determined not to look at the Great Hall doors for at least another ten minutes.

"Just because we've gotten used to it, doesn't make it okay," Draco muttered, "Why can't he be normal for once? Who's late to the Halloween feast two years in a row?"

"If he was normal, he wouldn't be Rigel," Pansy said, smiling, "And you wouldn't like him if he was boring like the rest of us."

"You're not boring," Draco said automatically, "And I don't want him to be boring normal, I just wish he cared about something besides potions."

Pansy sent him an admonishing look, which Draco supposed he deserved for making such an oversimplified generalization. He was working on articulating the complexities of a situation, like his father had been trying to teach him, but it was easier to generalize in an argument.

"As his friend, you know better than to believe that image he projects of himself," Pansy said while delicately spreading jam onto a roll, "He pretends not to care about anything but potions because he thinks that if he acts like his life is dull and boring it will keep people from getting too involved in his business. Underneath the manic academia, Rigel cares about us very much, even if he does only show it in stressful or unexpected situations."

"He's still the strangest person I've ever met," Draco said stubbornly, "Did I ever tell you he sleeps in his clothes? Like he thinks he'll be attacked at any moment."

Pansy raised his eyebrows, "That is a little…eccentric. Still, his family is very interested in practical jokes, are they not? Perhaps he was pranked in his sleep a lot as a child, and doesn't like to feel too vulnerable while unconscious as a result."

Draco shrugged, "When we asked he said something vaguely similar, but the fact is we'll probably never know. He lies too often for me to tell the difference, and I'm not sure the truth even matters anymore, because so much of the life he leads seems to be either a lie or a half-lie. It's like the lies are an inseparable part of him now, and just as true as the truth because they might as well be the truth. Does that make sense?"

Pansy nodded her head slowly, "I often get the feeling he's not telling us something extremely important about his life, but the part of him that lives without acknowledging that part of his life is just as valid as the part of him that he keeps hidden. Is that what you mean?"

"Sort of," Draco said, "It would be like if he said his favourite food was turnips when really he hates turnips, but he wants us to think he likes turnips so much that he eats them all the time, and he'd want us to get him turnips for Christmas even if he doesn't actually like them, so what does it matter if he doesn't like them? For all intents and purposes, he's a turnip-eater." Draco grimaced, realizing how absurd that sounded, and sighed, "I don't know. Either way he's our friend, right? I just feel so…it's like there's nothing I can do. He lives in this separate little world and never asks for anything from us."

Pansy's eyes lit with perfect understanding, "Yes! I think I've felt the same, as though I were useless as a friend to him, because there's never anything I can really do for him. He just doesn't share his troubles with us, or if he does it's after the fact or it's something we can't do for him, like studying. At the same time, though, he seems to do so much for us. He went to your birthday party despite the enmity between your families, and convinced Mr. Hagrid to help with you guys' present to me, but I'm not even sure when his birthday is. Sometime over the summer, isn't it?"

"I think so," Draco scrunched up his nose, trying to remember if Rigel had ever told them, "You're right, though. He always knows what to say when something bad happens to us, but he never gets excited or even brags about anything good that happens to him. Getting to know him is like trying to piece scraps of a photograph back together with spell-o-tape, only you're missing most of the pieces!"

Pansy laughed, "And then you realize you're actually putting them together upside down and backwards anyway, so you have to start all over."

Draco chuckled, "Yes, exactly. It's really annoying, but at the same time…I guess I don't mind too much. At least, I don't want to give up."

Pansy nodded seriously, "I agree. It'll probably take a few more years before even we can say we know Rigel Black, but I think he's a good person to know, and I don't just mean because he's from a well-known family, hugely talented with magic, and a you-know-what to boot. He's also a good friend, despite his quirks."

"Yeah," Draco said, glancing down at his goblet of pumpkin juice, "No matter what, it'll be worth the effort in the end."

"And even if it isn't, at least it will be interesting," Pansy said in a lighter tone of voice.

"What will?"

They both looked up to see the subject of their conversation slipping into the seat beside Pansy. Draco raked his eyes over his friend, and suppressed a click of his tongue at the sight of Rigel's plain black school robes. Honestly, who didn't change clothes for a feast?

"Dumbledore's speech," Pansy said smoothly, "You missed it last time, but this time I think he's saving it for the end."

"Which should be any time now," Draco couldn't help but add, "Seeing as you're over an hour late."

Rigel, to no one's surprise, merely blinked, "Sorry. I was finishing up a Befuddlement Draught in my lab. I had to put it on stasis for a while, though, because the belladonna I needed wasn't where I thought."

"Snape's got you on the Befuddlement Draught? That's really advanced, isn't it?" Pansy asked, "I think Rookwood was working on an essay about it just last month."

Draco wasn't even surprised that Rigel was now working on fifth year potions, but he was surprised when Rigel said, "It wasn't for Snape. He doesn't usually have me learn potions I'll be learning as part of the regular curriculum anyway. He says it would be a waste of time unless I was planning on skipping a year or two."

"You aren't, are you?" Draco asked worriedly, though he noted in the back of his mind that Rigel hadn't said what he was brewing the Befuddlement Draught for if not Snape.

Rigel gazed at him with amusement that added a small light to his grey eyes, "No, I'm not planning on it. I'd like as much time to study under Professor Snape as possible. Once I graduate I would have to apply for a formal apprenticeship, and those have to be approved by a board of Adepts from the Potions Guild. Too much trouble when I can get the best tuition right here without it."

Draco noticed Rigel said nothing about wanting to enjoy his childhood or remain in the same age group as his friends, as most kids would have. Still, whatever the reason, Draco was glad Rigel wasn't considering moving up a grade or two, though with his smarts he probably could with very little trouble.

"When did you learn the stasis charm?" Pansy asked curiously, "We don't learn it until OWL year, I think, but it sounds very useful to be able to put a potion on hold while you get something else done."

Rigel frowned slightly and Draco immediately knew they'd offended his potion-making sensibilities, "I learned it over the summer, but I almost never use it. You're really not supposed to, because a lot of potions don't like having their kinetic energy frozen like that. Some potions will even react extremely negatively to it—not while under the stasis charm, of course, but as soon as you lift it they go haywire. It's supposed to be an emergency-only kind of spell. It's just that Befuddlement Draughts take a couple of hours to brew, and I was wasting enough time tracking down my backup store of belladonna."

Pansy laughed, "All right, Rigel, I wasn't suggesting using the stasis charm every time my arm got tired of stirring. I just meant it would be useful to have, in situations like you described."

Rigel's face affected the slightly sheepish look that always came when he realized he'd rambled on about something he thought no one else would care about. Draco didn't bother to reassure him—after all this time, Rigel should know better than to think he bored them. How many times had Pansy and he reassured their friend that they were interested in whatever he wanted to tell them? It was like he'd been indoctrinated into thinking everything he enjoyed was dry and boring and no one wanted to listen when he spoke on a topic he actually cared about. What rubbish. Maybe Rigel's family was as big a bunch of dunderheads as Uncle Severus always intimated.

"You should have stopped brewing before you started the Befuddlement Draught," Draco said eventually, "Then you might have been on time. Getting forgetful about your potions ingredients is probably a sign you've been at it too long. Learn to take a break, Rye."

Rigel just blinked at him like he was speaking another language, "I didn't need a break. I needed belladonna."

Pansy frowned a bit, "It is odd that you would misplace it. You've never been careless with your ingredients."

Rigel frowned as well, "I know. I guess I must have used it in something else, though I can't remember…I have been making a lot of potions in the last month, though. I'll just be sure to order extra next month."

"Isn't belladonna poisonous?" Draco asked slowly. Even he knew it was never a good thing when potentially dangerous ingredients went missing.

Rigel shrugged dismissively, "Only in huge quantities. More than I had, that's for sure. It's only really dangerous to small animals. Sometimes squirrels and birds die from eating the raw plant in the wild, but even then they'd have to eat several stalks, and they'd probably get sick after one or two and stop first." Rigel looked thoughtful for a moment, then added, "Maybe if the animal was starving, or had lost its sense of taste somehow. Maybe if it had recently eaten some sort of pepper, and therefore had a compromised sense of smell that—"

"Okay, I think we got it," Pansy said quickly, "Not that it isn't interesting, Rigel, but finish telling us about it after the meal, okay?"

Rigel gave Pansy an apologetic look, and changed the subject, "So, did I miss anything else?"

"Besides our fabulous company?" Draco drawled just to coax a half-smile from his friend, "Not really. Someone charmed the suits of armour on either side of the doors to shout 'boo' at every tenth person or so, and judging from the way Professor Sinistra jumped and shrieked when she came in, I don't think it was the staff's idea."

Rigel nodded and quirked an eyebrow as though that were a very interesting piece of information, rather than a random fact. Somehow Rigel could make him feel like he was both rivetingly important and singularly unnoticed within the space of minutes.

They were spared further inanities by the flickering of all the candles in the Hall, which Draco supposed was supposed to signal the Headmaster's speech. All it really did was make people pause long enough in their conversations for Dumbledore to clear his throat in the ensuing moment of silence and gain most people's attention.

Draco dutifully turned slightly in his seat to pay attention to the old wizard who had out-classed and out-conned every enemy, political or otherwise, who had come up against him in the last century. Albus Dumbledore had all the potential to be truly impressive, but the elderly wizard ruined the effect by dressing like a circus performer and pretending to be senile. It made people underestimate him, Draco supposed, but the people stupid enough to forget a lifetime of unimaginable magical and political feats in the face of a facsimile of nonsense weren't people worth trying to fool, because they were probably too stupid to spell politics, much less participate in them.

At least that's how Draco saw it. Better to never let your enemies—and followers, too, for that matter—forget how awe-inspiring you truly are. It only left room for questioning and doubts, which made it all too easy for someone to uproot a person indirectly through the spreading of rumours and lies. That, Draco thought, was Dumbledore's weakness. He manipulated people as a matter of course, but didn't seem to comprehend that those same people he so easily swayed could be swayed just as easily against him. One didn't have to challenge Albus Dumbledore directly—too many had tried and failed for that to be a sane option anyway. One only had to use the man's own carefully cultivated reputation against him.

People were all too poised to believe anything semi-plausible, simply because it didn't occur to them that someone else would take the time to purposely deceive them. It wouldn't take much to get the general public thinking Dumbledore was as stricken with dotage as he seemed. Then one would just have to offer a younger, sharper version as an alternative, and people would jump at the opportunity for change, thinking it to be something refreshing and improving. Little would they know that the usurper is a farce, a clever plant by the enemy who would win their favour and votes and then use the power passed to him by Dumbledore's legacy to run the Light camp into the ground.

Draco pulled himself out of his thoughts with difficulty. He was learning how to think more like a politician, more like his father, and it was surprisingly easy for him, but it had the side effect of making him tune out some things in order to concentrate on others. He realized with an inner jolt that he'd missed most of the Headmaster's speech while occupied with his hypotheticals, but wasn't in truth overly concerned about it. Pansy would let him know if anything of import had been said, and in the best-case scenario he'd managed to retain a few extra brain cells, which he would surely have lost in the face of the Headmaster's usual driveling non sequiturs.

"And on a final note," the burnt-orange-clad (was he competing with Lockhart in a most obnoxious colour contest?) wizard was saying, "Mr. Filch would like me to announce that Mrs. Norris has been missing since this morning. I know you will all help keep an eye out for our beloved caretaker's cat, and if you see her please inform one of the—"

The Headmaster was cut off by the muffled sound of an explosion, like something unwieldy being dropped onto a heap of sand. A dull thudding noise reverberated distantly, like the ricochet of a swaddled piece of metal. They felt the tremor go through the Hall, rattling the dishes and setting the pumpkin juice in their goblets to trembling. There was a moment of complete silence in which the teachers all stood immediately and the students froze in confusion. Then the distant sound of falling rocks clattering against stone floors was heard and everyone scrambled into panicked motion.

"The castle is collapsing!"

Draco had enough time to roll his eyes at the first year behind that ridiculous comment, and then he was hurrying toward the nearest Slytherin prefect with the rest of their house, just trying not to get trampled in the chaos.

"SILENCE," Dumbledore's voice boomed over the melee, and all motion ceased once more. "Now, prefects will lead their houses in an orderly fashion to their common rooms, where the names of all students will be checked against the house master lists—prefects, you are in charge of this as well, as I will be needing your heads of house for a little while. The castle is perfectly safe, I assure you. One of our lovely house elves has just informed me that a portion of the corridor in the East side of the third floor has collapsed; however, the stabilizing wards and various other embedded structural spells installed by the founders themselves kicked in immediately, and so no other parts of the castle are under any architectural stress at this time."

The students seemed to digest this for a moment, and the prefects seized upon the momentary calm to begin subdividing their houses into more manageable groups and herding them more carefully out of the Great Hall, whose doors seemed to have been widened considerably by someone with a good deal of practical forethought. Probably Snape, Draco thought.

He felt a tug on his elbow and turned his head to see Pansy clinging gently but unmistakably to his right arm.

"All right there, Pans?"

She nodded, but her lips were clamped together in a tight line. Draco saw Blaise, Millicent, and Theo walking ahead of them, and turned his head to tell Rigel to take Pansy's other hand. The girl was obviously frightened, and Rigel seemed to have a soothing quality to his presence that often came in handy.

Except…Rigel wasn't behind them. Draco craned his head, but Rigel wasn't anywhere to be seen in the immediate vicinity. Draco was tempted to sigh with resignation but he was too busy being worried about his idiotic friend. Now the question was, did he tell Pansy? It would worry her more to know, but it would be bad form as her friend to keep it from her. Besides, she would notice any moment now.

"Pans," Draco said, bending down to her ear so she could hear him, "Don't be alarmed, but I can't find Rigel. Can you see him?"

Pansy stiffened and began looking around immediately, but carefully, suppressing her panic like a true pureblooded lady ought.

"Nothing," Pansy said tightly, "He does not appear to be in the Great Hall."

"How did he get out ahead of us?" Draco asked aloud.

"More importantly, where is he going?" Pansy said, frowning, "If he was headed to the common room, he would have taken us with him. You know how protective he can be sometimes. The fact that he went without us…"

Draco nearly groaned as he caught on, "Means he's going somewhere more dangerous than where he thinks we'll be going. Idiot."

"Thinks we're going?" Pansy asked, unspoken question obvious from the way she tilted her eyes toward him.

"Well of course," Draco said with a faint smile that had absolutely no humour in it, "We're not going to let him run off alone, are we?"

Pansy smiled back just as faintly, "No, we aren't."

They had reached the doors by that point, so Draco pulled the edges of his robes over his silver and green tie, motioning for Pansy to do the same, and they slipped away from the Slytherins and into the crowd of Hufflepuffs. They would be going down to the basements, but then they'd go east if Draco was right about where their common room was, and from there they'd just have to slip into one of the alcoves until everyone had passed. From there, they could take the East stairs and wind up exactly where Rigel was most likely to be right now.

Draco swore that this time when they found their wayward friend, he would have a lot of explaining to do before they were satisfied.

[Rigel's POV]:

Rigel had been quite enjoying the Headmaster's speech, intermingled as it was by the odd turn of phrase and delivered with Dumbledore's usual sense of airy aplomb. It was sort of graceful, the way none of his statements seemed to be apropos of anything else he talked about. He must practise very hard to be so perfectly random, or else his mind was governed by a very strict algorithm of chance, which made sure it only presented things in a random order.

Draco's eyes were glazed in a way that belied his apparent attention to the Headmaster's words, and Pansy had given up the pretense of listening after the first few minutes, seeming content to glance around at the other Slytherins, taking in their expressions and postures and probably drawing any number of political and social conclusions that would have gone right over Rigel's head.

All in all, it was a relaxing way to spend an evening, until, of course, it happened. Rigel hadn't known until that moment what it would be, but as soon as the explosion went off she knew. There was something about Halloween that had always made her uneasy. Perhaps because on her ninth Halloween, she had found her beloved copy of Snape's treatise on the treatment of undiluted venoms in antidote preparation stuffed beneath an uneven table leg in her father's study. Then there was the Halloween Archie and she had accidentally set fire to the curtains in Sirius' living room and had subsequently been sent to bed without candy by their parents. While those incidences weren't quite on the level of last year's Halloween—few things in her admittedly complicated life measured up to that disaster—every year without fail something bad happened to or around Rigel on that date, so it wasn't even really a surprise to her that one of the school's corridors chose this day to get blown up.

She stood with the rest of their house and began shuffling toward the doors, making sure to keep Draco and Pansy in sight ahead of her. She had been sitting on the side of the table closest to the Gryffindors' table, and she happened to catch sight of the Weasley twins as she passed. They were walking slower than those around them, creating a sort of obstacle that people were swerving around. Their brother Ron was walking with them, and he looked quite upset about something.

Curious, Rigel altered her course a bit so that she would come up just behind them, then slowed her pace to listen in.

"—won't thank us for butting in again," George was saying.

"I know, but what if she's really—" Ron's voice was loud and agitated, but she still couldn't catch every word over the tumult around them, "—have to know."

Fred and George exchanged a look, but nodded in the end. "Better not tell Perce," Fred suggested.

"Not that he won't realize as soon as—gone," George put in.

"But he'll be too busy—" Fred's voice cut out as a couple of particularly loud Gryffindor girls walked quickly by them, "—by the time he realizes."

Rigel moved closer, until she could hear every word.

"Right," George said, "I'd say we need a distraction, but everyone's distracted enough."

"We'll break away when we get to the stairs," Fred said, "Hide behind that tapestry with the goats till they've gone."

"What if she's not there?" Ron asked worriedly.

"Then we hightail it back to the dorms before the teachers catch us," George shrugged, "I'm still not convinced this is a good idea. Either Ginny was near the explosion, and was in danger, which we can't do anything about now that it's passed, or else she wasn't, which means she's safe somewhere else, and we're only going to get caught by the teachers who are all going to the third floor right now."

"That's a fair point," Fred said carefully, "And whatever set off the explosion could be anything. Might be dangerous, which is probably why they're sending us back to the common room in the first place."

"I don't care," Ron said, "I can't just sit around in the common room wondering if she's okay. One way or another, I want to know now."

George sighed but nodded, and Fred just shrugged, apparently not caring enough to argue about it. The three brothers kept moving forward, but slowly, hanging back until most of their housemates had passed through the doors ahead of them. Standing behind them, Rigel couldn't see Pansy or Draco anymore, but she wasn't worried. They'd get to the common room safely.

Rigel put her hand in her pocket unobtrusively and pulled out the innocent square of folded parchment that held the Marauder's Map. She whispered the password under her breath and when the Map began to bleed onto the page, she quickly muttered Ginny Weasley's name to it. It zoomed in to show a tiny dot labeled 'Ginevra Weasley' walking along the seventh floor corridor toward the Fat Lady's portrait.

Satisfied that Ginny Weasley was safe, Rigel tucked the Map away and debated for a brief moment about whether to involve herself further. Then she thought that if she had a sister, she'd want to know all she could if said sister might possibly be in danger. Rigel caught up to the Weasley brothers, tapping George on the shoulder to catch their attention.

"Rigel?" George gazed distractedly at her, "What's up?"

"Don't go to the third floor," Rigel said without preamble.

George grimaced, "Heard that, did you? Well, I can't let these two idiots go by themselves."

"Don't any of you go," Rigel said seriously, "Ginny's not there, so you'll only get into trouble at best and danger at worst."

"How do you know Ginny's not there?" Ron demanded.

"I can't tell you," Rigel said bluntly, "But I promise you she'll be in the common room when you get up there. I know that's not comforting, but it's the truth. Do you trust me?"

"With most things, yeah," Ron said, frowning, "With my little sister's safety? Not really. No offence."

"None taken," Rigel said, "But I really don't want you guys in danger for no reason. Look, how about I check it out instead? I promise if Ginny's there I'll come straight up to get you, but you guys should go back to the Gryffindor common room."

"That doesn't make a lot of sense," George objected, "Why should it be more okay for you to do it rather than us? She's our sister."

"But one person is less likely to get caught," Rigel said, "And it'll be easier for me to get there and then to the dungeons than it will be for you guys to make it all the way to Gryffindor tower before a prefect notices you're missing."

Fred opened his mouth to argue, but shut it again and instead started patting down his pockets, "Where is…? Must have left it. George, give me yours."

He reached into his brother's robe pockets and rummaged around until George rolled his eyes and fished something out of his back pants pocket, "Here, this is what you wanted, right? Good idea."

Fred snatched the small leather journal from George's hand and presented it to Rigel, "When you figure out if Ginny is there, use this to tell us. This journal has a match, which is upstairs in our dorm room. Just write something in it, and we'll get the message in the other one."

Rigel took the journal and tucked it away, "Okay. Now go, before Percy wonders why you guys are lagging behind."

The three redheads nodded and set off after the group of Gryffindors, who had just begun climbing the Main Stair. Rigel herself turned and followed the Slytherin contingent down toward the dungeons. She took out the Map again and checked it. Sure enough, Ginny Weasley was in the Gryffindor common room, her tiny dot seated on a miniscule couch in front of a little ink fireplace. Rigel would wait a few minutes, then check again to make sure she hadn't moved, before writing to assure the Weasleys that their sister wasn't near the collapsed corridor.

Curious about how the Map would reflect the damage done to the castle, Rigel zoomed back out and glanced over the third floor corridor. It looked just as it always did, which she guessed made sense if the Map was only spelled to update the locations of people in real time, not structures, but it was flooded with the names of teachers and staff members. At a glance, Rigel recognized Snape, Filch, Dumbledore, McGonagall, and various other professors' dots. More seemed to be coming, too, she noticed. A couple of dots were even now moving toward the corridor up the East…stairs…oh, no. Rigel read the labels on the dots and nearly groaned aloud.

What in Merlin's name were Pansy and Draco doing heading for the collapsed portion of the third floor? She could think of no logical reason for them to be going there now. Neither were overly curious when it came to possible danger, and in fact both were rather big sticklers for the rules most of the time. They'd been raised to respect authority, after all, at least when it didn't directly go against their personal goals.

Whatever they were doing, Rigel wasn't about to just pretend she hadn't noticed. She was already at the end of the group of Slytherin students, so it was no trouble to slip away as they passed the basement and double back to come up behind her friends. They had stopped moving and were instead poised on the stairs just below the landing that joined with the third floor, probably peeking around the corner to try and discern what was going on.

A few minutes later, Rigel had reached the East stairs. She took a moment to sweep the Map once more and write quickly in the little leather notebook to assure the Weasleys that Ginny wasn't in the vicinity of the explosion. It was curious to watch the ink disappear as soon as it dried, leaving a blank notebook once more, but Rigel would think about the spells behind such a thing later. She folded up the Map again and started up the winding stairs. Just as she started to notice a large amount of dust in the air—probably from broken pieces of stone—she heard a whisper echoing down the quiet stairwell.

"—don't see him."

"Are you sure he's—"

"Where else would he be?"

Rigel snuck up behind her two blonde friends, who were trying to use Pansy's compact mirror to peer around the corner to the third floor.

"It's just a bunch of rubble," Draco was whispering irritably, "Wait, is that? No, it's someone else. A Gryffindor? Why would one of them have been…?"

Rigel frowned. A Gryffindor? It couldn't be Ginny, but…she pulled out the Map and checked it one last time, more carefully. Ginny's name wasn't anywhere in the corridor, but another name, one Rigel should have recognized immediately, was.

Neville Longbottom.

His dot was in the centre of several other dots, notably Albus Dumbledore and Poppy Pomfrey. The other dots all wavered slightly on the parchment as their owners shifted naturally, but Neville's dot didn't move at all.

Rigel shoved the Map into her pocket and hurried forward. Draco and Pansy turned around at the sound of her soft footsteps hurrying up the stairs and the looks of surprised confusion on their faces would have been funny if Rigel wasn't so worried about Neville.

"Rigel, what—?"

"How did you get behind us?"

Rigel motioned for them to be quiet and inched around the corner of the wall separating the stairs from the rest of the corridor. The third floor was a complete mess. Normally, the third floor consisted of three parallel corridors connected by various smaller hallways and passages, and then connected on either end by the East and West staircases. The Main stair went up through the middle corridor, where the Charms classroom was located. The three of them were standing just behind where the South-most corridor met the East stairs, and from what Rigel could see, the wall that had once separated the South corridor from the middle corridor was now a lot less like a wall and a lot more like a window looking from one of the South corridor's storage rooms into the back of the middle corridor's Trophy Room.

Rocks, large and small, littered the floor. All the dust in the air made it hard to see anything, but the teachers seemed to be crowding around something. It was a person, small enough to be a student, who seemed to be passed out on the floor. Rigel could see a hand and a couple of trouser-clad legs from in between the professors' feet, so it definitely wasn't a girl, and as she caught a glimpse of red and gold around the student's neck, she couldn't deny the truth. It was Neville—it had to be. The Map was, as she'd been told so many times, never wrong.

She backed away slowly, aware that there was nothing she could do for her friend that more qualified people weren't already doing. Still, it felt wrong to just leave him there, though she knew they should get back to the common room. The school had been breached by something malevolent, and it would be just plain stupid to avoid the safety of the common room any longer.

Rigel turned and tugged on Pansy and Draco's sleeves until they started following her quietly back down the stairs. When they were safely to the dungeons, her friends turned to her.

"What did you see, Rigel?"

She ignored Pansy's question, instead staring at the two blondes very seriously, "What were you two doing? You should have been safe in the common room, not—" Rigel sighed and rubbed her eyes, "You could have been in danger. Something destructive enough to blow a hole in a castle this fortified doesn't just disappear once it's had its fun."

"Us?" Draco scowled, "What were you doing? We only went to find you."

Rigel blinked, "I only went to find you two."

Pansy frowned, "Then…we all were just worried about one another? Oh. We thought…"

"We thought you'd run off into trouble again," Draco said bluntly.

Rigel sighed, "Of course I didn't. Why would I? The explosion had nothing to do with me. I just hung back to talk to the Weasleys about something before heading back, until I realized you guys weren't heading to the common room with everyone else, that is."

"How did you know?" Pansy said, cocking her head to the side, "You got there just after we did, so you wouldn't have had time to go all the way to check the common room first. Even if you did, the prefects wouldn't have let you out again."

Rigel shrugged, "I just did."

"You can't just—" Draco started, but Rigel cut across him tiredly.

"Look, let's get back to the common room first, then argue about who knew what and how."

Pansy agreed, and Draco, outvoted, bit back his exasperation in favour of setting off toward the Slytherin common room at a brisk pace.

Soon enough, they were edging through the false wall. Their stealth was apparently unappreciated, as Theo almost immediately called out, "There they are! Thank Merlin. We were so worried!"

Selwyn, who was standing close to the common room door, scowled down at them before checking their names off of a long piece of parchment she held in her hands, "Finally. You're lucky I haven't sent the Baron after Snape yet. I only waited because I know Professor Snape is busy at the moment."

"Thank you, Alice," Pansy said, inclining her head graciously.

Selwyn rolled heavily kohl-rimmed eyes, "Sure, Pansy. Go see Rosier, would you? He's doing that pacing thing he does when he worries."

Pansy headed off to soothe her friend's concerns for her safety, and Draco and Rigel stepped over to where the other second years were huddled by one of the fireplaces.

"Where've you three been?" Millicent asked curiously.

"Long story," Draco said, "Bit of a mix up on all our parts, actually. So, what did you see, Rigel?"

Rigel shifted uncomfortably as several other sets of curious eyes turned toward her, "You were there, too. What did you see?"

"A load of dust," Draco said evenly, "And maybe…well, you apparently saw something that made you back out pretty quick."

"Yeah," Rigel said flatly, "Snape. I decided we should leave before he began testing for stray magical signatures and sensed us lurking nearby." Draco gave her an unimpressed look, so she reluctantly added, "There was a student on the ground. I know you saw him, too."

"A Gryffindor," Draco said, nodding.

"A Gryffindor blew up the corridor?" Theo blurted, "But the Weasley Twins were at the feast."

Draco shook his head grimly, "Looked more like the poor sod got caught in the blast. He wasn't moving."

The other second years exchanged solemn looks at that.

"Who do you think…?" Millicent trailed off, looking uncomfortable.

"Neville Longbottom," Rigel said quietly.

They absorbed this for a moment.

"Yeah, he definitely wouldn't have blown up part of the school," Theo said thoughtfully, "I wonder what did, though."

Speculation began, but none of the posited theories seemed very likely. Even Peeves wouldn't have gone so far as to destabilize the infrastructure, much less injure a student.

Some time later, as they were all still quietly milling about the common room, too wound up to turn in, Snape showed up. He came into the common room looking drawn and tense. Selwyn presented him with the list, which he glanced over briefly.

"All accounted for?"

"Yes, sir," Selwyn said evenly.

"Good," Snape said, his mouth pressing into a thin line, "Unfortunately not all the Houses were so lucky this night." He raised his voice so everyone could hear, although most of the Slytherins had already gone quiet with respect and anticipation when he arrived, "As you know, tonight a portion of the third floor corridor collapsed. At this point, it seems to be the work of a rather clumsy, and thoroughly overpowered, bombardment hex. The perpetrator has not yet been identified. A second-year Gryffindor was found injured in the corridor, but his wand was found clean of any destructive spells, so we believe him to be a victim of the crime."

He gazed around at them all and said, a bit more quietly, "I'm sure I do not have to tell any of you how serious a situation this is. Until the culprit for these actions is identified, all of you are to keep to the main corridors when possible. Don't wander alone. Don't turn a blind eye to anything remotely suspicious—contact a prefect, professor, ghost, or even house elf the moment you hear or see anything out of the ordinary. New wards will be erected around the common rooms at night, requiring an additional password. Your prefects will be around to apprise you of increased security measures shortly."

With that, Professor Snape left again, and after Selwyn and the other prefects had explained everything, the students slowly began trickling away to bed.

Rigel silently despaired as she lay atop her covers. Though Snape had said Neville was injured, not killed, she feared for her friend. Students being found unconscious in hallways sounded all too like the Sleeping Sickness. Snape had also said that he was found injured at the scene of the explosion, not that the explosion had caused his injuries. She hadn't seen any blood on the floor, as she'd expect if he'd been hit hard enough by rubble to be knocked out. What, then, had made her friend so still? Tossing and turning, it was a long couple of hours until she finally slept.

Why can't Halloween ever be normal?

Hermione's POV:

Halloween, Hermione thought to herself as she gazed over the festively decorated Mess Hall where the Halloween feast was taking place, was a very nonsensical holiday. It was only made more so when it was witches and wizards who were celebrating it.

She could understand if they had a ceremony honouring Samhain, as the wizarding community apparently had a lot of pagan roots, but after finding out last year that all the things she'd ever dressed up as for Halloween—witches, vampires, werewolves, ghosts—were in fact very much real, celebrating Halloween seemed completely ridiculous.

Then again, she mused as she watched an upperclassman in the Charms tract walk by with a talking pumpkin tucked under his arm, chatting away at it, in her experience a bit of ridiculousness never fazed the average witch or wizard.

Shaking her head, Hermione claimed her seat at the Healer's table and waited for her friend Harry to arrive. Harry was another sort of ridiculousness altogether. Hermione could still remember the first time they'd met.

She had just said goodbye to her parents and boarded the plane that would take her to the American Institute of Magic. She was feeling a little depressed, because originally she had wanted to attend the English school Hogwarts, until she found out that the school only accepted those of wizarding ancestry. Still, she was excited to be going off to a new place, and to learn about magic, of all things, in an actual school with a magical curriculum and everything.

She was also extremely nervous. At primary school, she hadn't been at all popular, and most of her classmates had only been remotely nice to her when they wanted help with their homework—as if they thought she wouldn't notice. She wanted things to be different in America, but she wasn't sure how to make them different without either dumbing herself down to fit in or else sucking up to the other students until they liked her. Since she absolutely refused to sink so low as to entertain either option for long, she was quite at a loss as to how to go about making friends.

It was at that moment, after she had primly stored her carry-on bag with A History of American Magic inside of it under her seat, that a boy about her age swept into the seat next to her like a whirlwind and turned toward her with a smile that should have come with a high-voltage label, it was so bright.

"Hi! I'm Harry Potter! I guess we're seatmates, are you a first-year too? Isn't this the biggest plane you've ever seen? Well, it's the only plane I've ever seen, but I saw a picture of one once and it wasn't nearly so big!" the boy began babbling happily to her about all the cool things he'd apparently seen in the airport that morning, including a set of moving stairs, which she identified for him as an escalator, and something he described as 'a portrait that couldn't talk back but never looped like a photo' which she worked out to mean the television screens that played the news around the airport.

At some point he took a breath, and she politely interjected, "I'm Hermione Granger. Yes, I'm a first-year, and why haven't you ever seen a plane before?"

"Oh," the boy, Harry, said, cocking his head to the side like a puppy and blinking silvery-grey eyes at her, "My parents are wizards, so I don't see much of the muggle world."

Hermione frowned, "Then why are you going to AIM? Don't you want to go to Hogwarts?"

Harry waved a dismissive hand, "I'm half-blood technically, so I can't, but I wouldn't want to anyway. Hogwarts is where the stuffy old families send their kids, and the magic they learn there is as old and dusty as their way of thinking. They don't even have a Healer's program! Not to mention Alchemy or Druidry or any of the interesting specializations in magic. If I went there I'd have to go to extra schooling after I graduated just to be qualified for anything, and of course none of the universities in Britain are very accredited, so I'd have to get an apprenticeship to learn anything really advanced, and those take ages to finish and—"

Hermione just sat there and listened as Harry Potter went on and on about how much better AIM was than Hogwarts and the other European schools. At first she just couldn't believe how hyper and talkative the boy was, but as she listened she gradually relaxed and even started to feel a bit relieved that she was going to AIM after all. Imagine seven years of butting up against all those oppressive pureblood customs and stifled ways of learning and thinking. According to Harry, all the homework and tests were based around essays—the oldest form of learning in the book, and seriously outdated in Hermione's opinion. Imagine, seven years without a single creative project or experiment for an assignment!

Eventually, Harry began to wind down, and that was when Hermione started wishing he'd kept babbling a bit longer. Having exhausted everything he wanted to talk about, Harry began asking question after question about Hermione and where she was from and what her parents did and so on. He had no idea what a dentist was, and didn't seem terribly enthused by her description, but eventually equated it with a very specialized Healer and thought they must be 'wicked cool.'

"So what tract are you going to choose?" Harry asked, "I'm going to be in Healing, in case you couldn't guess, because I want to know everything about Healing there is to know—oh, I might go into Potions eventually, though. I like them, too."

Hermione reflected that Harry Potter seemed like a very unfocused sort of person, though she would come to revise that opinion of him as she got to know him over the next year.

"I was thinking of going into Healing as well," Hermione said, "I thought about Alchemy, but I'm not sure my parents would really understand that, and Healing is both universally understandable and universally valued, so they can still be proud of me even if they don't relate completely."

"That's great!" Harry said, with more excitement than Hermione thought the response warranted, "That means we'll have all of our classes together, and be in the same dorms and everything. Want to study together? Want to be friends?"

She blinked in confusion for a second, then stared when her mind digested his strung-together way of talking. He wanted to be friends? That was…easy. Almost too easy.

"Why?" she asked, a bit suspiciously. Perhaps he had seen the book in her bag, assumed her to be a nerd, and was hoping for guaranteed help with his assignments in return for being nice to her.

Harry just blinked at her, still smiling that too-bright-to-be-natural smile, and said, "Why not?"

Having nothing to say to that, Hermione just smiled back, a bit shyly. Time to take a chance, she thought. Even if he turned out to have a hidden agenda, she wouldn't know unless she tried, "Okay, friends, then. So, you grew up in a wizarding home? What was it like?"

From there the conversation flowed quickly. They covered a huge range of topics, comparing the difference between the muggle and wizarding worlds across categories like music, entertainment, politics, family life, social engagements, education, work, and more. Hermione learned more from Harry Potter about the wizarding world in that plane ride—which was somehow only six hours, though logically she knew that a flight across the Atlantic should take much longer—than she had from all the vague, generally worded books she'd bought after getting her letter.

By the time they reached AIM and separated into groups based on whether they had a tract in mind or were undecided, Harry's cheerful and excitable personality had really grown on her. Even when they got off the plane and Harry had a chance to meet their classmates, many of whom were obviously richer or cooler than she was, Harry didn't even seem to notice. All of his attention was on Hermione, and she couldn't help but like how things had turned out.

Two days later, when he made them both late for their first general charms lesson by somehow getting his left shoe stuck to the ceiling with industrial strength bubble-gum, Hermione had second thoughts about her burgeoning friendship with the quirky would-be Healer, but then he somehow weaseled an extra fruit tart from the service elves who manned the buffet-style dinner line, and he gave it to her. And afterwards he didn't ask for help on the extra worksheet they had to do for being late, and when she tentatively offered her help he just smiled and said he understood it fine, and had in fact finished it in class while she'd been taking notes.

Shortly after that, Harry Potter and Hermione Granger became nearly synonymous. They were always together, studying or enacting one of Harry's elaborate schemes, and by the time Christmas break rolled around, Harry was easily the best friend she'd ever had.

Now it was over a year since they'd met, and Hermione was so used to Harry's antics that she didn't even blink when he collapsed, sighing bonelessly, at the table next to her, and began picking bits of bat-shaped confetti out of his mashed potatoes.

"Happy Halloween," she said mildly.

Harry wrinkled his pert nose and rolled his eyes, "Awful holiday."

Hermione turned surprised eyes to her friend, "Free candy, crazy decorations and costumes, two extra desserts apiece…I sort of thought this would be right up your alley."

Harry poked at his mashed potatoes a bit sullenly, "Something bad always happens on Halloween. It's, like, a curse."

Hermione raised her eyebrows. It wasn't that she didn't believe in curses (she'd read about quite a few and even knew the theory behind a couple now), but her friend was prone to melodramatization, "You weren't depressed last year on Halloween, and I don't remember anything bad happening then."

Harry shrugged, "I thought I was well away from it here. It doesn't always happen to me, anyway. Most of the time, it's my cousin Archie that gets the brunt of the curse. Remember last year when I got that letter from home that said my cousin had been injured somehow at Hogwarts? His injury happened on Halloween night. Turns out someone tried to kill him by putting corrosive poison in his drink."

Hermione gasped, "That's awful! How can that sort of thing happen in a school? He was okay, right?"

Harry shrugged, "Yeah, someone stopped him drinking it at the last second. The point is that nothing bad has happened to me so far today, which means something awful is probably happening to Archie right now."

"Well," Hermione said tentatively, "There's no use worrying if you can't do anything, right?"

Harry sighed, "I guess. I'm just worried, because even if something bad does happen to him, he won't say anything and it will be weeks until the school informs his dad who tells my parents who write about it to me."

Hermione kept silent. She had heard a lot about Harry's cousin Archie, who went by Rigel some of the time, and from what Harry had said, Arcturus Black seemed to be a singularly strange individual, though apparently he was quite brilliant. Then again, Harry always said Hermione was brilliant, too, and she didn't consider herself a real genius or anything. She just worked hard and applied herself diligently.

"Distract me, Mione," Harry said morosely, "Please?"

"With what?" Hermione asked wryly.

"I don't know," Harry said with a sigh, "Perhaps your stunning good looks and natural charm? You could flirt with me."

Hermione rolled her eyes, "We're too young for flirting, Harry."

"Are we?" Harry didn't seem terribly concerned, "My uncle Sirius says you're never too young for flirting."

Hermione privately thought his uncle didn't seem like the sort of adult he should be taking advice from, but she knew better than to say anything against 'Uncle Sirius.' Harry practically worshiped the ground his uncle walked on, and seemed to be even closer to the man than he was to his own parents. He certainly mentioned him more often, though he hardly wrote to him at all, curiously enough.

"Maybe boys can start flirting at twelve, but I'm pretty sure respectable girls don't start until at least fourteen," Hermione said with amusement. At first all the vaguely flirtatious words and borderline propositions Harry said to her had flustered and disconcerted her. She wasn't at all used to such flowery and exaggerated banter, and had in the beginning taken it rather badly. Soon it became clear that he wasn't teasing her, and he certainly wasn't seriously coming on to her. Harry just talked that way sometimes, as though it was completely natural. She supposed it had something to do with his exuberant and open-hearted nature combined with the influence of his uncle. It made him a terrible ingénue, but in an artless sort of way.

"What's so great about being respectable?" Harry said, grinning a bit, "Walk on the wild side, Mione."

"Why don't you go ahead and let me know how it is?" Hermione said primly, "I like this side of sensibility well enough."

"Someday I'll corrupt you," Harry said teasingly, "And then—prankers of the world beware! I bet you'd out-prank me any day if you put that brilliant mind of yours to it."

"Not if I corrupt you first," Hermione said, "Have you finished your paper on Mind Healing yet?"

"It's not due for another week," Harry pointed out.

"Have you finished it?"

"Yes," Harry pouted, "I guess your evil plan is working better than mine is. Maybe it's time for another grand adventure."

"No theft this time," Hermione requested, knowing better than to try and refuse outright. He would only use his puppy-eyes on her and then she'd end up agreeing to anything.

"What about arson?" Harry asked cheerfully.

As much as she was glad he wasn't depressed anymore…"No."

"Larceny?"

"That is theft," Hermione rolled her eyes, "Nice try, though."

"So, no misappropriating of property and no blowing things up?" Harry shook his head with mock forlornness, which suited him much better than actual forlornness, "What's an adolescent boy to do?"

"You could cry," Hermione suggested blithely, "Just try to avoid getting it in my pumpkin juice."

Harry laughed at that, "This is why you're such a perfect friend for me, Mione. The only other person in the world who deals with my antics so well is my cousin, and he's had a decade of practice."

Hermione felt her ears grow warm beneath her hair. She knew exactly what high praise that was, having heard Harry spout positively poetic about how awesome his cousin was countless times in the last year. No matter how strange or outright suspicious Harry got sometimes, when he said things like that she couldn't help but want to ignore all the inconsistencies a little longer. His friendship, she was realizing, was more important than figuring out his secrets. She would wait patiently until her friendship meant more to Harry than his secrets did, too.